<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="2078542ef42c7251c55682c8dd7c5f17" url=""><![CDATA[Great Old Dame I have been in Madrid several times before, I have stayed in many hotels there but none compare to the Palace! It is ideally located next to Madrid's main museums. Its service couldn't be better, the concierge can get you a reservation wherever you want, everyone is willing to help to make your stay the best possible. I also recommend a lot the hotels breakfast, it is simply amazing!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7a07bee8dd940a7222ba4addd4719dd9" url=""><![CDATA[Great Petit Hotel, Superb location! Very nice hotel, in the very center of florence, the street on which it resides is the street that goes from the duomo to the ponte vecchio, right in the middle of those 2 attractions and just 1 block away form the piazza de la republicca. Great fares! Service is very nice, views are amazing.The only thing I would improve is room size though...I extremely recommend this hotel!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b3913aab0df06fc0f953e810ac2b542c" url=""><![CDATA[Nice location, but don't expect much I was in Berlin July 2006 (for the worldcup final) and I decided to return because I loved the city. For my first stay I stayed at the Steigenberguer hotel, quite nice, but I didn't love the location so for my second visit I decided to go to the Grand Westin, since Westin had never let me down.I browsed their site and I saw amazing pictures, great rooms, very modern... an amazing hotel! When I got there, and my room was asigned I was in shock! My room was in the furthest wing from the lobby and it couldn't have been worse, it literally was more than 50 years old, the beds were very stiff, the bathroom was not very clean and it was very disfunctional. After going through a lot of talking with the managers they changed our room, but it was still quite old (like 30 years) and not much of a 5 stars room. I must say as well that location was incredible, and the service wasn't bad. But if you would tell me about going another time there I would really reconsider it.I must recommend the adlon hotel, right in the brandenburg gate, and an awesome 5 star hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>