<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="470146fb20ed4d5e0b2091dad9a72f45" url=""><![CDATA[Over Priced, Over Designed, Disapointment What a disapointment this hotel is!There is so much more to a trendy boutique hotel than just a beautiful building and unfortunately this is the only thing going for the Dylan. Hotel staff were very dismissive, to the point of ignoring you when you are actually standing in the reception room. We had early check-in booked as we were on an early flight, however the room was not ready until almost 3pm, none of the staff offered an explaination or apologised for the inconvenience. Check-in to the room, only to have house keeping come in about 10min after arrival to re-stock the mini bar, explaining they had not had time to do it yet, but would do it now so we would not be charged for missing items. Unbelievable.The rooms whilst supposedly designer chic, are ridiculously over designed. We had the kimono/japanese inspired room which required you to bend over to see into the bathroom mirror, sit on your knees to have a shave, or use the small shaving mirror which was located on the adjacent wall, but the lighting cast a massive shadow which made this useless. The shower dribbled against the wall, so we got the maintenance person to put a new one in, only to find it was equally useless. The rooms have a table and chair at the end of the bed, or a couch, located directly under the plasma tv on the wall, again useless. Not really designer chic!We expressed our concerns to the hotel manager who advised we could not be moved on out first night, but he could change our room on the second. Not wanting the hassle we opted to stay in the existing room, and having spoken to other guests it sounds as though the other rooms are equally overdesigned, although we did not see them first hand.A really disapointing, overpriced hotel. Definately not worth the money. Would not stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>