<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="698dc5794e81493a9ecc6e91798d5b2c" url=""><![CDATA[Small quiet and friendly Stayed here for 4 nights late September and were given a larger room with juliette balcony - rooms not large by American standards but good for Paris, they also have suites suitable if you have a family. Comfortable beds and air conditioning and unusually for European hotels a kettle with tea bags in the room and an iron and ironing board. I wish all hotels would do this. Excellent friendly welcome (good English spoken) breakfast with cereals, boiled eggs, pastries and good coffee and juice in small dining room. We particularly liked the quiet street without the traffice noise normally found in Paris.Small food shops just round the corner and not far to restaurants or metro but be prepared to do a lot of walking taxis are not that easy to get, take comfortable footwear!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1cb63187b884ea197ba7d77fe1515fed" url=""><![CDATA[Good value conveniently located with luxurious beds Having searched through lots of hotels on the web and tripadvisor reviews we were pleased we chose the Orchard. It had everything we needed without being a large noisy convention hotel. The beds and bedding were wonderful. At first I thought it was just my jet lag that made me sleep well but we were there a few days and slept soundly. Breakfast is adequate in a nice dining room. We had dinner there the first night as we were very tired and it was excellent. There is a small bar area which looks nice but we didn't use as we were out most of the time. It is a very short walk to Union square and we found San Francisco an easy city to walk around just take a jacket and sweater it can be very cold one day and sunny the next. The city attracts a lot of cloud.We went to Alcatraz and when we had tried to book on the web or by phone they said the boat was full for the whole of our stay but on contacting one of the tour companies we managed to go the very next day, they collected us from our hotel and took us to their central office (near Fishermans Wharf) and then we were taken to the boat and we then did a bus tour of the outer areas of San Francisco.If you are hiring a car after your trip to San Francisco as we did there is a Hertz office in short walking distance of the Orchard.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>