<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7a5fe114f50c1766345028ba39779a77" url=""><![CDATA[Not 5 Star! I recently got back from this hotel on the 21st December 2007 after a weeks stay in what i thought would be a 5 star hotel. Don't get me wrong it was well worth what we paid. However, WARNING! I advise that if you are travelling from the UK you DO NOT upgrade your room through your travel agent. Wait until you get there. I had set my heart on a room with a jacuzi and was utterly disappointed. We booked through the agent and paid an extra 300 dollars only to find that when we got there we had been upgraded to the Deluxe Suite which was in building 2 not 7. After enquiring at reception we could have paid that amount at the reception for the room we wanted however, although we had already paid one this was a standard upgrade charge so then would have to pay again! AS IF IM MADE OF MONEY! anyway after that we got into a room in building 2. It was adequate! the air con was an absolute god send. The alcohol was absolutely disgusting, i hardly drank anything all week. The food i would say was ok. Breakfast had a very good choice and was to a good standard and the evening meals were ok! didn't get ill thank god! As for the beach, it was lovely. However, be careful as you will continually be hassled everywhere on this resort by shop owners, time share guys, watersports guys etc! They drove me in sane! Also watch out for the local market people that appear at the resort twice a week! just dont even look, i spent half an hour getting very stressed trying to tell them that i WAS NOT going to pay 150 dollars for a stone necklace! They think your stupid! All in all i had a wonderful time here due to the fact that we booked on lots of excursions. Therefore, not spending much time on the resort. (Definately do the Outback Safari its a fantastic day out. Just hope you dont go on a day when there is a tropical storm like we did. ) If you go with an open mind you will love it here, just expect the rooms to be anything like the pictures. The food also looks like its from a glossy magazine! How WRONG!! Take money with you and do the trips! And last but most importantly if any one approaches you JUST SAY NO!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>