<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="91daa637cc4adc262556e13950f6ef9f" url=""><![CDATA[Very nice weekend downtown hotel This is probably the 4th or 5th time we have stayed at the downtown Omni Hotel on South Olive in Los Angeles. We stay there after driving over from Phoenix to attend the LA Opera, and can easily walk to Dorothy Chandler Music Center. Also, the weekend rates are reasonable, about $109.00 before taxes, via a website registration. However there a a $24.00 per night parking charge for guests!The rooms we have had were all large and very pleasant, often with good views. The bathrooms have separate tubs and showers, and excellent toiletries. The closets are spacious and have plenty of hangers. In short, this is a true 4 star hotel, and our only problem was that we requested a king size bed and received two queens on this stay.The lobby entrance is off Olive street on the first floor. The two restaurants, one the high end dinner spot Noe, and the other a full service cafe, are on the third floor, which leads out to Grand Avenue directly adjacent to the Museum of Contemporary Art. This occurs because the hotel is on top of Bunker Hill, so Olive Street is below Grand Avenue at this point.There are a number of downtown restaurants, but usually they are not busy on weekend nights. We often have breakfast at a deligtfully funky (and very inexpensive) spot about a mile and a half away on Figueroa and 9th Street.The hotel is fairly quiet on weekends, except for the occasional wedding or high school prom; but I imagine would be a lot more active during the week since it is in the heart of the Los Angeles high rise business district.We recommend this hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d165f2028fd36c895556a791d64a4d3f" url=""><![CDATA[Decent Downtown Hotel I stayed (by myself) at the Holiday Inn located at 350 Biscayne Boulevard, near the Port and downtown Miami for two nights; March 28-29, 2007; while attending a conference.The room was pretty decent, with a very large closet, comfortable single King Bed, the usual small bathroom; but with my smoke free request honored. I had made reservations on-line and checked in fairly quickly. The concierge was friendly and helpful when I asked about walking to a recommended restuarant called Garcia's; for seafood. He confirmed my choice but advised taking a cab, and he was correct. This is a very casual, locally patronized seafood place on the river, and was excellent. You should get a small order of stone crabs to go with the dinner in season. The hotel is across the street from the Bayside Marina, which is moderately hokey, but I had a pretty good Italian dinner at Lombardi's the next night.Miami is a construction mess and difficult to get around. Our conference was at the Hyatt Regency Downtown, which was within walking distance.I thought the hotel breakfast was pretty weak for the price, and walked over to El Cafe Restaurant in the Marina the next day. It was much better, although it does not open until 8:00 A.M., and the hotel restuarant opens at 6:30.The total bill (including all taxes but not breakfast) for two nights was $338.00. SuperShuttle to and from the airport is $16.00 pp + tip; and the cab websites said that the cab fare, per vehicle, is about $40.00; so for a couple it is about a wash.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>