<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="17adba06c5c7b3f20360662a2ee4417e" url=""><![CDATA[5 Star Grounds but 4 Star Service To set the table properly, my wife and I decided on this resort after a few early reviews regarding the place. We travel a couple of times a year and enjoy in order: Grounds, Beaches, Pools, Service, Food and Entertainment. We average 29 years of age and have been to Bahamas, Jamaica, Cancun, Playa Del Carmen, and many other places. I would rate this place a 5 star on its grounds as it exceeds to some of the nicest (and well rated) hotels and resorts we have been to. However, the service is inconsistent so although I want to drop it to a 4 star I imagine a better resort in the Resort is 'Grand' to say the least, it is absolutely gorgeous, very modern and just perfect. The restaurants are all very upscale with a focus on presentation. The room (we stayed Royal Service with a King bed and Sofa) is very inviting and upscale. The beach is beautiful, with the sand being perfect but the sea weed overbearing at times.The problems we encountered were directly related to Royal Service. To begin, we arrived late afternoon and were not on the Royal Service list so we had to wait about 45 minutes for a room (not a big deal). I tried to contact the resort to confirm reservations 2 times and I never received a response. Since we paid for Royal Service I expected a butler available for reasonable request. Three out of the six nights we tried to order wine or champagne and it never came, even after multiple calls. This was disappointing finally began to make requests for a bottle of wine at 5pm and still would not receive our request by 7pm each time (if we ever received it). Even with this being stated, I recommend Royal Service just for the cabanas at the beach and pool, in addition to restaurant and areas that you have privileged to. As we noticed that by 8am the cabanas were already taken by the non-Royal Service pool.I hope I am not overstating the disappointment with Royal Service as some staff were eager to please and did whatever they could to make your moment enjoyable. This is separate than order made for food was delivered promptly regardless of the time of day.In response to those that wander if the hotel will be able to function at full capacity, well here is the review: the resort was booked for 3 of the 7 days we stayed and we never had to make reservations at any restaurant. We were sat immediately at our arrival and neither the restaurants nor the pool/beach area were crowded. All in all, this is a magnificent place with 5 Star Grounds if/when they truly get the service together it will be amazing destination for anyone lucky enough to go.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>