<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="d1a81f8acd6e291acfdd62df443c96fa" url=""><![CDATA[Opaque pricing but still pretty good I like CityInns but their pricing has gone crazy. Their rates change daily and the staff are totally inflexible so my tip would be to book a flexible rate (ie one that is cancellable without charge) and wait and see if they offer others nearer the date of your stay as we ended up getting a double 'Club' room with taxes and breakfast (normally GBP 19.50 per person) for GBP 119 per night with 4 drinks vouchers worth GBP 9.75 each thrown in and a late check out till 4 pm (worth at least 25 quid). This was the Summer in the City special.Club rooms are no bigger than normal rooms but do give you a better class of service / attention. One moan: why do they offer you a 4 pm checkout and then have housekeeping knocking you up at 10 am!Location is great, staff pretty friendly though some of them lack basic English (don't know what a bathrobe or dressing gown is for example, don't know what brown sauce is!). I always try and stay here but I've had my fingers burned with non-refundable rates at other CityInns so thought I'd share my experiences
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c706fc84fa8626ae730b72c953c4ea51" url=""><![CDATA[olde worlde opulence I have stayed at the Canal House twice and love it but have to concede that it is an acquired taste. It isn't cheap but is a truly special place to stay -- like taking a stroll back in time. The location is perfect, on a quiet canal, near all the sights (Dam square, Ann Frank house etc) and near the Jordaan area which is chock-full of excellent bars and restaurants. Do not stay there if you want a minibar, a TV in your room, 24-hr room service, breakfast in bed etc as you won't get it. It is a very atmospheric place to sleep but not good for much else -- this isn't a criticism, just a statement of fact. Breakfast is fairly standard European: bread and cold cuts or cheese, cereals, croissants, boiled eggs and (tinned) fruit. The breakfast room ambience is amazing though. Staff are very helpful and attentive, as are the owners and receptionist.There is one lift and the corridors are very windy and twisty and the staircases VERY steep so anyone who is 'mobility-impaired' would have a big problem. The rooms I've had have both been full of antiques and had four-poster beds but are not modern -- as I said no TV though a radio. Bathrooms are a bit tired with 70s tiled decor (half-size bathtub) but are more than adequate. The bar is not a place to while away the hours -- not enough seating for more than two groups, closes at 22.30 -- more somewhere to grab a glass of wine or a beer before going out and yes, it is a bit chintzy but heck, you have the whole of the city to choose from .Make sure you settle your bill in cash to qualify for the 5% discount and to help them with their cashflow. This review may sound a bit negative it isn't intended to be so; it is simply to prevent you going with the wrong expectations since the CH's recent billing as a HIP HOTEL might make it appeal to the wrong crowd, which would be a pity for those of us who are the 'right' crowd.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="710ac33c7e18f6e13421c785267761c1" url=""><![CDATA[Amazing stay but stay out of the crack in the bed! Nothing to add regarding the location (could it be more central?), staff (amazingly helpful friendly, all speak perfect English, all willing to go the extra mile with tips, advice, bookings etc) and facilities (free English newspapers in the lobby, internet access, pleasant bar area with the most generous measures I've ever encountered). We paid top whack (EUR 250+)for a deluxe room on the first floor (102) with sitting area, bathroom with posh shower and jacuzzi bath, loo and bidet and a truly massive bed -- though in reality it was two double mattresses on one base, which meant that any Valentine's 'action' was hampered by one party constantly slipping down the crack in the middle if they slipped apart -- with added features such as automatic raise and lower so you could sit up and read or put your feet up. One niggle: both English tv channels (BBC and CNN) didn't work too well so we couldn't watch the news.Didn't ever partake of breakfast as the metal shutters were so effective at blocking out the light that we slept very late every morning but I think 15 euros was a bit steep though places on La Ramblas were not much cheaper; is it me or has Barca become very dear of late?I might try and get a better deal next time and I'd like to see some of the 'basic' rooms to see if they're better value for money but I'd certainly go back
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f63390270d5dca0a5ed93f831e75311a" url=""><![CDATA[Great location I have to disagree with some of the previous (negative) reviewers. I've just returned from 3 days at the Ambassador and wasn't bothered by any lack of soundproofing. We could hear the odd toilet being flushed and a bit of street noise but that was all -- we slept very well indeed. Reception staff were friendly, multilingual and very accommodating -- I requested and got a room change and ended up with one with a MASSIVE king-size bed. The location is great: close enough to La Rambla to be as good as on it but far enough away to not be kept awake all night. The decor is a bit on the tired side and the bar area could definitely do with a revamp as it is very sterile and merely functional. In sum the ambassador's not brilliant but it's as good a place as any to stay in the centre.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>