<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="42ab8c18a0af956f5c9a87deff9ae12b" url=""><![CDATA[Great Midwinter Vacation Spot We were at the Iberostar Bavaro 2/26/05-3/05/05. We traveled via a charter with TNT from Boston. This resort was great overall and I would definitely go back. We are a couple in our 50's and went with one other couple.Arrival: Our charter go us to the hotel at about 10:30 at night. We were very tired from a long day of travel and anticipated a tedious check in process. We were wrong. The hotel made check in a breeze. They had a manila folder all set for us with keys, towel cards, resort information and a registration card. We were told to simply get our bracelets put on by the friendly girl waiting for us adjacent to the check in desk and bring back the completed registration card at our convenience. We attached the supplied luggage tags to our bags, got our bracelets and got a drink at the bar. Once the entire group got settled with drinks on comfortable couches in the lobby a registration clerk came over and explained the ins and outs of the hotel tom us all. We knew that we wanted a safe key, so when he was done we filled out the registration card and returned it to the desk at which time we got our safe key. Having finished our drinks, we wandered down to our room and got there just as the bell men arrived with our luggage. One of the easiest check ins ever. By the way, they informed us that they were opening up the buffet restaurant for us at 11:00 pm for burgers, hot dogs, cold cuts and snacks as they assumed we were all hungry from our trip. The burgers were great!Room:We did try to get upgraded to a room overlooking the beach, but were told that none were available as some German tour group had paid extra to reserve them. We had e-mailed them a week in advance and made our request again when we were checking in. They offered a room overlooking the pool to the couple we were traveling with, but they did not bother moving as it was not much different than the one they had.Bavaro's rooms are all junior suites. Ours was on the ground floor just over the bridge from the main buffet restaurant and was very quiet. We did not notice any musty or other smells as others have reported. We left a couple of bucks for the maid each day and our room was always well cleaned and the mini fridge was always restocked with what we want. The safe is good sized and worked just fine. One day we had difficulty locking our sliding door to the balcony so we called the desk and they had someone there in ten minutes who fixed it on the spot. Beach:Fantastic, I cannot say enough good things about it. This is a large resort with lots of beachfront so, if you want a lot of activity all day just camp out in front of the pool. The Star Friends will keep you appraised of what's going on all day long. If you want peace and quiet, just walk a little ways to the left or right and you will be left alone. The sand here is very fine, the water warm, the views are gorgeous and there are lots of beach walkers going by most of the day.Food Drink:We really enjoyed the variety of food offered. There was never a time we could not find something good to eat. In fact, we made a game out of trying something new every meal. Some we loved, some we didn't but there was plenty of variety. We only ate two dinners at the buffet restaurant because we wanted to try the specialty restaurants. Both times were very good. There are steaks and chops available every night that are grilled to your order as well as a pasta station and fajita station. Frankly, if you cannot find something to your liking here you should not be going to an all inclusive resort. We tried the Steakhouse restaurant, (good sirloins done just as ordered); the Mediterranean, (fish that even non fish eaters can like), and the Japanese, (excellent-the best of the specialty restaurants). We were also invited to a Manager's Special Dinner one night at the Mediterranean where we had a choice of lobster or chicken. Both were delicious. Drinks were typical tropical fare, nothing especially good or bad though it should be noted that they premix the most popular fruity drinks like Pina Colada's in big dispensing machines. They are not made individually in blenders, but they are good.The beer was a local brand only.Shows:There is a show nightly. They seemed to alternate between fancy shows put on by the Star staff and follies shows involving the guests embarrassing themselves. The follies shows are very funny and the staff shows are OK. The staff sing and dance very enthusiastically. We wandered over to the Dominicana a couple of nights and saw there shows, which were essentially the same as Bavaro's. There is a disco and casino over there. The disco is fun but smoky and we did not try the casino.Shopping:There are stores at the hotel and a collection of flea-market type shops a short walk down the beach. Check out the prices at the hotel and then go down to the flea market to bargain if you're so inclined. Otherwise just buy things at the hotel. The prices there are set so no bargaining.Sickness:Bring Imodium. Two of our foursome had some minor stomach distress, (one was brushing his teeth with tap water. Imodium took care of it and neither missed more than one meal. Two of us opted for anti-malarial medication, (chloraquine) prior to the trip but we only saw a couple of mosquitoes one evening while watching a show. We did notice them fogging for bugs one day. Overall:I would go back in a minute. We had a great vacation. Iberostar understands how to do the all-inclusive vacation and does it very well. We only speak English and had no problem communicating with the staff. We tried our best to use simple Spanish phrases and the effort seemed appreciated by the staff, (my attempts at Spanish brought lots of smiles). The resort is beautiful, the staff is friendly and attentive and the beach is the best. Go-enjoy!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>