<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="05d15618a0578887e17178b511f546b5" url=""><![CDATA[Casablance saves the trip! (Beware when you book on line!) I had booked this hotel via the Trip Advisor web site and received a confirmation from Travelocity telling me that I had got the deluxe room I had asked for. A special occasion, I was taking my husband via the Queen Mary 2 to NY for our wedding anniversary break. The transatlantic sail was perfect, the ship, sublime, the suite, perfect and we arrived at the hotel in a limo along with a great deal of luggage! Confirmation in hand, we trooped to reception...only to find that they had no record of our booking! Yes, the bookers had told us we had a room, but neglected to tell the hotel, who were now full...leaving us stranded ( this happens a lot, we were told...so always check you have a booking...a confirmation with this company means very little!) We were stuck! No hotel! A great deal of luggage and no room at the busiest time for Christmas shopping in NY...it looked like the fantastic climax to our trip was ruined. However, the boys at the Casablanca were fantastic! Nick and the chaps immediately juggled bookings, made calls, put themsleves out and after a short wait, found us a room in their hotel (and had promised to find one elsewhere if they could not help us as they were very full!) It wasn't the deluxe room I wanted, they apologised the room would be small and not their best but I was so grateful for the fantastic service, we said yes! The room was great! If that is the worst, I look forward to staying in the deluxe when we next stay in NY! It was comfortable, well decorated and available straight away (11am!) On top of that, Nick took copies of all my paper work and has been great about chasing up the problem with me...really taking joint ownership when he really had no need. The hotel deserves all the praise you read in the reviews...coffee, juices and buns and biscuits available all day and a great cheese and wine evening (except Sundays). Breakfast is good too and though the hotel is just off Time Sq, we had an undisturbed trip and we were ideally located for shopping, theatre and everything else NY. Booking restaurants, taxis etc was no problem for the hotel and they really went out of their way to make sure we were happy and comfortable after our unfortunate start...they actually seemed to care about a problem that really wasn't theirs. I have stayed in many hotels in NY and I have to say that this is the best. An originally decorated, truly friendly, incredibly helpful establishment...I can't praise it enough for everything they did for us. On top of that...its half the price of the places we usually stay where you are pretty much invisable after check in.Thank you Nick and the guys and please, members, if you book on line, even through a great site like Trip Advisor and you get a confirmation...please please call and check! I shall not be using Travelocity again...they really didn't care and made no effort to apologise or even respond to my problem.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>