<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="d2f766fc9a23f5b263d4d12b397e89ef" url=""><![CDATA[There are better places to stay in Singapore Although not terrible, there are a lot better hotels for the same price to stay in in Singapore. The hotel room was very dated and not as clean as it could have been. There was a patch of damp in the bathroom too - in it's time this was probably a nice hotel, it's just a shame it's time was about 30 years ago!!The location too could pose a problem for some people. It is a 15 minute hilly walk to the main Orchard Road area and the nearest MRT station. Although this may not seem far, in the heat and humidity of Singapore it is a very hot and sweaty experience.I have stayed in Singapore 3 times now and this was by far the worst hotel I have stayed in. The Orchard Parade hotel and the Phoenix (no swimming pool) were a much better class of hotel and far better located. There are some alterations going on at the Elizabeth at the moment - maybe it will be better then, but for now I would choose somewhere else.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3bad4f1b1d268cff0c6c20af2991c1d5" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful place, beautiful people If you want a relaxing holiday in beautiful surroundings then this is the place for you.The staff and people are so friendly here you can't help being put at ease and relaxing. The hotel is right on the beach front in a beautiful location and also has a lovely swimming pool area. There are plenty of sunloungers owned by the hotel both on the beach and at the pool -they even put quilted mats on the loungers to make them more comfortable.There is some entertainment on at the hotel if you want to be involved including pool volleyball, cookery demonstrations and local acts on each night in the lounge bar. The hotel also put on special gala evenings too at an extra cost.The hotel is beautifully kept and the plentiful staff are always cleaning the hotel and pruning the gardens.Every member of staff you pass is so pleasant and polite be it a cleaner, gardener or entertainment staff and will always enchange greetings with you. The hotel is actually situtuated in Tanjung Benoa and not Nusa Dua as most literature suggests. This resort is much smaller and does not have much bar life although there are plenty of restaurants outside the hotel and the hotel bar provides nightly enterainment. It is much cheaper to eat outside the hotel and safe to do so. The hotel food is very nice but you will only have to pay about a third of the price to eat outside the hotel. Similarly it is much cheaper to buy souvenirs outside the hotel, be prepared to barter as on average you will only have to pay two thirds of the original price suggested. This is a wonderful hotel and the people there truly deserve your custom - I would definatley go here again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>