<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="52d7ceb9ffc915086f3f947c4c1dcdfd" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel, but not really a Seattle experience We live in the Seattle area and booked this hotel because of the wind damage and we were without power for more than a week. We stayed here for 3 of those nights in two different rooms. I guess I was surprised that this hotel was rated so high as most locals have not even heard of it. We only knew about it because our son does not live far from here.The hotel was totally booked during this time period because so many people were without power. The front desk people were overwhelmed because of all the calls, etc. but they handled it very well. The rooms are good size, the bathrooms are very nice. It is done rather modern style - but not cold. The restaurant downstairs does mainly appetizer type food, but the soups/salads, etc. are very tasty. They have wine tasting in the evening, but it is not like the Kimpton Hotels - you get a voucher which allows you to have a small tasting of a red and a white wine. Would I stay here again? Yes, if my power went out. But if I were a tourist coming here to Seattle for the first time? No. This hotel is a distance from downtown Seattle - 10 minutes by car when traffic is good. Is there anything else in the neighborhood? No. If you have a child or relative that is going to the University of Washington and you are here to see them and be involved in their activities - this is the perfect place for you. If you are here to experience what the vibe of Seattle is - pay an extra $50 if you can and stay downtown Seattle. It is so different. The restaurants within walking distance of downtown hotels are incredible. There are excellent restaurants in this same area as the Watertown (Tilth) but it is a cab ride. Also, as one of the previous reviewers stated - if this hotel is full - it is noisy. We were about 5 doors from the elevator, but I could hear it bling everytime the elevator hit our floor. Also, the people above us must have had children that were busy - they hit the floor at 6AM and it sounded like floor hockey above us for the next 2 hours until they took them for breakfast. If you aren't on one of the top floors looking south - you look at a busy street.This area is an interesting area of Seattle. We love it and have bought a condo in this area where we plan to eventually move. However, it is an area of transition - it is not a typical area of Seattle. There is not much to do or see here - you are dependent on transportation to see the tourist sights. That is why I would recommend this hotel as a hotel, but this is not what I would like you to think all of Seattle represents.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb4746c24c8fec4e5f52844da79057e7" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent except for one thing.... We stayed here for 2 nights September 7 and 8th. We had a lovely room. The staff is very accomodating and friendly. The food in the restaurant was very good and room service was great (although they only brought one butter for 2 orders). We have 2 complaints - the sink area in the bathroom is minimal. There is not enough room for one person, let alone 2 people to put out their toiletries, so everything has to be either kept under the counter or in your overnight bag. The other complaint is that the bed was really uncomfortable. My husband and I both had horrible backaches when we got up the first morning. I said something to the staff and they were most apologetic. They didn't replace the mattress, I think they just flipped it. It was somewhat better the second night, but it still was not great. I would still stay there again because I loved the room, the staff and the location. I would just hope for a better bed!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c8ee76839df1021a569a9498670132fd" url=""><![CDATA[As a local, I have a totally different perception I have been reading all the reviews of the hotels that have been ranked above the Mayflower, and I find it very interesting. I live within 10 miles of the Mayflower, but every year our dinner club books a night here during the Christmas holidays so that we can eat downtown, experience the city, and not have to drive after we have had many cocktails. This year was no exception. The hotels that were mentioned with a higher rating than the Mayflower are great hotels. However, the Mayflower is far and above the others. This hotel has a much better central location, the rooms are large and very well appointed, the staff is great and courteous AND for the location and room - the price can't be beat. The hotels in the University District and on Lake Union are great - BUT they are a cab ride away from downtown Seattle. The Mayflower is right in the middle of Seattle - within walking distance of the waterfront, Pike Place Market, Nordstrom, Macy's - all the best restaurants. Plus, it is so reasonable. If this is where the locals choose to stay - we can't be that wrong. We love this hotel. The staff is wonderful and the Anduluca Restaurant is superb. Oliver's Martini Bar gets crowded - so arrive early! You will truly experience what Seattle is at this hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1ce2977654407864b4c567595e4f0c21" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent location, rooms and staff.. My husband and I stayed here May 6, 2004 for two nights. The hotel is very centrally located and the staff was very friendly and helpful. We had a wonderful large room (#226) and I asked to see some of the other rooms. All the rooms are different and all uniquely decorated. Most of the rooms are quite large. It is a perfect hotel for people traveling with children because several of the rooms are so large that they can easily accomodate 2 adults and 2 children, or even 4 adults. There would even be room for a roll away. For European rooms, they are very large. Even the standard rooms are of OK size. As for the breakfast, it wasn't the best I have ever had, but it certainly was adequate. I would stay here again in a heartbeat!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>