<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="820acc93cb663c6d615074ff8760fc66" url=""><![CDATA[service through gritted teath! On arrival we were delighted to be told that we had been upgraded to a club floor room. The room itself was small, the bathroom tiny and the decor and lighting were poor. Internet access was available for a reasonable fee. After a long flight we were hoping for a lie in, sadly this was not to be as despite having the do not disturb sign on the maid ricocheted through the door armed with a vacum cleaner at 8am claiming not to have seen the do not distueb sign. A call to receiption failed to get an apology for this so they were not off to a good start. That evening we though we would check out the club lounge only to find out that as ''upgrades'' we would be charged for everything in the lounge - I mean that is like getting an airline upgrade to business class and being served economy class food. Bearing in mind we had not asked for the upgrade and it probably only occured becuase the hotel had oversold its standard rooms that came as yet another dissapointment.The service was extreamly average for Singapore, food was pretty much ok and in terms of location then the hotel is well placed for all the major shopping and entertainment areas.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9d4355ab4942fdcb9c0856b02d5f4eee" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderfully Grand When we walked through the doors of the Peninsula we knew we were in for a good time, the service was faultless from start to finish. Checking in was swift and efficient and we were personally shown up to the room. Our room faced the side street and for a city centre the room was pretty big, spotlessly clean and came with a huge bathroom with separate walk in shower. Everything you could ever think of wanting was available in the room and a floor butler was on call for anything else.As you would expect a stay at the Peninsula is not cheap but it is certainly worth it. Hong Kong is one of those cities where you can never be handy for absolutely everything but the Peninsula is right next to an MRT station so getting around by train or taxi is easy. As a final treat take the hotels Rolls Royce transfer to the airport, well worth it even if it does take longer than the airport express train. If pushed to criticise something about the place it would be the queues of tourists in reception that flock to the hotel for the legendary afternoon tea, a minor blip on an otherwise faultless stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d16b2aeb2204d81ddf90956fd3bbdd0b" url=""><![CDATA[debateable Having stayed here twice before (2001 and 2003) and loved the place we were looking forward to a long awaited return. The resort in itself is still well looked after and despite its age it is wearing well however it faces tough competition in Bali and if Le Meridien wants to keep its 5 star status they will need to start spending soon! Our room over looked the pool and the ocean and was kept spotelessly clean, in room wifi is available but at a fee with only 1 hour or 1 day packages available nothing on offer at better value if you are staying a week or more. The pool area is great and despite it being high season sunbeds were always available. Our main dissapointment with this property was the service which varied massively, the hotel is clearly marketing itself (and pricing drinks/food etc) to the Asian golfer market and as such has employed staff who speak other asian languages, this left most westerners explaining themselves 3 to 4 times in english to be understood, orders were often taken down wrong. The other area of dissapointment was the food, whilst on the whole it was good it was certainly not spectacular and a couple of meals arrived cold (and this was in thier award wining cerdana restaurant) with no service recovery from the staff.This hotel is off the beaten track and there is very little to do in the local area, great for golf or relaxing with a book but not for the traveller seeking plenty to do, in the evenings it is extreamly quiet. We will go back to Bali for sure but as for the Le Meridien then we will probably give it a miss next time as other hotels offer more for your money.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>