<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="2aa8a9e6bbb769fbda6b038a18ed64ab" url=""><![CDATA[All-Inclusive LAST Resort The beach was beautiful! The swim up bar was a lot of fun. But the service was lacking and the rooms were sub-standard. I heard that the experiences in the Royal Service side was much better. A lot of the staff treat you in a condescending manner, and it's far worse if you don't speak spanish. It was a hot time of year (June 27-July 1) so the only place that felt truly delicious was our AC'd room (some of the people in our party were having AC problems). Some of the restaurants were too warm to drink wine. And that's even if you had a reservation they actually honored. Most of the time we were arguing with someone about our reservations we set. We had made them before we got to the resort, confirmed them the night before while at the resort, and they still managed to keep us from enjoying dinner where we wanted and when. The buffets were only good if you got there as soon as the food was put out. The mixed drinks were nasty and the wine was pretty bad too. The bars were outdoors and not comfortable at all, unless your idea of comfort is sitting in sweltering heat with no moving air around you. The bartenders seemed to see you better if you had cash in hand. There are not enough huts on the beach to seek refuge from the sun, and believe me you'll need it. After 2 hours, my brain felt like it was frying. There were a lot of activities, amenities, restaurants and just things going on that we never knew about, but heard about on the trolley-train circuit that a resort of that size should at the very least have a print out of what's going on where delivered to their patrons rooms daily. We did receive housekeeping, but every day it was a different time, sometimes not until after 5pm. The casino was just about the only place to go at night, but if you don't gamble, you're basically just drinking bad alcohol. All the food at this resort tastes the same - soggy and tasteless. But i heard the Japanese was good, but by the time we were given reservations, i got sick from the food and it was our last night, so i did not get a chance to really enjoy. They tell you that there is food at night (9pm) buffet style, if the A la Carte restaurants do not have enough room, but if there are private functions going on, you are not permitted to enter, leaving you no choice but to buy potato chips or cookies at the gift shop. There was a couple of times we were at the buffet places ( which is the only place to go for breakfast and lunch) and the place was packed with more employees eating than resort guests, leaving the place cramped for space. There were 60 people in our party, and not one of our groups were given the dinner reservation that was asked for. The resort staff lied to us numerous times about confirming dinner reservations and changing them without our knowledge to suit other guests at the resort. We found out later that Royal Service guests were given our reservations. The room smelled really bad too. Like moldy, damp dirty. The paint on the walls literally comes off with your fingernail, it's so damp. The shower head didn't work. They left flowers in the room that were dead by the time we ever got the chance to see them (they shut off the AC after they clean your room). No room service, only the Royal Service side got that. The only good thing about our room was that it was close to the beach pool. The ATM machine only dispenses pesos at the resort (although dollars are accepted everywhere). Everything at the gift shop is at least double what you would normally pay in the states. The funny thing about Pina Colada's and other Fruity mixed drinks they advertise, not only do they make them different each time, different colors textures, but we later caught on that if you do not specify whether you want alcohol or not, they will give it to you without alcohol. And if you are prone to being bitten by mosquitoes, you will be bitten. I came home with 30 bites. I planned on writing far more about Melia Caribe Tropical, but realized that we got what we paid for and it wasn't about food, service or anything like that for us - it was about bonding with the people we were traveling with. As the saying goes - it's not where you are but who you're with that counts. But I do not plan on returning to the Dominican Republic, much less this all-inclusive last resort.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>