<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="ab060b2e976d73743a931ef2aaeb5930" url=""><![CDATA[Excellence in Miami! (Didn't think it was possible) I usually go to Miami a few times a year. For some reason I have never stayed at the FS, I have to ask myself why?Having stayed at the Conrad next door and several hotels in South Beach I can say this is the best i have experienced in Miami. (Although i have not stayed at the Mandarin Oriental)The hotel is lovely. The lobby and particularly the Botero sculptures are magnificant.We stayed in a premier bay view room - Great views of the bay, well executed color scheme and the usual tasteful FS bathroom. If you have a choice get a bay view room. Looking back at the city is not great. Much of Miami downtown is a construction site.Service was excellent. Everyone remembered and pronounced my rather long last name. The restaurant Aqua is pretty good. My mother is a vegetarian- they had no trouble accommodating her requests. The wine list is good and reasonable for a FS.The pool area is well designed and landscaped. The staff is attentive.There is one downside. If you stay here have a car. There is nothing to do downtown that you can walk to. Shop and eat in south beach walk around on lincoln road but stay here.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1ee00179a6ffbf8fc0744d75e76e3d5c" url=""><![CDATA[Average business hotel- Good value I was in town for Art Basel and couldn't get a place in South Beach. Downtown is really a ghost town but it was a nice change from the crush of people in SOBE. We were upgraded to a residence basically a suite with a kitchenette. Nice Molton Brown products. Huge marble bath and good light in the rooms.I did find the living room furniture to be a little IKEAesque but not terrible.This is a business hotel - not a luxury hotel. Not nearly in the class of a Four Seasons or Mandarin Oriental.The Staff was friendly to us, not especially professional perhaps more training would be in order but none of them had Miamitude I would stay there again if I had discount corporate rates.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0ddbadb1abd286d6ac4aac6e67e6ccf1" url=""><![CDATA[3.8 out of (Four) Seasons The problem with the FS - SF is that it is a hard comparison to the other properties in the chain. I expect perfection when i stay.We spent 4 nights this past weekend. Our flight was delayed - we arrived at 2 am. Our room was ready (really thank goodness) The front desk man told us that we had a premier room. I am not sure what was premier about it.(we did have a view of market st ). For a FS the room was not large. Color scheme was neutral (a little too neutral) and the artwork on the walls was sparse. Furniture was a tiny bit worn. All these things could be overlooked at almost any other chain.The bathroom was as usual lovely. Four seasons always is the benchmark in hotel bathrooms.The public rooms are delightful. Beautifully decorated with original artworks (not all to my taste -but money was spent on it). Food at the restaurant and room service was excellent.Service was very good. My boyfriend called the concierge to find a wine store in Berkeley- 15 minutes later an envelope with directions was under our door.The location couldn't be beat. I will be staying at the FS the next time but next time with more realistic expectations.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="86e819f58fb126c636c32aaaac9a08d8" url=""><![CDATA[Modern, sleek St. Regis My friends and I stayed at the St Regis over a weekend in July. My boyfriend and I returnd the following weekend for one night.On arrival the staff couldn't be any better. Our butler escorted us to our floor, gave us water bottles and demonstrated all the technology in our room.One minor point is that on our return weekend we were asked if we ever stayed there before. It seems that someone should have noted that we were there the previous week.Decor is by far the best i have experienced in a San Francisco hotel. I stayed at the four seasons and was disappointed at the lack of attention paid to the minor details. Not so at the St Regis, the bathrooms were well thought out, i particularly liked the ability to open the doors to the room from the tub.I loved the bath products- Remede SPA-. It gives the already generous room a bigger feel. In series 14 rooms the bathroom layout seems not to allow the door to the toilet to close fully- a minor flaw. Materials were excellent. Leather lined hallways and marble floors felt luxurious.The room was fairly large, the bed was comfortable. Pratesi sheets were a nice touch as was the chaise lounge next to the window.The automated blinds and the control panel are meant to wow but were mostly unnecessary.The lobby was not large but i liked the dark woods and the wall of fire. Food in Vitrine was good and the waitstaff pleasant.All around an excellent city property and on my next trip to SF i will stay at the St Regis.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8b23fedaeb189ea245594752e9e3f474" url=""><![CDATA[Stay here if you get a good rate I am surprised at the number of glowing reviews of this property.I stayed for 1 night last weekend and found the hotel to be of average quality. Nothing was awful but nothing was really great.We had a corner room on the 10th floor. Check in was good - took only a minute or so. The elevator carpets were dirty and the public areas were not decorated in any special way.Our room had great light and good views. The bed was comfortable but a little soft. Sofitel's bed is touted but i don't really care for the duvet only. The management puts out a note saying they are changed daily.The bathroom had a seperate shower tub combo but there were uneven paint marks on the ceiling and a little wear on the trim.You could see some mildew in the shower. The velvet curtains felt a little dusty as did the carpet.We had room service. It arrived promptly but the quality of the food was average. I am not sure how this hotel scores above the Four Seasons in Georgetown. If you want true luxury stay there (in a renovated room).I will stay at the Sofitel again but only if i get a sub $180 a night rate.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>