<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="4f15022e6e88640fc855f0f377c51c65" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, fine hotel We arrived on saturday for a three-days trip in Madrid. Since this was our first time there, we loved the absolute central location of the Best Western Atlantico hotel: in the city center, near the Palace, a few steps away from other touristic areas, we could not find a better place to stay in Madrid.When we checked in, we specifically asked for a room with a view on the street. Based on other reviews on TripAdvisor, we knew that some rooms were built towards a very small brick wall. The map for emergency exit that is displayed in the room made it clear to us that this choice was the good choice. However, you should know that the Municipal Police is very much active in this part of the town, which means that you hear a lot of sirens at any hours on the day or the night. If you care about not being disturbed while sleeping, you should definitively choose a room not facing the street, as this will probably inconvenient you. Also, we booked originally a smoking room. Since none matched the facing the street criteria, we were given a non-smoking room, and were told that this room was equipped with ashtrays, as were all rooms in the hotel. We were kindly asked to smoke on the (small) balcony. We didn't, as we chose to smoke outside the room as to not disturb other guests that would use the room after us, but the policy of the hotel might be worth noticing if you are somehow sensible to the odor of tobacco.The room we booked was a standard room. We were not expecting something big, and we got exactly that. The door opened directly to the bed room (no corridor, the bath room is located on the other end of the room). However, it was comfortable enough to say the we spent two wonderful nights in this hotel. The bed was not too soft, nor too hard: exactly as we wanted it to feel.After we were done with unpacking, we took the elevator up to the hotel bar, located on the ninth floor. Unfortunately, it was not yet opened: the bar is available only from 3pm to 1am (if we remember correctly). We managed to get back to the place when it was opened; the view is not as great as some suggested here (because two many uninteresting buildings on the other side of the street) however the free coffee (you can choose either filter coffee of espresso; we chosed espresso and did not regret it) and the nice weather managed to balance this inconvenient.One thing worth to note is that the booklet left inside the room indicates that you can get a free coffee from the room service at any hour of the day or night. This is a lie, as we learnt by dialing the number shown on the document: the only way to have a coffee is to move to the hotel bar, when it is open.Last but not least, the breakfast was typical from a 3* or 4* hotel. For person, you get a typical breakfast buffet. Worth to notice is that, although you get your coffee from an automated coffee machine, you can have either filter coffee or espresso. For the price, you also have fresh orange juice; but you have no hot chocolate. If you plan to have breakfast at the hotel, I recommend that you taste the kiwis: those that I eat there were from the most tasty and juicy that I experienced in the last few years.All in all, this hotel is typically not the best hotel down town (it is probably overrated in TripAdvisor, unless ranking reflects the quality over price ratio). Although I can give you a list of better 3* or 4* hotels in the world, the location and friendliness of the staff of the Best Western Atlantico makes it so that I would without hesitation recommend this hotel to anyone that is going to visit Madrid. In three days, we could see a lot of sites, do some shopping, drink and eat without ever using the metro once. At (booked through Expedia), this is probably the best deal we could find here.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>