<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="9664581ec9c2cb37198b16b5b18f1cc1" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel in nice location We have just returned from NY, had a confortable stay at Desmond Tutu Center. As other travellers have mentioned, the hotel offers good value for money at current prices, and it is conveniently placed for public transport, only two stops away on the underground from Times Square. The area is very nice and safe, and it's a 10 minutes walk to the underground. The rooms vary in size, we had a very small one, while our friends had a much bigger room for the same rate. Ours resembled a big cupboard, with only enough space to squeeze in past the bed and no lights on ceiling, only two or three desk lamps, which made it difficult to read in the evening. The bed is confortable, nice linens, and nice touches in room, with tea/coffee machine available, water, toiletries in bath etc. I phoned the hotel direct to book and got a decent rate, but then I noticed a much cheaper rate on the hotel website. I contacted the hotel by email and got the lower rate confirmed. There were also a few problems at check in, we asked for a room away from the street (10th Avenue can be quite busy and the hotel is next to the road), at which point the receptionist asked me if I wanted to cancel the reservation and go and find a better hotel! (very rude, she was a supervisor, as well!) After some convincing, she agreed to transfer us to another room, but then she made us wait for another hour before she dealt with the forms. After travelling for 12 hours, this wasn't the welcome we expected, but then the other staff were all nice and we had a good stay. Breakfast offers a good choice, but no cooked food, probably due to building regulations, it includes smoked salmon, boiled eggs, bagels, pastries, a selection of fruit and fruit juices, teas, coffees etc. There is a nice choice of restaurants in the area, we found two nice ones, Don Giovanni down the street from the hotel (5 mins on 10th avenue) makes fantastic pizza and offers a selection of other dishes, and the Greek restaurant on corner of 9th avenue with 23rd street, with a more modest decor, but an excellent selection of nicely cooked meals at very decent prices.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>