<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="f5ce6ef942bc21a8e05278e2fb4586e7" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect!!!!!! We stayed at the Renaissance Paris Vendome for 5 nights, from April 20th-April 25, 2007. We used our Marriott points and upgraded to a premier room for $60.00 per night extra.The hotel is in a perfect location. 2 blocks to the Louve, 1 block to the Tuileries. The room was pleasant, very clean and had windows that opened to the courtyard. The only drawback was that there is no bureau. We used the shelves, but they are a bit shallow.The bath is lovely, the shower small. I preferred to swim in the beautiful pool and shower in the locker room which is bigger and easier.We walked everywhere, prob 12 miles each day. Breakfast taken daily at Le Pian (sp?) up two blocks and around the corner. Ther are multiple cafes and restaurands in the Marche area...all wonderful. First dinner was at Cafe Flotte. Fabulous...concierges Davied, Julian and Olivier are top notch.Ah Paris, our first trip...most beautiful city we have ever seen. A special night at Cafe L'Homme with Paris friends...the Eiffle Tower is 1 block away..right in front of you and the light show begins on the hour at night. Eat on the open patio. I will never forget this fabulous sight, nor will we ever forget Paris....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7185147d7a6506396116b1fd63fc60fd" url=""><![CDATA[City of Freedom and Fun We were on an independent European tour and spend the last 3 nights at the Amsterdam Marriott on points. We were given a very, very large room (509, I think), which kind of was on a corner. It was great!The hotel was crowded with tourists, many on bus trips, which crowds the front desk and concierge. No matter, we just up and went.Of course we walked everywhere. The location of the hotel is ideal, as already noted.The first morning we ate at the hotel. BIG mistake. 22 Euros per person for a buffett. Don't bother. Walk past the Vondelpark to the first street on your right. Walk down to one of the caffes and take your breakfast. Much more charming and much less $$! We are learning...never eat in the hotels! We had our last dinner in Amsterdam at the Italian Restaurant across from the hotel. It was lovely and we met a charming young couple...she was 7 months preggers wearing high heels..nevertheless, they hopped on their bikes and rode home! Bikes everywhere!!!!!!Anne Franke house is excellent and disturbing;most important.Take time to stroll the canals and feel the flovor of this lovely and most interesting city of freedom and fun!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>