<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="fe4f0f1a15c28d6545548634e8c807e5" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel - Great Location After many nights researching hotels for this trip I decided on the Intercontinental Mark Hopkins. We were so glad we ended up at the Mark Hopkins. Great location, beautiful hotel in Nob Hill. ROOMBooked the Excutive Level King - Room 1422. This room had a grea view of the Golden Gate Bridge/Bay, Grace Cathedral and California Cable Line. Ask for this room.It is an older hotel like many in San Francisco but well-maintained and nicely decorated. We didn't find the room to be any smaller than a normal hotel we've stayed in during our travels.CLUB LEVEL A MUSTMake sure you book a Club Level room. Its well worth the extra cost in snack and drinks alone. Its a very nice lounge that serves 5 mini-meals throughout the day starting at 6:30-10:30 I believe. Great for grabbing breakfast, snack or tea in the afternoon, lite appetizers and drinks in the evening. Especially nice if traveling from east coast and haven't adjusted to time difference. I went down and read a few mornings so not to disturb others.Nancy at the Concierge Desk is very informative and can answer any questions you may have. She was my morning friend each day!TOP OF THE MARKThe views are great! Dress up and go on up for a drink and dance!If you book through the website or hotel directly, check back to see if rates drop. We booked and found a reduced rate a few days prior to leaving and hotel matched price. Also check if your company has corporate rates. I was able to get a great price and worth it to stay here.WARNING: PRINT RESERVATIONS WITH RATESMake sure you print out your reservation including rates. My only gripe is after calling and speaking directly to a reservationist my new rate was not reflected in the system. Had I not brought along my new confirmation I had been charged the higher price. Even after presenting email confirmation I was second guessed by Front Desk. Not at all how you want to start your trip after traveling several hours. Note to Front Desk staff you are the first impression to your guest. Only gripe about entire tripI highly recommend getting the City Pass (Citypass.com) with the California and Powell Cable Cars running literally in front of the hotel it makes getting to any place in city a breeze. It includes unlimited cable cars ($5 one-way) and muni buses for $57 for a 7-day pass and includes admissions to attractions and museums. If you got time also check out Mr. Toads Tours. Sounds corny and 100% touristy but who cares it was well worth the money!Tadish's on California Street worth the wait.If your there over a weekend a must is the Farmer's Market at the end of California Street - Take the Cable Car down the hill quick walk to water.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>