<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="ed7d5698d08e563f895b2d9019341a9a" url=""><![CDATA[Hands down, it was our best and favorite vacation!! Neither my husband, nor I, had anything to worry about, and neither should you! I am truly saddened by those who felt they had such poor customer service, because we felt quite pampered... :-)Our stay was July 19 - 26, and was it ever HOT! Never a cloud in the sky the entire week. We love hot, so we didn't mind, but were glad we brought plenty of sunscreen, we almost used up 3 bottles between the two of us... I must say that we had the most amazing vacation at the Majestic, and will ABSOLUTELY be back next year! We are already planning a two week stay with extended family. Our room was perfect, if you can get 2250, you will love it. Great view of the pool, and the ocean as well, can't go wrong with that! We could never hear anything outside of the patio doors once they were closed. And we were right across the beach restaurant, so that says a lot. The room was immaculate, the maids did an excellent job. The mini fridge was always well stocked. We left a note asking for more water on the first day, and every single day after that we must have had 6 bottles waiting for us, plus pop! The pool is like none other I have ever seen. It's the full length of the resort, and was NEVER crowded. You could probably put everyone who stayed at the resort in the pool and you wouldn't touch each other. So that really eased up the beach as well. The beach was never crowded either. We walked up and down the beach quite a bit and found that the other resorts' beachfronts were much more jammed with people. My husband and I really couldn't care less where we were, beach, pool, whatever, everywhere you looked was an amazing view. Which takes me to the grounds. The staff works VERY hard at keeping the grounds well manicured. My husband ran each morning around the perimeter of the resort, usually around 6:30/7:00, and would see all the workers dropped off ready to start the day. There was one morning they were spraying the bushes for bugs/mosquitos, we never had a mosquito bite the entire trip. At that time of the morning, they are cleaning, having staff meetings at the restaurants, all making sure we all would have the best vacation possible. I am so appreciative of their hard work ethic, most of them were there from sunrise to way after sunset. So, to tell me the service was bad, sorry. I didn't see it.There were so many options for meals, we couldn't possibly get to everywhere we wanted to try. Breakfast was incredible. Tons of food to choose from, I really can't think of anything they didn't have. Lunch, we always went to the beach buffet. Every day was amazing view of the ocean while we ate, we didn't want to go anywhere else! Never had an issue with any of the food there. There is a lot I can't eat due to allergies, but I ALWAYS found something. Dinner, you must make a reservation for the Japanese Restaurant, Matsuri. I could never eat half of what they gave there's that much food! I wanted to finish it because it was the best food there (the shrimp is to die for!), but couldn't stuff it all in! I liked the french gourmet restaurant, the chicken was very good. The seafood and steak restaurants were not bad, but weren't our favorite either. I chose food at the buffets that were cooked in front of you, for the most part. That way I ensured the temperature was good and the food wasn't out for too long.We're not the ones to ask about nightlife. We are up so early in the morning, that we were too exausted by the time the shows were starting. So, we never made it to any. But after dinner there was always two guys playing just outside of the main buffet in an open air stage area, one on keyboard and one on either an alto or soprano sax. The last night we were there, they had a full band with three singer, performing what I think were very popular latin songs. They were fantastic!I'm sure I'm leaving a million things out, but I will say this. I LOVED this resort. We have never come home so rested and relaxed, it could not have been a better vacation. BIG thank you-s to AnneMarie for always providing fabulous service, and for being there for any questions. I am so sad I didn't get to meet you! To Victor at the front desk, who was very accomodating and made sure we were happy. To Oscar at Matsuri, who provided great entertainment and fabulous food! I really wish we could have taken you home! And lastly to Victor at the pool bar!!! YEAH BABAY!!!!! He made every visit to the bar a great one, we looked forward to seeing him every day. The man LOVES his job!! If anyone has any questions at all, please feel free to private message me. I will do my best to help. I seriously can't stop talking about the Majestic, I might as well be of some use to all of you!! I'm still mourning the fact that I have to cook for myself, and CLEAN... just terrible... :-)
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>