<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="e9087ae7f6b93159a4a6bf7b50adc1c8" url=""><![CDATA[Puzzled Usually we read up on hotels before we book. This time we got a very late deal and did it backwards. The negativity of some reviews made us very apprehensive -but -Only just got back on line since we returned. This is the first time we have posted on Trip Advisor because,even if we disagree, we can usually see where people are coming from. Not here though!.Sunbeds on the beach. Some naughtiness in booking late at night. My wife joined a get up and see the sunrise ad hoc group. If people are that keen so be it. Perhaps the hotel could manage the situation a little better.The shows we never saw. 10pm is very late when you get up before dawn!.Ann has mobility problems but we were given a groundfloor room close to the beach and we didn't find getting around much of a problem. Our room we rated up to standard for the area (our 15th holiday this way in recent years).We rated the buffet excellent for all three meals, even made a point of complimenting the Chef. Only been impressed enough to do that on one previous occasion!. Drinks with meals and service never a problem.The beach buffet was the best we have come across yet. We discovered this on day three and lunched there for the rest of the fortnight.We enjoyed all the speciality restaurants, especially the Oriental. The Steakhouse, I suspect should be called the Grill. Give it a miss if you like big portions. We rated it a pleasant change.Almost throughout we found the service to be excellent. Having read some complaints on this, we started to look for evidence. Found none. I spent some time at all of the bars (as one does on holiday!). Impressed with how all of the bartenders tried to serve guests in order and remain cheerful and polite.On the last night we had a disturbing problem. We thought it a pity that the hotel should let itself down at the 11th hour so on the following morning we informed the management of our concerns. In the couple of hours it took us to pack, the incident was investigated and comprhensive explanation was given - including steps the hotel had taken to prevent a recurrence. Very impressed.We like to try new hotels. Have only done repeats to one in this area before but we will be looking to return to this one.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>