<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="a0dd418c797297afe55bc5bc2c82f1cf" url=""><![CDATA[Soulless We were looking forward to staying here based on the hotel website and pictures displayed there. We booked a superior room and would recommend doing so based on some of the previous reviews. Our room was fairly large and came with stylish lighting and decorated with a modern theme. Breakfast was good with a large selection although the layout of the table can mean that this can be an impersonal affair. The location of the hotel is ok and a easy walk along the river takes you to the Ponte Vecchio and all of the Florence sites.The staff were not great and one day we arrived back at 3.30pm to find the room had not been serviced, however a quick call to reception fixed this. Overall a nicely decorated hotle but let down by the staff and lack of character to the place.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="947a6564bc0c8aca6f31c22f6be46a6b" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location!!!! We stayed at the Renaissance Hollywood for the final 3 nights of our honeymoon. Check in was very swift and efficient and we had a room on the 16th floor (i had requested a room with a good view) with a tremendous view of the hills and the famous 'HOLLYWOOD' sign. We would sit and admire the view in a morning and evening. The room itself was large, light and airy and very clean. Tea/coffee facilites were useful. The main attraction of the hotel is its location, right on Hollywood Boulevard with the walk of fame, chinese theatre, El Capitan theatre, Kodak theatre and other tourist sites. The centre is part of the Hollwood and Highland complex with plenty of dining and shopping available. In terms of dining, the hotel restaurant was excellent and reasonably priced and was probably our best meal whilst staying there. We happened to be there whilst the 'Love Guru' premiere was on so caught a glimpse of Mike Myers as he went in to the chinese theatre. The following evening Warren Beatty was at the Kodak Theatre so no shortage of star spotting opportunities.The hotel is also well located for public transport as it is a 2 minute walk to the top of the metro red line, one stop from Universal Studios (we spent a day there and thoroughly enjoyed it) and a simple bus ride to Beverly hills and Santa Monica/Venice (be prepared for an hours ride on the 704). With more time we would have also gone on one of the tour buses and visited some more sights.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c5cd9fbc214873fcebee9f5fc875d485" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel After reading several reviews of hotels in Waikiki we decided to stay at the Hotel Renew.In short we would agree with all of the previous reviews for this hotel. We had a room on the 7th floor with a fabulous ocean view, the only downside is that you also overlook the Outrigger Waikiki. From checking in to checking out the staff at the hotel went out of their way to make our stay as pleasant as possible. Chilled juice and wet towel on check in, champagne in the room (we were celebrating our honeymoon). We were upgraded to a Premier room which we were delighted about. One unexpected bonus was the free newspapers in the morning and complimentary continental breakfast, coffee/tea/juice and pastries/muffins were more than enough for us. Leonor Wong, the executive housekeeper, was on hand in the morning to ensure everything was running smoothly and help advise on any queries. We had an early check out on the day we were leaving and the hotel provided us with fruit and some chocolates on our departure since we would miss breakfast. The hotel itself is an oasis of calm after the hustle and bustle that is Waikiki. The lobby is styled in a very modern way and was getting new front doors whilst we were there. The rooms are all very comfortable with modern lighting, flat screen tv etc and are wonderful having just been refurbished. There is no restaurant but you have the pick of the Waikiki hotels all within easy walking distance. Of the ones we ate in the Moana Surfrider was our favourite. The location of the hotel is at the south end of Waikiki, one block back from the beach. There is an ABC store next to the hotel entrance, bus stop around the corner.We used the bus to visit Pearl Harbour and the USS Amazon memorial, this is easy to do and is only a single bus ride but be prepared for a long journey. We also rented a car for the day to explore the rest of the island - Dole plantation, the Polynesian Cultural Centre and North Shore are worth visiting.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>