<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="bcd2671661b1427a209930d0aa90a874" url=""><![CDATA[It's gotten cheaper -- in more ways than one This was the seventh of the last eight Christmases at the Hilton Hawaiian Village's upscale Ali'i Tower. It was more economical, but the service plain and simply wasn't what it has been in previous years.The room itself was fine and scenic. I asked in advance for an upgrade to Ocean View Ali'i from Partial Ocean View Ali'i, and it was waiting on arrival. Also asked for a quiet room, and it was that, too. Room itself was fine, and the view of the Pacific from the 12th Floor for a retireee rate of $269 a night plus tax, including free hors d'oerves poolside each night, and (with my Hilton Gold membership) free continental breakfast, was in my opinion a good bargain. Also got a complimentary fresh fruit amenity plate on arrival.The price had dropped twice since I booked it in March -- Hilton didn't tell me this, but when I saw it on their website I rebooked it each time. Considering the category -- Ocean View Honolulu Beach Resort at Christmas -- I have no complaints about price.So, what's the problem?Mainly, housekeeping and service. Specifically, little things that were omitted. When you read this list, it will seem petty, but remember, the Ali'i Tower is supposed to be the upscale tower of the Hilton (Ali'i means elite in Hawaiian). Earlier this decade they used to have a fancy-white-uniform doorman at the tower door, and they serviced rooms three times daily (that was overkill, I admit -- even a bother-- but it shows how seriously they USED to take service. But now, no doorman, once-a-day housekeeping, and, my gripes: *No laundry/dry clean bags in the holder provided for them. *No ice bag liners for the ice buckets two nights out of five. *TV remote that wouldn't work, and when I called Guest Service Hotline rang so long it went to a recording. Finally got a human to take the TV trouble call, but then no one showed up and I had to call again. *Forgot to leave regular coffee packets the last day, only decaf.*Hilton bedside chocolates only one night out of five.*Poolside continental breakfast had now gone over $20 for those who weren't Gold members, the fresh-produce quality seemed to have declined, and they had switched to disposable plates and dishes, and plastic utensils.Is it still a decent hotel? Yes.Is it a good bargain? It certainly can be if you book carefully, and keep checking back. Sure was for me.Is it the luxury deluxe tower it used to be? Absolutely not.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>