<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="38e4f5674ecaa1fd3615cefec7d33222" url=""><![CDATA[***** Star Service SO much has been said about this property already, but I am happy to report The Hotel Vitale is my new found fave in San Francisco. I'm usually a creature of habit, but decided to give Hotel Vitale a try. I always love walking along the water, visiting the Ferry Building and Farmers Market, Dining, Shopping, Exploring-and this property makes a great base to experience the best of San Francisco. The service was incredible from the moment I arrived. I felt genuinely welcomed by the Valet Bell staff, Front Desk etc. The Concierges are !!outstanding!! and every recommendation was spot on. The Vitale attracts a nice diverse all ages mix of people (singles, families, couples) and is such a comfortable place to stay and relax. I was truly surprised at the quality of staff, quality of food, and water view/s at reasonable prices. The Vitale has a cozy Lounge and stylish Restaurant offering some truly delectable food and delightful service, and let us not forget about the simple comfortable rooms complete with every amenity.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d856079abd1972afa6fc3cdf5d1e387e" url=""><![CDATA[Not all experiences are perfect I loooove looove love the Ritz Carlton product, and especially look forward to staying there twice a year when visiting San Francisco. Many of the things I adore about this property have not changed but unfortunately some important things have slipped. For this visit, my reservation was made directly through the Hotel two months prior to my stay. I called direct in order to book a specific room --which I liked very much in the past-- or a room in the same approximate corridor offering a similar view. This was not a difficult request due to the size of this property and number of rooms that fit this description- if my first choice was not available, I was hoping for an exterior view and was not restricted by budget. I also requested two dinner reservations for this visit. When I arrived at the Hotel and checked in, I inquired about the location of the room and was told it was interior facing. This was not what I had requested or ideal. I asked the young woman at the front desk about my special request and she said it could not be accomodated as the Hotel was quite booked. I asked if they might have a higher category room or Suite available. Unfortunately, she told me there were no other options. Not happy about the sitaution, but still happy to be in one of my favorite places I succumbed and headed off to my room.Things went along as they usually do...lovely flowers, pleasant staff, well maintained facilities, nice displays of food and drink (on the Concierge Floor) and the expected top notch Ritz Carlton SF experience. Day two after hoofing it around the city all day we returned to the hotel to get ready for Dinner and had a message in regards to our Dinner plans-the RC had mistakenly made an 8:00 P.M. Dinner reservation for that evening. It was now 5:45 P.M. and the Concierge contacted the restaurant but unfortunately they were unable to accomodate us. The concierge suggested a few other options-we took her suggestion, and when she phoned us back she notified us that the only opening was at 6:45. Unfortunately since it was Saturday night our options were limited. We quickly showered and headed off to Dinner. After returning from dinner the Concierge greeted us and asked how everything was. We told her the restaurant was very pretty and had a nice atmosphere but the food was just okay. She inquired about what we ate and how the rest of our stay was and we told her how dissappointed we were with a few things and then breifly detailed the room situation, missed reservation, etc. She then stated not all experiences are perfect and to contact her in the future so she could assure we would be taken care of. Hmmmm-can you say stunned? I thought I'm sorry or I hoped you would enjoy the food more might have covered it more tactfully. I enjoyed the remainder of the evening but thought Wow-did that just happen?It is true, not all experiences are perfect but as a frequent traveler I fully well know that. I don't think that line should be uttered by a staff member under any circumstances let alone this one especially since I was (and we were) just answering her question. People make mistakes, and that is why they call them mistakes. I was irked but willing to overlook a less than flawless stay. One mediocre visit would not prohibit a future one. I hoped it was just a hiccup. All I can figure is the place seemed understaffed (turn down service was occuring well after 10:00 P.M.), dirty plates and glasses were everywhere especially during the Morning and Cocktail Hours. And lastly we requested a late check out and that too was something that could not be accomodated. Not a big deal but certainly not the expected for $600.00 a night.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="622ac3c3e6211456ffa81c46f8cedcc7" url=""><![CDATA[One of the finest Hotels in the World This was the one and only Hotel I wanted to stay in when planning a trip to Paris, and it exceeded all my expectations. The Four Seasons Paris is in a word '' beautiful . The Four Seasons is well located, and every detail impresses. The world famous floral displays will astound even the most jaded, there is a gorgeous modern/ formal center garden, magnificent dining room, lovely bedrooms/ bathrooms, and generous closets! All of the staff we encountered were excellent and every space immaculately maintained. The dining room is a surreal Dinner setting and as you arrive to your table a staff member magically blankets the table top with fresh rose petals, tucks in cymbidium orchid blossoms, and candles. During my stay, there was a large VIP event in Paris and despite the high number of recognizable actors and sports celebrities swirling about, every Guest received the same VIP treatment. This is an extremely comfortable property despite the formality of the decor' and excellent in every way.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4101428734935e024c443ce09b87bc97" url=""><![CDATA[Impeccable The 41 is impeccable. The moment you step in the door you feel as if you are entering a private residence. The excellent decor combines traditional elegance with a twist. Black and white dominates the bedrooms, and the lounge (think elegant private Library) with it's large conservatory style roof, repeats the theme adding in a discreet bit of animal print. The young polished international staff provides finely tuned personal service.I don't want to emphasize the smallness of the room or property -it happens to be a huge part of the charm. Guest rooms provided everything imaginable and then some. I spent about 20 minutes aquainting myself with the immense list of turn down gifts special bath elixirs, relaxing pillow spray, lengthly pillow menu (this list goes on) and if your cherished pet is fortunate enough to be traveling along, 41 has special meals, signature bedding, welcome baskets, and numerous treats for your companion. NO request is too large as evidenced by the self explanatory Whatever/Whenever button on the phone.Back to the room, heavenly bedding (and bed), fireplace, small writing desk, two chairs and cocktail table, a hefty stack of great magazines, simply the best map and listing of local attractions I've seen, small ice bucket and slices of fresh lime and lemon alongside a bamboo skewer (great touch). A place for my iPod Yay! Speakers tucked in all the corners! The bathroom was well stocked too with lovely smelling Blenheim bath bubbles and soap, nice big soaking tub with rain showers in tub and separate shower, heated towel bar with loads of fluffy towels everywhere (amazing how so many hotels miss this item and only give you 2 large bath towels and pairs of hand and wash cloths). The lovely ebony wood fitted closet also provided for every need, desire, and luxury. On arrival the young lady checking us in provided us with a pre-dinner welcome cocktail and small nibbles in the room while we unpacked our things. When returning to the hotel after dinner we were greeted by scented lit candles, fluffy robes, and faux fur bed throw-can you spoil us more? Ironically on check-in we were asked if we were celebrating any special occasion during our stay and we said no-I can't wait to return for a special day just to see what 41 has in mind for those special occasions!Breakfast is served in the Lounge (or your guest room) and the attention to detail continues. A.M. food choices such as fresh fruits, berry compote, gorgeous baked goods, juices, numerous cereals (organic too), cooked english breakfast, and a la carte menu.Phew! Now I know what life is like across the street at the castle.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ec7754904c95042db3f998bf20af8b3f" url=""><![CDATA[W SAn Francisco This is a cool Hotel true to the W brand. The W San Francisco is situated just perfectly for business or convention purposes straight across from Moscone. It's also a good home base if you want to just shop, tour, or visit the Museum. The public spaces are stylish and the Lobby attracts good looking --young-- locals too -so it's a nice mix of tourists, business people, and city dwellers. This property is definately geared towards a pretty specific age and interest group (sophisticated mostly mid 20's-40's singles or couples w/ no kids tagging along). It's all about hanging out to chill music and dim lighting. The rooms and bathrooms are attractive, comfortable, well thought out, but a bit small even by SF standards. Still a completely enjoyable property that is great fun and a decent value for a weekend in this wonderful city.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>