<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="e48b3f888c2f7ff4f1953f033a7e4915" url=""><![CDATA[Quick access from Terminal E After a 8 hour intercontinental flight it's nice to have a clean, comfortable hotel at hand.Hilton Logan airport is such a hotel.Quick, sufficient check in.Upgraded room without asking (as a Hilton Honors gold member).Pool/sauna/steamroom OK.Breakfast buffet average. Free transportation to subway was efficient. Pick up from subwaystation after request by telephone was quickly.Quit room, no noise from planes.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="027e107cb78b00dad5bf677a9b90042f" url=""><![CDATA[OK to stay The Amsterdam Ramada has a good location. Near Central station. Public transport right in front of hotel. Lobby and restaurant recently refubished. Modern design. Good italian coffees!Rooms are small but efficient for 3 stars. The bed I slept in need to be replaced. When you have a room at the back of the hotel than take a look out the window. Surprise! You think you are in the red light district. Youre not, but some of the girls have there red window in this street.Overall OK. Nice breakfast buffet. Not overpriced pp. Book the room on there website. I booked a special offer at an agent and turned out to pay more than on there website.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1765bb7bcf0d3d6e04672a911a2273ca" url=""><![CDATA[Brand new Hotel - Airport location Brand new hotel (opened 1 week ago) in the airport area.Modern style hotel. Nice rooms. Standard rooms - no bahttub - no minibar. Very comfy beds! Nice flat LCD screen.Hotel looks a bit sterile. But everybody was very helpful and friendly.Buffetbreakfast is worth the cost of 20 euro.Airport shuttle is free from airpo to hotel. Return cost 5 euro.Public transport to Amsterdam city center. Walk about 15/20 min. to tram stop (ask reception for direction) Take tram nr. 1 to city center (about 25 min. to Leidseplein)4 star hotel. So no fuss like a pool, sauna etc.Stay was above average. Looks promising for the future. Hope they keep the pricelevel.Now euro 99/night.Hotel is isolated. No nothing, no shops, no restaurant in the near distance. So buy your drinks, snacks or whatever in the city or at the airpo.Or from the vendingmachines or bar or restaurant in the hotel of course.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="92c7ba63d35b3db968696f099b424528" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful BCN We stayed 3 nights at this nice design hotel. Mainly spanish and british guests.Quick check-in. We paid a good + 7% tax for a double room incl. breakfast.Room was quiet, very clean, but smaller than most rooms in a 4 star categorie. Maybe because spanish people are overall smaller than north european people the room and bathroom are a bit smaller than average.But furniture, cleanliness are OK.Breakfast: cold meats, cheese, assortement rolls, fresh fruit,eggs, sausage, bacon, cereals, danish rolls, toast, juices. All from a buffet.The hotel is in a residential area, only 5 min. walk from metro station Hospital Clinic. From there good connections to the center of BCN.In the neigberhood are very few restaurants. So you have to dine in the hotel or find a restaurant further away.When you walk up to the Hospital Clinic station you pass a nice supermarket. (about 200 mtr. from hotel) Skip the hotel minibar and buy your drinks, snacks in the supermarket. Specially mineral water because spanish tapwater has lots of chlorine.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>