<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="4ccd6af033a1d437a712803a6217807e" url=""><![CDATA[Great Stay at the Intercontinental Our Room
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e17e3d24e953d2c807d628c4cf5701a6" url=""><![CDATA[Almost impossible to check-in - Beware! Booked this hotel through Hotwire many months before and got a great deal - however, it may not have been worth it for the aggravation suffered.We arrived here on a Sunday afternoon around 1:20. The line was already horrendous but the worst was still to come! There were 3 cruise ships disembarking in San Juan this day and the Sheraton OSJ was in no position to accept the incoming guests.Pre-registration was done and we were told they start giving out keys at 3 PM. We moved to the restaurant Chicago Burger and had a decent lunch while we waited. Food was good - service was a little slow.At 2:50 we got back in the dreaded line and were told rooms were not ready. OK - wait some more - at 3:30 we are back in line and once we reach the desk we are told Nope - still no rooms. I very calmly said that was fine - I would wait at the desk til one was ready, as I was not going through that line once more!They told me I could not wait at the desk and since I refused to move they did call security! Fine - he stood behind me but I did succeed in getting one of our 2 rooms. The very rude front desk staff did promise our luggage would be brought to the room and another room key would be delivered within 10 minutes....whatever....they just wanted me away from the desk so we all got our wishes.The security guard did promise my husband that he would stay on it and true to his word we had our luggage and another room within 10 minutes. Our room was on the 9th floor - near the roof top pool. It was very dark and had the appearance of being clean but I'm not totally sure. The lighting was very poor - not even a lamp on the desk. No closet - just an armoire - that's OK because we're only staying one night. Happy to see an operating safe in the room as I have learned to trust no one! The bathroom was very large but once again I wasn't sure about the cleanliness and thought I saw a bug in the corner - it turned out to be fluff but why was it there in the first place? The bed was very comfortable and we did sleep well.Enjoyed a nice breakfast in Pallio the next morning - the staff was friendly and the portions were large.The final insult from the front desk was that they could not - or would not? - make change so we could tip the valet.We were told the hotel check-in nightmare happens every Sunday so beware - you could spend hours trying to get a room. Other guests told us the hotel has a practice of allowing guests to enjoy a late check out, for a fee, and this is why rooms are not ready at the prescribed check in time. Whether this is true or not I do not know. I only know we will never stay there again no matter what the price.The location is perfect - the one true plus for this hotel. You can walk anywhere in Old San Juan and the waterfront area. Next time we will stay in the Isla Verde area and take cabs!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e8d4021190f7d4b4537f970b1848f704" url=""><![CDATA[Add me to the list of those who love this hotel! We stayed at the Brooklyn Bridge Marriott for one night before boarding a cruise out of Brooklyn. We booked directly through the Marriott's website many months before and secured a favorable rate using the Senior discount.Arrived around 3 PM and had no problem checking in early. The front desk staff were both professional and friendly. After check-in we moved to the bar for a couple of drinks and found this to be a fun place. The bartender, Michael, makes a great Manhattan!Talked with the doorman, Nick, who recommended a great dinner spot - the Queen Italian Restuarant. There was 6 of us and he had no problem arranging transportation for our ride there.After dinner we returned to the Marriott for coffee and dessert. They serve Starbucks and a wicked cheesecake sampler platter ($13) which easily fed us all - we may not have finished it all! Great attentive service as well.The rooms were clean and comfortable and good sized. The bed was very comfy. Very large bathroom and lots of hot water and pressure in the morning.The hotel itself is very lovely. There are escalators from the main entrance up to the lobby and they are surrounded by lots of greenery and flowers. Security is also very evident and appreciated.We enjoyed a great breakfast the next morning in the hotel restaurant. A buffet is offered in addition to the regular menu. Portions were huge and I'm not sure any of us were able to finish. Service was extremely friendly but a little slow.As this was a quick trip we were not able to enjoy the pool - hopefully we will on our next trip, as we are staying here again next May.To sum it up we had a great stay and look forward to the next one!Transportation notes: there were 4 of us traveling from JFK with at least 8 bags. We arranged to have Arecibo pick us up - the fee to the hotel was $50 plus tip. Our doorman, Nick, arranged our transportation to the port and that was $25 plus tip.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="02b306b875b6a274a5f495754ea0ba93" url=""><![CDATA[Langham is Beautiful!! Stayed at the Langham from 9/1 to 9/4. We arrived early in the morning and planned on checking our bags until later in the day. To our delight we were allowed to check in! We had booked a moderate Queen room and were given a lovely room on the 6th floor overlooking Post Office Park. The room was immaculate as was the very large gleaming bathroom. Furnishings were lovely and new. The hotel furnishes plush bathrobes and slippers and our nightly turndown service, complete with chocolates on the pillows, made us feel like we were on a cruise ship! The radio was left turned on to a soft music channel - a nice touch.The staff was friendly and accommodating, from Stacey at the front desk, who checked us in and out, to Juan, one of the very nicest bell men ever. The housekeeping staff was right on the mark and we could never pass one of them without receiving a smile and a greeting. The Concierge supplied us with umbrellas for our one rainy day, which were greatly appreciated, since we prefer to walk until our feet fall off (!) when in Boston.The lobby and other public rooms are gorgeous. Sadly, we did not enjoy any meals at the Langham - that will have to wait until our next visit.The only annoyance was having to go to two floors once and three floors once to find ice! Not a showstopper by any means - just took a little longer to chill our wine!Having stayed previously at Jury's and the Wyndham (now Hilton) many times - we think we have found our new favorite hotel to be the Langham and look forward to our next visit.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>