<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="ef7f6ca2f3442fec8c5a45e26bbf0648" url=""><![CDATA[Quality accommodations in the heart of Seattle Whenever I travel on business, I now consult tripadvisor reviews prior to my trip. Based on the glowing reviews for this property, I chose the Holiday Inn Seattle, and I was not disappointed.Centrally located in an urban, but commercial section of town, the entrance to the hotel on Dexter Avenue is a bit claustraphobic. If there are several arriving, you may need to wait your turn to get into the lobby, but once you come in, the front desk is quick and courteous. After you check in, return to your car and turn right into the hotel, right behind the hotel, and right into the Holiday Inn garage (not the Express garage.) Swing wide on the last turn, because you use your room key to open the garage door from the driver's side. The second time I did this, it felt natural! Even the parking garage is well done. Although the spaces are small, the ceiling has an acoustical treatment making the garage quiet and relatively warm: a great benefit for Seattle weather.My room was large for a standard room with two queen beds and a sleeper sofa. The TV has a sleep timer (controlled on the TV itself) and about 20 channels of cable. There are several nice touches in the room in the form of instruction cards on how to operate the TV and internet (wired only... bring your ethernet cable or be billed $7.50!) The iron and board in my room were passable, but somewhat damaged by previous guests. The in-wall heater/AC was quiet, and there was little to no outside noise that disturbed my sleep.The other amenities are somewhat limited by the small size and location of the hotel. I noticed that the exercise room is somewhat larger than most with several cardio and weight machines. There is a business center with computer, printer and high-fee ATM machine.One of the other reviews raved about the Emerald Grill. I found their food above average, but nothing to write home about. However, for room service and a general service hotel... that's the kind of food you want. Room service was delivered in a timely fashion and at correct temperatures. Tip: If you want bread with your room service meal, you need to request it.Most of my days were spent away from the hotel, so I don't have any reviews of their ballroom or other facilities. However, I don't hesitate to recommend this location - it's a quality property.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>