<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="f6b76e55871689c721f78363de0b647d" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Choice for Theater Weekend We were part of a family group of three couples who stayed at the Omni in the beginning of January for a theater weekend. We booked broadway tickets through a special we saw on travelzoo and then used their site to search for hotels. The Omni was very reasonable so we used the travelzoo discount code and booked online at the Omni's site. We are very pleased we stayed there. The room was spacious, bathroom large and staff very friendly. I really liked their web check-in process. We said we'd be there at 11:30AM, showed up on time and our keys were ready on arrival. I appreciated that they treated us with great care even though we'd booked using a discount. All three couples enjoyed the hotel and agreed we'd like to stay there when we do our 2009 theater weekend.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="65ff5aeeae12b4128d1b28eb785d561d" url=""><![CDATA[Casablanca great again! We (3 couples) stayed at the Casablanca for a theater weekend January 9-10. Once again the hotel worked out well in every respect. Good location, nice size queen rooms with large upscale bathrooms, wine and cheese by the fire place as well as breakfast in the 2nd floor lounge area, great and friendly staff and reasonable prices.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c02d0f4e959d7432b7f80f2f2fef6b00" url=""><![CDATA[First Time at Elysee - Great Hotel We stayed at the Elysee the weekend of Feb. 23-24 to attend a wedding. We tried the Casablanca, our favorite hotel, but it was full. However we discoved the Elysee is owned by the same owners so booked it. It was a great hotel. We had a small changing room, large bedroom with a sitting area and large upscale bath. The staff were very attentive and we enjoyed the sitting room(s) on the 2nd floor as well as a very nice continental breakfast included in the room rate. We'd recommend this hotel in a heartbeat.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>