<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="2c5072096daf1c1e5cc73ebab1afd986" url=""><![CDATA[One night at Hyatt harborside Stayed one night (friday) at Hyatt harborside as we had a transatlantic flight to catch at 9am. We check in during the early afternoon with the plan to spend the afternoon /early evening in Boston. Our plan worked well, and is worth considering for those with a morning flight out of Logan.No queue to check in on arrival, left luggage with bellman headed up to the room - luggage was delivered within 10 mins. Our room on 9th floor, had a fantastic Harbor view - so good you could take a photo from the room!!.Room had 2 Queen beds, medium to firm matress, with good quality linens, room was decorated in a modern style. Armchair by window, ipod docking station, bathroom with tub shower but no bathrobes. Toiletries were basic - I have to admit though am not a fan of the hyatts portico toiletries. Room was clean but not overly large. Glasses ice bucket provided (ice machine on each floor). NO aiport noise whatsoever from the room, but you can hear noise from the corridor - lucky for us we had quiet neighbours!!The lift is fun - you get a waterview as you travel up down!!There is a nice patio area outside where you can dine or have a drink with a great view (at night the staff light candles lanterns its quite lovely) - but the indoor bar area was a dissapointment, not inviting not a place to linger. Staff seemed overstreched but remained polite. Food was good but not great, Calamari appitizer was very large (enough for 2) and tasty.The water taxi is available just outside the hotel - be sure to use the walkie talkie to call for a taxi as they appear to wait offshore rather than at the dock. We used the service to get to Boston it was a fun experience. Taxi service runs till 10pm, so you do not have to dine at the hotel restaurant.Although hotel was busy the pool/gym was empty, we used both. Lockers/towels provided water, cool towels apples were available. Pool is saltwater affords you a view of the harbor whilst you swim The jacuzzi was very hot. There is also a sauna which we did not use - With the heatwave Boston was expereincing we were hot enough!!.Early morning bellstaff came for luggage we had a short wait for one of the two (free) shuttles to the airport.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>