<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="6104fe9fca582ae85eec89487711a410" url=""><![CDATA[Could Not Wait To Leave If you want Dominican service at New York prices, then this is the place for you. We experienced all of the pitfalls discussed in other reviews -- bone jarring ride from airport, lackluster food, ridiculous costs, and the feeling that once you get there, you're trapped in a Dominican Bizarro World of rip-offs designed exclusively for foreign tourists.Then add to that the huge man eating spiders in our luxurious ocean front room. (I am traumatized, and to this day am still afraid to open my underwear drawer at home.) As mentioned, many guests have either scalding hot water or ice cold water from the showers. A tropical squall flooded a couple of ocean front rooms with an inch of water, while folks upstairs with the thatched roof experienced little worms and insects falling from the ceiling. (I hope they slept with their mouths closed!)These are the stories of the folks that traveled with us as part of a corporate reward / retreat for my company. Of the seven couples that went, we all had freaky little horror stories. Our stay was a lesson in Dominican dysfunction, which would be cute if it were not supposed to be at a luxury resort. Nor is it cure that you are presented with a water menu whenever you dare to eat there. (Several in our party became ill from the food.) They tell you the water from the tap is undrinkable and then sell you $8 bottles of water with your meal. I found the local rum to be both tastier and cheaper!The front desk staff was ill equipped to handle any of the cavalcade of issues their hotel was presenting its guests. For example, they were unable to offer me change for a $50 bill, and had no stamps for my postcards. although they promised to send them for me, and I paid them to mail them. my little nieces and nephews never received their cards. In addition, the internet connections promised in the rooms were (again predictably) not working.The spa semed to have lots of nice things in it, but the whirlpool was lukewarm and the stream room was not working. The sauna was nice when they remembered to turn it on -- which seemed to be every other day. They invested a lot of money into the spa to not have it functioning properly, and such seemed to typify both the Agua resort and the surrounding area.When we tried to escape from Agua and venture to go out for dinner one night to the nearby Al Navigante, we were again subject to another fiasco. When we were served wine that had turned to vinegar they tried to charge us for the bad wine. They also added two additional dinners to the tab. When I protested the extra charges they tried to negotiate. Indeed -- they exemplified the apparent Dominican business ethic when dealing with tourists: Take them for all you can!A day trip to a Dominican cigar factory took us to a shop in Bavaro run by a woman from Switzerland who had two guys rolling stogies, and while the guys in our group smoked free samples, the ladies were shown local jewelry for purchase. Indeed, it seemed as if the only place where we were being scammed worse than in the hotel was just anywhere else in the DR!Yes, there were some positives. The wait staff at Agua was entirely friendly and they seemed to genuinely enjoy teaching Spanish to my wife and I. Also, the beach is very nice and the water was inviting. (However, the water was also pretty cloudy when we were there and I am told it is largely unsuitable for snorkeling.)When our week was over, we were all very anxious and quite happy to leave. Again predictably, the driver was late to pick some of our fellow travelers up. They were late to the airport and almost missed their flights.Perhaps luxury resort and the Dominican Republic are mutually exclusive. It sure seemed so at Agua. After all, in the DR even the sidewalks have potholes! Yes, the people we met were for the most part very nice, unless you had to deal with money, and the beach was very nice. However, there are far too many negatives to outweigh the few positives, and Agua charges way too much to expect its guests to overlook those negatives. To Agua I say Adios and good riddance!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>