<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="1233cb0f700d0e085dc8620acb7c0231" url=""><![CDATA[Great place for the right price This can be a great place to stay depending on what you pay. We booked this on Priceline (bidding) for $115 per night. For that price it was a steal. We booked it for before and after a cruise. It is actually a very nice hotel in a great location and has an excellent pool and beach. The hotel has a large open air lobby which is nice but not as classy as the Wyndham El San Juan but nice enough. The hotel has been built in phases over the years. We were in the original building which I prefer since all of the rooms have great water views. Some of the later buildings have sections that look out on other buildings and parking garage, etc. The rooms are a decent size with nice bathrooms and very nice beds and bedding. The furniture is a little dated. The hotel has an excellent location on a peninsula into the water on the outskirts of Old San Juan. You are only about a 10 minute ride from the cruise ships and Old San Juan. If you are looking for a lot of nightlife and shopping outside your door this is not the place for you. The nicest part of the hotel is the beach and pool area. The beach is on its own cove, not much in the way of waves, but otherwise very nice. It has a great pool area and a nice area with hammocks and palm trees for shade. We are members of the Hilton Honors and were put on the club floor. The club floors have the use of a very nice lounge with free snacks drinks, newspapers and computer. For $115 per night this was a great deal. We were originally booked at the Marriott for the stay on the return from the cruise, but at $350 a night for the Marriott and $155 for the Hilton it was a no brainer. If you are going to pay $350 a night I would consider the El San Juan or the Marriott, but with the discount rates on the Hilton it is well worth it. My only complaint was that it does not have a casino, so you need to get a cab to go to a casino or to go to other restaurants. We ate at the Morton's on a great web promotion, 2 excellent meals for $99, but the other hotel restaurants looked very overpriced. They do have a Starbucks in the lobby.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9ab4bb4f77fe6dcf5c63e865f54381d8" url=""><![CDATA[Depends on what youu pay for this hotel This hotel may be worth staying in depending on what you have to pay for it. We had two rooms for 4 nights, booked on Priceline for $200/night each. We were upgraded to the Rainbow Tower on the water at no additional cost. The tower you are in is very important, since only a few have a decent water view and many are back away from the water with no water view. We had a very nice view looking out on a marina with the ocean and coast beyond. The grounds and common areas are actually very nice with lush landscaping. The resort is set up as a number of high-rise towers with the pools and landscaping between. There is also quite a number of shops and restaurants in a village type atmosphere. My reason for not rating the resort higher are two. First, the rooms are very dated, and two, the resort tends to try to get every last dollar out of you by charging you for everything they can. The furniture in our rooms was very dated and more like what you would find in an older Holiday Inn and not a luxury resort. While the bathrooms had been redone, they left the old sinks and faucets, which are very dated. The 3 sinks even had rust around the drains they had been there so long. The hotel had no chairs to use on the beach unless you paid an unreasonable fee to use them. The resort is actually very attractive and in a nice location, an easy walk to the shopping at Waikiki but in a nice quieter area. If you can get a very reasonable price, the Hilton may be worth considering. If you are not getting a decent discount I would stay elsewhere in a place that had more up to date rooms.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0167ed49072e5e343ce9184fa06feb8f" url=""><![CDATA[A terrific hotel in Florence We had two rooms at the Berchielli for three nights in September 2007, and this is a terrific hotel for visiting Florence. When we checked in we asked if we could be upgraded and we were told that we had been. The rooms faced out on the Arno River each with a balcony and views of the Ponte Vecchio Bridge which is a half block away. For exploring Florence this location can't be beat. Everything is an easy walk. The rooms were comfortable and nicely sized and the bathrooms were very nice. The rooms had Frette linens and towels. The hotel had a nice lobby lounge and bar and a great rooftop terrace. The included breakfast was excellent and extensive with hot and cold foods. The hotel has a lot of charm and a very friendly staff. They have a computer station in the lobby with free internet access. Since the hotel is made up of a number of older buildings, the room views, sizes and features vary. You may want to see what is available when booking, or ask for features you may want. The Berchielli is an excellent choice for visiting Florence.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ebb4fab66bb53d8b73bf5470b3dd2c34" url=""><![CDATA[A terrific hotel in Seattle The Pan Pacific Hotel in Seattle is a wonderful hotel and well worth staying at in Seattle. My only complaint is that the hotel could be a little more centrally located to the downtown core, however, everywhere was an easy walk and public transit is just outside the door and can take you anywhere. The hotel, itself, is brand new and extremely comfortable and tastefully done. The lobby and common areas are very well done, including a fireplace in the lounge area. All of the furnishings and decor are extremely tasteful, and well beyond the quality of your typical upscale chains. The rooms are very comfortable and well done, again, quite a cut above your upscale brand name chains. Nothing but great things to say about the hotel. It is well worth staying here if you need a hotel in downtown Seattle.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>