<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="b8473d1c275ec95f67d2c44d57eebae4" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location and would recommend Stayed for 3 nights in the Belvedere Hotel and was delighted with the room. From what I understand rooms in New York can be quite small so we was pleasantly surprised. For the price we paid this is great value. If you are looking for pure luxury - look elsewhere. If you are looking for a comfortable 3 star in a good location with pleasant staff and a decent sized, clean and comfortable room then this is what you getOur room was on the 17th floor and had a little kitchenette with coffee maker - coffee suplied - also microwave. The bathroom was small - as other reviewers have said - but it had everything and there was nothing to complain about. Shower was very good.We arrived a little early but our room was ready and we were able to check in. We were also allowed to check out a little later when departing which was great - they held our bags after that.We never had problem with the lifts - probably as we were on the top floor. Once it arrived up it was usually empty - however when it stopped at the various floors on the way down - it was often full. Lifts are definitely small.We had breakfast included in the price and it was very good. It would be very expensive it if were not included. Continental was about $13 and full american was nearly $20. The continental included tea, coffee, breads, cakes, cereal, fruit, cheese etc. The American had in addition suasage, bacon, eggs, home fries, pancakes, french toast. Plently places close by for breakfast otherwise.The location is great and we always felt safe walking around. We ate in the mexican next door one evening - Sombrero - and it was nice. There are plenty bars and restaurants close by and I would definitely stay again - we went to The Social (gets a bit noisy after 5), Hurleys, Pigalle just to name a few.We flew to Newark and got the NJ Transit to Penn - taxi only $8 to hotel. We got a taxi back to airport - hotel porters got it for us - - it was $80 including tip.Would have no hesitation recommending hotel or staying there again
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b78ac3b37bbdf70bd11c00a4bfe9a69a" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel and Value for Money We are just back from a 3 night stay in the City Inn - over the Easter weekend. I must agree with a lot of others regarding their positive reviews of this hotel.We had breakfast in the hotel each morning - if you are having the full english you order at the table and they serve it up to you - huge choice, bacon, sausage, eggs, mushrooms etc. You can also serve yourself from the buffet which had yogurts, cold meats, cheese, rolls, cakes, fresh fruit etc - plenty options and we had no complaints. Some people have said that there are long delays for breakfast - we were down every morning about 8 and had no problem. To be fair the hotel did have a little note in the room adivsing that at the weekend breakfast was busy after nine so if you were on a tight schedule then perhaps come before that time. We did not see too many places around where you could have got breakfast.The rooms are clean and have everything you would need - tv, tea and coffee making facilities ( complementary milk in the mimi bar fridge), proper hairdryer, safe, mini bar. Bathrooms are as previously described - I agree they are small but they have everything you would want and the shower is very good. If you need the use of a computer to check in online or anything then there are facilities on the fourth floor just next to the liftThere were newspapers available in reception all day and also as you went into breakfast.We went to the bar in the hotel one night on our way back from a show - it was very busy and had a good atmosphere. With regard to the location we had no difficulty with it - it is close to Pimlico station and Westminster Station. Pimlico is about a 5 minute walk but for a lot of lot of places you would need to change lines. We had no problem with the tube - hopping on and off and changing lines etc - if however you would be a bit nervous of this then perhaps the hotel might not suit you. Also for someone not able to walk too far and not too mobile then maybe might not be suitable - having said that there were always taxis outside the door. There was also a bus stop around the corner - we did not use this so not sure where it went toOverall this hotel is great value for money and for the service offered. The staff were always very pleasant from the reception staff to the breakfast staff. I would have no difficulty staying there again or recommending it to anyone - the only thing would be the location if you had a problem using the underground and did not want to be walking or paying out for taxis
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="93da4ee191d1cff622bfbe119a3243cb" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Stay - delighted with our choice Just back from a 4 night stay in the American Amsterdam and were absolutely delighed with our choice of hotel.We had booked a double room with balcony and canal view and were not disappointed. The room was on the 4th floor and was large, comfortable and quiet. The bathroom was on the small size but had everything you would require and a great shower. Slippers and dressing gown also provided. Room had a flat screen tv, mini bar and safe. Tea and coffee making facilites available in room and were replaced daily. There was also an iron and hairdryer.We had breakfast included in the package - would be a little expensive otherwise at per person. Great choice - juices, cakes, breads, fresh fruit, yogurt, cold meats, cheese, salmon, bacon, sausages, mushrooms, eggs etc - something to suit most people. It was served in the lovely Cafe American. Breakfast was served from 6.30am - 10.30 am weekdays and from 7am to 11am at the weekendWe never ate dinner in the restaurant but did have drinks there one evening and was very enjoyable - on arrival we had received a voucher for a welcome drink in the barAll the staff we deal with were friendly and helpful.There is internet access available on the first floor - 35 cent per minute - can pay by credit card or charge to roomOn arrival we got the train from the airport - public transport in Amsterdam is very cheap and easy to use. Have change available to purchase your train ticket to central station - machines would not take notes - so other option is credit card. - approx for the 2 of us. We were able to buy our tram ticket on the tram. There is a metro stop right outside the hotel. As our flight home was early the hotel booked us a taxi to the airport - takes about 25 minsThe location of the hotel is perfect - Leidseplein. Just outside of the hotel you can get the canal bus - this was per person and you can hop on and off all day and is valid until 12 the next day. Stops at the major sights and museums and is a great way of getting around. There are plenty bars and restaurants around the hotel - we tried to avoid the big noisy bars and opted for smaller old style onesMost sights are also within walking distance if you prefer that option. Having been all over the city - would definitely opt to stay in this area again and preferably in American Hotel
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>