<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="5517dad2721e5c1850788bc08cb96866" url=""><![CDATA[Okay Hotel in the University District of Seattle My wife and I travel to Seattle four or five times a year. As a couple that enjoys boutique hotels, my wife and I found the Watertown Hotel to be satisfactory, but certainly nothing to get excited about. We usually stay at one of the Kimpton Hotels (there are three in Seattle), but all three Kimpton Hotels were sold out for the July 6 to 8, 2007 weekend due to the Kenny Chesney Flip Flop Summer Tour 2007, so we looked over Seattle hotel reviews on Tripadvisor. The Watertown Hotel was the only top 5 rated hotel in Seattle with a room available (they told me on the telephone it was their last available room), so we booked the room for $185 (plus tax) per night. The Watertown Hotel is located in the University district, about six miles north of downtown Seattle. It is a safe area with plenty of restaurants located within walking distance of the hotel. Our room, like the property itself, was clean and well looked after. The room had a comfortable King bed, basic washroom, tiny fridge and a small television set. Our room was located off the elevator lobby on the fifth floor, so there was a lot of hall noise until well past midnight both nights of our stay. There is free, secured parking, located under the hotel for hotel guests, but the parking stalls are tiny and the ceiling only six feet, six inches high, so larger vehicles may have problems parking. Also, the breakfast selection was not satisfactory (limited items, with no fruit or healthy eating options), so we wandered over to the Farmer's Market (five blocks away) for breakfast one morning and we drove to the 14 Carrot Cafe for beakfast the second day (located a couple miles from the Watertown Hotel at 2305 Eastlake Ave E on the way to downtown Seattle). In summary, we would stay at the Watertown Hotel again, but it will never be our first choice in the Seattle area.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="67460cd88ed16d58c16f1820b16c3e80" url=""><![CDATA[My Wife Loved It...Enough Said My wife and I spent three nights at the Argonaut Hotel during January of 2005. We loved it! The California King bed was great, as were the feather pillows and overall room decor. Location is everything, and the Argonaut Hotel has a great location at the corner of Hyde and Jefferson on Fisherman's Wharf. Although a little large for boutique hotel status, we loved the place and recommend it highly to anyone wanting a great place to stay in San Francisco. The only negative is The Blue Mermaid Restaurant in the hotel, which we found to be tacky and expensive. Do yourself a favour next time you are in San Francisco. Stay at the Argonaut Hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8ce620f84515abc082e6650000cdbdff" url=""><![CDATA[A Windy Long Weekend in San Fran My wife and I stayed four nights at the Serrano Hotel in San Francisco from January 3 to 7, 2008. We had never stayed at the Serrano Hotel before, but since it is part of the Kimpton boutique hotel chain that my wife and I enjoy, we thought that we'd give it a try. I booked our King Deluxe room via the Kimpton website for $126 per night (plus tax), a rate that I thought was very reasonable for downtown San Francisco.We arrived Thursday night at 10 pm during the worst winter storm of the season (our flight from Canada was delayed 3 hours due to the storm conditions in San Francisco). Unfortunately, after a long trip getting to San Francisco, we did not get the warm Serrano Hotel welcome advertised on many web pages and websites. Don't get me wrong, everyone was decent to us, but there was no offer of a game of 21 to upgrade our room (as mentioned in the bedside book in our room), and the concierge desk person was less than enthusiastic when I asked about any half-decent places to eat on a late Thursday evening in the immediate area (we had missed dinner due to the flight delay).Speaking of the immediate area around the Serrano Hotel, it is less than upscale. In fact, the neighbourhood, despite being only two blocks from Union Square and kitty-korner to the San Francisco Hilton, is what one might call Transitional. That is, by day the neighbourhood is okay, but come darkness, the streets are taken over by homeless people and panhandlers. Furthermore, the streets in the area are very dark, lacking sufficient municipal street lighting. Some people may find the idea of walking alone at night too scary to try...As for the Serrano Hotel itself, it is a three star property (based on the five star scale). Some websites refer to it as a four star property, but it is not! The lobby is nice and clean, with a feeling of the roaring 20s. Our room, a King Deluxe, was also clean and contained the blessed Kimpton King Size bed (there are no Tall Rooms at the Serrano Hotel). As always, we had excellent sleeps in the Kimpton bed, but our room was extremely small with a very plain and basic bathroom. We can only hope that one-day the Kimpton people will hear about flat screen Plasma and LCD television, and start installing 42 inch sets into their hotel rooms instead of the small 20 year old television sets they currently utilize. Other than our first night when we enquired about a local place to eat, we found the staff to be quite friendly, with many staff members going out of their way to say hello to us or to ask if we needed help with anything. The various concierge staff were excellent at arranging dinner reservations and taxis for us, while the cleaning staff did an excellent job of keeping our room clean and tidy.Overall, we rate our Serrano Hotel experience as okay, but not quite what we have come to expect from Kimpton properties. If one must stay in the Union Square area, then the Sir Francis Drake, also a Kimpton property, would be a much better choice. But our favorite Kimpton San Francisco area hotel remains The Argonaut Hotel at the corner of Jefferson and Hyde on Fisherman's Wharf. For just a few dollars more, The Argonaut Hotel is in a far superior class to the Serrano Hotel, and at The Argonaut Hotel you get the bonus of staying in an area of town that is fun, safe and filled with excellent tourist and eating options.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>