<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="2f4f29936cf4752881643b2688310a39" url=""><![CDATA[Enjoyable stay at the Colon Hotel The hotel was very clean, but could use some updating (worn carpets, paint chipping). Our room faced the interior courtyard, so there was no view, but it was very quiet. The cathedral was under construction while we were there, so paying more for a room with a view would not have been worth it in my opinion. The location was fantastic. The staff was very friendly and helpful. We were surprised by the 2 twin beds, but we made the best of it. The internet service was very expensive. Much cheaper to go to an internet cafe, but not as convenient. Mini-bar prices were reasonable. Overall, a great time in Barcelona!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1471c3201e4074571b2fe30ff7f58cfb" url=""><![CDATA[Home away from home We travel often and have never encounted the level of hospitality that we found at the Hotel Europa. Miriam helped us with museum reservations and recommended a tour company for a day trip through the Chianti region (the highlight of our trip) before we even arrived in Florence. Her father Gassim greeted us with an ice cold bottle of water when we arrived at the hotel and gave us a great recommendation for dinner (Zsa Zsa's), which we loved so much, we ate there twice during our 4 night stay. Our room had a nice view of the Duomo, it was very clean, and there was plenty of space for the 2 of us. The bathroom, on the other hand, was very small (even by European standards), and the shower left much to be desired, especially for my husband, who pointed out that you could go to the bathroom, brush your teeth, and take a shower all at the same time. There was a shower head sticking out of the wall and a curtain in the corner of the room, but nothing to keep the water from soaking the entire floor while showering. Breakfast was included, but just ok. The location was great, right near the Duomo, and easy to get to all other major sights in Florence. Overall, a good value for the money and we would definitely recommend this hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="63db291ff90a571974f03a0ca52b4300" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful hotel, great location I stayed at the Campton Place Hotel for 2 nights on business earlier this month. The hotel was very nice, the rooms were large and comfortable, the staff was very friendly and accommodating and the location is fantastic (right in Union Square). I would highly recommend this hotel for business or pleasure!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="61482534d59d64bb5971dc18bc31cf62" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel, great location We stayed here for 4 nights at the end of August/beginning of September. The hotel was beautiful, very clean and modern, and the location was fantastic. The beds and pillows were the most comfortable we have ever encountered while travelling! There were also numerous TV channels in English...not that we went to Madrid to watch TV, but it was nice to be able to watch the news in English and my husband enjoyed being able to watch movies in English while he was waiting for me to get ready to go our for the night. The front desk staff was very friendly and helfpul for the most part, but we did have a leak under the sink in our bathroom and the shower wasn't draining properly. We notified the front desk, but these problems were not resolved during our stay. The breakfast buffet selection was very good, especially by European standards. The views from the rooftop bar were amazing, although part of the bar was closed for a private party the night we went up there. We ordered room service for dinner one night and it was surprisingly good, although a little on the expensive side. We found a discount rate through Travelzoo (145 euros/night) that included breakfast. At this price, the hotel was a great find, but I'm not sure it would have been worth paying their normal rates.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>