<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="1fac6bbcd0cca6dc0df3cf2b444fd597" url=""><![CDATA[I would never go back! I was there from July 12-July 19.First, the hotel and beach are beautiful. However, the hotel front desk managers are incompetent and have no idea of the meaning of good customer service. I had booked the 1 bedroom Majestic Colonial suite and they did not have it when I arrived. I was given a room that was 2 categories lower. Additionally, they never apologized for not having my room available when I arrived. They acted like they were doing me a favor by helping me at all.Also, we were not taken to our room. We were given verbal directions to the room and we were lost as the place is so big. Victor, the general manager would not come out of his office to talk with me. On 3 separate occasions he sent different managers to talk with me. I asked the mangers to tell Victor to come out and talk with me but he never did. They tried to compensate us with a massage for my girlfriend and myself but as we have back issues we told them that we needed a different form of compensation. It took two days before they agreed to give us a romantic dinner on the beach. When I asked them what the room difference was between the room I paid for and the room I was given, they would not tell me. I asked them how I could determine if I was being fairly compensated if I did not know how much the lower cost room was.After further questioning they told me the price was $30 for the two of us. However, the price of the room on their own web-site showed over a $150 differenceAs for the dinner, I do not eat Seaford so I was supposed to get a non-seafood substitute dinner. When dinner arrived I was given a Cesar salad with lobster, this had to be taken back and my girlfriend had to eat alone as the waiter on the beach had to return to the restaurant to get the chicken Cesar salad. Then the appetizer arrived, a fish dish. Again, I told them I eat it and I was not given a substitute dish. Then for the which was surf and turf, they just gave me of the the steak.One day we went back to the room and the card key did not work. We had to wait a while for them to bring us a key. When we asked them what happened to the lock they kind of blamed us and said you store your key near a camera or cell phone. I told them that I did not have a camera or cell phone anywhere within 10 feet of my key and yet they never gave me an apology for the inconvenience.Mike - Astoria NY
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>