<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="d512f4cd149699d6a1fa892653014eaf" url=""><![CDATA[Nice clean hotel, GREAT service We stayed at the France Albion recently (June 2007) for 4 nights in a Superior Double Room and we loved it. The hotel and the room were very clean and the service was remarkable. We were veryimpressed with this nice 2-star, which is definitely a very superior 2-star. This hotel is not luxurious and the rooms are small like they would be in most European hotels, but they are not tiny. In any case, we were not looking for luxury. When we first walked into the room (Room 10), we thought about how small it was, but we got over that pretty quick. The room was clean and tidy. The room has a small tv and a safe (great plus!). Our room had one window overlooking what they call I wish taken a picture so you could see, but the which much, is what I was told that makes this a Superior room. I guess it makes for a quieter room, but in any case, Notre Dame de Lorette seemed like very quiet street. If I stay there again, I think I would try out the regular room. The bathroom had the usual basic amenities (bathrobes were a nice touch), a window which makes it nice and bright, and a shower/tub. Even in 4-star hotels you may find a dirty or slightly moldy shower curtain, but I don't think you ever will in this hotel. There was hot water all the time and good water pressure. I know in France probably want to try a lot of different places to eat, but the American-style buffet was really nice. I would definitely recommend trying it (scrambled eggs, bacon, potatoes, delicious cheese, ham, yogurt, cereal). Once you sit down, they will bring you great coffee and wonderful bread and croissants.Now, our favorite part about this hotel was Kelly! Kelly works at the front-desk and was extremely nice and helpful. She made recommendations, gave us directions, marked our maps, and even made us reservations for a dinner cruise and a cabaret-show. She is definitely one of the reasons we liked this hotel so much and why recommend it so highly.Two more things...Use the metro... there is a couple of stations a block from the hotel and incredibly easy to get around (Once you can explain to the metro person the kind of tickets you want in English and a bitof sign language... Of course if you speak French you will do much much better than us, but we had Kelly write it down for us on the second day, because the first day we had no luck with a kinda-rude metro lady) All the stations have easy-to-understand maps and signs.Also, the cabs always take longer than they say they will when you call them and extremely hard to stop one on the street, so take that into account. It is a shame I remember the name, but there was a wonderful restaurant, about two blocks from the hotel with incredible food and great service. We had lunch there on our last day. As soon as I find the business card, I will edit this posting... but I did give a card to Kelly, so if you are heading there pretty soon, ask her (it is notthe Fontaine Fiacre, she recommended it but we never tried it). Have fun in Paris!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>