<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="c3cfeb02ccaf7fdb1ccb87cb5152af11" url=""><![CDATA[Whoa Nelly My first visit to a Day's Inn in 25 years. I got this one onHotwire, and was upset based on TA's reports. This is not a bad property for a two * hotel.My room was 216. It was clean, everything worked,the bathroom was painted, the floor was new, and theshower had plenty of hot water. The front desk clerk/manager Angel was friendly and efficient.She rebooted the wireless router for me, and I had greatInternet access for free. The breakfast had a waffle maker, cereal, juice, coffee, yogurt,and mini bagels. There were two kind of muffins. I used the airport shuttle, and it took 19 minutes for a pickup.Drivers were friendly. The exercise area has one non working bike, but the othertwo machines performed well. In review. Motel was clean, everything worked, it was as sound proof as any airport property. I suggest a lower floor, if you are a light sleeper. I was set for the 4th floor, but they changed me to the second. Friendly employees. This is a solid choice, contrary to other reviews.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="680e56a983f7c1d0282571a474e30337" url=""><![CDATA[A Waikiki bonus bargain I've been traveling to Oahu since 1966. For the past ten years I stayed at either the Hyatt Regency, or The Hilton Hawaiian Village. I was always a Diamond with both of those hotel chains,so I received upgrades to suites. I used points for my stays. Since I've retired, I needed to find rooms in Waikiki that wereclean, with extras like free Internet, and breakfast, located close to my favorite restaurants. Trip Adviser had the Aqua Palms ratedpretty high, so I made a reservation for two separate stays inAugust. My room rate was about one third of the two previous hotels,it was less than $100 per night. My check in was great, both the male and female clerks werefriendly, even the Bell man was great. The room is small, buteverything was nice and neat. Everything worked. On my second stay , I wanted a different room. I was contacted by a nice young woman who was Guest Service manager. She really wanted to help, and she did. Breakfast was a simple muffin, coffee, banana, and yogurt. If you are really starved, there's a dynamite Coffee House a few doors Mauka. The location rocks, it's directly across the street from thegigantic Hilton. You're on Ala Moana, which is the main drag to shopping, the airport etc.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>