<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="dc9cf327f85aa2b0cbd425e97bdb8a92" url=""><![CDATA[Agree, much improved. We returned to the MO NY this past weekend for a last minute getaway and were quite impressed. We were there soon after opening and agree with prior reviews about the dismal state of the service then. This seems to be mostly taken care of, with a few notable exceptions. The service is still not on par with some similar hotels. For instance, at the Four Seasons SF they always know our names by the time we get to the reception desk and everyone miraculously calls us by name throughout the stay. When my partner returns from runs at the FS SF or Ritz Phili, the doorman will have water and a towel waiting. Service is simply less personal than I would like at the MO. That being said, everyone was very warm and friendly. We booked our room through Platinum Travel (though not the FHR rate) and were upgraded to a Premier Central Park View room. It was at the end of the hall and shared a vestibule with only one other room (a Premier CP View Suite). As a result, it was very quiet and we did not hear all the door noise other people have complained of. What can be said except that the view of the entire length of Central Park and Mid-town is spectacular. It is unfortunate that even on the highest floor the Trump building partially obscures things, but the view is still quite amazing. Sunrise was great and the reflection of the sunset off the surrounding buildings was also very nice. We have stayed at many of the top hotels in New York and there are few that can provide quality views from the majority of rooms. I also like the aesthetic of the MO more than most top NY hotels, which tend to be too traditional and fussy for me. I found the bed extremely comfortable and the shower was wonderful. The bath products are also very nice, much nicer than at other MO properties. There has been a lot of criticism of the technology in the rooms and complaints that they are too complex. Perhaps it is my younger age and residue of growing up with computers, but it seemd pretty intuitive. The HD LCD TV was great, as was the speaker system. The phone took a few minutes to master, but then it was easy. I also liked that the LCD TV in the bathroom was adjustable. It was odd though that it didn't have all the channels of the larger TV and that the networks were on different channels. On the negative side, the restaurant remains a problem. Though our food was consistent, if not overpriced ($90 for breakfast daily), the service was irregular. They never quite got everything right. We were not served bread the first day, but it came the second day. We were given a small amuse one day, but not the next. I had to ask for butter for my toast. No huge faux-pas, but annoying. Finally, one of the thing I like to do if I like a hotel and think I may come back is to ask for a tour of other room types I might book. They did not seem to know what to do with this request. First I was told no problem. Then the second person to get on the phone told me that it was not possible because not only did nobody have time (!!!!!), but I would need to make an appointment with the front office. What did she think I was, a reporter wanting to do a story? I was a guest, and they should have been happy to show me other rooms. At this time it was 1:30 in the afternoon and she finally said that the only person on staff who could show me around was not going to be back until this afternoon and could I stay in my room until she came back. When I informed her that it was already this afternoon and asked what she meant she said 2 p.m. Seeing as it was was 30 minutes and I had no plans I said fine. When nobody called me by 2:30 I left for the afternoon. Over the course of 2 days they were never able to fulfill my quite simple request. We left without seeing other rooms, something that might have enticed me to spend money for a better room or suite next time. Their loss. It won't stop us from returning, but was an annoying way to end our stay.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>