<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="a22240e5e96cf7ee5598a698fcf55527" url=""><![CDATA[Jen Hotel, Western side of HK Island We stayed at the Jen hotel from 04/03/2008 -14/03/2008. Our room was situated on the 21st floor and had a wonderful view across the harbour,we lay in bed watching the passing ferries and turbojets heading to Macau. The hotel was formerly the Novotel Century Harborview, it has undergone a major face lift and is very modern and clean. The hotel is located on the Western part of Hong Kong island, which is the old Chinese area, it is also home to the University and many HK citizens. The people who live nearby and work in the shops are very friendly.There is a Bank of China about four doors away. A great every day restaurant Tai-Saku about 10 doors down towards the water, which was frequented by locals, we had somewhat of a celebrity status after our 4th visit...great food for very little money.The housekeeper and the bellboy did a great job with our room and luggage. There is a shuttle bus which drops you off to the Macau ferry, Star Ferry, the bus/train station in Central and then on to Admiralty. We took two trips into China and did not worry about the extra time to get to the KCR In TST East, just enjoyed the Star ferry trip.There are still good bargains to be had at the lovely Stanley Market and the Lanes in Central.Victoria Peak is a must see as is Cafe Deco at the Peak and Simpatico, two good eateries. The taxis pull up at the front of the hotel and we used them many times, very cheap and convenient.I have recommened this hotel to my sister and her family who will be visiting Hk in Jan 2009. I would have no hesitation in returning to the Jen Hotel, it is a great value for money .
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="388e56786e05b90f78f64e975e6759e1" url=""><![CDATA[11 days in HK We stayed at the South Pacific Hotel from 07/03/2006-16/03/2006 and found our stay to be most enjoyable. The hotel is quite basic,with a bar fridge and kettle,very clean and well located in Wanchai,with shops (two good bakeries nearby) and Times Square an easy walk, transport is very close. The concierge, the doorman and the cleaning staff were very friendly and attentive.The twin bed room was more spacious than the double room, the beds are easy enough to push together.We would have no hesitation in returning to this budget hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>