<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="7f197de9e4f95bfdd3ee5ba777b029b1" url=""><![CDATA[Great starting point to a beautiful city I booked this hotel through Trailfinders and after researching it on tripadvisor.com . Excellent location-just off Union Square-close to not only cable car stop but also Alamo car rental a 5 minute walk away. Chinatown in close proximity too.Small lobby but well staffed efficient reception and very informative trip service desk with adjoining small shopping kiosk.Rooms were fine-don't be put off by the fact there is no air-conditioning-the ceiling fans were fine.Also we expected it to be quite noisy at night-not at all-no problems. No coffee/tea makers in the rooms but in the lobby coffee and teas available around the clock-just help yourself and no charge. Also mouth watering cookies and muffins as well ! A jar of sweets-replenished daily-was also in our room. I musn't forget there is even a pillow menu-you can try different pillows to aid your sleep !Close by were excellent shopping and dining facilities. We had breakfast twice in the hotel-daily specials-all around $9. I've had better but it was very convenient.Staff throughout the hotel were very helpful without being in your face.I would thoroughly recommend this as an excellent base to explore this beautiful city and surrounding area-about 35 minute walk to Fisherman's Wharf so take a cab.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="708c4eebe240b23dff7b7adb87a1e34f" url=""><![CDATA[A bargain I booked a room in one of their periodic sales. I didn't get a confirmation as indicated online and only found out that they had taken my booking when I noticed it on my credit card statement. I then had to call the hotel to check what date I had booked.They admitted they had had problems with their booking system but as I on;y paid for a twin room who's complaining ? The hotel was great; lovely room with fridge and cold drinks as well as milk for teas and coffee and breakfast in a bag was a nice touch. We did eat in the restaurant too on a special 2for 1 deal but it was only ok. The Hoxguide in the room recommends some really nice places and Spitalfiels market is well worth a visit. The area is so so -we got a taxi back in the evening rather than using the tube but there again I'm a middle aged old f**t so not a risk taker. But I would certainly stay at the Hoxton again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>