<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="9cdf42a45609ed713cb0e7dc853ec2f1" url=""><![CDATA[Good Business Hotel This is a mega-convention type business hotel connected to a shopping mall and Hynes convention center. Rooms are pretty good, standard Sheraton. Nice furnishings, TV, bedding linens. They need to do some work on the bathrooms. Most fixtures and tile are dated, though they have the newer Speakman shower heads. Pretty good views at this tower hotel, too.They have a decent indoor pool with an outdoor deck chair area. The gym may be a bit small for the size of the property - it may be tough to get a treadmill during peak a.m. hours.One big plus, this hotel is a short walk to Newbury Street area with many unique dining and shopping options. Of course you can also hit the mall for your standard chain stores if that suits.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1aeaf4cf443193ca0c6638bc36e737e1" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel on Bourbon Street Stayed here for two nights in conjunction with a conference. Had a King room w/ a sidestreet (i.e. not Bourbon Street) view. The room was a bit small but perfectly fine. Pretty nice bedding and furnishings in good shape, new flat TV. Bath was pretty average, not too impressed w/ the shower, towels were fine.Gym was OK, not very big. Two decent treadmills, ellipticals, bikes. Some weight equipment. A little stuffy. Did not use the outdoor pool, but it's in a beautiful courtyard and looks quite nice w/ lots of deck/chair space.Service at the hotel was great. Desk staff, concierge, bell, door. All superb. That is really the reason I'd return - along w/ the charm of this classic property. Good on site dining, bar, etc., too.Some final points you may find useful:* If you don't have an interior view, you're going to hear some street noise at all hours. * If you're a business traveller, you may be disappointed there is no desk in the room. There was a sidetable w/ the Internet port, but there wasn't a power strip or similar to charge all your fun devices.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="62c568bdbd403eb80523cb9b6dbaecc8" url=""><![CDATA[Solid Choice Stayed 3 nights in March. All amenities associated with a good business hotel at an above average level. Excellent fitness room, though I did not use the spa/pool.Great location, a short walk to shopping many popular points of interest (e.g. Brandenburg Gate, Reichstag, museums, checkpoint charlie). U-bahn station directly in front of hotel for easy transport to attractions farther west.Note breakfast and 24-hours of Internet use were an extra 22 euro each.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>