<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="5d405f5d1915fd6c3a1ee2fdb957d546" url=""><![CDATA[Great for Business, not so much as a tourist even though location is great I've stayed in this hotel numerous times over the years for business and find that it's wonderfully accomodating for the business person. The conference facilities are great for the 50 or so folks I've had the pleasure of working with during our stay here. It's always felt a bit strange to have to walk under the street to get to the conference facilities, but that's probably just me.Internet access and a high degree of cleanliness and helpful staff for all sorts of one-off requests during our business meetings always makes me feel comfortable during my stays here. For business in Amsterdam, centrally located and close to anything else one might be interested in doing to augment their stay in Amsterdam, this hotel is highly recommended.One odd comment overheard on a recent trip was How can this be a 5 star hotel if the bar doesn't open until 1700?. I don't know the answer, but that is a very strange aspect of the place. The bar is, however, wonderful when opened (if a bit expensive).Otherwise, another great stay! The management of this hotel are doing a great job.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="60982059ae4b9f4376747b4fcdef0665" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent location and wonderful bed Definitely in the leading hotels of the world category. Didn't get to partake of all on offer, but was pleased to be close to the Arche De Triomphe and Champs Ellysees. Wish I had more time for the breakfast (looked good), but the wonderful bed sucked me under and I had a good nights sleep. Perfect location for a business trip and different than my experiences out in the no mans land of La Defence.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="78ea5355823f59d0268314ffa6e22113" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect for a Convention, not for casual travellers I've stayed here once a year for the past 5 years. It's a great location for the conference centre next door and it has lovely rooms and a decent bar. However, there are little odd things I've never sorted out: where breakfast? when do the little shops open (if ever)?It's a beautiful hotel, but a bit far from the hustle and bustle of Barcelona. You can get places quickly from here, but tourists shouldn't think of this as a well-located hotel for nightlife and ambience of the rest of Barcelona.All in all, an excellent hotel for business and very comfortable. The staff are accomodating and it's well situated for the conference facilities (including their own).
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>