<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="23c2bb45ca53ca972c93ef4f1cbb9111" url=""><![CDATA[Average hotel at a great price My husband and I styed at the Intercontinental on what may have been the hottest Friday of the season for San Francisco (6/20). The hotel staff is friendly, but no more so than any other upscale hotel in the city. The hotel is located across the street from the Museum of Modern Art, yet no mention was made of the Frida Kahlo show going on there. It wasn't until we were leaving the city that I realized the show was even there. I would expect more from a hotel that (normally) charges so much and is RIGHT ACROSS from the museum. I got a screamin' deal from Hotwire though, and would stay there again if I were able to get another such deal ($129/night).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dcb99410430599aea86dde945cf2a4a1" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect location With great reviews and a fabulous deal thru hotels.com, my husband and I opted to stay at the Affinia Dumont during our vacation to New York. I must admit, I expected a bit more. Check-in was a breeze, and all staff was very friendly, but I expected a little above and beyond after reading all the reviews.On the positive: great room size and loved the full-sized frig in the kitchen. Perfect location: a block away from a subway, half-way point between Wall Street and the museums, and close the the UN.Did I mention the super-friendly staff?Bummers: awful in-room coffee (as in any hotel) - with the horribly wasteful one-cup coffee maker, thereby impeding my ability to buy coffee grounds locally and brew my own. Lobby coffee was not available early (0630), either. We resorted to buying coffee from Guy Galland every morning (so much better than Starbucks). Our neighbors opted for coffee from room service.Another miss: I was hoping for some sort of summary of what was going on in New York that week. I've gotten something like this while in Toronto and Washington DC, and sort of expected it in New York. We did get a magazine telling us what was going on in the Fall, but I think a 1-page summary would have been a nice touch (and a way to generate revenue for the front desk for tickets to shows, etc).We'd stay here again, but not if we had to pay full-price. With some changes, though, they could move from Above Average to Excellent.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>