<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="2008dd1654273338dc576aad4290a637" url=""><![CDATA[Not bad for the $$$..... Just got back from New Orleans yesterday and stayed 5 nights at this hotel. Purchased on Hotwire for about $60/night, which was about what it was worth. When we first arrived we couldn't decide if it was charming or a dump. Yes, there was peeling wallpaper, burn marks on the blankets in our non-smoking room and a microwave circa. 1983, however it didn't smell and we finally decided that the room was decent, especially for the price. The close quarters make for a lot of outdoor noise with people coming and going all-hours of the night. Here are some tips/recommendations to make sure you have a plesant stay:1. Call ahead (like 2-3 weeks) to request a particular room. I called 2+ weeks in advance to reserve a room with two double beds. We did end up with a loft-style room, which worked out well. I was given a confirmation number when I called to request, so make sure to ask for one!2. Request a quiet room AWAY from the ice machine and the area where they set up for their breakfast. It was VERY noisy around 7:15am when they were gettting ice and putting up tables for the breakfast crowd. I would suggest something toward the backside of the building. (and bring earplugs, just in case.....especially if you're a light sleeper!)3. Don't plan on eating anything worthwhile at the continental breakfast. It's pretty worthless. However there are a few places 1-2 blocks away that serve breakfast (Le Madeline, Wendy's, Dunkin Donuts, etc.)4. We did NOT have to pay for parking in their lot! There is quite a bit of on-street parking anyway....not a big deal.5. The location was great! It is NOT a bad neighborhood at all! It is 1/2 a block from St. Charles and 1 block from the streetcar stop. Emril's Delmonico restaurant is 2 blocks away....and there are several other restaurants nearby as well. There is also a Walgreen's 2 blocks away.6. The staff preformed their duties. They definitely didn't bend over backwards for us, but were plesant in the few time we dealt with them.Go with few expectations and you will enjoy this hotel. For the price, and with what I know now, I would definitely stay here again. However, just remember....it ain't the Ritz! :-)
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>