<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="539ca55983664e962f1cde2df0746a45" url=""><![CDATA[Great Value in Waikiki We stayed 16 nights in the Diamond Tower-we booked the ocean view hotel room-the room was small and clean with an outstanding ocean view between the hotels in front of us-We have stayed here before in the Pali Tower Kitchenette Room-The Diamond Tower is less noisy and will definately stay here again-This hotel to me is such a bargain for those who want a simple room to sleep in-if you are fussy and want alot of amenities this hotel is not for you. I used to be a travel agent and after comparing many hotels at varying prices I really think the Castle Ocean Resort is a huge bargain. Our room only had a refridgerator so if you want more I would suggest staying in the Pali Tower.It is a3-5 minute walk to Waikiki Beach-on the side by the Zoo-there is an enclosed area that is great for families with children-Hope this helps-I know there are some bad reviews for this hotel but you'll get none from me-Aloha
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d1cd1d5b627da562148cf1f165f828c1" url=""><![CDATA[Rude Rude Staff!! My daughter was married in Oahu last October 30th-she had called and made reservations for the hotel explaining she was staying with her parents in another hotel and would like to check in early on her wedding day-she was reassured this would not be a problem-she called again upon arrival in Waikiki and was once again reassured it would be fine-to make a long story short this did not happen-when she called the day of her wedding the staff on the phone were rude and said the room was not ready-after many hours she and I-her Mom-went over and once again just rudeness-I went back an hour or so later-two hours before the ceremony and sat and listened to the staff laughing about this situation-they of course did not see me until I sat up and asked to speak to the manager-Low and Behold her room was ready right there and then! I have never seen such rude,unfeeling staff anywhere-The rooms are kitchy but cute-which was bittersweet the way she was treated!!! I think it would have been better if she would have been advised to have gotten the room the night before but it was the reservationist who insisted it looked like there were plenty of rooms and that it should be fine.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>