<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="bd697d97cfa4a61a42c7779fa48aae67" url=""><![CDATA[Great Value, Very Nice Hotel, Clean I stayed 4 nights recently for a business trip. The hotel is centrally located right on Ala Wai Blvd and Kaiulani Ave--it is next to some older low-rise apartments (NOT crack houses!) and only a 150 yards from Kuhio Ave which is one the main streets of Waikiki. I had room 1207 which was a standard room on the 12th floor right behind the elevator shaft. The room had a single and queen size bed, and a small desk. The bath was adequate, the carpet was excellent and the room was very clean. The linens were also more than adequate. The furnishings were in very good to excellent condition. There was a Panasonic TV and a nice size refrigerator. The rooms have a small safe with Medeco high security locks (no charge). Overall, I was very pleased with the room. The only negative for the room was that it was noisy. One reason is no fault of the hotel--Ala Wai Blvd is main street out of Waikiki and Waikiki itself is a densely packed and noisy environment. The other factor is that the elevator shaft was right behind the wall of this room and every time the elevators moved you could hear the noise elevators. The parking valets were extremely friendly and really hustled. The normal parking rate is $15/day but I got it for $7.50 by making my reservations through AAA. This is cheap parking for Waikiki. I don't drink so I can't comment on the bar. I did try the fish and chips from the menu, though. It was $8.95 and was excellent. The food prices were very reasonable for Waikiki--I don't know who thought the prices were expensive. The hotel had a lot of Japanese tourists and caters to this clientele. There is a food service in the lobby that makes bento boxes for the Japanese crowd--I didn't try them but given that the proprietors were from Japan, the bento lunches looked very appetizing and authentic. The Hospitality room had 6 computers and I used them to check my email and surf the web. The pool was large and very nice but I did not use it. The continental breakfast was served at poolside from 6:30-9am. This was very basic with coffee, cereal, toast, bagels and donuts and some kind of juice. (There might have been a few other items as well). This was the only disappointing aspect of the hotel. Overall, the public areas of the hotel were very clean and well maintained and the staff were all very friendly and helpful. Since the hotel breakfast wasn't appealing, you can walk to several restaurants within 2-5 minutes. There is a great restaurant 150 yards away in the Ohana West Hotel which offers fast and reasonable meals. Just a half a block away is an ABC Stores--it's like an upscale 7-Eleven and they are everywhere on the islands. The hotel is centrally located and close to the beach or if you are driving, as you exit the hotel you're right on Ala Wai Blvd with takes you out of Waikiki. Best of all the average cost per night for my 4 nights (one weekend night) including tax was only $97! This hotel wasn't luxurious but it was clean and comfortable, the staff was friendly and the price was more than reasonable. I will definitely stay there again when visiting Honolulu.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>