<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="642ac29f5613b9cc6c1a49488fd542dc" url=""><![CDATA[Amazing Honeymoon We stayed for 5 nights at Secrets Excellence. Let me start by saying I'm sorry the review is coming so late. Before booking our honeymoon I read several reviews, and this resort was reviewed well. Right after booking our honeymoon the resort began to receive bad reviews; you can imagine my fiance and I were a little nervous. We had nothing to be nervious about. We got off the plane at the grass hut style airport. It was so cool we were greeted by singers and dancers. They even take a picture with some local ladies and try to sell it to you later. The ride to our hotel was a little long and bumpy but nothing you can't manage. Its worth the ride to get to the resort. Just try to enjoy the scenery and do not pay attention to the driving. When we arrived at the resort they took our luggage from taxi and we didn't touch it again until we unpacked it in our room. We paid the extra money for the Excellence Club. We enjoyed it and it was a great added bonus since we were on our honeymoon. If we go back we probably wouldn't pay the extra again; but I don't regret doing it once. We stayed in an ocean view suite. The rooms are very nice. Everything is marble. Don't pay the money for a swimout suite. You really aren't that close to the pool. We were so glad we didn't after we saw how far the door was from the pool. Also if you book an ocean view room make sure you request 2nd or 3rd floor. If you are on the 1st floor you can't see the ocean well because of all of the landscape. The food was great. We tried all the restaurants excecpt the asian food. Our favorite was probably the steak house. The seafood was good also. Bourdeaux was nice but not our favorite. You have to keep an open mind though. Things are seasoned differently there--be bold, branch out, and try something new. We stayed on the beach a lot and didn't do a lot of the organized activities. Lunch on the beach is great, don't miss it. We were there to relax so we didn't really participate in the organized activies. We did take a half day snorkeling trip. We were able to swim with shark and stingray. It was unreal. I suggest you try it. We went to the shows each night. They aren't vegas but they are still fun. Like I said earlier keep and open mind and drink lots of coco-locos. Those are the best drinks ever. The drinks were great and they flowed freely. We would be lounging by the pool and people would constantly keep your drink fresh. We had an excellent stay. We want to go back for an aniversery. So when you see a bad review over look it and look forward to your trip. We used allinclusiveoutlet.com to book our trip
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>