<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="9d264e1da989610820c3d4a9d69d9475" url=""><![CDATA[excellent bargain We stayed at the Bali Mandira two weeks prior to our wedding in Bali. We payed the extra 10 dollars for the upgrade to a deluxe cottage, and it was well worth it. The cottage itself was nothing special, not a lot of natural light came in, so it was quite dark and cold a lot of the time, however the bathroom was terrific! It was half enclosed, half open air, so you could stand in a little rockwalled shower, with tropical plants surrounding you and look up at the clear blue sky! Also included with the upgrade was access to the lounge area, which provided soft drinks and cakes free all day long, with a happy hour from around 5 to 7 with free cocktails - my husband was in heaven! The location is terrific - the beach is separated from the hotel by a pathway, however the beach itself was immaculate, a big change from the last time we stayed in Legian. Although you are only a short stroll from the main shopping streets, the hotel itself is very quiet. The two pools are fantastic, particularly the one on the roof top, and at nighttime, the candles on the tables that surround the other pool from the restaurant give it a really nice ambience. We were so happy with the Mandira, we will definitely stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="81a5f6297c3f922367dc79fdbdbfa919" url=""><![CDATA[A little disappointing We stayed here in April for our honeymoon after getting married at a villa elsewhere in Bali. We chose it as our honeymoon hotel based on reviews and star ratings in brochures, and to be honest we were quite disappointed. We had stayed at the Bali Mandira and the Bali Hilton prior to the wedding, and preferred both of the those to the NDBH. The rooms are quite small, particularly compared to the Hilton, the beach wasn't that great, the pools were cold, the lobby not that spectacular. On the plus side, the buffet breakfast was terrific, but not all that different to the others. Considering that both the Hilton and the Mandira were cheaper, we felt really let down, having spent more money on what we thought would be the better hotel for our honeymoon.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3213b50b04805825671fb56173629441" url=""><![CDATA[Impressive! We stayed at the Bali Hilton prior to our wedding in April this year. We were extremely impressed from the second the taxi pulled into the driveway. It is an enormous hotel, with lavish grounds and beautifully decorated lobbies, restaurants and rooms. We had a standard room but it was huge, immaculate and cleaned spotlessly every day. The grounds are terrific, with lagoons and bridges interconnecting everything. The breakfast that was included was awesome, and the location of the hotel was particularly convenient - just a short stroll to the main street of Nusa Dua for shopping and eating. The only downside in my husbands opinion was the pool. There is just the one, and it is in full sun with no shade, so it could be quite scorching - if you're like me and love the heat, then this is no problem. In general, we were very satisfied, as it is quite a good bargain for what you get - would definitely stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>