<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="5ed474bcc6305393299bdd18ff4932da" url=""><![CDATA[Do NOT Have Your Wedding Here!! Well we found this hotel through long internet searching. We planned for a small beachside destination wedding in Puerto Rico. We both have never been to the island and not sure what to expect. We then found and spoke to the wedding and catering sales manager, Marilyn at the Water and Beach Club. There she said not to worry about a permit for they have there own platform and quoted us a price. We were happy to have found a place that seemed to good to be true, that's because it was! After receiving her rate we sent our contract back to the hotel through air mail. She said that the canopy priced increased and because she had not received anything, this was the price to set. Ok, not happy about that but will get over it. Then THREE weeks before the wedding they tell me they can not do the beach side wedding without a permit. This permit was a non refundable extra $500.00. And still this permit may not have enough time to review and if it was denied we would still lose the $500.00. THIS IS AFTER THE CONTRACT HAD BEEN SIGNED AND ACCEPTED! This is very upsetting so close to the date and the worst part was they did not seem sympathetic at all or offer any compensation. After settling for the site on their terrace I ask for some compensation. After a week of not hearing anything from them, even after multiple emails and messages. I call the GM and he does not offer anything, we had to demand a free stay at there hotel for failing to live up to their contract. This was a small feat at which should have been easy for them to arrange and still that was a struggle. The worst is yet to come. When we arrive THE DAY OF Marilyn says the seating arrangement we had would not be able to comfortable seat the people we had in its original spot. So she offers 3 other sites within the hotel. After we choose another alternative, she then says we can not have the space due to THE POSSIBILITY THAT THEY HAVE PAYING PATRONS USE THE SITE FOR MASSAGES!!! Then after expressing my distaste in this hotel she says that I may use that site for an additional 250 charge. This hotel does not care at all about the thoughts and feelings of there guests!! A wedding is a special event and should be treated as so. Yet massages for other guest were more important then my dinner reception. These people falied to first know the limitations of their beach permits then treat me like it didn't matter to them how we felt about the situation. Not even to offer something to ease the situation. Even the GM did not give any consolation. I felt as if they cared only for the money they previously received and since they knew we couldn't leave after such short notice and took full advantage of that. DO NOT use this hotel!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="89fd10df93f90de8572983ce60fcafc0" url=""><![CDATA[Would NOT recommend staying here! I had my destination wedding here and through that event had a terrible experience here at this hotel. But putting the event aside I wanted to inform readers of the actual hotel. Hotel is what people would label for male teenagers. The hotel is not what you could call comfy or classy. They had neon blue lights everywhere. Reminds me of a sleazy adult video set. The hotel has nice potential but needs remodeling and some definite cleaning! The conceierge and the front desk were nice but the upper managment carries the immpression that they do not really care to help you out in a situation with the hotel. The only thing this hotel has got going for them is the fantastic view of the ocean and being only steps away from the beach. I would not recommend this to families but is suitable for partying people only staying for a night or two. But the bar is so loud during the weekend and you can hear it all from your room. The regular rooms are small with hardly any closet space. But the suites are much roomier but not a good value for the price of the hotel. This is not a good place to stay for longer then a couple of days.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d3213d52d5ae53c8aa005f098bc7c127" url=""><![CDATA[Great 3 star hotel could pass as a 5 star hotel! We honeymooned for a couple of days at this resort and could not have asked for a more relaxing time here. This resort was huge with a great golf course and spacious rooms. We did not use the royal sevices but still felt the service was excellent. One problem that we did have was the check in and check out times were considerably longer then we expected. They seemed to be short staffed and created a long wait for rooms and then again at check out. But after that the conceirge was excellent and proficient in making sure that we were comfortable. The rooms were large as well as the bathtub and all were immaculantly clean. And our beach view was excellent.The pool is luxiurious with a swim up bar and lots of room to be comfortable. The beach however is not so hot. This is not one that one would like to swim in. The sand is rocky and unpleasant without shoes and the man made beach was not something I would recommend to swim in. The lobby, and other common areas of the hotel were lavish and beautiful! Had an exotic feel in the evening with candles lit everywhere. The restaurant was beautiful but lacked the service at the outside terreace seating and the food at Tempo the italian rest was mediocre at best. But overall the experience here was wonderful and would def come back again!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>