<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="8d200a1cd124c61e6feb6fc4cf5fda70" url=""><![CDATA[fantastic location! I stayed for 4 nights at this hotel, The whole hotel was immaculate and the staff courteous and professional. The room was well equipped (very grateful for the air conditioning) and everything in the room worked.The bathroom was very small (shower only) but was well decorated and everything was in full working order.The location could not have been better, about 3 mins walk from centraal station and practically on the Dam.I did not eat in the restaurant, but please do not take this as a criticism, I just didn't get round to it. Every time I walked past the restaurant, at any time of day, it was either full or very nearly full which as a hotel manager in the UK, I know is the sign of a very, very good restaurant!In summary, a very well run hotel, clean, well presented, with a good restaurant (going on number of diners). My only criticism (and it is very minor indeed) is that the welcome from some of the staff was very polite and courteous but felt a little 'mechanical' and not too genuine. However, do not let this put you off! The Roode Leeuw is very, very good!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="99240500d81ee9bd25519f4f024fa850" url=""><![CDATA[just the job! I stayed at the Rembrandt Centrum for 4 nights and it suited my needs perfectly. The room was absolutely spotless and everything was in working order. The staff were very efficient, helpful and polite. The hotel is in the perfect location for sightseeing (about 3 mins walk from Dam square) and over looks the Herengracht (when you open the curtains in the morning it is a most beautiful sight!)If you want 5* luxury then this hotel is not for you (but then you wouldn't be looking at this review would you?) if what you want is a well-run good, clean, honest hotel in stunning surroundings then press the book now button, trust me you'll not do better than this!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>