<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="615bd232ea30e2afff8271bbdd316af4" url=""><![CDATA[Great Service and Property We arrive late and unfortunately the hotel did not have our requested two bedded room available but the desk clerk volunteered to get the front desk manager who appologized, compensated us with a free dinner in the hotel restaurant and by the time we were through eating our request room was ready.The room was very large with two queen beds and plenty of room to move around plus large desk space, large closet, large bathroom with tub shower.The place was immaculately maintained and service always very professional and friendly...the even loaned me an umbrella one day and went out of their way with typical tourist questions.An excellent location just a block from Times Square, buses, subway, tour buses and all the conveniences and trappings of this great big beautiful ciy.Definately recommend.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="34353f01e4437279c4a099446132739d" url=""><![CDATA[Generic Motor Hotel Two Holiday Inn's, back-to-back: This one and the H.I. Express Seattle. Very close to the space needle and a couple of blocks to the free bus zone going downtown. Generic rooms with microwave and mini-fridge. Newer properties, very clean and well equipted. Parking was $4.50 a day. This place is clean and well located to Seattle Center and within decent proximity to downtown.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dc2b1d7462c2955da4c577241d7d8879" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent choice Supurb location directly across the street from a fantastic beach that is like a private lagoon which is protected by a breakwater wall allowing for calm waters to about six feet deep. The hotel is very nice, well maintained with a lovely lobby and fine rooms.This hotel is in a perfect location, all Waikiki activity within easy walking distance yet gorgeous room views and stunning giant aquarium restaurant.Highly recommended and would most definately stay again. The price / quality ratio is outstanding.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>