<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="e30592540cdac1ed76603325c141c3fb" url=""><![CDATA[Stay somewhere else! This was the final night of a 28 day trip around Australia and New Zealand and I booked this place to break up the long trip from New Zealand back to the UK.The Good:- Location is good right on the waterfront and if you have a view of the harbour I expect it would be pretty nice (although not as good as one of the circular quay hotels such as Four Seasons or the Marriott)- Decor is nice and modern with nice colours in the room and a big (I'd guess 32) TVThe Bad:- Check-in was only manned by one person who was clearly very busy. I checked in and was told to go to my room and given a key. Imagine my surprise when I walked into the room to find two other guests already in there. They were extremely surprised to see me as I was to see them. If I had been them I would have been very angry with someone walking in unannounced - I felt very bad about this.I understand mistakes do happen but I feel this could so easily have been avoided and put a downer on the whole stay at the hotel. The desk clerk was verbally apologetic and I asked him to call the occupants of the first room to apologize.The second room I was given was by far the smallest of all the hotels I stayed at during the trip and was the furthest from reception there was on the 3rd floor. It had a small window which was high up and did not open. This faced the street and had a view of a tiny bit of the road leading to the harbour bridge. The notepad in the room still had the previous guest's notes on it.No mention or further apology for the room incident was given at check-out or at any other time during my stay.- I was not met by a porter at the arrival door and had to drag my heavy bags up some stairs to reception and to my room(s)- Left luggage is kept behind a roped area right next to the door rather than in a separate secured room as in other hotels. I suppose this is secure if there is a porter watching it permanently but I was still anxious leaving my belongings there.- The other person in my party in another room found a cockroach in their room as they were departing.I would definitely not stay at this hotel again. Earlier on in the trip I stayed at the Marriott Sydney Harbour for a week and this is a fantastic hotel. It is preferable in every respect with far better service, an excellent exec lounge, excellent views, and better service, location and rooms.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a49a41ffd96fa84faf488142633399a3" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic hotel in a great location View from room at night
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>