<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="93ed823a61034e63fb653f9d8285fd94" url=""><![CDATA[All we expected from the TripAdvisor reviews! We chose Amsterdam for a short post Christmas break and selected this hotel based upon the Tripadvisor reviews. Excellent hosts, with obvious pride in ownership, very helpful and friendly. Well furnished, clean, small rooms with little cupboard or draw space, but certainly warm enough during a cold spell in January.. Good quality breakfast (included in our rate). Location is ideal for the concert hall and other Museum area attractions although a little far from the centre of town unless you use public transport ( which is close by).We enjoyed our stay here and I would think this hotel excellent for a short break where you don't expect to spend much time in your room.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1665b614ce04b4081ad6da155a69c34f" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Location For a long weekend and first visit to Madrid this was an ideal location. In the pedestrianised area, close to two Metro stations (Calao and Sol)giving good access to all the major sights/sites either by (cheap, efficient) Public Transport or on foot. Using the Metro we were in our room in about 70 minutes of touching down! The trip involves two line changes which involve some walking and stairs so you might not enjoy it if you have heavy luggage. We chose to use a shuttle bus service the hotel arranged for our departure (8 euros each), very efficient and easily organised. We had the buffet breakfast and found it good quality and reasonable value. With better weather we would have looked for more interesting alternatives after our first morning.The room we had, at the back, was quiet, clean and well maintained. We thought the bathroom was better than 3 star standardThe staff were all cheerful, friendly, helpful and with varying levels of good English.Overall the hotel contributed to an enjoyable break.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ec9acb5dcf1cd9a394424e96994d481e" url=""><![CDATA[Location OK IF you use the Metro! We stayed 3 days(2 nights) over a weekend at the end of October. The hotel room was good. clean, modern and quiet (we faced a blank wall at the back). The staff were efficient and fluent in English. We did not try the breakfast buffet preferring a cheap light meal in a cake shop (coffee/croissants/bread for less than 5 euros each.) My only doubt about returning would be location. We walked from Sants station when we arrived and this took at least 30 mins. It takes 15 mins to walk to La Rambla and whilst this does not sound much it is a pain at the beginning and end of every excursion! We walked 16 miles on Day1 and then tried the Metro. (nearest station 5 minutes) This was very easy efficient cheap and safe. I would recommend it to everyone.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>