<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="564e4a69cd32e3e37a395726262ea6f9" url=""><![CDATA[We had a very nice experience at the Inn at the Market! We stayed at the Inn at the Market over a long Labor Day weekend. I've read a lot of mixed reviews on the Inn and all I can say is we had a really nice experience there.We're not big on paying a lot for a view in any hotel room because we just don't spend that much time in our room so we opted for a city view. We were in room 408 and it has a view of the courtyard that you walk through as you enter the hotel. For a view of the water, we were very satisfied with simply going up to the 5th floor deck where you had an unlimited view of Elliot Bay, Mt. Rainier, the waterfront and everything you'd see if you had a water view room. We took so many pictures from the deck and just stood there and admired the view. It was a nice place to strike up a conversation with other guests and overall, a nice place to escape the hustle of the Market area below.Our room was lovely and spacious and we saw no signs of any of the wear and tear that some reviews have mentioned. The bathroom in our room was the size of a small bedroom! And one thing I really loved about the bathroom was the shelving unit available for us to put our bathroom things on. Every hotel should offer this so that you don't have to live completely out of your suitcase or have a thousand things on the back of the toilet simply for them to be handy.The tempurpedic bed got a mixed review. I had no issues with it and found it quite comfortable. My husband...not so much. He would have liked a firmer mattress and he said he felt as if he was sleeping on his head the entire time. Overall though, it was fine.We don't normally make a lot of use of concierge services, etc. and we're not big users of room service either so I can't speak a lot about that. We did order dessert through room service one night and it was very nice. For breakfast, we went to the Market Bagel shop over on 1st Ave. (about 1/2 block south of the hotel) for a very inexpensive breakfast a couple of days. One day we walked a few blocks to a nearby coffee shop (no, not Starbucks...we avoided corporate coffee), Cafe Ladro. VERY good coffee and pastries and worth the 6 or 7 blocks to walk.Dinners were mostly eaten in and around the Market area. We can highly recommend Shiro Sushi (again, within easy walking distance) and it was highly recommended to us by one of the front desk staff. (Just a tip: Ivar's is so overrated don't waste your time. We live in the Midwest and we've had fish here that was so much better than that Long John Silver's knockoff.)The Market area itself is a zoo. If you don't like walking into people/crowds in general, you'll go nuts here after a couple of days. Granted, we were there over a holiday weekend and during the last day of Bumbershoot but even after that ended, it was still nuts. It really wasn't the crowds that got to us so much as the buskers (annoying with a capital A and basically everywhere you turn) and the seemingly endless supply of insane people. That was our biggest takeaway from Seattle: is every third person on the street insane? Not that we ever felt threatened, quite the contrary. But we had people just randomly yell at us (and everyone else around them), hiss at us like a cat, skateboard by us singing a song about Chairman Mao...it seemed to never end. I guess you can call it free street theatre.The Inn is in the midst of all this and we were definitely at the heart of all the action. The bell staff was incredibly friendly, the front-desk staff was helpful, the room was very nice, the location was tourism ground zero. Not really sure how we could have improved on the experience. (Oh and it was sunny and 68 every day we were there! So much for the Seattle drizzle experience!) Honestly if I had one complaint it would be the TV channel selection. There are about 20 channels, half of which are sports, the other half local government and news. Boring, boring, boring. But again, we don't go on vacation to watch TV. But if you're looking for something interesting to watch as you fall asleep...good luck to you my friend.If we were going back to Seattle and wanted to stay in the city itself, I wouldn't hesitate to go back to Inn at the Market.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5ea316f22c138dba377c10388af90d6a" url=""><![CDATA[Like coming home only better... We just returned from spending the past week at the Royal Palms and there simply aren't enough good things to be said about our visit.From the moment we arrived, we were greeted by an amazingly friendly, warm and caring staff who went out of their way to make us feel welcome. Our first contact was with Tony, one of the valet attendants, who opened our doors, introduced himself and thereafter, always knew us by name. (This was a trait of everyone we met on the property...it was as if we were staying with friends who always greeted us this way.) He took care of our luggage while we checked in and then gave us a tour of the property and then showed us to our room.We splurged on a deluxe casita and it was well worth it. The room was beautiful, but then again, what isn't beautiful at the Royal Palms? The only other place we have seen that was so completely visually appealing was a resort we stayed at in Tahiti. Obviously very different environments but beauty is beauty no matter where it's found. The entire property makes you feel like you are living in a lovely, watercolor painting. The colors of the buildings and flowers and artwork all make for a serene and soothing atmosphere which you find yourself melting into very quickly.The casita was beautifully decorated and very roomy. We had a private patio in the back with a view of Camelback Mountain. We had our own patio in the front as well (there are curtains you can let down to increase the feeling of privacy) where we sat and enjoyed the lovely evenings. The bathroom is a slice of heaven. The huge, walk-in shower with built-in, tiled seating is a spa treatment in itself. And the selection of soaps and lotions that are provided are wonderfully luxurious.We can't offer enough praise to everyone, and we mean literally EVERYONE, who works there. Everyone is so happy and I don't mean in a freakish Disney/Stepford way. It's as if everyone there is absolutely thrilled to be doing their jobs and in finding ways to make you feel content and welcome. We never heard a raised voice, saw a scowling face or felt as if we weren't the most important guests there.The food in the restaurants is wonderful if just a little pricey but then again, you're paying for unsurpassed quality and service. T. Cook's serves marvelous meals and the Cabana Grill has wonderfully casual lunches (and breakfast brunch on Sundays) and poolside drinks. The poolside service is unsurpassed and again, Rick and Jose (I can't say enough good things about the two of you either!!!) make you feel as if you're visiting their home. And by the joy they demonstrate when doing their jobs, it's no wonder you feel that way.We didn't use the spa but we visited the boutique area and it was beautiful as well and also well stocked with a wide assortment of spa products.On our last night there, we had the privilege of attending the General Manager's reception in the Presidential Villa (where President Bush had stayed just 2 weeks prior...regardless of your politics, it's pretty cool to know you're standing in the bedroom where a world leader has recently slept!). Our wonderful friend Jose was there and we also had the joy of meeting Greg Miller, the GM, Rick Behr, Delores (I hope I spelled your name correctly!) the Director of Experiences, and Gregory Casale, the head chef. They were all entertaining and charming and we had lovely drinks and hors d'oeuvres which made for a great send-off on our last night. We were truly sad to leave them, in fact when we left to go back to our casita, Jose made a point of stopping us and letting us know what a pleasure it had been to have us stay with them. It felt so much like saying good-bye to a friend that we hugged him before we left.My husband had seen the resort on Great Hotels on the Travel Channel but could not remember the exact name of the resort. Since we had never been to Phoenix before, that meant we had to search through every other high-end resort property before he recognized the Royal Palms from its pictures. Even after having looked at all those other properties, we just had a feeling about the Royal Palms and we couldn't have been happier to have made the choice we did. There will be no other place for us to stay on any future visits to Phoenix. Why would we? Coming back to the Royal Palms would be like coming home.And as a testament to the commitment to service and care the Royal Palms offers, look at the negative reviews of any of the other comparable resorts. Do you see any responses from those properties' management? No. And in the scant negative comments I've seen about the Royal Palms (both of which seemed to come from completely unreasonable people in my opinion), they took the time to respond and see if they could make things right. That says it all to me.This is the finest property in Phoenix, hands down. I don't need to stay anywhere else to know that. Thank you to everyone at the Royal Palms who made our stay with you an absolute joy. We will be back!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>