<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a00e0d63997bed68cac16c66c061dace" url=""><![CDATA[5 star resort with 2 star food We just retuned form Bahia Principe and had a great time. A beautiful looking resort with many things to keep you busy throughout the day and night. I have rencently turned 30 and have travelled all throught the Caribbean and have stayed at mostly 5 star resorts. This could be classified a five star resort if the food was upgraded. The rooms are nice, the grounds are beautiful, the pools are great and the staff was very helpful and nice but the food has to be changed to get an honest 5 star rating . The two words of the week were OIL and UNDERCOOKED. Everything that is served is undercooked, bacon, sausage, burgers, be careful and if it was cooked it was floating in oil. Oil in you eggs, oil in your pasta and even oil in your bacon containers. Believe it or not the bread, as it may sound funny was nice and fresh daily and a nice addition to our meals. The last thing that I want to do is scare people from this resort, I am not a picky eater but like most who travel have conserns on what I eat. As posted earlier book your specialty restaurants the first day you arrive or you will miss out. The other problem I have is a pay safe. I have stayed in a dozen all inclusive resorts and this is the first resort that I had to pay for the use of a safe, $28us a week. Most resorts charge you for a lost safe key but never for the use of their safe.The pools were great, nice and big with plenty of room to yourself to float at your own leisure. The chairs were usually no problem to get a couple as long as your not too late of a sleeper. Usually we would get up and get them around 8am and had no problems at all, by 10:00am the were getting full but there were still some to be had.The beach was nice with plenty of chairs and plenty of trees to get some nice shade and even a nice nap. The water was beautiful and the beach was nice and clean.Everyone who writes here will have a different experience even if there were there on the same week. I had a great time with just food being my only real concern from rating this resort real good. Take what we write with a grain of salt and go enjoy yourself. We all need a holiday and we make that holiday special with the people we go with and the people we meet.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>