<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="dab2324973cb63f97e133c856aa19db5" url=""><![CDATA[So lucky to find London Bridge! I chose London Bridge Hotel because of the great rates- 99 pounds a night and the great reviews on tripadvisor.com. The hotel proved to be excellent from check-in to check-out.I arrived in London on a 6am flight. I had alerted LBH that I would be arriving early and requested early check-in. Upon arrival, the hotel staff let me in and checked me in quickly. This was most appreciated since I hadn't slept on the way over.Upon entering the room I noticed that it was small, but comfortable (with plenty of space to move around). The bed was huge, covered with pillows, a nice duvet, and very cushy though it felt as though it had had some wear. The flat screen tv was nice as was the minibar. I also appreciated the in-room safe and closet space. I also had a dresser which came in handy during my stay.Another huge perk to the hotel was that it was very close to London Bridge Station. (A two minute walk). I often returned to the hotel late at night and at times got a little disoriented (using the different tube exits). Nevertheless, the area was quiet and seemed safe so no worries about wandering a few extra minutes to get my bearings. Another great thing about the area was that LBS connects very easily with other tube lines. I could always be where I needed to be in only a few stops. This hotel was extremely central though quiet- just outside of the hustle and bustle.As this was a short trip packed with London walks and visits with friends, I never seemed to make it to breakfast which was included with my rate. Still, the hotel was a welcoming place each evening. Magazines and newspapers were always handy and a staff member always on hand. I never required much help from concierge or reception, but the one time I had some questions, I was struck by the Spanish receptionist's willingness to help me, even provide me more information than expected (I never expect that level of service). In terms of any problems with my stay, I noticed that my toilet handle didn't seem to want to flush. It worked well enough so that I did not have to bother maintenance. Still, I received a letter from the hotel (today in fact) thanking me for my good feedback as well as a note that they would look into the toilet handle to make any necessary repairs. I always appreciate follow-up to concerns and compliments. Rarely do hotels make this contact, but when they do, it is forever appreciated. Just writing about the hotel makes me want to go back. I am sure I will not forget this hotel and should I have a chance to come back to London I will check LBH first.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>