<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7a7b351d72633185069f915d2722eaa8" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Holiday My wife and I just returned from the Ambar on Jan.4/09 and had a wonderful holiday. The check into the hotel went very smoothly with no problems. The room was everything that I expected and upon arrival was decorated in balloons as it was my birthday the following day. The beach area was what we felt the nicest along that stretch , as it was very deep with lots of lounge chairs available even though you had to go and put something on them early in the morning. The pool area was very large but we spent most of our time at the beach even though making numerous trips to the pool bar for refreshments. It was enjoyable being at an all Adult resort in particular that time of year when families are travelling with young children. We had no problems with reservations in any of the a la carte restaurants. I spoke to some people who had problems getting the reservations and when they showed up without were not allowed in even though the restaurant was not filled at all near capacity.I clarified this with guest services who advised me there are times when people reserve and do not show up so they have to book around the numbers showing. If everyone showed up whenever it would be disastrous and reservations would not work. I would suggest taking the shuttle around the full property on your first day as it is very large when leaving the Ambar property itself. This way you know where everything is located early on your holiday. As for the workers not speaking a lot of English they were very encouraging to try to assist us in speaking Spanish and took extra time in doing so.( we should attempt to adapt). All in all in was an excellent trip with great service. I only had one meal not satisfactory during the week and it was only because of what I ordered. I enjoyed the quietness, relaxing evenings with my wife and friends in the lobby bar. If you look on the liquor menu in the lobby it will tell you which of the drinks are on the all inclusive, that way I was able to order Bacardi Gold. Make sure you take insulated containers for drinks, they are great. I have the Bubba containers and could have set up a stand and sold them.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>