<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="bb725e4068fb980b3135097876681452" url=""><![CDATA[Value for Price I spent 5 nights at the Hotel de France for vacation in San Francisco. The location is excellent close to the cable cars and within walking distance of Union Square and Market St. There are many restaurants close by and the hotel provides a breakfast that is free with your stay. That said the breakfast is just average and there is no choice of juice, something which I found inexplicably annoying. The rooms are of average size, clean but a tad down at heels. Mine had an ugly black vinyl sofa that somewhat spoiled the effect of any attempt at decor that might have been attempted. That said the rooms are clean and the baths are more than adequate and there is a huge claw foot tub. (If someone in your party is physically challenged this may be a problem.) Public areas are quaintly charming and the elevator is amusing and works remarkably well for its age. They have an excellent dining room, however I am not sure as I would recommend the package that they offer due to the many dining choices offered in SF. Service is wildly variable and I agree with a previous reviewer that the gentleman who owns the hotel does not always seem like he wishes you were there. There also seems to be an unseemly emphasis on the bill, and while I only ate one of the two meals in the dining room, nothing was deducted from my bill. While all in all I was not dissatisfied with the stay, given the wide range of accomadations in SF I most likely would not stay there again
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dae50fe75d0bde90f98741cae289a208" url=""><![CDATA[Unique decor, nice service good location I stay at Kimpton Hotels whenever I can. First because they are pet friendly and I often bring my small dog and second you can always rely on them to be interesting, well appointed and comfortable. I found the Serrano to be no different. An older building it is attractive and has a decor that is unique. The rooms are slightly on the small side, but the beds are comfortable, there is good water pressure and they are are attractively decorated. The toiletries are nice and the rooms are always clean. The staffs are always friendly and helpful and the concierage service extraordinary. As per a previous reviewer I too have found that as Kimpton loyalty member, the Serrano does not always provide the amenities the you are supposed to get, but that said a bottle of warm water and a biscotti (that seems to be the usual for me)is really not missed. But if say you are going to provide something you should.I would definately stay at the Serrano again, in fact I am booked for this upcoming weekend. As far as the location is concerned I never felt unsafe and it is close to Union Square and Powell Street
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5462f449e64de07b078e3f8433f0a651" url=""><![CDATA[A Great Little Hotel I have been meaning to write this review for awhile and am just now getting around to it. I stayed at the Best Western Regina for two nights prior to a transatlantic cruise. It was my second choice and I have never been so pleased. The hotel sits on a street not far from Las Ramblas in an old building that has been redecorated in modern European style. My room, while not large was attractively decorated and had french doors leading to a Juliet balcony overlooking the street. As far as I was concerned this was worth the cost of admission. The bed was comfortable and in a alcove and out of the way. There were great Bath amenities and the Bathroom was good sized and well appointed. I still don't get the glass half door thing on the tub, but there you go. There is a great bar although one night it was full of unpleasant americans (and I am an American) and a decent restaurant in the sister hotel next door. I had breakfast that came with the meal and the breakfast was excellent and the room attractive The location is great near the main plaza, Las Ramblas and El Corte Angles (great department store) is nearby. There is a tourist bus stop across the way. I found it conveniant to walk to many things. A few caveats (which would not keep me from going back) Several times early in the AM someone would rattle the room door And the staff while friendly and efficient was unable to cash a travellers cheque or convert currency which I found odd. That said this hotel was a find and cost about 140Euros which I felt was a deal
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>