<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="bf4e09272e745887589388e7d3efc7fb" url=""><![CDATA[lives up to the reviews We just returned from a 4 night stay and can echo the positive reviews - the hotel is definitely a gem and lives up to the descriptions here.We paid more than the price listed on this tripadvisor page and as a result it is was the most I've paid for a hotel of this class, but considering the cost of hotels in Paris it wasn't unreasonable. As others have commented, the rooms are spotlessly clean and the staff are very nice and helpful. But the best part is the location - we were able to walk everywhere - as a result we were hardly ever in the hotel. It's incredibly easy to get to/from the airports on the RER - we came in from ORY (flew OpenSkies from NYC, a great airline!) and it took less than 30 minutes. I'll definitely call the HGH first the next time we go to Paris.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fdf5f6e045a128a86c17e1f5c14e3a32" url=""><![CDATA[Second stay, just as good Stayed at Jurys for the second time on the weekend follwing Thanksgiving. Upon arrival we were welcomed back (acknowledged for having stayed there once before) and given the same room we had during our last stay.The room is of decent size, was perfectly clean and the bed is very comfortable.Given the consistancy I've experienced and the relatively good value, considering the amenities and location, Jurys is my first choice when staying in Boston.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="da37756dd67ade1b4e639b45eb3910c7" url=""><![CDATA[Sweet and Sour My wife and I stayed here for two nights in January, each separated by a week as we traveled abroad. The first night was fantastic, among the very best of our 2 week/4 country vacation. The room was huge and beautiful - filled with delicious incense as we entered for the first time. Room service was great and, I thought, very reasonably priced. The staff was very friendly and gracious (void of the South Beach attitude). We left the next morning very much looking forward to returning for another night a week later.Unfortunately when we returned we had a completely different experience. The staff seemed completely inundated with a conference that was being held there and we were obviously not the priority - we didn't even get assistance with our luggage. Our room was right next to the elevator despite the fact that I had specifically requested one away from the elevator (and it's in my 'profile' with MO). When I asked the manager if another room was available he said he could give me a suite for a good rate!!! They tried to up-sell me after giving me exactly what I had asked not to have - I felt like I had been scammed. An experience I would never have expected to have at a service oriented 5-star hotel.That experience burned me so bad I'm not sure I'd go back, despite having had a wonderful stay on the first night. My advice - ask if there will be a conference while you're there. If so, check out the new Four Seasons.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>