<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="3f2a49251154d0e918a573170cb7f867" url=""><![CDATA[The best at Boston Logan We stayed at the Boston Logan Hilton earlier this month (June) prior to flying back to the west coast. In a nutshell, this Hilton-franchised property may be on the spendy side, but on balance it's worth the price paid.This Hilton has recently undergone a change in ownership, and as a result the hotel has undergone some cosmetic improvements including new bedding, new carpeting in the rooms and common areas, and new tile and fixtures in the bath. The result is that the hotel is in almost new shape and is exceptionally clean and well-maintained. Our room was on the 10th (highest) floor; rooms at the ends of the hallways are quite a walk from the centrally located elevators. This Hilton does have a lounge on the 10th floor. HVAC worked well, bedding was exceptionally comfortable, and linens and towels were spotlessly clean. The hotel recently equipped its rooms with large, LCD flat-panel hi-definition televisions with digital sound. The hotel has the best location at Boston Logan and two recently-opened sky bridges connect the hotel directly to the International Terminal and to Delta Airline's new terminal. We have stayed at this property a number of times over the past few years, both on business trips and vacations. When on business we actually prefer staying at this Hilton property, either using a cab or the nearby water taxi to get into the downtown core. We were pleased to find a number of bell and front desk staff still at the hotel since our last visit in October. The staff is generally very, very helpful and eager to please. As an example, my wife and I had a number of perishable items that had to be kept cooled/frozen. Aside from a mini-bar, the rooms do not have mini-fridges. to our amazement, within five minutes of calling the guest services line, a mini-fridge was delivered and set up in our room at no charge. Additional added-value touches include that the hotel's shuttle van will deliver you to or pick you up from any of the nearby car rental centers, again at no cost. This level of service is extraordinary in our view.Others have mentioned here that the hotel imposes many charges on guests. It's true that parking can run $35 per night and that internet access runs about $10 a day. Food - especially room service - is similarly very expensive. We didn't havea car to park, we used the business center internet-equipped computers that can be rented on an hourly basis, and frankly the food we ordered was delicious (especially the clam chowder!!).Our stay at the Boston Logan Hilton was great from the painless and rapid check-in to the ease of checking out and the helpfulness of the shuttle driver. We highly recommend the Hilton Boston Logan.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="88382ad37c3f879bf658d17a7eb611d2" url=""><![CDATA[For the business traveler overpriced, noisy, and crowded I am a Hilton Diamond HHonors member and recently stayed in the Ali'i Tower on a business trip to Honolulu as I have for over ten years. Sadly, I plan to not return to the Hilton Hawaiian Village, but shift to the Hilton Prince Kuhio.For the rates one is charged to stay in the Ali'i Tower - presumably the best lodging offered, one would expect a higher level of guest service and certainly a better stay experience. Unfortunately, both were lacking from the time I checked in right through my stay.Making my reservation using the Hilton Family website was effortless as is always the case.The only way I can desribe checkin is the word bedlam. The valet parking ($28 a night) personnel were overwhelmed and cars were backed up for a 20 minute wait. After leaving my car, I went directly to the Ali'i Tower, which touts its separate check in facilities. Unfortunately, the check-in counter was innundated with groups of guests. Checking in involved a wait of almost 30 minutes and I was disappointed to find no automated check-in kiosk.The greatest disappointment of my stay was my room. I had requested a quiet room. As an aside, at the Ali'i Tower, you can reserve - and of course pay for - one of three room types (full coean view, partial ocean view, or garden view). Frankly, the only way you'll see the Pacific Ocean if you're in a partial ocean view room is if you're an acrobat and hang over the balcony. If you want a view of the ocean, plan on paying $100 or more per night. Otherwise, save your money and content yourself with a view of the pool or a view of the wedding chapel. When I arrived at my room on the 6th floor, I found that I had been assigned a connecting room, a room with a single key-locked door separating two guest rooms. The result is like having no door at all between rooms. The desk staff claimed that no other rooms were available in the building and that, in essence, I was stuck with what I had been assigned. A family with two or three very, very young children were in the connecting room and the noise throughout the night kept me from getting much sleep. My adivce to you is that if you're assigned a connecting room you refuse to accept the room and seek a replacement room.The simple truth is that a stay at this property is a process to (a) separate as much money from you as possible and (b) incessantly market the Hilton Grand Vacation Club to you. DIning prices (let alone room service prices) are obscene, even by resort standards. I agree with others who have recommended that you buy food and beverages at the nearby ABC stores and/or dine off-property. Frankly, if you are staying here with your family, my advice to you is this: if you have a rental car and a Costco membership card, stop at the Costco that's just off the Nimitz on the way in from the airport (right across the parking lot from the Dole Cannery). Stock up on pretty much anything you'll need (the Costco even sells hard liquoir!!!) before going on to the hotel. All the rooms have small fridges with a tiny freezer.The HIlton Village is crowded with conventioneers, grumpy families, and an almost endless stream of wedding parties. If you want a quiet island vacation, the Hawaiian Village is not for you.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>