<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="caca8d21794a6170e1474f3264a2a3fa" url=""><![CDATA[Great location and room, but minimal services We spent a week at the Hotel Jazz.I can't say enough about the location, just about every neighborhood is walkable from the hotel.The entire hotel is extremely well taken care of, and the room on the 7th floor had a nice little balcony and was clean and elegantly designed/furnished.Unlike previous reviewers, I did not experience any subway rumble or noise, and the double paned glass really did a good job of keeping street noise to a minimum.As long as you appreciate Hotel Jazz for what it is, and come to terms with it's shortcomings it's a solid choice. In some ways it is more like an apartment stay than a full service hotel. My complaints have to to with the services. There are really no public spaces to speak of, so if you get a little stir crazy in your room you are out of luck. There is a very small bar area, but it closed around 9:30 pm on the two nights we tried to go there!The breakfast is expensive, and in no way worth it. The staff are either helpful, or very unhelpful. There are times when there is only one person at the desk which can be frustrating. When unhelpful, the staff borders on rude. We had bad experiences with room service as well with it not being delivered at all on two occasions.Their toiletries were also pretty disappointing. Were I to return, I would bring my own.In addition, their recommendations for restaurants and the like are pretty awful. I can wholeheartedly recommend a new restaurant in the area on RamblasCatalunya (I think #13) called Mata Mala. We are foodies, and this place was not a tourist trap like what the hotel recommends, but was a modern ingredients-driven place that we really liked. It is one block off Place Catalunya.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="283caa02d25df7b667b7736cf1a6efd9" url=""><![CDATA[Showing its age but good service and location I was booked into this hotel for business travel. One thing off the bat is that even though starwood owns the hotel, they do not offer SPG points! That is pretty odd.Great location for the hotel. It is right around the corner from hotels costing 2-3 times as much as this one charges.The first room I had was pretty small, but clean and decently furnished if a little old fashioned and out of date.However, there was a smell of sewage coming from the bathroom, and next to no hot water in the shower.I complained about this, and was upgraded to a tower level room which I thought was the correct way to handle situation.This room was larger, had great hot water and was thankfully devoid of any sewage smells. It also came with access to a lounge that had complimentary breakfast in the morning and drinks and hors d'ouvres at night.I would stay here again for business, but the style of the hotel is not my thing if I were paying. That being said, service was excellent and the location can't be beat for the price.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>