<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="96a7da1aed020a5b4277634ea52b4ee2" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Service at the InterContinental My wife and I visited Singapore in February 2008 and we stayed at the InterContinental Hotel, 80 Middle Road.I booked the hotel for three nights via the IC website back in April 2007, with a room rate of approximately SGD 303.00 per night and including breakfast for up to two adults. Anyone who has travelled frequently will know that breakfast in a five star hotel can cost between and per person, so to have this included in the room charge seemed more than good value. Booking through the website meant that I had a confirmed reservation at an excellent price and I have to pay for the room until I had completed my stay. After our stay I checked my credit card statement whilst continuing our travels and I was more than pleased to find that the total cost for my stay at the InterContinental was equating to slightly over per night for a wonderful room and a sumptuous breakfast.The hotel is ideally located and not too far from Raffles Hotel as well as a subway station. We each purchased a Singapore Tourist allows three use on the metro system and is excellent value for money and allows visitors to take advantage of the excellent rail links and low-cost travel around Singapore.I have visited Singapore twice before and on both occasions have stayed at the Pan Pacific Hotel and the only reason I choose it this time around was because it was more costly than the InterContinental. However, we decided to visit it whilst we were there to see if it had changed - and unfortunately for my taste it had! The interior and layout had been changed to an ultra-modern style with extremely bright colours, which probably impresses guests staying there for the first time - but it is not to my taste. Therefore extremely pleased I chose the InterContinental and would most certainly recommend it to any first-time traveller to Singapore, I would also recommend it to any traveller returning to Singapore who has been disappointed with their accommodation on previous visits.I can not praise the hotel personnel highly enough as they are always friendly, professional and courteous in all their actions. At breakfast all of the staff in the restaurant was extremely attentive to the requirements. You only needed to get up from your table for a short while to get something from the excellent buffet selection, and you would find that any dirty plates and cutlery would be removed and clean cutlery placed on the table, in addition to finding your napkin neatly folded again. One need to look around for staff when a tea or coffee refill was required as someone was always at hand to offer a refill.The hotel rooms are well appointed and as I have already indicated the breakfast is a joy to feast on and there is a wide variety of food to cater for Europeans and Asians. I never took advantage of the swimming pool, however, I did walk around all the facilities with my wife and everything looked in pristine condition.I hope I have another opportunity to visit Singapore and the InterContinental Hotel will by first choice of hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>