<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="67bd6ea095c84cf3b1c70635d9480e2c" url=""><![CDATA[Good location Needed one night accomodation in the city and wanted something centrally located. Also wanted to earn double honors points! Location of hotel is great. Staff was very friendly. When we got to our room we immediately noticed the very noisy elevator on the other side of our wall. We asked for a different room but they were sold out. The noise through the night was awful and in the morning we brought it to the attention of the manager. They were very apologetic and immediately offered to give us the night for free.I told them that everything else about the hotel was great and that a 50% discount was quite acceptable.Breakfast was typical of most Hamptons. They didn't have a business center but offered to let me use their office computer to look up the location of a local festival that was in the city.Parking was right next door and staff there was also very friendly.We left our bags with the bellman for the day and he quickly retrieved them for us when we returned at 3pm.I would pick this hotel again but request a room away from the elevator just in case they aren't able to resolve the noise issue.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8fda2ce05fadddc6a4cc8b7920694e15" url=""><![CDATA[Never again! March 25 and March 26, 05. Booked through New York Auto Show (Expo Travel). Guaranteed our room with a credit card as usual. Arrived at 11pm. We were told by the Marriott staff that they didn't have any rooms for us and that they would send us to another hotel. Clerk disappeared for 15 minutes and finally came back to tell us that they found us a hotel. In Brooklyn! I told them that there was no way I was taking my family to Brooklyn so late at night. I told them that I had specifically booked this hotel because of its proximity to the auto show-otherwise I would have booked us at the Hilton because we are Hilton members. I also asked them why they hadn't bothered to contact us earlier in the day when they knew they were overbooked. They had no answer. Finally at midnight they found us rooms at the Sofitel about 4 blocks away. They did give us cab fare and payed for our rooms. They told us to come back the next day and they would have 2 rooms for us as reserved. We returned the next day at noon and 1 room was ready. No problem it was a bit early and we understood. Came back at 6pm and 2nd room still wasn't ready. Finally at 7pm we were able to get into the 2nd room.Elevators in this hotel are ridiculous. We waited 1/2 hour and then had to take the service elevator. I will say that the staff was friendly and probably as frustrated as we were about the room situation and the lack of elevator service. Bottom line, if they are in the middle of renovations than they should consider not booking to capacity until they can reasonably accomodate all their customers. Last weekend I was due to stay at the Embassy Suites in Charleston , SC and the hotel called me at 8am in the morning to tell me they were overbooked and would appreciate it if I would consider staying at the hotel next door (Hampton Inn) at their expense. That is the way business should be done. In this day of modern technology there is no excuse for the poor management of reservations at the Marriott. The Marriott staff kept stressing that they were going to pay for our room as if that should make everything ok, despite the potential inconvenience of being sent to a hotel 45 minutes away from where we planned to stay. As I explained to them staying at the Marriott was about convenience for the event we were planning to attend, not the price. They should not assume that everyone who stays here is only interested in getting a free room because they have poorly managed their reservation system. Saturday night we ate in the hotel restaurant on the 8th floor. Service was good and so was the food. Prices were reasonable for a tourist location. It will be hard for me to ever consider staying here again. The Marriott staff needs to be better organized. We travel very often and this is the first time in many years that we were faced with so many obstacles in such a short time. Should you be considering this hotel call to reconfirm your reservation and ask the status of their elevators. Had we had theater tickets or dinner reservations it would have been extremely difficult to arrive on time for either. I shudder to imagine what this hotel would due in the case of an emergency evacuation. There is no way they could properly handle any type of emergency.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="566977699115ef2b995a97aba4004a5f" url=""><![CDATA[ok, not great My family of 6 spent 2 nights (thanksgiving) at this Hilton. The lobby is very small by HIlton standards. Check in was smooth. Got to the room to find that the double beds were smaller than standard size. So we called to the front desk to order roll aways. No problem, $25 per bed per room. Yikes! Our sons room mini fridge was full of old and smelly food. Housekeeping came up quickly to remove. Later that evening I called for more washcloths as there was only 1 in our room. An hour later they were delivered. Plasma screen tvs don't impress me like they seem to impress so many other guests. tv is tv. We go to NYC to see the sights not watch things we can watch at home. Exercise facilities and pool are very nice. Having to pay for internet service is ridiculous! I find it funny that Hampton Inn's don't charge for internet service and yet the more upscale Hilton properties try to grab more money from you for something that should easily be included in your hotel quote.Location of this Hilton is only a minor inconvenience. Subway is just across the street and taxis are plentiful. Valet parking only at $45 per night. No in and out parking available. Takes about 25 mintues to get your car.Had desert in the hotel restaurant. Very good and staff was very friendly. Breakfast was suppose to be included but my husband had to go to the front desk to have the charges removed.Being across the street from the World Trade Center site was humbling and my family spent some time just looking out our windows at the site as well as walking around the area.No real perks at this Hilton for belonging to Hilton Honors. Would I choose this Hilton again, probably not. I wouldn't mind the distance to main sights if the hotel itself was more appealing. We have stayed in many hotels in NYC that had more ambience. However, if you get a good rate and it's price you are interested in than you'll probably be okay here.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>