<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="eb58fa5647bd70f2b9640c90c271d269" url=""><![CDATA[perfect position As all the reviews state, this hotel is in a perfect position to be able to walk to the main strip.The fact that it had a kitchen was perfect for the family as we were all sick of eating out after spending a week in Disneyland. There was a big supermarket ( Fresh and Easy I think it was called) on the main drag where fresh meat, vegetables and fruit could be purchased.The room itself was quite spacious - it also had a safe which was handy. The pool was well maintained and perfect for a dip after a day out and about.They also provided free internet access on a computer located on the 2nd floor which was great for checking e-mails, getting directions, booking tours etc.The free parking was also a bonus, as was the laundry that was resonably priced.All the staff were pleasant and the service people did a great job cleaning the rooms every day.Just a tip - do not get sucked into doing a tour of the homes of the stars. They are overpriced and you really don't see anything!!I would recommend this hotel to anyone.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7abc5e085e0a4e1a114edb9041832061" url=""><![CDATA[Not unless you are desperate The only thing this hotel has going for it is that it is only one block from the beach. Even so, there are plenty of other places to stay that are just as close or even closer.While the room itself was adequate, don't expect to be spoiled.The building is old and leaks - one morning they had water dripping out of the ceiling near the lift on the first floor.The pool, or should I say a pond, is only accessible by walking out of the hotel and through the underground parking garage. Not exactly a convenient location.The 'free' continental breakfast is a disgrace - no milk or butter. Bread (no toaster) and a few bread rolls. IF you arrive in the first ten minuted you might be lucky enough to get a banana!!!! The coffee from the urn was cold and the only juice available was guava!!!!My advice is to anyone who is unlucky enough to stay here is to go next door to the bakery and spend a couple of dollars on a croissent, then head to Starbucks across the road for a coffee.Don't bother trying to get any information from the travel desk - the people who work there seem to know less than the average tourist - that is if they will get off the phone long enough to talk to you.Sorry to be so negative but these were my experiences.My advice is to look elsewhere
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="190fa2875ab4886b4a033d456b002001" url=""><![CDATA[this is the best! Out of all the five stars that I have stayed at in Sydney, this was the best by far!The level of service was outstanding, from check in through to dining room service.Had booked a room and was upgraded to a suite because it was my wife's birthday! They have an Executive Lounge that you are given access to which has free coffee and drinks. The staff in here went out of their way to make us feel welcome and could not do enough to help. The room itself was very comfortable with magnificent views over Sydney Harbour and the Opera House.Breakfast was very nice with an egg chef on hand to freshly prepare omelettes, pancakes etc.I would not hesitate to recommend this hotel to anyone.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>