<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="424f85ee666a8752c1b94509546de644" url=""><![CDATA[Good Club Lounge and Staff Stayed in a Club Room here on Friday night. Hotel has recently been renovated and a new Club Lounge created since our last stay (approx 6 months ago).Likes- Very friendly and accomodating staff especially James who was excellent and always smiling even when struggling with out large suitcases!- Great restaurant for dinner (Garden Court), food was excellent and particularly liked the extensive list of water available- Attractively designed Club Room with good quality food and beverages- The Sofitel bedDislikes- The renovated rooms still have the shallow old bath and low water pressure- No poolOverallI thought this was a hotel well worth staying in. The Club Lounge could expand it's food and beverage range slightly but no real complaints. Staff were friendly, professional and very helpful
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="54838c0cd7dfce598f7d0b00fbfbc08c" url=""><![CDATA[NIce Amenities and Pool Area Just checking-out of this hotel at the moment and thought I'd take a minute to write a review...Likes - Great bathroom amenities from - Nice sunny pool area with two large pools- On top of the Raffles Plaza shopping centre- You can charge your room when dining at the Swissotel and Raffles hotels next doorDislikes- Very small rooms for the price- Rooms could do with a makeover (eg old carpet etc)- Some of the Fairmont President's Club benefits unavailable (eg Aveda Travel Kits)- Fairly average housekeeping (eg replacement shampoo and soap etc just thrown onto the bathroom bench top)OverallProbably overpriced for what it is, if you get a good deal I'd recommend it though. Staff are very friendly though especially Raj at the President's Club desk and the location is good with an MRT station just downstairs and Suntec city a 5min walk away.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="065c8a0658db990550969f04b7b092c1" url=""><![CDATA[Nice new club longe and rooms Having seen the recent reviews we were a little hesitant to book here but we use Hyatt Passport so went with it. We requested a newly renovated club room so review is based on this.Likes- Good size room- Great decor in the Club Lounge (with free WiFi)- Location- StraitsKitchen!Dislikes- Maintenance issues in the bathroom (door handles and plug both broken) nb they were quickly repaired- Limited food range for breakfast and cocktail hour in the Club Lounge; especially when compared with other Hyatt's (eg Taipei)Overall- A pricey hotel, if you get a new room then is probably worth the money.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>