<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="ff848b74eebf9f5d694a74d83a784bf0" url=""><![CDATA[Great Service at Hotel Pierre During our third trip to Florence, my husband and I were booked at the Hotel Pierre. It's a lovely boutique hotel with 44 rooms on five floors. When we arrived, at about 1 pm, we were greeted warmly, our room was ready and we never touched our bags until they were brought to our room. The room was beautiful, with a wood floor and marble bathroom. Breakfast was included and the chef was proficient at American scrambled eggs! They don't have a restaurant but there are many within walking distance and the staff gives excellent recommendations. One minor problem is noise - if you're on the Via Del Lamberti side, you might encounter loud talking and, how shall I say it, exhuberent spirits. This went on some nights until 1 or 1:30 am and disturbed my sleep but not my husband's. Otherwise, this is a lovely place, situated perfectly for all the sights you would wish to visit.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="374f063589b80039f6422822a1aa845c" url=""><![CDATA[Comfortable and Charming Hotel We chose this hotel because of the philosophy theme and because of the garden. This was worth the price on both counts. We had a lovely breakfast every morning and drank our Dutch coffee in the garden befoe heading out. Some people have written that the hotel is a bit off the beaten track but there is a tram stop about a block away that makes it easy to get around town. The room was a tad on the small side and the amenities weren't lavish but the view of the garden from the room was wonderful - the bird songs were soothiing as well. Leideseplein is about a 10-15 minute walk and on the way there is the tourist kiosk where you can purchase your I Amsterdam books with several options for your length of stay. The hotel is in a quiet area and the guests were quite nice as well. There are a few steps to climb to get to the main level so I wouldn't recommend it for those who can't get their bags up or down several steep stairs. The elevator works well and is lavish by European standards (think twice as big as Italian hotel elevators!). All in all, this was a quiet, delightful property and if I went to Amsterdam again I'd certainly stay here a second time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>