<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="867b856b48c1a7bc6609078099e5cacb" url=""><![CDATA[The studio rooms here are great We stayed at this hotel for 7 nights as part of an extended holiday. The location is great very close to Darling Harbour, the Rocks and only a short walk to Wynyard station where you can get the rail and buses. It is in the CBD so at night and weekends the area is a bit lifeless, rather reminiscent of the city of London, but it is not far to get to somewhere where there is some nightlifeThe studio rooms are very large and are like a mini suite - it is well worth paying the extra. We had been travelling for two weeks by this point and it was good to have the option to just make and eat something simple rather than always having to go out to a restaurant. There is a supermarket in the station (you access it via the station entrance next to The Menzies Hotel, which is just opposite the Travelodge)The staff were very friendly and helpful. We didn't use the restaurant so can't really comment on that, but there is a Starbucks opposite if you need a caffeine fix!It has a laundry, but no dryer so if you do do washing then you will have to drape things around your room.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="41fc8be04afb4df47aaa8b1328a82c84" url=""><![CDATA[A wonderful hotel This is an amazing hotel in the centre of Barcelona. It is on the edge of the old town and has an amazing terrace with a great view over the marina and port. The pool is rather small a bit like a large bath rather than a swimming pool, but there are tables and chairs together with loungers, although as it was November we did not use them.The rooms are a good size and air conditioned if it gets too hot. We were lucky to have a room with a view over the Passeig de Colom, which we did not find too noisy unlike some other reviewers. The en suite bathrooms are large and the shower was very good.The breakfast was included in our room booking (14 Euros usually) and was a continental buffet style. We thought that it was a good selection with cold meats, cheeses, bread, fresh fruit, freshly squeezed fruit juices, various pastries and some traditional Spanish touches as well.The best feature however was the friendly staff. They could not do enough for you. An another touch that was a first for us was a card that they sent round the night before telling you what the weather forecast for the next day was meant to be, tehy even gave you a choice of air freshener that the housekeeping staff could offer.We have already recommended this hotel several times and have only been back two days!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="aa4930b2f0d49b929c9c6102b6d86f2f" url=""><![CDATA[Good Hotel for a stopover The staff are really friendly and the rooms are a good sixe and have all your really need. It is in a good location close to the MTR, several bus stops and a tram stop!The rooms do need a little updating, but it is good value and we didn't really spend much of our three days in our room or the hotel.If you are looking for luxury or a pampering time then look elsewhere, but as a base for sightseeing this fits the bill.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>