<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="bb5a0e443a3af8d3ab30e3e01adf2071" url=""><![CDATA[Holiday Inn Fisherman's Wharf - Perfect. We traveled to San Francisco for a weekend while visiting family in Northern California. We were there for 2 nights and I would say the Holiday Inn Fisherman's Wharf was the perfect hotel for us.The trip wasn't all sunshine and roses, and i will get into that later, but the SF portion of the trip was great.The Hotel. We arrived around 7:30 Friday night. We were put up in the main building, on the 3rd floor. We had 2 double beds, so when I asked if they had any King's left they said yes, but they were in the other building. Rooms were plenty big. Clean. We didn't have a view at all, but thats OK. We were with our 16 month old, so we needed a crib. Called housekeeping when we got to the room, and the crib was there minutes. We tipped housekeeping $2.50 Saturday morning. I know thats not much, but they seemed to really appreciate it. Left us a note thanking us, and then every time they saw one of us they asked where the baby was (sleeping) and always said hi. The Location. Absolutely perfect. Just a block from the Cannery Ghirardelli Square. 2 blocks from Fisherman's Wharf. 10 minutes to Pier 39. Plenty of food nearby. Food. The onsite Denny's seems expensive. We had the Lumberjack Slam that we split between 3 ways. It was 2 Pancakes, 2 Eggs, 2 Pieces of Bacon, 2 Sausage Links, Piece of Ham and Hash browns for $13.99. Thats a lot of food, and was perfect for us to split. However Waffles were $11 and Hamburgers were $10+. The first night we were there we ate dinner at the Boudin Bakery on Fisherman's Wharf. I had the Bread Bowl of Chowder and my wife and daughter split a grilled cheese (it was huge and apparently VERY GOOD). Add a brownie and a bottle of water. Dinner for $20. The second night we went to the Wipe Out Bar and Grill on Pier 39. Standard american food there. Cool atmosphere. Sat outside.Yes parking is expensive, but thanks to Trip Advisor I was prepared for the $88 charge.Must do's. Go to The Stinkin' Rose. Great restaurant with a focus on garlic. Good stuff. Also visit Liguria Bakery (1700 Stockton). Not much of a store but the foccacia bread is outstanding. We got an order of the pizza bread and an order of the raisin bread. Great stuff. Get there early as they run out of stuff as the day goes on. If traveling with children, check out the Aquarium of the Bay at Pier 39. Kids under 3 are free, and adults are $14.95 each.The bad stuff has nothing to do with the city of SF or the Holiday Inn and all to do with Dollar Rental. Terrible. I won't go into all the details here, but it starts with them putting a hold on my check card for the rental, which I know is standard stuff, but they added 15% to the hold and when you are on a budget that extra $120 can go a long ways. I didn't realize this until Friday night. I called the 800 number and was told that I needed to talk to the Customer Service department, which at 8:00 local time was closed for the weekend. Thats helpfull. They said they would release the extra 15% when we returned the car. Which as you could imagine was at the end of our trip and the $120 really didn't do us much good.All in all, we had a great time, and would recommend The Holiday Inn to anyone.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>