<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="fa256194755e5b33d92767cf2b70b38c" url=""><![CDATA[The beacon really does shine!!!!!! :-) We have just returned from New york, and stayed at the beacon hotel, this was our 3rd visit to the city staying at various hotels/ Apartments each time, but the Beacon Hotel was by far the best!!, We booked a 1 bedroom suite, as we wanted space, and space is exactly what we got, our apartment in the hotel was huge compaired to others we have stayed in ( for the same price 2!! ), we had our own living room, with a sofa ( folded out in to a double bed) 2 chairs, a dining table with 2 chairs, coffee table, tv, with stand and storage space, the living room overlooked the hudson river, ( we were on the 24th floor) and it was a wicked view at night!, off the living room was a small but compact kitchen, and was spotless, and had everything we needed if we wanted to stay in and cook ( but who does in nyc), and the maid, which is daily service, left fresh coffee, teabags etc for us on the days we requested them to come in and change our sheets etc. The bathroom was a decent size, it had a bath and a shower, sink/ toilet, ( The maid also left us lil shampoos and conditioners etc, the mouthwash looked a bit toxic, but it was the thought that counted haha) The bedroom was huge, it had x2 double beds in (very comfy) and it had plenty of storage space, along with a tv and sky also in the room, it also had a personal safe ( free of charge) you could programme yourself, if you wanted to store your cash. I found our room very well kept and very clean, and believe me im quite hard to impress with regards to the way hotels clean their properties, sure there is always room for improvement but it was nearly spotless! ( could have done with a change of carpet in the L room, but hey! ) The hotel itself is situated on 75th street broadway, which is 2 blocks ( about 1 min away) from the 72nd street main subway where you can get a Metro card fun pass ( good for rail and bus) for the day for $7 you can go anywhere in nyc on the card. It has its own resteraunt on site so if you didnt want to go out, the resteraunt/ diner style eatery has all you need, it also has its own wine shop, which is pretty cool, and the prices are fair.On 72nd street, heading towards central park, is a place called BBQ's, its a stonesthrow away from the Beacon Hotel and the have Texas Style frozen cocktails on offer for around $7, they are not to be missed ( they are the size of fishbowls, delicious, and your hammered after 1, $7, you cant complian!! ha) also across the road from the Beacon, is the famous fairways supermarket, it has everything you need , even if you didnt want to see a supermarket on your hols, its worth just going in to see the amount of food that place has!. The beacon hotel is about 5 mins from central park, and you could either walk, catch a cab or catch a sub if you wanted to go downtown where Macys, and to where all the other hustle and bustle is, The beacon hotel is brill for anyone, and it especially brill for the people who like to venture in to the hustle and bustle of new york when they fancy, but enjoy a more peacefull laid back pace where the hotel is situated, The Beacon hotel is just fab! :-) P.s Coney island is a must, although the cyclone roallercoaster gives you some major bruises!! :-)
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>