<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="db99a482b53ee1becb256a27f749030d" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent small hotel We booked direct with the hotel in January 2006 via their website for a trip in May 2006. Booking was simple and straightforward. The price actually charged was exactly the price quoted in the email booking confirmation; note however that the price quoted is ex-VAT (7%) although to be fair this is clearly stated. The receptionist also went through the prices very carefully in arrival to make sure we were clear. The only slight niggle was an extra charge for a room safe (2 eruos per night) which was not mentioned anywhere.The hotel is very quiet which for the centre of the Barri Gotic is quite unexpected. However, our room opened on to the central open courtyard rather than the street - outside rooms may be noisier (but you don't go to central Barcelona for peace and solitude do you?) The hotel appears to have been recently refurbished and is a good mixtrue of of the old and modern in terms of architectecure. Brilliant location just down from the Plaza Catalunya and close to the cathedral. It is in the pedestrianised zone so taxi access may be a bit limited - we walked from the Plaza Catalunya where the Airport Bus deposited us (about 10 minutes) and no traffic to worry about.Staff were very friendly and helpful and spoke reasonable English (much better than our Spanish). Our room was an adequate size for two and was spotlessly clean. Internet access is free. There were no tea-making facilties in the room (although there were some self-heating drinks but there was an additional charge for these. However, there is a little bar with self-service tea and coffee (and croissants, rolls and cakes) at no extra charge, and these could be taken up to cool sitting area in a pleasant courtyard on the first floor. I guess this would be nice and cool in summer.Breakfast was excellent and well worth 14 euros extra each (50% discount on the first morning) - huge choice of fruits, cold meats, cheeses, crudites, cereals, cooked bacon and egg etc.The age-range of the clients was wide, a couple of children aged about 10 through to retired couples, and were mostly English, Dutch and American, so far as I could judge
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>