<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="80f3c45e91348d269cf16e0603c49031" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect! We booked this hotel through Mr Mrs Smith so we knew it would be good we weren't disappointed.Location - The hotel is in a fab location just one street away from Times Square, so you're close to everything but it was also a lot quieter than we expected.Staff - ALL the staff were lovely, very friendly helpful. They helped get us taxis when we were in a hurry reserved a table for us at the Russian Tea Rooms (if you want to go to the Plaza, book in advance - we couldn't get in unfortunately!)Room - the room was great, bigger than we expected. The bed as a lot of people have said already was v. comfortable had great sheets too, loads of wardrobe space, massive shower, v.well equipped - safe, TV, DVD player, iPod dock, fridge, hairdryer, iron ironing board. It was v. cold when we were there so it was great we had control of the stat too.Facilities - the pool, gym, sauna steam room all looked great but we were so busy sightseeing we never got chance to use them. The shop in the lobby was v. well stocked with drinks, snacks, magazines etc. The bar (open til 1) was great, we had some lovely v.strong cocktails. The hotel transforms into a nightclub in the evening with DJs people in the pool (using the swim-up bar) and this is our only criticism of the place - it had a strange mix of tourists (like us!) and wannabes posing in / around the pool, the latter made it feel a bit like a swingers convention some nights! Food - it was great staying in a NY hotel where breakfast is included, as it gives you a chance to wake up properly before joining the chaos outside. Lovely continental breakfast - croissants, muffins, bagels, yogurts, fruit, cereals, juice, tea coffee. The take-away menus in our room looked v. appealing too, but we ate out all the time we were there.Value - we stayed over Easter when loads of other hotels were coming up at crazy prices, this was excellent value, especially considering the location.We loved NY and this hotel will be recommending it to our friends family and hope to return one day ourselves too.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>