<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="0d3a5c2fc0a438f02e781c0aa5f2b173" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location So I had a single night in New York before I headed upstate for a conference and decided that Times Square was the place to be. Unfortunately, staying in Manhattan on the first saturday of December was always going to be expensive, but I didn't realise how expensive it would be!The taxi driver managed to get lost (how is this possible for a taxi driver to get lost going between JFK and Times Square?), but eventually I spotted the single door leading to the hotel's lobby. Or at least, I thought it was the lobby. Due to the nature of the location, the ground floor is just an entrance, and an elevator is required to get to the lobby. I was checked in within 30 seconds and up to my King Room. I had a great view of a scrolling ticker out of my window (what else in Times Square), but the curtains were thick enough to block out all light. The room was very pleasant with a comfortable bed, clean and crisp bedding and a large and powerful shower. Internet access was charged at $17 per day which i thought was a bit expensive considering the price of the room, and it was also wired (ethernet cable was present in the room). One thing that may help others, was that the network connection on the desk was part of a multiplug that also had connectors for DVI and HDMI. I presume these led to the large LCD TV so anyone travelling with a laptop full of movies could theoretically play them on the TV, or fine tune any business presentations on a big screen - quite a plus. Unfortunately, having a MacMini meant I had left my $30 adapter back at home and could neither test nor use this facility.The location was excellent and I went for a walk in the evening to take a look around. The large Christmas tree in the Rockefeller Plaza was about 10 minutes away, as was 5th Avenue. 10 minutes walking south got me to the huge Macy's (where I got lost) and also to the Empire State building. Even though I was on the 7th floor, the hotel was suitably soundproofed and no noise from Times Square entered my room.The staff were most helpful in every way and are happy to mind your luggage upon checking our (which is 12:00 by the way) should you want to look around the city before you head off to another destination. In addition, the staff downstairs can provide advice for locations, dining and the best way to get to another location. In my case, they recommended against getting a cab upstate and called their own driver who took my to my next destination. Friendly and very efficient service!All in all, a very pleasant experience and I would recommend this hotel to anyone if the rooms are a little less expensive (which I believe they are given a different date). It has been recently modernised and won't be to everyone's taste, but as a very pleasant room in the centre of Manhattan, it is fine. I would have rated it as excellent apart from the cost.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b8c7748d636f0b1fd80bf1fa1be546e9" url=""><![CDATA[The steepest hill in hotels! I last stayed in the Luxe in 2004 when I had a pleasant few days. After reading some reviews on this site, I was concerned that the place had gone downhill, however I took the chance as I wanted somewhere with a balcony (to smoke) along with a restaurant and bar.I shouldn't have worried. Unfortunately it seems that people are more likely to write a review after a negative stay - I feel that positive stays deserve a review also!Let's start with Customer Service. I could not fault it at all. Unfortunately (through no fault of the hotel, they got the wrong booking information) I was put into a standard room rather than the Jr Exec Suite that I booked. I mentioned this at the front desk and spoke to the desk manager to apologised profusely for the issue but mentioned that they were fully booked that evening. He promised to sort it the next day. It was sorted the next day without bother. I went out and when I returned I had a new room with all my cases moved over. The suite was great. Extremely spacious with additional seating, huge bed and desk to work upon. The bathroom was also large with a sunken bath and a shower that could take at least four in comfort if you are so inclined (I did want to try it out but couldn't find another three people to join me :)Unfortunately my AC stopped working on the first night in my new room, just as a wedding started outside my window. I had to open the window to get some air into the room but just as the wedding music was making me stir crazy, the maintainance man fixed my AC - again, great service - fixed within 30 mins.As for food, it is quite expensive (well for the US anyway), but it was okay. Some dishes were great, others less so but the guys in the restaurant were incredibly friendly and polite. Likewise all the staff!Parking is a pain. Valet parking is compulsory at $25 or so per day, but again the valet team were incredibly quick and efficient - less than five minutes to get the car from turning up at the front desk.So what was bad? Nothing really, only a few really picky grumbles. Firstly whilst their website and the general hotel sites such as travelocity and hotels.com state they have smoking rooms, all rooms are non smoking. Not a problem if you get a room with a patio or balcony, but I had neither. Mind you, the 20 yard walk outside was far better than the 10 minute hikes I have had in previous hotels!Another problem was with the events. Rooms in the lower complete that are odd will tend to overlook the party area. Not a problem if you don't go to bed until later as they tended to be over by 10:30, but for early sleepers it can get quite noisy.The hotel is also split with the lower complex with restaurant and event areas, and the upper area with spa and pool. Rooms are at both locations but they are split by the steepest hotel hill in the world. Seriously, this baby must by 1:4 and 30-40 yards long! You can get a ride up to the top, but having to tip someone just to get to your room can be frustrating.The location is a little out of the way however (given good LA traffic) you can get to Santa Monica, Hollywood etc.. in a few mins. The place is right on the corner of Sunset and 405 so you can get anywhere easily - just don't try it in the morning and always take the garage exit to get to the highway!So all in all, a very pleasant stay and I will definitely be back if only to enjoy the excellent, polite and friendly staff that the Luxe employs - thanks to you all!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f685078d3d504bdb942dfc80cdaae959" url=""><![CDATA[Great - but beware if a smoker! So I spent five nights at the Westin back in February. We booked at a supposed reduced rate as we had a conference in the Moscone, but soon afterwards I heard that some people were getting their rooms for under $100 - ah well, not to worry.I also saw some split reviews for the St Francis which sort of worried us but we needn't have been concerned. The hotel is very big and whilst my room was quite small and overlooking a wall, I didn't go to SF to stay in my room so it wasn't a problem. The bed was comfy as all Westin's tend to be, and the shower was fine. I did have an issue where I couldn't turn off my tap (probably because I am a bit of a spanner), but it was quickly sorted.Staff were very friendly and helpful and you couldn't ask for a better location on Union Square!The only niggle I had and this is purely because I am a smoker, is that it was quite disconcerting smoking outside the building before the bell-hops got on duty as there was a tendency for every homeless person on Union Square to congregate around you. Those who fly in to SF from Europe will know all about the 'wake up at 4:00 syndrome' and smokers will recognise the need for a smoke when you wake up - just don't go outside before 06:30 (or try one of the other two entrances).All in all, a decent place in a good location with reasonable prices. Just don't take/hire a car - it was $50 a day or thereabouts to park!!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>