<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="4c978f018a9c9784174b0910e49ddb44" url=""><![CDATA[The Good and the Bad I stayed at this hotel the day before and the day after a cruise I took out of San Juan. During the first stay, they upgraded me to a suite right next to the pool that was a room of the quality you would see on MTV Cribs! This was amazing! I suspect they did this because it was my first stay at an Intercontinental Resort and Holiday Inn wanted me to keep coming back. However, on the second stay, I was in a typical room ... which was nothing special.The hotel has one of the nicest pools with beach entry that you will find on the beachy section of Puerto Rico. There is a nice bar area in the middle where you can sit and have one of the weakest $9 drinks you will ever get. However there are plenty of lounge chairs to lay out on and a nice (but crowded pool.)The hotel room (I am reviewing the standard room here ... if you have the money to get a pool side suite, you will thank yourself as the suite was one of the nicest hotel rooms I've stayed in anywhere) ... had yellowish stucco walls and medditeranian style furniture. It didn't really make me feel comfortable being in there for some reason. There was a balcony that overlooked the street (they were booked up and could not move me to one that overlooked the ocean in the back). The bed was comfortable but the room just lacked style. It felt like one of those cheap Florida condos. The bathroom was small and cheap looking.The location is good if you want to be on the beach. It isn't very glamorous. It reminds me a little of Atlantic City. The casino inside the hotel is small and there are a few good (but very overpriced restaurants). There is a Palm Steakhouse and a Japanese Hibachi style restaurant. The area around the hotel is pretty run down ... if you want to go to Old San Juan where the cruise ships dock, it will cost you about $15 for a cab there. It is several miles away. The weird thing is that the airport is only 1 or 2 miles away from the hotel yet because Puerto Rico charges cabfare by the zone, you will still pay $15 to get there.The hotel overall is kept up pretty nicely. If you can talk yourself into the club lounge (Priority Club) they have great hors d'erves and an open bar! The lobby area and casino area of the hotel are fairly classy and it does feel a little upscale. However, I wouldn't be comfortable paying more than $150 - $175 a night for the hotel based on what you get. If you are looking for nightlife and the real old side of San Juan instead of the beach/pool scene ... this is not the place for you. Stay in the heart of the old city if this is what you want as this is more of a beach resort.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>