<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="60df34304ac12f94efece88d380fc830" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Vacation A group of 6 from Wisconsin stayed at the Edenh from 1/18/08 to 1/25/08. The group consisted of myself, my wife, my son and his wife, and my daughter and her fiance'. We had 3 rooms total and all three were the Edenh Club Adults Only catagory. Just letting you know that this is my first post on Trip Advisor. When we started planning our vacation I was informed about the forums on TA. I never knew about the forums before this trip. We had picked out the Edenh from Apple Vacations mainly because of the great price that was being advertised at that time. Before we booked at the Edenh I was reading the forums numerous times daily and quite frankly I had bad vibes from what I was reading. It sounded like the resort would not be ready to open on time. From following the forums I learned about Punta Cana Mike. I emailed Mike a couple of times and he reassured me that the resort was opening on time but the casino, spa, gym and bowling alley would not be open when we got there. Then I read the first two reviews that came in around the last week of December and then the video testamony from laurie from California while she was staying there. After hearing and reading the few reviews and the assurance from Mike we decided to take the chance and we booked at the Edenh. When we arrived at the resort we entered the VIP check-in area and immediately were greeted by Wendy. She said they were waiting for us and she was very pleasant. Within 10 minutes two of us were off to our rooms. The other room was not ready yet but Wendy said within an hour that room would be ready. When we got into our rooms we were very happy. Everything was clean, bright and cheerful. Our chamber maid was cleaning the room next to us so she immediately came over to our room to make sure everything was OK and at the same time the person who fills up the mini fridge on a daily basis was there also so he came to make sure everything was OK. So within the first 2 minutes of being in our room we meet the two people that would be taking care of our room for the week. Both were very nice and said to let them know of anything that we needed. I did tell the maid that we were supposed to have bathrobes in our room. She said she would bring them right away. She brought them to our room within 10 minutes. While we were unpacking our stuff someone delivered a fresh fruit basket and someone else brought us a bottle of rum. Talk about service, within the first 1/2 hour we were in our room and received everything that we were supposed to get. Our room was on the 4th floor and had the whirlpool on the balcony. We had a wonderful view of the ocean and of the pool area. My daughters room was 4 doors down from us and her room was exactly like ours. My son went down to see if his room was ready and it was. His room was on the 2nd floor and was identical to ours. He really wanted to be on the same floor as us but Wendy said there were no more available but to try in the morning to see if they could move him up to the 4th floor. All 6 of us then went to explore the resort. First stop was the lobby bar. Met Miguel who was a great bartender. He made our drinks with Absolute vodka. Next stop was the Tantrah bar which was not open yet but Bladamir the bartender was there and he made our drinks with Grey Goose vodka. Next stop was the Paradise Club bar and swimming pool. This is the area that was supposed to be adults only but there were a few kids in the pool. No big deal but we were wondering why they were there if this was the adults only area. This is the area and bar that we pretty much hung out at all week. The bartenders name was Carlos. He was an absolute joy to be around. He took care of us like we were royalty. He never let our drinks get empty. One of his favorite expressions was Carlos is happy everyday. He sure lived up to that expression. Always had a smile on his face and sincerely seemed happy to see us and wait on us. We asked Carlos if this was the adults only area and he said yes it was and it also was for VIP people only meaning those that had pink or yellow wristbands. Not trying to be demanding or anything like that I asked him why then are there kids in the pool and why are people in this area and bar with green wristbands. With that Carlos went and told the kids they had to leave and told people with green wristbands that they could not be in this area. Some of those that he kicked out evidently were not happy about this and must of complained about it because Carlos left for a while. When he got back he explained that his boss questioned him about the incident. As it turns out that was a good thing because from that time forward Carlos said that no more green wristbands or children would be allowed. Throughout the week I witnessed Carlos kicking people out of the area that were not supposed to be there. The problem with this was that there were no signs posted anywhere to let let anybody know that this was adults only and for Edenh Club guests only. I think if signs were posted that would have solved any problems with who was allowed or not. Just letting you know when we left a week later, there still were no signs. The 2nd day we went down to the same area and Carlos was there and again he was very happy. He introduced us to another bartender and his name was Carlos also. So they were called Carlos #1 and Carlos #2. All week long both of these guys wonderful to us. We ate at the buffet every morning for breakfast. They had a nice selection of food and they made you eggs and omelets any way you liked them No complaints about the buffet. Every afternoon we had our lunch at the buffet down at the beachfront. Again they had a good assortment of food but much less than the regular buffet. Every night we at dinner at the ala carte restaurants. The first night we waited for about an hour to get seated. It was well worth the wait. We were at the Shore Grill and had a very tasty steak and lobster dinner. The 2nd night we at at the Italian restaurant but we got there right at 6:30 when they opened and we had no wait at all. Again the food was very good. We decided that we would make a point of having dinner at 6:30 every night so we would not have to wait. 3rd night we ate at the Asian at 6:30 and again had no wait. We sat at the hibachi cooking station which is were they prepare your food in front of you. Again great food. 4th night we went back to the Shore grill at 6:30 and we had to wait, and wait, and wait. We finally got seated about 9:00. Obviously we were not happy about waiting so long. The next morning when we went to the buffet for breakfast there was a table outside that was there to make reservations for dinner. We were told there were two times that we could make reservations for 6:30 and 8:30. We made our reservation for 6:30 for the Romantic Restaurant. We were ok with the new procedure of making reservations after we had waited so long the night before. We showed up at 6:30 and we waited about 30 minutes before we were seated. Don't understand why as there were 7 empty tables when we finally got in. The food was good, not great. 6th night we went back for more steak and lobster at 6:30 and we were seated within 15 minutes. 7th night back to the Shore grill and we waited for about an hour. I don't know if the reservation system was any better than no reservations. Either way we ended up waiting. The wait was not that bad, we just went with the flow. Also the lobby bar is right there so while we waited we just kept going in there to fill up our drinks. Over all, all 6 of us enjoyed all of our meals. I am happy to report that none of us had any ill effects for the food. As for the bars, like I said our favorite during the day was the Paradise Club at the adult pool. At night before and after dinner it was the lobby bar. For late night it was the Tantrah bar and for the wee hours of the morning it was the sports bar. The problem we had with all the bars(except the Paradise club) was that sometimes we were served premium liquor and other times we were told that we had to pay for the premium. Even after telling the bartenders and showing them our pink VIP wristbands we still were not served the premiums. Again we went along with the flow. As long as we had a drink in our hand we were happy. However, part of the reason why we upgraded was to get the premium liquors. On Sunday the 20th there was a party atmosphere all afternoon and evening in the lobby bar were the playoff games were shown on a huge TV. It was alot of fun. Only bad thing was that the Packers lost. Met PC Mike the 2nd day we were there. VERY nice gentleman. He actually took the time to sit and talk with us for about 1/2 hour. We brought Mike a Packer t-shirt and he said he would wear it on Sunday. He did. We also met Carmen during the Packer game. Muy bonita! During the week we saw Mike a couple more times and once he was walking around with Mike Fisher. Mike Fisher again was a very nice guy. While we were there we heard some of the horror stories about people getting bumped to other resorts and other stories of how people had to change rooms 3, 4 or 5 times because of various reasons. I definately feel sorry for those people. You go on vacation to get away from the hassles of everyday life. You don't need hassles while on vacation. I believe the resort did the best they could do to help guests out but the overbooking of rooms and sending people to other resorts just is not good business. Don't know whose problem that is whether it is the Edenhs' or the travel companys. We heard about some of the problems from the very first day we were there. So my son decided that his room on the 2nd floor was ok with him. He did not change rooms. Overall, we had a wonderful vacation. Rooms were great, food was great, beach was beautiful, pools were nice and the drinks were cold and plentiful. I believe once some signs go up and all the workers know all what each catagory of guest is supposed to receive, things will be much smoother. I do not regret going there and I would go back there tomarrow if I could. Hope you all have as great of a time as we did!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>