<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="cffccf1e0167b1c05ad8de9911302272" url=""><![CDATA[Good Solid Hotel What a lot of nonsense people talk.My wife daughter and I stayed at this hotel 17th - 24 November. This was our first trip to NYC but not to the USA. It was a treat for our daughters 21st.The hotel staff were polite and helpfull. The porter had our bags up in the room within ten minutes. What do you want from a room when you are a tourist. You want it clean tidy safe, functional. It was all of that. Yes the room was hot but we hit upon a magic idea of opening the window - even in November it was quite pleasantHere are the facts.Room 1420 facing 48th street2 double beds with clean fresh linen and bedspreads. The beds were soft and comfortable.The room was not huge but it slept the three of us and had plenty of storage space for our clothes. The room was equipped with ironing board and safe free of charge.The bathroom had a toilet. tub/shower and wash hand basin - what more do you want. It wasnt big enough for a foam party but it easily met our requirements to use all the facilities comfortably. It again was clean and the towels changed every day. Small point on the towels if you are over a 36 inch wats then the towels ar small, however a quick call to houskeeping had an additional batch at my door in under 15 minutes.The kitchen had a microwave, fridge, coffe making facilities, and a sink. I wasnt cooking thanksgiving diner but as a tourist eating in all the fantastic restaurants and diners it easily satisifed our requirements.Yes there is a fire station at the end of the block but it is no noisier than all the other noises in New York.The street felt safe and was definitely well located for all the attarctions and shopping.Would I recommend it YES I wouldAll in all what I am syaying this was a good hotel, some people just seem to gripe for the pickiest of things. Ok so the Internet access was a bit dodgy but so aree internet cafes. I can olny assume that if the wrong attitude and approach was made to the staff you would get the same back.If you want top class service with people fawning all over you and you want to live in your room then go somewhere else and pay over the oddsMy reasons for not giving it 5 stars was beacuse the towels wer too small and the heat in the roomI am a genuine tourist and it you wish to e-mail me then do so travelandtunes@aol.com
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>