<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="4187aa5f61f00db0367ab7a19895a286" url=""><![CDATA[Don't Believe Bad Reviews....This Hotel is Great!!!! This hotel is a true resort on beautiful island (Puerto Rico). I would not believe the bad reviews. This hotel was great. I was at the hotel over winter break and the hotel was happening. The pools are great, service is great, and the hotel property is great. I would say that if you could get a rate below 250 it is definitely worth it. The location is a okay at best, but it is no big deal. There is a subway sandwich shop on the property and a convenience store too. Cabs are expensive in San Juan and based on zone. A 4 minute cab to old san juan is 11 dollars and Condanado is 15 ( I walked to Condanado in about 10 minutes) and don't even bother going to Isla Verde for 19 dollars. I had access to the Executive Lounge which was great. I recommend going to the lounge on floor 9 of the main building instead of going to the lounge in the Hhonors tower. They have fridges full of water and all types of pop that are free all day. I took the drinks and put them in the fridge that is in the room. I wasn't with little kids, but it is a fantastic hotel for kids. Plenty of shallow water in the pool area and the beach is protected by rocks, which limits the high waves that most of san juan sees. The beach is fantastic, not many waves, but a nice little stretch (especially compared to other hotels in San Juan). The rooms are a little above standard, but not extremely fancy. I went to the Old San Juan Hotel and Ritz and was not impressed. Those hotels are for people who want to tell people that I stayed at the Ritz or I stayed at the InterContinental. Lunch by the pool and drinks are expensive, but what do you expect, its a hilton not a Motel 6. I am not a little kid, but the coolest thing at the hotel is the fish feeding pier. They give you bread to throw in the ocean, and you get to see many different types of fish (size and color) without having to go snorkeling or scuba diving. I did not use the spa, but it did look nice (but expensive...what do you expect). The workout facility in the Spa (which if free for guests) is fantastic and overlooks the ocean. So the moral of the story...don't believe the bad reviews and if you get a good rate don't hesitate to book it. The hotel doesn't have a casino, but the candanado hotel which is about a 10 minute walk and the Marriot which is about 15 minute walk have casinos (I'd go to the Marriott...I won Big). Keep in mind this is San Juan not Las Vegas. A couple restaurants that I definitely recommend: Parrot Club (Old San Juan/Local Cuisine/Average entree 20-30), Dragon Fly (Old San Juan/Fusion between Asian and Latino Cuisine). I could write another couple pages, but I hope you get the point. This property is fantastic...if you get a good rate book it and don't worry about the bad reviews. Keep in mind most people only review a hotel when they have a great time or a terrible experience. As you could tell, I had a great time and can't wait to go back.P.S. Don't freak out about the weather forecast before you go. I checked weather.com and it said rain for the whole week I was down there and it was sunny 99% of the time. I think they just predict rain at 50% everyday so they wont be wrong.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>