<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="09e2d3179254d02b9648b2b49f5d1dc5" url=""><![CDATA[Very nice resort experience My husband and I try to get to Hawaii at least once a year and we had not been to Oahu for awhile and decided to try the Hilton Hawaiian Village Resort. It is a huge sprawling complex of different towers that have (I'm told) around 3400 rooms. So this is not some little Mom Pop hotel. We were booked into the Rainbow tower with an oceanview with a king sized bed. However, the desk clerk told me when checking in that the room had a decent view but was overlooking all the construction going on and asked if we would mind moving to an ocean/Diamondhead view with double beds instead of a king sized bed. We agreed and were very happy. The view was awesome. We could see the ocean, Diamondhead, the beach, etc. This resort has numerous restaurants and shops all throughout the resort. Too many to name or attempt to name here. I looked at prices and felt many were high (of course everything is expensive in Hawaii) so we did not eat on property except for one morning we had breakfast in the New York Deli there. It was good and the portions huge. We did not finish there was so much food!!! I felt considering how much food was given the price was reasonable.There are many high end retail stores in the resort and also an ABC Store (for those of you not having been to Hawaii, these small stores are scattered throughout Hawaii and offer food, drink, medication, tee-shirts, souvenirs, etc at reasonable prices) which was very nice to have there. You can purchase your own beer, soda pop, candy, chips etc. So that was nice to have onsite. If one wanted to youwould never have to leave the resort as restaurants, shopping, swimming, the beach is all right there. There are several pools, bars, etc. scattered throughout the property. My husband and I are not ones to lie in the sun next to a swimming pool, but for those who want to do that, the pools looked clean and well maintained. Of course where ever there is a swimming pool, there are lots of kids. While I don't have small children, the resort seemed family friendly.They have a spa onsite and I went one evening and had a massage which was excellent. The spa was beautifully appointed and very relaxing. I recommend if you are staying there and have the time to work in a spa treatment. I think you will find it worth it.The staff at this resort were all very nice and helpful to my husband and I. We enjoyed our stay here very much and hope to go again. Again, the only thing I would caution against is if you want to go to Hawaii to get away from people, this would not be the place for you. It is a very busy, popular resort.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2d66d74ea5e56b05215f332d9659ba29" url=""><![CDATA[Overall nice experience My husband and I recently were in NOLA for a business convention and stayed at this Marriott property for 3 days. This hotel is in downtown New Orleans and is within a few blocks of The French Quarter. I liked the fact that it was within walking distance of pretty much everything we wanted to see and do, yet not right on Bourbon Street where all the music and people partying stay.There is shopping and restaurants galore nearby, some high end shops such as Saks Fifth Avenue were a couple of blocks down on Canal Street and of course just a few blocks from The French Quarter, so there is plenty to eat, drink and shop nearby. The location of this hotel was perfect for us.The room we had was nothing special, not bad at all, just nothing to knock you out. Typical Marriott hotel room. We were on the 28th floor and there was a nice view of Canal street, the downtown area and further down, the Mississippi River. The housekeeping staff did a good job of keeping the room clean and well appointed. This is a large hotel, and others on this site have commented about how well the elevators work to serve the towers. Personally we had several bad experiences waiting and waiting and waiting for the elevators. To be fair however, there was a huge convention going on and the lobby was packed night and day, maybe if it weren't so busy there wouldn't be this problem, but it was a bit of a hassle waiting upwards of 10 minutes for an elevator, and I am not exaggerating, that is how long I waited at one point.There is a Starbucks in the lobby and also a restaurant (which we did not eat at). Also, there is a bar in the lobby that was consistently crowded with people attending the convention. You can get sushi and appetizers here. The service at the desk (check in, concierge, bellman, etc) were all very nice and pleasant. The service in the lobby bar was terrible I have to say. Drinks were not refilled and servers were no where to be found. Maybe since Katrina they are having trouble staffing? I don't know, but that was a little annoying. Here are all these people with an open tab at the bar, ready, willing and able to spend MONEY and no one was around to take orders. Kind of not a good business move, but overall everyone else we encountered at this hotel went out of their way to help and make our stay enjoyable.I would recommend this hotel to anyone wanting to stay near the French Quarter in NOLA and if I ever return there I'm sure I would stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3c45f1161e38cb9afe58efedfedbdce1" url=""><![CDATA[Very happy with this hotel I don't understand the negative reviews on this site---we had great service while we stayed there. We were upgraded to a nicer room for free, the staff were all friendly and helpful, the concierge was very nice. The rooms are not extravagant, but very clean and well appointed. We had a room with a partial mountain (Diamond Head) and partial oceanview. The only thing I wish would be improved is the restaurants, expensive and food only okay. Also, the entertainment in the bar ended way too early at only 9:00 pm or so. Otherwise this is a very nice hotel, that is close to the heart of Waikiki. I would stay there again and recommend it to anyone.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5a9f87252b70fcfcf7faae9b5bd648f3" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful hotel This is a very lovely hotel in Barcelona. It was truly one of the nicest hotel rooms I have ever stayed in, and I have traveled all over the world. The room was spotlessly clean with beautiful hardwood floors and very contemporary, modern furniture including flat screen tv's etc. This is not some outdated hotel. My husband is a Hilton rewards member so we were able to go to the executive lounge for drinks, tapas, snacks and it was delicious and well presented. We did not eat in the restaurant there, choosing to go to a restaurant across the street in the mall so I cannot comment on the food served other than in the executive lounge. We did have drinks in the lobby bar and that was great. Everyone we spoke to were very nice and helpful and spoke great English which was helpful. We only stayed 1 night as we were on layover from a cruise, so we didn't have a chance to explore much of Barcelona, but I could tell this was a little off the beaten track, not right in the heart of things, but there was a nice mall right across the street with several restaurants that was nice. I would love to return to Barcelona someday and explore it further, and I would not hesitate to stay at this wonderful hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>