<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="3d6237ffbaea1b77ce0bde3a4bb59d00" url=""><![CDATA[Central and Easy-Going We stayed 4 nights in this hotel. 3 nights first, then returned for an extra night after visiting other cities. (Both stays were on weekends) We easily booked the rooms on the website - the only hotel in Spain where we were able to successfully do so on this trip. That alone makes the trip so much easier. We expected it to be like the Standard Hotel in the US in terms of service, efficiency, and hipness. It turned out to be quite true - except that it's a smaller hotel. But thank god no one sipping cocktails at the lobby, a party hotel in a party town would be too much.Room is small but not cramped, since bed is installed at an angle (hard to explain) which maximizes the space. No bathtub (we won't soak in hotel bathtubs anyway), and the shower is built in a way that the water will definitely get the outside floor soaking wet (unfortunate for the ones who does room cleaning).We stayed in one room facing Calle del Prado which we preferred (very cute and old Madrid, facing residences with their screened doored balcony), and another room facing the more bustling Calle del Principe (main thoroughfare for bar-hoppers) which we didn't like as much as it was also on a lower floor. From the floor plan it seemed there are some rooms that don't have outer street views. I will definitely ask for one that does.Floor to ceiling double windows (you cannot open the outer ones though, but they provide much needed sound proofing) with vertical blinds give stretegic view of all the action on Plaza Santa Ana (with tons of restaurants and a great site to see waking up, though we avoided them since they look touristy to us). We easily walked to Chueca, Lavapies, La Latina, Thyssen-Bornemisza, Prado, etc. and never took a taxi or metro (note: we live in New York and do walk a lot) on our entire stay in Madrid except to and from airport and Atocha train station to our next city.A couple of problems. We did have to request new soap after our first night there (being Aug in Madrid for 2, it is essential. Regardless, if the soap is out, we expect it to be replaced). On our last night there, we found during check-in that the safe is busted (the numerical pad is gone and safe is not usable). We wished we were told about it before taking the room. We informed reception (but really was politely confronting) and he only confirmed that it's true it's broken but didn't give an explanation about whether someone forgot their # or someone got their stuff stolen. I think it would have helped if they explained to make visitors feel at ease.Breakfast was okay - not revelatory. We ate much much better outside of the hotel and only ate there the mornings of checkouts, since it's silly to not explore such a great culinary city.We don't know if we will stay there again, because we do like to try new places. But I would not dissuade anyone from staying there.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>