<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="9cb55df020a7443cc1b6ffd862006a58" url=""><![CDATA[Great Place -- Great Value We stayed at this resort 8/31 - 9/7. We enjoyed our experience very much. I was a little concerned due to some poor reviews -- but that certainly was not our experience. We booked through USA3000 vacations and for $75 more pp, had the VIP Suite upgrade -- well worth it, I feel. Our room was on the 3rd floor (no elevators), but directly overlooked the beach -- very lovely. It was large -- with a nice sitting area and balcony. The room was clean and well appointed. Several reviews stated that they had to get to shaded chairs by 6 am -- I find that hard to believe! We never had problems getting a shaded chair (the ones around the pool with the bar filled quickly, but there are two other very large, and quieter, pools where we never had a problem). In addition, most shaded chairs on the beach were empty. The resort was only about half full, so this could have been the difference -- but even full, there appeared to be ample shaded chairs. There were 5 speciality restaurants and a buffet. In addition, there were two premium restaurants -- La Cava and El Pescador, which required a $25 pp fee. We had one option apiece for these with the VIP package, and it was good (La Cava), but I would not pay $25 extra pp. You needed reservations for the other 5 restaurants, but a concierage was available in the buildings all day, and we had no problem booking. The food was good and varied. We really enjoyed the Dominican restaurant -- typical Dominican food. We enjoyed a complimentary 20 minute back massage on the beach (part of the VIP package) and since I was a certified diver, had a complimentary dive with the VIP. The grounds are spacious and well kept, the staff very friendly and accomodating. There is a shuttle bus to and from the main building from the room buildings, but we always walked. We did not go to the shows -- they didn't start until 9:45 pm and we preferred sitting on our balcony and listening to the surf. This was a great time to go (albeit the threat of hurricanes) -- the weather was great and far less crowds. We did three off site tours: the Marinarium (swimming with nurse sharks and rays), Outback Safari (an all day journey to the rural area of the DR), and an on the beach horseback ride. All were good and worthwhile. All and all, I feel this is a good choice and great value.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="234d7099903f62e7e4032c3302c026ff" url=""><![CDATA[Great value and location This is a great find in Barcelona for reasonable lodging in a nice, quiet neighborhood 1 block from the metro. It is a small, family run hotel -- clean well apointed rooms -- including a small kitchenette. The bathroom even has washclothes and an electrical outlet for curling irons (a rarity in Europe!). The staff were very accomodating and all spoke English. There was free internet access in the lobby. The cost (August, 2005) was 80 Euros per night, including all taxes.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8f9b1b032dddf280cb57b3c50ddcc8e6" url=""><![CDATA[Great Resort -- Great Time! We stayed at the RIU Palace Punta Cana from December 12 2008. What a lovely resort many amenities. Our room was a large, including a bathroom with Jacuzzi bathtub, sitting area with sofa and TV (even FOX News!), and nice balcony. There was a minibar stocked with beer and softdrinks and liquor dispensers with brandy, vodka, gin, and rum. sure you could have asked for a substitute if desired, but we did not. Tap water is not potable, but we were given gallon size jugs of purified water. Water and ice in all the restaurants and bars is fine. My only concern was the self-service ice machines which had no scoop reported this to the front desk (not exactly sanitary to use hands!), but it never changed. I just went to the bar near the ice machine and then filled the ice bucket a scoop! There were five alternate restaurants went to all except the Japanese. All were good and each was a uniquely different venue. You need a reservation for these can make them between 8 am and noon earlier is definitely the rule if you want a particular restaurant and time (6:30 or 9:00 pm choices). I went between 8 and 8:30 and got our requests. The grounds are immaculate, very spacious, and truly beautiful. The beach is spectacular as well and lots of lounges and trees, if shade is desired. The swimming pool is very large, clean, and well maintained. A large, swim-up beach bar is also there with prompt service. The rooms were very clean and maintained that way. We read about problems with musty odors, but did not experience that. We had brought a room deodorizer, but did not need it at all. We did give our maid $2 daily know if that makes a difference, but she did such a good job and the $2 to her certainly meant more than to me is a very poor country. All the staff were very polite and accommodating. We had been to Punta Cana about 15 months before resort, and therefore had done some of the off property activities. I would recommend the Outback Safari goes into the mountain region and gives you a chance to see more of the countryside. The other good trip is to the Marinarium great marine park with an opportunity to swim with nurse sharks and rays. All and all, it was a great trip do like the RIU properties, but the is definitely the most elegant and has the most amenities.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>