<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="8a8ee4eb03e09d9fd616be4099c56985" url=""><![CDATA[A Good Time I have never been the one to write a review, but I feel unfair that this hotel is getting such bad reviews. This hotel in on great property and is situated on a gorgeous beach. The swimming pools are amazing. There is one pool which is livelier and plays music, has entertainment and has the swim-up bar. The other pool is very relaxing with built in loungers to lye down on and spraying water, both pools are very big. The water playground makes me wish I was a kid all over again, very cool for families. The food at the Italian, Dominican, and Japanese restaurants was amazing! The buffet food was okay. Defiantly check out the Tex Mex restaurant for lunch if you are looking for a sit down, relaxing lunch near the beach. Yes, this hotel did have some problems but what do you expect when you staying at a 6++ (And trust me things do go wrong at ANY hotel you stay at). I am a very experienced traveler so in comparison to the many other resorts I stayed at which were mostly all 5+ hotels, this hotel did very good! Some of the negative aspects of this hotel include: our room was clearly one of the older rooms, but it was kept very clean and we were never in it anyways. And if I had to search for another negative the nightclub did stink like vomit. The worst part of this hotel was the service. Unfortunately the service was the worst I have seen out of any resort I have stayed at. Not the typical and you would expect to interact with at a hotel. It seemed as if most people care if you handed them a tip (some never even said thank you or smiled) yet, other people at the resort had no problems and found the service to be very good. The wait to get a drink at the lobby is out of control. They defiantly need stronger management. But overall, the hotel was very nice and we met some really cool people and had an awesome time! Defiantly if people need to rely on a 100% perfect hotel, this is not your hotel. This hotel is for people who want to have fun, have patience, and make the best with the people they are with! I went on this vacation with my boyfriend and we are in our twenties and it was perfect for us.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>