<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="096274a1f1ef81fa3ec2c491346876f5" url=""><![CDATA[disappointed Like a previous reviewer, we expected our 2 night stay at the Singapore Shangri La to be one of the highlights of our Singapore / Vietnam / Bintan trip. But like that person, we too were disappointed. In 2006 we stayed at the Shangri La , Sydney, on a Horizon Club deal. This was excellent value for money, superb room, great complimentary evening snacks and drinks etc.So we booked the same deal in Singapore. Room was fine, but no better than any other Singapore 4 or 5 star hotel. Bathroom did not have a separate shower, just curtain round bath. We queried whether we were actually in a Horizon room, and were told that it recently been upgraded to Horizon Status . Other than notepaper with Horizon Club heading, we could see any extra advantages.The complimentary evening snacks were very average, and there were long waits while the empty dishes were replenished. Although the first drinks were brought quickly, the service became markedly slower after that. Eventually my husband tired of waiting for a drink that never came , so we left.Although the hotel has a lovely pool and beautiful gardens, we felt that we had paid over the odds for what we got. We would happily return to the Sydney Shangri La, but not to the Singapore hotel.On our return through Singapore we stayed at the Intercontinental on Middle Rd. Much better value, and better room and breakfast buffet
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c2599e2c501ecb42133000d754315f15" url=""><![CDATA[the gallo is great Have just spent three nights at San Gallo Palace hotel and would definitely reccomend it. The room was of typical city hotel size, and the bathroom very well appointed. We had standard room no. 101, which happened to have a terrace over the bar area, a good room to request.Despite being close to a busy traffic roundabout, there was no problem with noise.Yes, the hotel is a little distance from main attractions, but we enjoyed the walk, ( we are reasonably fit fifty somethings ), and never used buses or taxis. On our first night we walked to the Oltrano district, across the river, and had a very good meal at the Osteria San Spirito in Piazza San Spirito.The other two nights we ate at trattorias reccommended by the hotel reception staff, and were very pleased with both reccommendations. The first was Alfredo's, very close to the hotel, and the other was Accademia, just a little further away. Had delicious food at both.All the hotel staff were very pleasant and helpful. Would definitely stay here again.P.A. Wrexham, Wales
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>