<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="877112dd12673dc76672f14a2b111b19" url=""><![CDATA[Bali Hyatt - we loved it Me and my boyfriend together with friends (2 adults + 2children) spent 10days in Bali this June , 6 nights at Bali Hyatt and 4 nights at Nusa Dua Beach Hotel and we were very pleased.I would say rooms at Bali Hyatt (we stayed in the ordinary oceanviewrooms, our friends had 2 rooms with a connecting door ) are good 4 star standard, nicely furnished, a good-size balcony but the bathrooms even though charming in a way are a bit dated BUT the servicelevel and the friendliness of the staff was the very best ! There was lots of staff, when having breakfast for example there was always someone close by to pick-up the empty plate or to bring extra coffee or whatever you required. Always a smile and questions about how you were doing etc. They really made us feel at home from day1.The beach is nice BUT there is lots of seaweed in the water which makes it difficult to swim at low tide. The hotel has 2 pools, both very nice.Apart from breakfast we had just one lunch and one dinner at the hotel. The food and service was excellent but a bit expensive. There is a good choice of restaurants and shops in the Sanur area and if You want to go somewhere else fo shopping food Kuta is only about 30 minutes away and transportation is easy to find and cheap - we paid about IDR70.000 one-way for a big car (room enough for the 6 of us).One night we went to Jimbaran for seafood; food was excellent and it was a lovely experience to sit directly on the beach and have dinner. The smoke from the restaurants was a bit annoying however. All and all we were very happy with our stay at the Bali Hyatt, Sanur and if I come back I would definitely stay there again
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8de82299efe9edb3a75e6cb895339011" url=""><![CDATA[great facilities Travelled to Bali in June 2007 with my boyfriend + friends of us (a family with 2 children aged 8+14years)I actually stayed of couple of nights at Nusa Dua Beach HotelSpa already 7 or 8years ago but not on holidays..After 6 nights at Bali Hyatt, Sanur we moved to Nusa Dua Beach Hotel.Everything about the hotel met my expectations. Me my boyfriend stayed in a deluxe room and our friends stayed in a superior room for 4. The hotel was nice enough to give us rooms with poolseaview. If just looking for a room for 2 people it is definitely worth the pricedifference to stay in deluxe instead of superiorroom. The bathroom of the deluxeroom is so much better - both shower and tub and open shutters so You get a view of bedroom and even a bit beyond. Beach is very nice but again seaweed in water makes swimming a bit difficult. The 2 pools are very nice. The table tennis and snooker table was much appreciated by everyone in our company. Brekafast was plentiful. Apart from breakfast the only meal we had at hotel was one lunch- pizza and it was OK but too expensive! Service was good as expected at 5star hotel BUT not more - I did not feel the same personal touch as I did at Bali Hyatt. Our friends and especially the children however liked it more at Nusa Dua - more things happening around the hotel area!If You do not want to have all Your meals at the hotel there are some restauarants( and also shops) right outside the gate into Nusa Dua area, it takes about 10minutes to walk (and if You do not want to walk all restaurants have transportation)
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>