<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="966738f70357ac315d641a8c3b6f7cb2" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent service, great room I was really impressed with the attitude of the bellhop and valet as we arrived. They were so friendly and full of information. We had a lovely big room with very spacious bathroom. Only a few blocks walk to Chinatown where we had dinner and then walked on to North Beach for drinks. We love San Francisco and prefer this location to Union Square.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8eed3dcc7bd3a007acb57278adfb95da" url=""><![CDATA[superlative service and room! THE most comfortable bed I've ever slept in! Also, huge tub in the bathroom and separate power shower, Frette bathrobes. Jasmin tea and cookies delivered to room upon arrival, chocolate strawberries and biscuits for our honeymoon. Lovely view of bridge. Very knowledgeable concierge.We did feel slightly untidy though walking through the lobby on Saturday evening, returning after a day's sightseeing as the ambiance is quite formal! Perhaps not the best location for sightseeing but handy for Chinatown and we like to walk anyway.We loved it here though and were given booklets about Carmel as we checked-out when we mentioned that we were driving down the coast. A nice touch!SF is a great city. All the tourist attractions are really worthwhile doing and the city has an energy simialr to NYC but not quite so frantic! Loved it!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="482f4aa6a1487a5bdd6cd1cdf6fca827" url=""><![CDATA[Disappointing Firstly our room was really shabby and I couldn't believe it was a Westin hotel. We could hear our neighbor on the telephone for hours, the walls obviously paper thin. The bathroom was very small and generally our room had nothing going for it other than the view of the Christmas tree in Union Square.I also thought the security was lax as there are several entrances into the hotel which lead to elevators and it would be easy for someone to wander in.We were woken by housekeeping at 8am as there was no Do not disturb sign. Also the Housekeeping closet was just along the hallway and the staff chatted loudly for quite a while, spoiling our lie-in.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>