<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="bd93460d703734eb45d1504cc05c450e" url=""><![CDATA[Quiet, Clean, Great Value -Best Little Motel in SF! The Castle Inn is our favorite small hotel in San Francisco! We have stayed there on 2 occasions the wonderful staff, convenient location, clean, quiet rooms keep us coming back! Located at Broadway Van Ness, Castle Inn is in a nice neighborhood with drug store, grocery, cafes cute shops within close walking distance. It's also right on the bus line is a straight shot down to Fisherman's Wharf. My dad I stayed for 4 quiet comfortable nights. We rented a car on our previous trip, but found that with a little planning, getting around on the bus was an easier less costly option. The Castle Inn does offer free parking though, which is a real bonus in SF! Parking throughout SF is difficult, pricey hard to find. For this trip, we purchased 3-day Muni Passes at the airport when we arrived, used those to travel the city on busses cable cars - a good value if you don't mind the challenges of riding city busses! Make sure you get a bus route map when you purchase your Muni Passes!Rooms at the Castle are clean comfortable - not fancy or large, but decent reasonably priced compared to many SF hotels. Our 2-bed room had a hairdryer, small fridge, coffee maker, free cable tv table with 2 large chairs. Our 3rd floor room overlooked a lovely yard of trees next door we could just see a bit of the Golden Gate Bridge in the distance. There is a nice little continental breakfast (coffee, cocoa, yogurt, fruit, pastries, granola bars) in the lobby. The best feature of the Castle Inn is our favorite hostess, Versa! She is always so pleasant, accomodating knowledgeable with good advice about the city. They also gave us a chart showing busses/stop locations to go to various tourist locations throughout the city. Castle Inn also has a nice website worth checking out.If you want a clean, decent room to sleep in at night a hot shower in the morning without a lot of pricey luxury, the Castle Inn is a little gem of a motel in a convenient location to get to the tourist attractions easily. I have will continue to recommend San Francisco's Castle Inn to anyone considering a trip to the City by the Bay!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>