<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="1b37ddd7a8e177c483ef58b4883656ba" url=""><![CDATA[Nothing spectacular This was my first time in the DR and my first time doing an all inclusive in years. First let me say I had a renovated room right near the lobby and the room was great. My advise, request a renovated room PRIOR to yoru departure. The hotel grounds were beautiful, the beach was clean and the staff was very very helpful.....As for the food....you will get sick of it after a while. I was there for 5 nights. The Gourmet restuarant was far from gourmet...but the food was tolerable/average. No one I traveled with got sick. If you want more action, then I would stay at the Domicana. Thats where the casino is and its pretty lively there at night. The bavaro is pretty dead. We went to the small casino every night and had a good time. The drinks were pretty terrible. Only 1 beer to choose from and sometimes when I ordered a frozen drink it came w/ ice. But what do you expect for the price i paid for this trip through apple vacation? The trip from airport to hotel was terrible, way over an hour on bumpy roads. Listen, for the price it was a really nice vacation. Would I go back? No but that doesnt mean I wouldnt recommend it for someone looking for a nice relaxing cheap vacation as long as you dont care about fine dining.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a353eb8d1b55af808e91571821dc4cf8" url=""><![CDATA[Just okay We had come for a wedding and got a decent rate of 185 a night. Puerto Rico in general if you stay in San Juan I dont think is a very luxurious vacation. The water is not crystal clear blue and the sand is not white like some other islands in the carribean. The drinks were priced outrageously. Lunch for 2 was 50 bucks a day. They were doing construction on the elevators so be prepared to wait. The restaurants are nothing special. There is a japanese restaurant that is very casual and small and as for Ruth Chris, you can eat that any time in the States. The pool area is clean and pretty. The service is pretty good. Its close to the El San Juan which is where I recommend going to at night. Its right next door and is a fun place to hang w/a large casino, shops and good eats. There are tons of airline staff staying here and business people which is who i think they cater to. Overall, it was not a bad stay just nothing special. I would recommend the EL san juan next door which or a different island altogether. And bring bug spray. I got bit up really bad on the beach.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>