<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="bd66473056387ef1b06abcacbde65c47" url=""><![CDATA[Loved the Sofitel We stayed here in August, peak season and had a wonderful time. Initially booked 4 nights stayed another 3 and came back for our last night after a tript o Ubud for a few days. Checkin was welcoming, room was fine....a bit dark but not spending much time here anyway. Staff were friendly and very welcoming and requests for ice/extra towels etc were always speedy. Loved the pool, had a problem with the sunbeds being reserved early in the morning (not just the best ones!) and at 10am there were 42 saved beds with towels and no people and nowhere to sit. This was dealt with by pool staff and later by Leisure manager who was apologetic!Can't agree with the comments re the buffet. Maybe the buffet is different during peak summer months but I have never had a better buffet. There was a huge range of fresh fruits, dried fruits, crystalised fruit, poached fruit, muesli, cereals, seeds, nuts, homemade yoghurt. Then there were freshly baked breads, the best croissants I have had outside France, pastries, cake, cheeses, cold meats, lots of Asian hot food and Yes you only got one freshly squeezed juice included but there was endless 'non freshly squeezed' on the buffet. The coffee was excellent, freshly made espresso coffee, unlike a lot of breakfast buffets where you get lukewarm filter coffee. The separate cooked breakfast a-la-carte menu meant you could have eggs, french toast, bacon etc freshly cooked to order insted of the usual overcooked buffet style. If this buffet changes off season, I will find out as we are returning in May!All in all, I would highly recommend the Sofitel as a great international style hotel, not particularly Balinese in style but beautiful gardens and great relaxing pool.The restaurants were relatively expensive compared to local eateries but great food especially in the Thai restaurant.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>