<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="0723ce9d8a3fdd884393c96529156aab" url=""><![CDATA[Friendly Service. Just back from 3 days in Hong Kong, our first visit, 2 parents and 3 adult children, booked through Trailfinders. Lots of positives about the Ciy Garden Hotel although we really only slept there.When we arrived at the Airport late at night I went to the nearest limo desk to ask for a transfer, the helpful girl (all HK staff we met were helpful) suggested we go to City Gardens own desk at the airport for advice, about 50m from the arrivals exit. There he explained all the options for transfer, the speed and cost of each one, when we opted to use Airport Express he explained where to buy the tickets to get the discount for buying 5 at once.At the Hotel as others have said, very friendly and helpful staff, fast check in, during the stay dealt with our only problem immediately. 6.00 pm checkout an unexpected bonus as we were flying late at night and when we checked out at 6.00 pm and asked for 2 taxis back to Airport Express station they suggested we go on their free shuttle instead which was about to leave for the station.We bought their buffet breakfast as it was good value, high quality, and excellent service, but otherwise didn't use their restaurants as we were out all day. Local supermarket if needed.We were put on the 16th floor, I've no experience of other HK hotels but it does seem that space is at a premium in HK so I would say the rooms were fine for space. It was a bit of a squeeze to get 2 single beds and a rollup in the childrens room but plenty of room around our double bed. Shower over bath rather that separate. Clean and very attentive housekeeping.It is located in North Point area on Hong Kong Island, away from absolute centre of activity in Central, but very close to Fortress Hill MTR, tram and on main bus routes. As the public transport system is so efficient, easy to use (I recommend an Octopus card) and air conditioned, location is not a problem unless you particularly wanted to walk and only visit one part of the city. It was so hot and humid in July that we often dived for the MTR or a bus just to cool off and to travel a distance that we would have normally walked.I would recommend City Garden Hotel to others.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>