<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="fb79bbe34e0e03a011c764e80c266df0" url=""><![CDATA[A pleasant surprise I never write reviews, although I do pay attention to them. I read a lot of bad reviews before going to Paradisus this March and was a bit nervous. I'm happy to report that after a week with my husband and 2 grown sons, we all had a wonderful experience. Check-in was a breeze. We took our luggage to our room so delivery of baggage wasn't an issue. We had Royale Service, which I highly recommend. The room (ocean view) was very nice, clean and well appointed. Maid service was excellent .The Royale Service pool was fabulous. We reserved a private palapa each day with no problem. The bartenders and attendants were extremely efficient and friendly. (When a gentleman dropped a piece of fruit poolside a nearby bartender quickly picked it up, washed it, and returned it to the man's lounge chair. ) Our private butler introduced himself to us the first day. And although we never used his services, he saw my husband 3 days later and spoke to him by name! (very impressive)The grounds are beautiful and extremely well kept up and clean. No surprise....the beach was not great - can't really walk it or swim. But the kayaking was fun.We didn't expect gourmet food and didn't get it. (This is the reason I'm not giving this resort a 5* rating) The breakfast and lunch buffets were terrific (But avoid the Mirador Grill - ugh! opt for the Carribean instead) Romantico is over rated. We enjoyed Avocado and Tuscano better. Bamboo is your typical hibachi place.(Avocado has great beef) Overall we found that the beef was much better than the fish -fine for my sons but my husband and I prefer seafood. The snacks that were always set up in the Royale Service Lounge were great.There was a problem with a restaurant booking one night. When the RS manager called to explain we couldn't get the time we reserved at our chosen restaurant, we didn't make a big deal about it. He quickly got us a table at another restaurant. Fifteen minutes later he, along with a waiter, arrived at our room with a bottle of wine and a plate of hors d'oeuvres to make ammends for the mistake. Now that's great PR!!! I cannot stress the cleanliness enough - everywhere! Especially the bathrooms. EVERYONE (maids, shuttle drivers, bartenders, waitstaff, gardeners, watersports staff, etc. etc) was extremely warm and friendly, and always quick to greet us.Certainly everyone cannot expect to have as good an experience as we had. But I do recommend it highly and hope that some people will take advantage of this great all-inclusive resort before it no longer is all-inclusive as of May 1.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>