<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="3b6ec89a5d43a203c93124ec1634a29b" url=""><![CDATA[Hotel National Not What We Hoped This hotel is not accurately represented on their website. The room was dirty carpets, dusty, but bathroom was clean. They said they had AC but only a desktop fan. I tried my best to communicate with staff in German, but some English had to be spoken. They were very rude once they relized we were Americans. Positive--the inclusive Buffet was AWESOME in the morning. Also, location being across from subway station was convenient, but confusing for a new tourist.Bottom line: The resort talks itself up to be better than it is. My suggestion in to go next door to Hotel Color. The area was so-so, but not a good place if you have children/teenagers.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d8449181b6120f2a09f5ee6e3b9a9d15" url=""><![CDATA[An American in Germany Radisson SAS is a unique find in Europe. It gives you the feel of American travel, so if it is your first time in Frankfurt and you don't speak German, this is a good place to stay. All staff is very internationally acommodating. The building is top of the line eco friendly.Rooms are 5 STAR. All modern, new construction. Eco friendly. Even glass in shower with speakers so you can watch tv while you shower.Bar/Restaurant with patio deck and lobby is 5 STAR. very modern and hip.Staff was 5+ STAR.Pool and Sauna etc area was 5 STAR. the pool overlooks the city on the top floor. it is a small pool, but a neat location. all facilities were clean and chic.The negatives--refridgerator in room doesn't let you store your own items. it has a laser sensor and will charge you thinking you are taking beverages from it.Room keys were needed to ride elevator, but we had to have our keys reset 2 times during stay.Location was not the best if you are there for leisure visit to Frankfurt. Business travelers will find this a good location.HOWEVER, Frankfurt has an incredible subway system, so getting around from there was ok.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>