<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="e7e418ab0b5843749a6bd2eed747f9bd" url=""><![CDATA[I wish there was a Hotel Europa everywhere... Dante Suite - please excuse our stuff (we were just so excited about the room!)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1459638ed8b008634a7a15c00c4a66b7" url=""><![CDATA[Upgrade to the villas - trust me The Sofitel Seminyak is located at the end of a great restaurant strip in Seminyak. The hotel has direct access to the beach - unlike some Legian and Kuta hotels which have a road between the hotel and beach.The hotel grounds are massive with divine private villas, the typical hotel room spread, lovely gardens and ponds. There are two pools - one big one that overlooks the beach, and a smaller private one in the gardens. There are heaps of sun lounges, with waiters coming around periodically to provide drinks, cool towels and fruit kebabs - yum!I stayed in a 'Superior' room and wish I had spent the money for a villa. The room itself was huge - the biggest hotel room I've been in, and it had nice views, but doesn't compare to a villa. The room had a mini-bar, safe, big TV, balcony and outdoor setting. The king size bed was sensational. The bathroom was marble, but the paint a little chipped and made the bathroom look a bit tired.Unusually, the bathroom only had one towel (king size) per person - not the usual two towels. Also, no face washers. But, good amenities (hair brush, toothbrushes, bubble bath, shampoo conditioner, lotion).Breakfast was average. Sure - lots of fruit and asian dishes. but I've travelled quite a bit to lots of 5 star hotels and am used to having direct access to the chef and watching them cook a hot breakfast. Eventually, I just had fruit salad every breakfast.Seminyak is the BEST location for restaurants - they are really outstanding here. I recommend 'Bennys Bistro', just up the road. Not glamorous, but great food at good prices. And eating outside is nice. Also recommend 'Studio 5'. This is a sensational place - 5 star quality food at rediculous prices. I had a four course meal for what turned out to be AUD$8!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="955f99074dc514cc52d475f5f1e38825" url=""><![CDATA[Great location and great for the price (comparitively) Stayed for three nights and loved every minute.We actually booked a standard room with 2 double beds and was not expecting much at all. When checking in we were advised that we'd been upgraded to a pool view room with king bed.We had room 712 and it was fabulous - great view of the pool, the Moana Surfrider across the street and also some ocean view. The room was tastefully decorated and updated - had the most comfortable (king) bed I've ever slept in. Was like sleeping on a cloud. The room also had a small 2 seater couch, desk, wardrobe with iron and safe (at a charge!), TV and large mini fridge.The bathroom was smallish but lots of towels and shower over bath. The shower had good pressure but when filling the bath the water didn't seem to get hot enough.The lanai had two chairs and a table, which was great to sit out on at night and listen to the music playing from the pool side.We were actually staying as part of our honeymoon, and returning to our room on the second day we had a lovely bottle of sparkling wine waiting for us, which was really nice and thoughtful.The pool is a good size and there are lots of lounge chairs to sit on. The strange thing is that the pool is incredibly deep - starts at a meter and then goes to almost 2 meters deep. the water was over my head after leaving one end of the pool by a meter or so. In otherwords, watch your kids - there is no kids pool either.Lobby was huge and lots of internet stations. The concierge can give you a great little bus route map and the travel desk always seemed busy and not very helpful.Front desk people were always really nice. Checking out was very quick.One thing I would fault is that the in room safe is charged at $3.25 per day! The location is superb - walking distance to anywhere and the bus stop to either the USS Arizona memorial or Hanauma Bay (or anywhere for that matter) is just around the corner.I really liked this hotel - i've stayed at the Moana Surfrider before, and also the Ohana West around the corner. For the room price and location, I was really impressed and would definetly stay again!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>