<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="8f17f37ff90c8011f6d3c570c8b6e762" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful experience We booked the Premier Grand Rooms, we were thinking about booking the corner room, but corner rooms can't add extra bed. We have a huge window with a very nice view of the Tokyo city. Room was nicely decorated, the room is pretty big comparing to other tokyo hotels. I love the bathroom, it was really nice. Service was wonderful too, the conceirge desk helped out a lot with the area info, book restaurants train tkts for us. We'll def. stay at MO next time when we're at Tokyo
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="78f05c61522fad419f4d8b755850d87c" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful location We had a truly wonderful stay at the Four Seasons Sayan. Though I love luxury life, I do not like worldwide chain resorts, so this is my first Four Seasons experience (which already ensures me that I will def. check other 4 Seasons next time !!)The location is perfect, it really gives you the wow factor once you entered the resort from the not-so-special winding roads. The resort seems to exist in another world with the peaceful lotus pond in the jungle. We find the architecture fascinating with all the rooms/villas down below the lotus pond.We were very lucky and got a generous offer for an upgrade to a two bedroom villa. The view is just breathtaking with the jungle around us and the ayung river right at our sight. (A staff told me that our villa got the best view!)Our villa is very spacious. Amenities and toiletries basically got everything you need. Rooms are clean and well appointed, I found our beds pretty comfy too. Our indoor pool is beautiful and allowed us to enjoy the view. Oh, and there's also an outdoor shower which is pretty fun.We were pretty satisfied with the service as well. Everyone was really friendly to us, and I didn't find them pretentious at all. We were greeted by staff members with smiles all the time, and they are also professional enough not to intrude us in any way.Spa is great (though pricey), do ask for treatments in spa villa though, the amenities and seclusion is a lot better than the main villa.Some minor comments would be on food. The food is good, but they are really pricey. We liked the food but we just don't think it's worth that price (especially in Ubud). Like other members suggested, I also highly recommend Mozaic restaurant. The food is much better and the price is less.I also wished that the hotel concierge did offer recommendation on activities upon our arrival.Overall, it was a really great experience staying at four seasons sayan, if I ever go back to Bali, I would definitely stay there again. I know a lot of people are deciding between Four Seasons Amankila, I also stayed at Amankila, check my review on Amankila if interested
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="beec6bbc5e0d65553478b9a1832e98dd" url=""><![CDATA[Best in HK We were on a winter getaway package, and this package can immediately upgrade your room the next level suite (Superior Suite)However, when we got the hotel, we were upgraded to a Deluxe Harborview Suite, which is like 3x better than the room we booked. It definitely hit us as a huge surprise (we went on a busy weekend)The suite is very spacious and I love the decor in our living area. Peninsula HK got its own original style different than the other hotels around Victoria harbor.The view in our suite is amazing, we enjoyed looking out to the window over the river in our bed at night. The jacuzzi in the bathroom has its own view too (not the river though)We only stayed for two nights, but we didn't get newspaper the 2nd day, and there was no turndown service, I was a bit surprisedThe afternoon tea in the hall is like night market, we didn't have the tea but was scared by what we saw....I think they should have some other area especially for the staying guestsI don't really like Gaddi's in Peninsula, the food is average though the service is top notch. I've heard some other restaurants are really good but didn't have the chance to try them allOverall, Peninsula is still the best place best location to stay in HK
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="05999306fc045ac9d5be2922d4cab5f5" url=""><![CDATA[Impeccable Service !! I've heard tons of compliments on Amanresorts, especially on how great their service is. When I thought I know what's to be expected, the Amankila experience definitely exceeds my expectation !!The Aman shuttles (yes, they sent two Toyotas for us!) picked us up Four Seasons (Four Seaons had no airport shuttle). We did feel the royal treatment with cold towers, drinks and snacks on the car. The driver was very friendly, and told us about different villages and Balinese tradition along the way.Upon arrival, we were warmly greeted by staff members. The hotel is stunning looking over the Lambok Strait, and the legendary three story pool area is gorgeous.Our room is nicely appointed, though I do wish they can provide more toiletries at that room price. The room hides all the ugly little details, but then it was tricky to find the plug-ins. I noticed other members talked about no bugs in the room, but it was a different story in ours. Our room had a lot of bugs, and it really annoyed me when I had to scream out of my shower when I saw a huge spider on the wall. Although we booked an ocean view room, it is basically no difference than the garden view room unless you spent a lot of time on your porch area. I don't know if it's just my room, but I couldn't even see the ocean in the room. I would recommend either book the garden view or just skip to the pool suite, 200 for a view on the porch is not necessary to me personally. Privacy is a big issue to me too. The room is not secluded enough to us, and we can actually see people walking around in their rooms. Sometimes I lay in my bed trying to relax, saw some gardeners walking by and had to jump up and close the windows (and I need to close the windows to use bathtubs as well)We also did the some of the highly recommended activities, including the private beach dinner, breakfast at the bale and morning cruise. The beach dinner is a truly romantic wonderful experience, but the food is just ok which is a bit depressing with the great service and sound of the wave around. I personally do not like the breakfast at the bale very much. Honestly, we did not like the food at all, and the view is just ok, very $$$ too. But the morning cruise is fun and worth a try (if you skip the food part, too)Service is impeccable from getting to the hotel until we're ready to leave Bali. You're being taken care of to the smallest details possible, and we were so surprised to get airport assistance right off the shuttle. And we can not thank much to the wonderful driver who rushed us to the airport that got us in time to catch our flight (his driving skill is really mouth-dropping!). Everyone at the resort is friendly, and special thanks to Hosaiyo (I hope I didn't spell wrong!), who is so friendly so helpful during our stay. But sometimes I found some staffs a bit too chatty when we just want to be left quiet. I know they're just trying to be friendly but it is a bit hard to understand their english and it got a little annoying and intruding somehow.Food, we can not comment. The chef is a nice person but we do not like the food at all. The spaghettis we ordered is so dry and so hard to digest....everything else is so blah....The menu is lack of variety as well with only Indonesian food and Western. With the price charged, we really expected something a lot better.The beach area and the rooms involve some walking, so be prepared. Private beach is secluded but the sand is black, a bit disappointing but we still enjoyed the view.Overall, the hotel itself and the service is excellent, but the food needs a lot of improvement. But that's just my two cents, since food always takes a huge part on my vacations. Would I go back again? Not sure, but I'm interested in visiting other Amanresorts. I doubt I will go back to Amankila soon until they improved their food. (otherwise excellent)
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>