<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="bd0b9b7c9f1d1dde56c64bd70de7c477" url=""><![CDATA[I need to forget this place!! Our Honeymoon had been going so well! We had been staying at some excellent hotels.........then we stayed at this hotel!From the time we walk in we hit probelm after problem. Where to start???1: The room was not ready when we arrived and we had to wait 15 minutes while they looked for something for us. This was at 3.30pm and the guaranteed check in time was 2pm!........No apology for the wait!2: We were informed the Club rooms were under some rennovations. This was ok but they put our room directly under the drilling. We were very tired from our early morning flight and could not rest. We were told the works would stop at 5pm. At 6.30pm i had to ask the Duty Manager to get them to stop the works........he thought they had gone home already!!......no apology for the disturbance!3: The in room internet did not work. We were told that sometime it does not work??? When we wnet downstairs to use their internet desk we were told we would need to pay $1.00 a minute! 24 hours of in room internet would have cost us $24.00!! We asked where the closest internet cafe because $1.00 a minute was the most i had ever experienced and were told it was just down the street. After much hunting around we were told by a few locals that there was no internet cafe so we walk for 10 minutes further and found one for only 8 cents a minute! Lucky we used our own initiative!.......no apology for the internet not working!4: After speaking to the Guest Services Manager about the noise in our room we were offered a room move. We wanted to check it our first and found they tried to give us a downgrade! Not good! We decided to check out the following day as things were getting worse and worse..........The Guest Services Manager apologised numberous times (she was a great help by the way but to little to late)5: I had booked the room direct with the hotel. They stated that because it was my honeymoon i would get a fruit basket on arrival. This was not there and i alerted front desk who said his colleagues would take it up while we were out. I wonder where it went because it sure was not in the room! I informed the same staff member it did not turn up and he just shrugged his shoulders..........no apology for it not arriving!Over all i really need to forget this place exhists! Honeymoons have to be memorable and this place was memorable but all for the bad reasons. Unfortunately we wasted oe whole day in Singapore due to this hotel We will not be back!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b8600edc10b3cbbb4c14a6962ef0fc1e" url=""><![CDATA[Totally Excellent Experience! Having just got married in Fiji we arrived in Hong Kong for the start of our honeymoon. I had chosen the Langham Place Hotel from the reviews on Trip Advisor. I booked my accommodation direct with the hotel and was very impressed with the efficiency they showed with my booking\enquiries. I can honestly say this hotel throughly deserves it top rating on Trip Advisor!Both my new wife and I were extremely impressed with the service, the room and everything else about the hotel. Everything from the efficiency of the booking process to the warm welcome we received from the 'Pink Ladies' made our stay in Hong Kong extremely pleasant.Having worked in 5 star hotels myself, i can honestly say this hotel definately lives up to its 5 star status. We had a room on the 26th floor which has the most wonderful view looking back into the main city of Hong Kong. Located in Mong Kok the hotel is close to the ladies market as well as the best place to buy electronics. Pay no attention to any feedback about Mong Kok not being a nice looking place. Remember that you are not in 'Kansas' anymore as i felt like i was experiencing the 'true' Hong Kong. The hotel is excellently located to the MRT which we used everyday. The MRT is even better than the cheap taxis that are prevalent around Hong Kong as it is fast and cheap (although quite crowded at times but thats the wonder of Hong Kong!). Food outside of the hotel was cheap and abundant. Walking around we felt completely safe although you do tend to feel a bit worried when the stall owners chase you down the street when you dont buy thier goods (if they are really keen on selling you something they will keep offering you a lower price and hound you until you cave in but its all done in a very friendly manner).Price wise this hotel is very resonable. The money we saved on accommodation we spend at the stores! Due to our wonderful experience both my new wife and i will be returning to Hong Kong and we will definately be staying at the Langham Place Hotel again!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>