<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="ab2d875f3256267a8330e539bc0163b5" url=""><![CDATA[Convenient Conrad I visit Hong Kong regularly and stayed at the Conrad 3 times. The check in process was always fast and efficient. I always booked the mountain view room - being their standard room and everytime I had positive experience. However, I cannot call this hotel perfect as the room size is small and although everything else seemed to look right, the general decor and furnitures were dated. Conrad seriously need a big round of refurbishment in their rooms if they havent started planning to do so - to really make the guests' money worth. Otherwise, Location is fantastic. I totally love the Pacific Place, it just feels great to know that the big mall with everything you need is right underneath. Few hours of shopping and then drop of our stuff to rest our feet is always a plus. My next trip in December, I will be trying The Lanson Place in causeway bay for the first time since their rooms look spanking new with very good deal I found on the internet. I will return to Conrad only if the company pays for my stay or after their future renovation!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="43b2816b4613f087acf33a558aa6e3c8" url=""><![CDATA[Pleasant Stay at The Lanson place Being a dedicated fan of Small Luxury Hotels Group, I did not have any doubt trying out the Lanson Place during my christmas vacation. The promotional rates on the hotel site were good value for money and it should be booked through internet only. Upon arrival, everything seemed up to standard, the atmosphere, the lobby, the recpetionists and although there were a few other people checking in at the same time, the process was done within 3 minutes. The room was very well designed - I'd say a very high standard boutique hotel. The size of the room was not huge but the frequent use of glass partitions and mirrors made the general ambiance very chic and relaxed. It was nice to have a basket of snacks provided for free of charge daily and the living area was very comfortable. Bathroom was too small for 2 people to walk in and out at the same time, but the shower area was in a decent size. Oh, and the bed was one of the most comfortable bed ever! A perfect choice of bed to catch up with proper sleep from those late party nights. My experience would have been execellent if the breakfast buffet was more interesting. The dinning area was beautiful but not exactly practical to eat your breakfast. The choice of food was very limited and there were only pastries, yoghurt, some fruits, 2 choices of juice and that was it. I was expecting much more considering the standard of the hotel, that was honestly my only disappointment. Location wise, very good. I dont like the neighbourhood much as nextdoor was Indonesian supermarket but this was not a big deal. Getting around Causeway Bay was convenient and a cab was always easy to catch.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9ceff57aea7680a08eded79ca2c78ac0" url=""><![CDATA[Good experience Stayed at The Marina Mandarin in Nov 06 for 5 nights with great promotion from expedia and I don't have much to complain about really. While checking in, I asked for a room with a nice view and was provided with a 14th floor corner room overlooking the Marina and The Oriental was right opposite - fantastic choice. The only downside was the walk from lifts as I had to walk in a big square shape every morning and night! The room has been partly renovated and was in a suitable size and good condition. Some pieces of furniture looked tired, but wasnt a big deal. Bathroom was clean and spacious but looked kind of late 80's. I agree with every reviews below about the noise from the lobby area which sometimes the songs could put me to deep sleep and sometimes it could be a little frustrating. The location is perfect in terms of physical comfort. Restaurants and shops in Marina Square were easily reached and if you need to take a cab, there is always one - I never ever had to wait for it. The spa was amazing. The atmosphere was so serene and I just loved going there for treatments. The rates were not friendly but service was spot on - highly recommended.The two problems I came across while staying at the hotel were the conceirge and the crowd. I was a solo traveller and hardly know anyone in town so when I was asking for crucial information, this man seems to always be rushing to do something and never let me finished my sentence. I just got fed up with the service so I helped myself with the directions in the end. As for the crowd, there were wedding receptions held at the hotel twice during my stay which made it troublesome getting in and out from the main entrance.All in all, I would not mind staying at the Marina Mandarin next time I visit Singapore.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>