<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="eb36af0884db8a0869305cb568584791" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect!! The prefect place for a perfect getaway. Booked a triple room for ourselves. We were given the family deluxe room which was super huge and could easily accommodate a couple more people.Only emailed the hotel for a transfer from the airport one day before I was scheduled to arrive. They manage to reply me on time and I received their email confirming my transport right before I went in the waiting area of my flight. Excellent start!!Driver was already there waiting for us when we landed and check in at the hotel took us less than 15 minutes. We got complimentary welcome drinks while waiting as well.Only thing was our room was on the third floor and no lifts to carry us up after a long day out. But it wasn't much of a problem for us to complain. Rooms were cleaned every day without fail. Bottled plain waters refilled and fresh towels changed. Beds are also made up nicely.Breakfast was a bit of a letdown. Same menu every day and food was only so so. But nothing to complain about here as well as there are many other food outlets jsut around the corner. Pool was big with enough sun to keep warm after a cool swim. Lots of lounges available and I don't see a need to reserve any for your session of tanning.Also must try their spa! Cheap and good!! Tried the Bali Massage for Her package.. Includes basic facial.. foot scrub.. steam bath..jacuzzi bath.. herbal bath.. herbal drink and brownie and all for 300,000IDR only!!!Location is superb. Only a few minutes walk from Kuta Centre and Kuta Square. If you need to go to Kuta Beach.. You can always walk to the Discovery Centre and cut through the shopping mall. Nearby to all but still i the quieter part of the town. There are also a lot of the tour counters nearby fr you to book your day tours.Been to Bali 4 times and I've enjoyed every single trip like it was my first time!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>