<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="6b9c8929f55e8c1d9ee277259e8a8bb4" url=""><![CDATA[Hard to beat We had a great time at this hotel of the other comments on here seem very unfair and over-expectant.Location location, right in the heart of Waikiki, and one of the few hotels to back right on to the beach. Great to be able to walk out of your hotel and 30 seconds later be on the beach. Very well situated for the local bus service, so we never had to rent a car, always a plus!Check-in got checked in immediately, the desk staff were very courteous and had upgraded us as it was our anniversary. While completing the process, we were presented with beads and a lei, as well as very refreshing lemongrass juice. If you stay here definitely enroll in the Starwood program before you book to get extra very worthwhile benefits.Room requested a room in the historic part of the hotel. It was very spacious, had a good view and was very modern. It was well cleaned, bed was very comfortable, and the room even had a refrigerator in it. There was an in-room safe, although a few days in it stopped working. We had a free local paper each day (even Sunday) and the room had very comfortable robes. Our room overlooked the courtyard, and we never had a problem with loud music or noise from the bar that others have complained about (they must have gone to bed at 6pm!). In fact, due to the close proximity of the beach, you wake up to the sounds of the surf lapping at the beach. Restaurant ate at the breakfast buffet twice. The food was good, but nothing special. Usual breakfast items, sausages, bacon, eggs, fresh fruit, yogurt, cereal. There is also Japanese fare. Wait staff was okay, but could have been more attentive, with refills etc. The price is a little expensive (but what in Hawaii?) The real plus to eating here is the location. You sit in the gorgeous Banyan Tree courtyard, enjoying the unparalleled view and cool pacific breeze. We never felt rushed to finish and help them turn the table over, so a relaxing breakfast by the beach! We had dinner there once and again a bit overpriced, but nice atmosphere. There was a hula band playing which was a bit too loud, so we asked to be seated indoors, and were impressed by the modern feel of the indoor area. Food was good, with a decent variety. Amenities has a nice sitting area both on the courtyard and indoors. This is an ideal place to wait after checkout before going to the airport. Nice rocking chairs at the front entrance which is a great place to watch the numerous wedding parties that arrive daily. They also have a PC setup in the reception area so you can check-in online and even print out your boarding pass! I have never seen this in any other hotel, and it is a definite plus. There is a pool and yes, the beach chairs do go early, but if you really want one you have to book the day before. We found this information on-line before we arrived so this a surprise to us. We had no problem getting a beach chair in the evening, so we could sit and watch the sunset. The concierge staff was very helpful in getting us information about going to the theatre and with bus schedules. The hotel offers an interesting tour of the hotel which goes over the history of the Surfrider. There is a fitness room, which is fairly well stocked. Overall, I would recommend this hotel highly, and imagine staying anywhere else in Waikiki.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5b476d468f636371539c71a2032464e8" url=""><![CDATA[What a delight! After a long train ride from Rochester, it was a quick 5 minute walk from Penn Station to the Hotel. We checked in and they had our reservation immediately to hand. For unknown reasons (but to our benefit) they upgraded us to the Penthouse! The staff were very friendly and accomodating, and efficient. We were given free bottled water (nice brand in glass bottles!) and made our way to the room. 3Wow! In-room safe (big enough for a laptop), nice flat panel TV, gorgeous bathroom (two sinks, my wife was thrilled), robes, and a small deck out back, with nice furniture. Not much of a view, except of surrounding buildings, but really nice for a warm summer evening. The bed was clean, and very comfortable - best nights sleep I have had in a hotel in a long time. We enjoyed a very nice continental breakfast (bagels, muffins, danish, toast, OJ). Nothing fancy, but this is one of the few hotels I looked at that gave you ANYTHING for breakfast. The Bar area and the lobby are very chic and sophisticated. Again, the staff at checkout were very nice, friendly and answered questions we had without making us feel rushed or as if we were imposing. The location is fantastic; steps away from Times Square, 5 minutes from Penn Station and MSG, 20 minutes walk to the village. Our only regret? We only stayed one night! I can't wait to go back and stay here, for a much longer stay. And the price just can't be beat. I cannot recommend this hotel highly enough. If for a future trip to NYC the Hotel 41 is booked up, I would consider changing the dates of my trip!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>