<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="1851e31efff386515a688591a95219c6" url=""><![CDATA[You wont find a better combination in Amsterdam - location, amenities and value I have been traveling to Amsterdam for many years and have stayed at what I thought were the best hotels (Krasnapolsky, Grand Demure, Amstel, Victoria, Jolly, Golden Tulip, l'Europe, etc.). This past week I decided to go celebrate my 33rd birthday with a group of 20 friends from Puerto Rico, the U.S. and London and wanted to try a different hotel. I was looking for a decent place, at least four starts and centrally located, but that it would not cost me 1200 euros per room for just three nights (the trip was on me and I knew we would rarely use the room). Thus, I booked rooms at the Swissotel through bookings.nl at a pretty good price (498 euros for a standard room for three nights and 689 euros for the suites). When more people wanted to come to the trip and the hotel appeared to be sold out using the online travel sites they contacted the hotel directly and they gave them the same rate I got. I must mention that the attention and service via email while doing the reservations directly with the hotel was outstanding (thanks Ms. Schutte). Even the concierge emailed me giving suggestions for restaurants and answered most of my follow up questions. It sounded too good to be true so I kept some cancellable reservations at five star hotel where I had stayed many times before across the square just in case that we did not like the hotel. However, upon arrival, the service was as expected, they had most rooms ready for early check-in. The hotel is perfectly located in Dam Square, five meters from the tram stop! and the best thing is that you cant hear any noise in the rooms despite the location!!! The rooms were comfortable and had all the amenities customary of a four star hotel (what we are accustomed in the U.S.). The service, its worth repeating, was impeccable.Everyone had an amazing time and the hotel was one of the highlights. To anyone traveling to Amsterdam; solo, couples or as a group I think you will be pleased with the Swissotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>