<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="c2c1c6be61672af1d50468203c56d009" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel, rubish staff! My Girlfriend and I already knew first hand that this hotel was a bit of a distance from the centre of Amsterdam, we had stayed there before. Two years ago give or take a couple of months. We where impressed enough to return to the Artemis by the modern spacious design, the adequate fresh clean rooms and the excellent buffet style *FULL* cooked breakfast included in the price.On this first stay we had found one member of reception staff (who checked us in) to be quite unwelcoming almost to the point of being rudely abrupt. However, we never thought much of this and the rest of the stay was perfect. We stayed again this year (from the 1st Jan 08 in fact!). Whilst some aspects of the hotel where the same, the general appearance and well maintained quality feel of the room and the rest of hotel remained, other aspects had without a shadow of doubt, got worse. When we arrived at the hotel at around 9am, we intended to get a couple of hours sleep to top up the few hours we had managed to get before our early flight. We where told that the check in time (earliest) was 2pm. We looked, and this was indeed stated in small print on the reservation form. Whilst of course it was not the receptionists fault at all, and we where fine with coming back to check after 2pm, it was the way she dealt with us which concerned us. She was very unsympathetic and inhospitable towards us. We ourselves had to suggest simple things like leaving our luggage in the hotel until check in, and filling out our forms and necessary details in advance so she could have our room ready as quickly as possible when we returned after 2pm (we still intended to catch those couple of hours sleep before seeing some Amsterdam nightlife). When we returned at *5pm* to check in things got worse. We stood at the reception desk for *TEN MINUTES* looking at the*TWO* receptionists behind the desk and trying to make them engage with us or at least say that they would be with us in a minute or anything just to acknowledge that we where standing there waiting. They *BOTH* continued however to deal with a rich European woman who was also it seemed still waiting to check in. When we finally got seen to by the frosty female receptionist, we explained that we had already given our details and signed check in forms that morning. She left us waiting for a further 5 minutes before the guy asked us all the same questions. It turned out the girl earlier had messed up and had left the form lying around or something. When they eventually found the it, the guy said (after trying to charge us a further 100 for a deposit we had already paid) that we would have to wait to check in as system was He gave us 2 free drinks (one each lol) at the bar whilst (he said) he would fix the problem as soon as he could. Another 20 minutes past. We had long finished out tiny Artemis cocktails (he specified which drinks we could have!), so I suggested to him we WOULD be having another complimentary drink which he agreed to. When we eventually checked in the room was clean and fresh as was the bathroom to the credit of the cleaning staff. The other problem id' like to mention will no doubt seem very petty to some of you but let me explain. Remember, we had stayed here before and the things we liked about the hotel where why we returned for a second stay.The breakfast before had included hash browns, tomatoes, and a selection of eggs (not just scrambled).Worse still we where told at check in that the breakfast service would finish at 11am. We went down at about 10:15am to find that breakfast was (for a reason which nobody bothered to explain to us) finishing at 10:30am instead of 11am. Again the staff where very defensive about this and again not apologetic in the slightest! They where taking away trays of food whilst people where coming down to eat!!! The earlier time was the same for the whole stay.From reading other reviews it would seem that the rudeness of the staff at the Artemis is a problem for lots of people. A smile and polite hospitable attitude are expected from hotel staff the world over. It allot to ask for.(*pleas read*) What we are most upset about is that we missed pretty much a day of our stay in Amsterdam because when we finally checked at 6pm, we fell asleep and wake until the next morning as we where so tired. This is a nice Hotel but I give them any more of my money in the future.For a 4 star Hotel they lack allot of hospitality and simple etiquette.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>