<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="d0c27369f437ce1a6f2902b03c36306d" url=""><![CDATA[Pretty good...I guess..... We booked this hotel through expedia for a July 2008 stay. Prior to booking early in the year, we checked tripadvisor to see how it stacked up. Back then it rated a little higher than it does now. I want to like it more than we did, but I guess it was the intangibles that left me feeling like we could have chosen a better place.Technically, there were no problems at all. We checked in quickly with no issues. But somehow this Sheraton left me feeling cold and empty. What was it? Maybe it was the little things.First, we had a little trouble finding the place - it is actually hidden off Kalakaua Avenue. Second, the number of guests in the entryway and lobby is staggering - we've never seen so many people at a single hotel. And what is it about that lobby? Took me several days to figure out that they must have replaced all their lighting fixtures with flourescent lights with a cold, bluish tint. Totally uninviting.Our ocean-front room was tiny, with no dresser and minimal furnishings. The bed, however, was excellent and very comfortable.There were 10 elevators and usually the wait was minimal.The beach area was just okay....with the Royal Hawaiian under complete renovation next door, the beach area felt confined. The sand was slightly rocky and rough on the feet. The pool is fine. Ourview of Diamond Head was great, and we watched sea turtles feeding right off the beach from our balcony every evening.They have live entertainment every night poolside, which might keep you up if you are still stuck on mainland time. Bring earplugs.This Sheraton is okay, but somehow we didn't love it, and it was not the highlight of our trip through the islands. Compared to the price of the Moana Surfrider, the Sheraton was definitely a bargain. But you might be happier at the Outrigger or the Hotel Renew.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="38175e291c0fce75bcf8a042ba4c05ab" url=""><![CDATA[Our best hotel experience in Hawaii Anyone who has been to Honolulu immediately understands what I mean when I say it is crowded and congested, very touristy, offering little in the way of tropical paradise often associated with Hawaii, and with too much traffic. My wife and I have spent some time there and concluded that we never need to spend any more time in this capitol city.One hotel has single-handedly changed our minds about Honolulu, and now we can't wait to return.We spent a couple of weeks on three Hawaiian islands in July 2008. We needed to get back to Honolulu for our last night so we could catch a 7 am flight back to the mainland, so after reviewing numerous accommodations on tripadvisor, I settled on the Outrigger Reef on the Beach (rated #16 at the time I booked). How I wish we had arranged for more than one night in this excellent hotel.First, let me say that, yes, there is major construction going on at this hotel. It was actually a little difficult to find, but once we located it, we were treated like royalty. The staff called us by name throughout our stay, and were courteous and very helpful. I can honestly say I have never encountered such as excellent staff at any hotel. They enthusiastically assisted with every request, and offered several good tips.We received a wonderful room upgrade and abolutely loved our room. Our balcony looked out on Diamond Head and the beach. The bathroom was nicely appointed and very spacious.The bell captain, a young man named Kawika, took us to our room and actually checked us in on our balcony. When I casually mentioned that our anniversary was the next day, he immediately sent up a complimentary bottle of champaign. Kawika, you are the best - thank you!The rooms have recently been updated with nice furnishings and comfortable beds. The rest of the hotel will be brought up to those standards later this year.The pool is beautifully tiled and is sandwiched between two towers, offering shade through much of the day. When we were there, Waikiki Beach was quite rocky directly outside this hotel, but that can change with the tide and the seasons. It might be fine now.The Outrigger had an excellent restaurant and shops inside. It is also extremely close to the US Army Museum of Hawaii, and across the street from Roy's Hawaiian Fusion restaurant, which provided us with our best meal on the islands.I simply cannot say enough positive things about this hotel. And it is the staff that makes it special. Once the construction ends, I expect this to be a top 10 or even top 5 Honolulu hotel on tripadvisor, and it deserves to be that high.We visited Hawaii with friends, who happened to stay at the Moana Surfrider. They were also upgraded to a suite when they checked in, but our room was better than theirs, with a better view. They visited us in our room, helped share our champaign, and were impressed with our accommodations. I can proudly say our experience at the Outrigger was better than theirs at the Surfrider.To the staff at the Outrigger Reef on the Beach, I want to say thank you. You have earned our affection and loyalty. We will return to visit for a longer stay as soon as we can.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="695e50162e016b0f2fab2280e615391f" url=""><![CDATA[Pretty good place to stay We stayed in three different hotels in the San Francisco area in July 2007, and the Holiday Inn Golden Gateway was probably the best of the three. Clean, large rooms, attentive staff, and a great location add up to make this place worthy of a return.The downside? Extremely crowded. Numerous tour groups from Germany and Netherlands were there. It seemed like tour buses were loading and unloading at the front door on a continuous basis.Other pluses: Just steps from the California Street cable car stop, and Muni buses are also available right on Van Ness. Good restaurants are a short walk away, including Mel's, Kyoto Sushi, and the excellent House of Prime Rib.The front desk staff was attentive and polite. The breakfast buffet was expensive, but moderately good. Excellent coffee.This Holiday Inn is a good value in a city of over-priced hotels. Well worth a stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1d08f1bbe288bd16f510d9de791d2095" url=""><![CDATA[Nice quiet accommodations The Orchard Hotel is a nice hotel just a couple of blocks from Union Square. As I write this review (8/3/07) it is rated the #1 hotel in all of San Francisco. That's probably a bit too generous...its probably not the best this great city has to offer, but it is definitely good and worthy of your consideration. And a pretty good value. We paid less than $200 a night.This is a small, clean, comfortable, and most importantly, a quiet hotel. It is very clean, and they also offer free WiFi, which some others in the city charge for. There is also a laptop in the lobby you can use for checking email, flight status, etc.The bathroom was great - larger than average with an elegant appearance. The room was probably larger than most hotel rooms in San Francisco, but not large by any definition. But it was comfortable. Our room had a lousy view of an alley, but then again, we didn't choose this place for its view. Our room location may have been a factor in the quietness.Also, the hotel is just steps from a Hyde St cable car stop, so you can get quickly to and from Fisherman's Wharf. Chinatown is 2 blocks down Bush St, Union Square is 2 blocks down Powell. Extremely convenient location.The staff was friendly and helpful, especially the doorman. We've stayed in 4 different hotels in San Fran, and The Orchard is the best we experienced.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="19ce9af6a67155875eaafc299b514629" url=""><![CDATA[Good location, very good value This hotel is typically available for about $80 a night and is well worth it. You can easily spend more elsewhere and get less. In fact, we couldn't come close to this price in Baton Rouge, which is interesting because there is far less to see and do there.The location is good, on Magazine Street about a block and a half off of Canal Street, easy walking distance to the French Quarter and Jackson Square. It's directly across the street from the New Orleans Board of Trade.Valet parking is $23 per night. The fitness room includes 2 treadmills, 1 recumbent bike, and 1 elliptical. The pool is tiny, really an oversized spa, but it is heated.The rooms are really nothing special, but perfectly adequate and reasonably comfortable. Remember this is a converted warehouse, so you wil see exposed wooden beams, pipes, and painted-over brick. We will definitely return to this hotel on our next visit, simply because of the value and the location.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>