<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="5e65f3949f801cd8ab9d7ef34ebea23b" url=""><![CDATA[Huge hotel lacking character- 5 star rating a stretch I have ended up at the Krasnapolsky on three different occassions, and each time has been a completely different experience. On the first trip, 5 years ago, I was in an executive room which was acceptable and clean. Last year, however, I was in a standard room which was really quite grim- a walk in shower, folding bathroom door, and dated, tattered linens and decor. I had vowed never to stay again, but because my most recent trip was spontaineous, it was the only central hotel with availability, so I booked the executive room to be on the safe side...The room which was said to be in the newly refurbished royal wing was very basic and was certainly not like any other 5 star hotel I've ever stayed in. When we asked to upgrade further, the staff insisted that we were in the nicest possible area of the hotel...The inconsistency probably lies in the size of the hotel- it is really massive. Despite the disappointment in the rooms, the staff are lovely and friendly and the service has been fine...It's suitable for a business traveler, but not especially comfortable for a romantic weekend or family holiday.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d96bada0ba20817f62cd389cfcd34a7d" url=""><![CDATA[Simply Trendy We stayed at Hotel de las Letras last January and were very pleased. A frequent traveler, I am also very picky when it comes to hotels. Our room was spacious, bright and clean and even had an outdoor hot tub on our very own private balcony. Unfortunately, the door to the balcony was stuck and we didn't bother asking for someone fix it so we didn't take full advantage of all the room had to offer...The bar was relaxed, but buzzing all day- a nice place to meet people or have a quick drink before heading out. Locationwise, the hotel is very central. Will definitely be staying there again...Do beware...the beds are on wheels.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>