<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="c4ff52b52568938ab548047631ccac23" url=""><![CDATA[Nice and Relaxing at the Sunscape Punta Cana Grand We stayed at the Sunscape Punta Cana Grand my husband and I from May 25-June 1,2005. We loved the resort. It was a samller resort which required no wrist bands and we loved the fact you didn't have to worry about making reservations at the restaurants. We stayed in building 5 on the third floor with a huge wrap around balcony as we were on the end. We had a view of the adult pool and you could see the ocean. No problem with hot water or the air. There was a king size bed and it was comfortable. There was a mini-fridge in the room stocked daily with bottled water, pop and beer. No problems with that at all restocked daily. We used the fitness center daily it was a nice place to work out as it had treadmills,bikes and some weights. We are more of the beach people so we would start the day at the beach no problem with getting chairs and usually we would get there after 11. The weather was great all week sunny and hot only rained one time in the middle of the night. The main pool was nice had a swim up bar and floating mattresses around. One night we saw some people taking the mattressess to there room. Whatever floats your boat. We never had any problem getting any mattresses. There was an adult pool which was quiet. The only problem was there was a bar but no bartender. There was pop and water set out but if you wanted a drink you had to go get it. I think because the resort wasn't that full which was nice for us. The staff is wonderful these people work hard all day long. The grounds are well kept and beautiful. Kudos to all that work so hard. We had a wonderful vacation. I think it was best that we ever had. I would go back in a minute. We exactly what we wanted to make our anniversary and my birthday special. The food was great better then we thought it was going to be. The beach and domincan night buffets were great. The only problem we had was being harrassed to buy things from the vendors but we just said no thanks and kept walking. The same as on the beach when you walk there is a group of shops and the people will come out and start talking to you. We just kept walking and said no $$$ with us. We did buy a some braclets , earrings and statue of a family which were nice. Don't forget any items as the gift shop is high priced. I paid $8 for a magazine. The sun is really hot bring lots of sunscreen. We came home with nice tans and my husband hair is bleached out people thought he colored it. Overall a wonderful relaxing vacation.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>