<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="09843dc144747590d26b4d0c5b703006" url=""><![CDATA[We liked Hotel Washington There were 6 of us who stayed at this hotel for several days in April. As it was our first trip to Amsterdam, we have no way to compare this hotel to any other there.We found the Hotel Washington to be very clean, very quiet, and loaded with atmosphere. The owners have had it just since January, so are still getting things worked out, but they, and their staff, proved to be quite friendly and very helpful. They gave us suggestions for places to eat, sold us stamps, answered our questions patiently, etc.Our room was up one flight of stairs, but others were higher. (As I had recently had a total knee replacement, I was glad to have just the one flight to climb!) There is no lift, so any guests must be able to climb steep stairs, or fly.The room was large and comfy, the bed was comfy, the bathroom was huge and had both tub and shower. We were given clean towels every day and the bed was made every day. The breakfast was tasty and all we needed. They offer boiled eggs, bread/toast, fresh fruit, orange juice, corn flakes, granola, slices of ham and cheese, coffee, tea, milk, and hot chocolate. The boiled egg is served to you in a neat little egg cup. The 'dining room' can seat maybe 18 people, so you can easily visit with other guests. At night, if I wanted a cup of cocoa, I just took my own cup down to the kitchen and asked for hot water, then returned to our room and made my own. No problem.The hotel is located within walking distance of many small shops, and a huge outdoor market, and is a block or so from a tram stop.We would definitely stay at the Hotel Washington again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6cc94a3524d2316693a09346031f8462" url=""><![CDATA[We liked this hotel. We just returned from 8 days in Amsterdam, and we stayed at the Mercure Hotel--the one downtown, not the fancy new one out by the airport.This hotel is old and looks it here and there, but it's clean, most of the staff are quite friendly and helpful, and it's an easy walk to the tram. We found the bathroom quite nice, tho a shower curtain would have prevented water going all over. Our room had a little closet with good hangers and several shelves. The bed--oh, that bed!!! SO-O-O-O comfy!! Fluffy pillows and a duvet contributed to a good night's sleep. We got clean towels every day, the carpet was vacuumed daily, and the bed was made daily.The breakfast costs E15/person. There is a good variety of American cold cereals, granola, several kinds of juice, rolls, the usual beverages, and you can have your eggs cooked anyway you want. The bartender, Amin, has a great sense of humor and is a very interesting person to chat with.Yes, we'd stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c4d1cab99c0716649ea4249e981d862d" url=""><![CDATA[A bit noisy, but very charming There were 6 of us who stayed at the Silla for several days in April. (My husband and I had never been to Italy before, so we have no basis for comparison with any other hotels.)The Hotel Silla is very clean, very charming, and the staff was very friendly and helpful. The hotel was a convent at one time, hence the many narrow halls, arched ceilings and little rooms. You feel like you are walking thru a castle when you are just going from the lift to your room!We were quite comfortable in our room, and the bathroom was fine (shower, no tub).We were given clean towels and soap, every single day, and the bed was made every day. Our room looked out on the river, and as there is a busy street between, it could get noisy at night. We just used earplugs and had no problems sleeping.The breakfast is yummy! It is buffet-style, but the hard-working ladies will bring you coffee, hot tea, hot chocolate, all you have to do is ask. The food offered was two kinds of dry cereal, scrambled eggs, slices of ham and cheese, every sort of roll/croissant you can imagine, bread, little wedges of cheese, jams, honey and butter, fresh fruit (one morning there was a huge bowl of fresh, sliced strawberries), yogurt (plain and fruit), milk and 2 kinds of juice, usually orange and grapefruit. There is a microwave to heat things up in. It was hard not to stuff myself!The hotel is within walking distance of several very nice restaurants, and several little shops selling everything from fine quality leather goods to Pinocchios to postcards. It is also walking distance to the Pitti Palace, and on the other side of the river, the Uffizi, etc.I was just 3 months out of a total knee replacement and was able to get everywhere (used a cane) with little trouble.The staff was also very kind. Every night, my husband would take a ziplock bag down to the bar area and ask for ice cubes, then bring it back up to the room so I could ice my knee! They had no problem with that.We enjoyed our stay at the Hotel Silla and would stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>