<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="0d4a6d31c06826f49d9334a3c87c160d" url=""><![CDATA[Fine for nondisabled guests, problematic for those of us with disabilities. We stayed here for four nights and the stay was a better than average experience. The staff was extremely friendly and helpful but didn't always give us correct information. The computer in the lobby was a wonderful extra. We are used to that amenity in Best Westerns and it's one of the reasons we often choose Best Westerns when we are traveling. This is the first time I've seen this at a Radisson and it meant we didn't have to lug our own computer and could still stay in touch with work email. The room was clean and comfortable. But the disability accommodations in the shower that were extremely problematic. The built-in tile seat at the end of the shower farthest from the shower head and controls was a bit too far to be reached by the shower head on the hose. The shower head on the hose was so difficult to turn on and to figure out how to turn on that we had to call the maintenance person -- who couldn't figure out how to turn it on, either. Finally, my husband figured it out -- accidentally. The shower curtain wasn't long or wide enough to contain the water and so the floor got flooded. There was always ice water in the lobby and that was wonderful because it was so incredibly hot outside.Although I had made a special call directly to the hotel to make sure that the disability accommodations would work for us and to make sure that we would have a fridge waiting for our medications and that all feather pillows had been removed, when we arrived there were feather pillows on the bed, no fridge, and the shower had the problems I mentioned above. AND they had no record of my calls and requests. VERY annoying -- but, alas, very common.Still, the staff responded as quickly as they could to the problems, corrected them as well as they were able, and made sure to give us a first floor room. Nice people on the staff but not trained to deal with guests with disabilities, only technically in ADA compliance. But we would stay here again because most hotels are no better in terms of disability issues and often not as nice as this place.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>