<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="9d8e745f79700a34b87b53301b6d5f96" url=""><![CDATA[Great LOW BUDGET Resort I must justify my review (and title) by saying that my wife I have travelled extensively and usually stay at 5 star Riu resorts or Palaces.If this is the standard YOU are used to, this resort will disappoint you in many ways.This resort just changed hands from Sunscape to Globalia and you can tell Sunscape let it run down until they finally sold it off.In General, the grounds are clean and maintained. The building are showing their age, but you can see the attempts being made to do repairs.In one corner of the resort the Casino is STILL being built, and on the other side of the resort another building for more rooms is being finished. You will NOT escape the sound of saws or hammering, but you can keep it to a minimum with the right rooms.Courtyard rooms are best if you don't want the noise from the 24 hour restaurant bar during the night, and closer to the beach keeps you away from the construction. As mentioned by another reviewer the 3rd floor has very high ceilings and makes the room look larger. Thank to that review, our request made the holiday tolerable.Food was take a chance. In the Italian restaurant we found quality and service acceptable on the Tuesday, however on the Friday the service was hurried. Seafood soup was the vegetable soup with a couple shrimp thrown in. My lucky wife even had a centipede swim to the surface and bob around before swimming to the edge to climb onto the bowl rim and check out the room. The waiter called the manager who calmly took the soup away with out saying a word and disappeared. Guess its normal for them, but I prefer my soup to stay in the bowl. The angel hair pasta was normal spaghetti and the Ceasar Salad was made with greenberg lettuce even though the menu stated romaine.All is not lost though. Windows (the main buffet) offers a reasonable selection and there is something for everyones taste. Do not expect 5 star quality. Expect the same quality you would get at a company barbeque at a local park.Chairs were plentiful. Some people are saving chairs by leaving their towels and going off to eat or sleep. I usually gave 30 minutes grace, if they didn't return the chair was available. But staff would bring out more chairs if asked.Bar service was good. The people make the difference.They make em weak, they make em strong, they make em however you want, just ask.My complaint would be the absence of the International brand drinks as advertised. I could find no Canadian or American brands at any of the bars (and I asked). Maybe the International Brands are from Spain.English is the THIRD language here. The Entertainment manager is Spanish as is the General Manager and the country is primarily Spanish. Most announcemnets are in Spanish first and if they remember, English. Most of the maids, maintenance, waiters, and some of the bartenders do NOT speak english. I can see why Americans do not come here.One final item about food. It is billed as 24 hour, yet between 10 11 pm and 10:30 11 am none of the eateries are open.Pools are great, as is beach and most of the activities crew will keep you entertained.If you want a LOW BUDGET resort with all the trimmings this will be great for you. If you are used to 5 star resorts, you will be disappointed. The country cannot be used as an excuse, since we have stayed down the beach at the Riu as well.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>