<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="7">
		<document id="911610e7cdb6aeb6ba5fb676a060e62c" url=""><![CDATA[Really Like This Hotel We really do like this hotel. We stayed here for 3 days in May 2005, for 3 days again in May 2006, and for 3 days in June 2006. We wouldn't keep coming back if we didn't love Barcelona and this hotel. The exterior of the building is old, but the interior is all new. We have had 3 different rooms: two were small by American standards but average or better by European standards, each with a queen-sized bed. The third room was large by European standards with 2 twin beds. In each case, the bathrooms were larger than average, and adequate for 2 people to operate in at the same time. The rooms are very nicely appointed: all tile in baths, wood floors and furniture in bedrooms. Beds are very comfortable; I like a very firm bed, my wife likes a soft bed, we sleep on the same bed in this hotel and neither of us complains. The location is exceptional: in the Barri Gotic, 3 blocks to Placa Catalunya, 2 blocks to the Ramblas, on a narrow quiet street. If you have wheeled luggage, you can easily walk from the Aerobus stop at Placa Catalunya to the hotel (5 minutes, maybe). We have only eaten breakfast there once; the buffet was large with lots of variety and very tasty, although perhaps a bit pricey (13 euros per person). We have paid varying rates for different days, but the rates run approximately 125-150 euros per night--not a bargain, but good value for the money. The front desk staff is helpful, housekeeping is excellent. When we return to Barcelona, this will be our first choice among hotels.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="390835f01a17831dc847f4ae7002085a" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel This might be the most luxurious hotel we've stayed at in a long time, and especially at the price. We spent 4 nights here in May. Previous reviews commented on street noise on lower floors. Based on these reviews, we sprang for the extra cost for a room with a terrace in order to ensure we were on a higher floor. When we checked in, no rooms with a terrace were available. The front desk agent (Lorenzo, I believe, who was especially cordial and helpful, but all the desk staff were excellent) gave us a large corner room and assured us we would be moved the next night and the first night rate adjusted accordingly. The corner room was on the second floor overlooking the Gran Via, which is a very busy street, While the street noise did not keep us awake, it was definitely there. The room was exceptionally nicely appointed with a large and equally nicely appointed bath. The next morning, we were told to pack our belongings and leave them on the bed and everything would be moved when we returned. We did so, and we came back in the afternoon we had been moved to a two-room suite on the 8th floor with a large terrace overlooking the Gran Via. This seemed to be the top-of-the-line accommodation in the hotel. We were offered this in lieu of an adjustment in the first night's room rate and we were happy to accept. The view up the Gran Via was spectacular. The hotel's location is excellent: a few minutes walk to Puerta del Sol and a few minutes more to Plaza Mayor, about a 20 minute walk to the Prado or, in the opposite direction to the Palacio Real. The Gran Via metro stop is at the front door. While we used a taxi (expensive--34 euros from Barajas) when we arrived, when we left, we used the metro to Atocha station with no problems even maneuvering smallish rolled suitcases down the steps to the metro station (larger cases or those that don't roll might be a problem). There are two negatives about the location. First, there is street noise if you are on the front of the hotel or on the Gran Via on a lower floor; I'd advise asking for a room on a higher floor or overlooking the narrow side street opposite the Gran Via. Second, as other reviewers have pointed out, the red light district is on the side street just below the hotel. However, from the other reviews, I did not realize this meant the main street between the hotel and Puerta del Sol which is the heart of centro Madrid. This street is a bit unsavory, lined with hostals, tattoo parlors and piercing emporiums, and prostitutes. However, it is also thick with police (among the things that stand out about Madrid are the presence of police everywhere and the presence of street cleaners everywhere at all hours--I felt safer and cleaner in Madrid than almost anywhere else I've been). We didn't hesitate to use this street to get to Sol and back, but if the unsavoriness bothers you, there are several alternative routes that are only slightly longer and more circuitous. Included in the room rate (125-150 euros per night) was breakfast which turned out to be a full breakfast, anything you wanted including eggs cooked to order, which I thought was a great deal. This would absolutely be my first choice for a hotel should I return to Madrid.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="486b05c2faf546199f2609227b21d70e" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Stay Spent Labor Day weekend at Cambridge Suites in Toronto. Decent but not spectacular price, but an excellent accommodation. The location was convenient for everything we wanted to do in downtown Toronto. We were able to walk everywhere, even though the wife had a broken foot in an immobilizing boot (but she's a trooper). We liked the extra room provided by a small suite. It was clean, comfortable, and quiet. Parking was on-site. We did not use public transport, but it was nearby. There was also an excellent and inexpensive breakfast restaurant across the street in the next block.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0bb0d839a62d80f0658b53ddd95d0ff5" url=""><![CDATA[Very Satisfied We stayed two nights in a deluxe room (7th floor at the corner of Olive and 4th). The rate was competitive with other downtown hotels that were highly rated on this site, and I was unable to find a better rate on Hotwire for a hotel of the same class. The room was large with an excellent bed and a comfortable sitting area, adequate closet and drawer space, nicely decorated and appointed. The bathroom was small (no vanity) and I had some difficulty maintaining constant water temperature in the shower. There was some noise from the hallway but muffled, not loud enough to disturb the peace except doors slamming in the morning. The staff was uniformly friendly and helpful (parking valets who offered to take care of luggage if we wanted, front desk staff, and especially concierge). The location is excellent, especially close to shopping, a few blocks walk to Pike Place Market and the waterfront, about a 15-20 minute walk to Pioneer Square. Were I to return to Seattle, I would return to the Mayflower Park unless an equivalent hotel offered a substantially better price.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="71ce826232f132bc1f51bcfa85498c32" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Value Stayed one night prior to flying back to the States. Location is excellent for access to the airport--walking distance if you wish. Rooms are small, but clean and comfortable. We had two adult parents and one adult child. Restaurant was satisfactory. And the hotel price was an excellent value, better than we are accustomed to in the U.S. Not luxury, but a cut above a basic hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9ed683493978c3d6897ebbfc27cc0aa3" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Hotel Excellent small hotel. Large rooms, large bathroom, very clean, very comfortable. The room and bathroom are just as they appear in the TripAdvisor traveler pictures. The location is also excellent--two blocks north of Union Square, about halfway up Nob Hill. We used BART from the airport to Powell Street and walked 6-8 blocks to the hotel with small rolling cases (the last block is a bit of a climb). On departure with a 6 am flight, the hotel booked a car to the airport for us. All positives, no negatives about the Orchard, and we got a terrific deal through hotels.com.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0b50a9f27ab2862bd3d7640c2e17299f" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Value This was a cut above a basic hotel. Small rooms, but clean and comfortable for two adults. Location was very convenient--walk to the Hauptbahnhof, walk or take a tram to Frierichstrasse and the Brandenburg Gate, convenient to a laundry where we washed clothes (a tram ride away). And the price was exceptional, lower than we would expect to pay in the U.S. In fact, we found in general that hotels in Germany were better priced than their U.S. counterparts, and definitely the least expensive places to stay in Europe.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>