<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="d0a0682d42c14b98186cd750f255b5ed" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent resort for everyone I just got back on Sunday, May 25/08 from the Dominican Republic, Punta Cana where a friend and I travelled to. We went down to stay for our yearly 2 week stay away from all the stresses of everyday life. We stayed at the Occidental Grand Flamenco Punta Cana for 1 week and didn't have a very good time at all. The grounds are beautiful and clean, the staff were amazing especially Cesar and Alexis who were always willing to help with what ever was needed. However we had problems with the dirty public washrooms that always had feces and paper in them and wouldn't flush, there was no water for good parts of the day and we were supposed to have satelitte t.v. and didn't. Both my friend and I ended up sick and I have been to Punta Cana 11 times and my friend 8 times and we have never been sick before. We paid an extra amount of money through Air Transat to be moved to another hotel and we ended up at the MELIA CARIBE TROPICAL which was AMAZING. The grounds are beautiful and clean and the staff are all fantastic. The a la carte restuarants where to die for especially the french Ma Maison and the Gondola Italian. The rooms are comfortable and the beach is well kept. There are trains that run every 15 minutes to take you around the grounds as it is a very large resort but so worth going to. Many activites for the kids like wall climbing, zip line etc... I am booking this resort for Christmas and taking the whole family. I highly recommend this hotel to all groups of travellers. Hope you have a great time if you choose to go to the Melia Caribe Tropical Punta Cana - i luv to travel 28
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fbd29813db35077ea0c8d89e71b80bc1" url=""><![CDATA[Kids had a blast and I got to relax The Ocean Blue resort in Punta Cana Dominican Republic is a 4 1/2 star vacation haven for certain. I have been to Punta Cana now 14 times and will keep returning because there are no beaches in comparison as far as I am concerned. I took my 13 year old son and his best-friend from July 3-11,2008 and they had a blast!! The waves were huge which suited them just fine as they called themselves the wave warriors and would spend hours in the ocean. The beach is spectacular and the water is crystal clear and there are many sun huts to be found. The grounds are immaculate and the staff are amazing. Many activities for all to enjoy including bowling, archery, wall climbing, euro bungie jumping, beach volleyball, boce ball, pool tables, ping pong tables just to mention some of them. The food is plentiful and there is a large amount of choices to eat. The coffee shop was a huge hit as they make specialty coffees, and milkshakes, smoothies etc. Make sure you have some of the sweets at the coffee shop because they are delicious. We certainly didn't go hungry. If you are looking for a fun excursion while in Punta Cana I HIGHLY recommend the Jurassic Buggies. Make sure that it is the Jurassic Buggies because there is another company but they are NOT good. My family have made a tradition to go on that excursion whenever we go and it is so worth the money. You get to drive the buggies on the road(very scary) and through mud and dirt so be sure to wear OLD clothing because you get filthy but it is so much fun. You drive the buggies to the most beautiful beach that is uninhibited for 15 minutes and then back on the buggies to swim in a natural cave. The cave is amazing but the water is cold so prepare yourself but really you get to clean off from the buggies. The final part of the excursion is horseback riding for about 20 minutes and believe me that is all your bottom can handle. I guarantee you will not be disappointed in this trip. All and all Ocean Blue is a wonderful fun-filled resort with happy, friendly staff and have decent food. Just remember that a SMILE goes a long way and the people that work there are people too. Hope you have as much fun as I did with my son and his friend. I have booked my family vacation for all 6 of us for December already and I am counting down the days until we go. Happy holidaysiluv2travel28
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>