<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="ad0606bcc92a6f2854da391ac6f1d1a0" url=""><![CDATA[Good Cheap Base If you are looking for a good budget hotel to stay in in San Fran then this is the place for you. Nothing special about the hotel and on 1st impressions it looks a bit down trodden from the outside but then for the price you pay you can't expect too much. The rooms were clean, comfortable, well equippped and spacious and the hotels location was perfect for us. The bed was big and comfortable and the shower hot and powerful. Only 1 block away from Polk Ave where most of the bars and restaurants are, 15 minutes walk to Fishermans Wharf, 20 minutes walk from Union Square for shopping. The hotel is located on Van Ness Ave, the main route in and out of San Fran so its easy to find and has good access to all the other major roues so it's easy to navigate around the city.I'd read reports about it being a dodgy area but I never felt unsafe at all. You get bums on every street but most look too weak to bother you, the others try and make you laugh for some change. The worst place we saw was probably around the Hilton on Union Square.Minor complaints were the rooms were a little noisy due to people checking out at stupid hours and traffic noise but you'll get that at almost every hotel in the city unless you're on higher floors. Parking was a little tight but we got our full size rental car in and out every day ok, just get someone to guide you, and the TV looked like it belonged in the 80's and had no remote control but thats just being picky.San Fran was an expensive city to stay in overall but if you look around you can find cheap places to eat and drink. Avoid Peter D's on the hotel premises, expensive and you don't get a lot for it, The Star of India buffet around the corner on Polk and Joes Crab Shack on Fishermans Wharf gave good food at decent prices as did the numerous small Chinese Restaurants around the city.If I were to go back I definately consider staying at this hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>