<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f7b98efc895d1a44e293376c86547c58" url=""><![CDATA[Location, location, location Just spent 4 gloriously hot days in the Dutch capital - hot weatherwise, that is (26C) - nothing to do with the Red Light District ;)Arrived at 11pm, after a stress-free journey from the airport to CENTRAAL STATION (train platform located right under Schipol - 1 way ticket to Amsterdam cost THEN got conned by a Turkish taxi driver outside Centraal, who charged us more because of ramps en-route to the hotel. Charged us a staggering 25Euros for a 5 mins journey. Compare that to 12Euros for a hotel ride back to Centraal for our journey home (booked via hotel). You have been warned...Courteous English-speaking staff at reception. Tidy, spacious en-suite room, with TV and coffee making facilities (a rarity for Amsterdam hotels apparently). On my first morning, found out that the shower head was broken and leaking everywhere. Uh, oh, here we go I thought. After noting the problem to reception staff, it was fixed by the time I returned at midday. Breakfast was fine - the usual croissants, rolls, cheese, hams, boil-your-own-egg, toast-your-own-bread, juices, tea, coffee.Fantastic location for hopping on Tram no. 1, 2 or 5 (PRINSENGRACHT) to Dam Square - tram stops right opposite hotel. The only downside was tram noises from 6AM - 12AM daily.Fantastic location also for nightlife. The cafe bars and restaurants of LEIDSEPLEIN was 2 mins by foot from hotel. Spoilt for choice, with abudance of Italian / Chinese/ Indonesian/ Indian/ Greek / Mexican eateries. Macdonalds and Burger King also, if you must. Perfect spot to people-watch and chill out with local Amstel or Heineken beer. Again, the ONLY downside with this location was the street noise from partying passers-by heading home to bed at 4AM.Great location for the museum quarter, with RIJKSMUSEUM (handy for those of you who want to see Rembrandt in a hurry) and VAN GOGH MUSEUM 5 mins walking distance. Went for a stroll to litter-strewn VONDELPARK as well - which was dissappointing to say the least. Even the lakes was like a rubbish tip. Litter was a problem at DAM SQUARE as well - had the city's binmen gone on strike?? I'm surprised Queen Beatrix hadn't complained from her nearby PALEIS...All in all, a hot, hectic couple of days in a fun-filled city. Head off the beaten (cobbled) tracks, to the quieter canalside streets for an oasis of calm.One final tip? Pack a good pair of trainers/shoes, and BEWARE THE CYCLISTS! Their right of way rules!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>