<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="df0d47fee4f5d93e0688cee39308e08d" url=""><![CDATA[2 Star Hotel with a 5 Star Facade The Pan Pacific is a hotel that looks 4 star, but provided me with 2 star quality service, at very high prices. I suggest you sort the reviews by Lowest First if you want an honest look at this Hotels Reviews. During check in, the man at the counter actually tries to barter with me. He begins a whole act right in front of me, telling me that I had reserved a smaller, cheaper Twin room, for the same $200 rate. I disputed this, and he tells me that I am mistaken. He takes it a step further and lies to me, saying there are no King rooms available anyways. Then an awkward silence, conveying that his decision was final. Astonished by this, and fully aware of what he was doing, I pulled out my reservation and showed it to him. King room with a view. Visibly annoyed he mysteriously finds me my King room with a view 10 seconds later. Not to be deterred, he then tries to upsell me. Sir, for $90 more per day, you can have free internet and breakfast. I replied I am already paying $200 a night for this room. You basically just lied to me about my reservation so I'd take a cheaper room at the same cost. Internet should be free, and I dont eat $90 worth of breakfast every day. He continued to try and persuade me. He would not take no for an answer. It was very uncomfortable and awkward for me. I felt like I was in a flea market trying to haggle for a bead necklace with a hippie. Then something surreal happened. He actually has the audacity to inform me - like its the first time he's said it - that he is giving me a Twin room. I started laughing. Seriously? He actually was hoping I had forgotten?? Unfortunately, this theme continued throughout my stay. The light bulb was out in my bathroom. The grout along the tiles was messy, and smeared. The toilet doesn't flush unless you pump it a few times. When I turned on the sink water, the handle moaned as if it were old metal. The magnet holding the door open doesn't work, so I watched the bellhop try 5 times to make it stick, unsuccessfully. Internet is $30 per day. Absolutely ridiculous. If you go up to the Business Center they actually charge $7.50 for 15 minutes of internet use. I mentioned this to a group of Indian fellows in Little India at an internet cafe, and they responded with roaring laughter. Laundry service here is $10 per shirt. Yes, per shirt. That works out to about $200 USD for an average load of laundry. I opted for their outside laundry service, paid $45 for one load (ugh) and my clothes came back wet. I couldn't make this stuff up, folks...On a Sunday night, I walked outside to get a cab and get some dinner. I ended up standing there for 40 minutes. Yes.... 40 minutes ... in a line with 30 other people, and it was 97 degrees outside. Fully drenched in sweat, I went back in to the hotel to the concierge and said Are you aware that there are 30 people standing in line for a taxi outside? He apologized and started calling to have taxi's come by. I should point out there were six employees standing out there with us the whole time, doing absolutely nothing. The day I checked out, I had overslept and was late for my flight. I conveyed this to the concierge and meekly asked for a taxi as soon as possible. As I stood outside, I watched the hotel staff fill up 6 metered taxis with people from the Taxi line, while I stood there, without a ride. Turns out they had called the more expensive taxi, which I did not want or need. It costs twice as much, and took 10 minutes longer to arrive. Great idea guys! Make that money!!! To top off this already disappointing stay, the more expensive, late taxi driver dropped me off at the wrong terminal. He knew what airline I was taking, yet despite the mercedes and double-fee, he apparently didn't know his job well enough. Remember, I was late for my flight. He takes off, and I had to pay another taxi driver to take me where I needed to go.There are a lot of exceptionally shining 5 star reviews on this hotel, here on TripAdvisor. To the tune of literally hundreds. Way more than one might think is normal. Way more than the other hotels in the same area of Singapore, even right next door. Its interesting to see that the hotel's PR firm heavily involved in responding to reviews here, too. That is something I don't normally see. I can promise that this review was written by a real traveler.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="da74a6b3d4669e3677133a1c217a2b06" url=""><![CDATA[Rip-off Central Simply put, they rip you off, bad. Parking is $22.50 per day, for hotel guests. Visitors pay $84 per day. A Cheeseburger and Coke costs $35. To work out once, costs $14. Internet costs $10 an hour. Wetbar is empty. Breakfast not included. Enjoy!The parking fee's alone justify a 1 star review. The arrogance required for the hotel staff to have sat down at some point... and agreed that its okay to charge visitors $84 per day... and hotel guests $22 per day... tells me that they are intentionally taking advantage. Parking isn't the only problem...The $22 cheeseburger is met with an additional 17% service fee. On top of that they charge a $6.00 .... per person.... cover charge. On top of that they charge sales tax. By the time they were done, my cheeseburger with coke cost $35.00. Thank goodness I hid my girlfriend under the bed. My burger would have cost $41. Oh wait, it did cost $41... because I tipped the lady. Because she told me the hotel, in its infinite greed, does not give them the 17% service fee. Its part of the whopping $7.00 per hour they pay her. At age 45. Nice.There are no complimentary water bottles in the room. There's a wetbar (and mini fridge) but its completely empty. If you have a rental car, they force you to park in their parking garage at $22 a day. There is nowhere else to park. They have a fitness center, but they charge you $14 per visit to use it. There is nowhere else to work out. They have internet through the television, but it costs $10 an hour. They have no Wifi. Haha!The room does not come with breakfast. Nothing is included. The cheeseburger took over an hour to make. The delivery person told me they have 3,000 rooms and only one small kitchen. She said they once charged a room of 10 people an additional $60 cover charge for their food. The elevator roars like its about to fall apart. The door on the inside is a dark, stale, rusting steel sheet. The beds are amazing. You will sleep like a baby, but only if you aren't under anyone else. Three kids in the room above, jumping up and down kept me awake. Front desk staff acted annoyed, as other reviews here reveal. Changed rooms and ended up with a sliding glass door that creeked every time the wind blew. Four star hotel? Slept with the door open to avoid its movement and noise due to the wind. On its own merits, this hotel might warrant a 3 star rating. However, the crappy elevators, the rickety sliding doors, and the thin floors all show a general lack of attention to detail. A lack of attention that the hotel has no excuse for, given the outlandish fee's they charge for everything. If this place were plated in gold, I would give it a 3 star review despite all the extra charges. But... it's not.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2c791c5cdb9fa778c1af0177e783a431" url=""><![CDATA[Shockingly Basic The Spectacularly Beautiful View from my room!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4f505cd5043e125f3d397855ce390d3f" url=""><![CDATA[Important Info before Staying Here Okay there are always tips and hints and tricks with every hotel which you don't find out until you're staying there. Here are some lessons learned:1) Make sure you reserve a Guaranteed Rate room. This not only means you are guaranteed the rate, but it also guarantee's the room. If you do not select this TYPE of room you may show up and be told the hotel is full and you have no room. Be aware of this. I unfortunatley had to watch an incredibly patient businessman calmly argue for a room and get denied because he was unaware of this little twist. He had booked 3 months in advance. So get the right type of room. Its usually $10 to $15 more. Not much. 2) They have two buildings now. One is the main building you walk in with the beautiful lobby. The other is a building you walk to by going outside in the back alley (very safe). Rooms in the main hotel are carpeted and quiet. Very nice. Rooms in the other building are hardwood floor and also very nice, but potential for more noise depending on your neighbors above. 3) They have a notice up as of Christmas 2007 that they are planning to replace all TV's with widescreen flat panels soon.4) My little old african american cleaning lady had the face of an angel, and a smile that would melt your heart, and I immediately took to her. Until I got to Prague a week later and realized my $100 brand new leather shoes were not packed in my suitcase where I had left them. I will not make any accusations, but lets just say the hotel has not contacted me to inform me that I left them behind. Also my $150 in-ear headphones are missing. Use the safe, or put a lock on your suitcase. And no, it doesn't matter that she was african american, except in the sense that she reminded me of the kindest old lady I once knew, who also was. 5) Room service was a disappointment The first meal I had was spaghetti and they didn't bother to include anything they were supposed to. I ended up paying $18 Euros (thats $26 us dollars) for a very small plate of spaghetti. No bread. No salad. Nothing. And $5 Euros more for something to drink (Thats $6.00). A tiny old fashioned coke bottle that was empty in 3 gulps. I was disappointed with this. Crazy expensive and poor food service. The next day I ordered the same spaghetti (I was starving and working in the room), and the same exact meal showed up with side salad, and a basket of bread and butter and cheese. I guess the night person didn't care. Good to note. Make sure you get everything you're supposed to get. Room service people were super nice and always very friendly and patient and very respectful, not even making eye contact with you or anything in the room while you rummage for money. 6) Soap in the bathroom is tiny. Like the size of a match book tiny. And thin. Like matchbook thin. Like 1 shower and its gone. And they give you two. So bring soap, or ask for more when you arrive. And its orange colored, and smelling. 7) Room was nice. I will never get why they can't buy Queensized mattresses, but you will be stuck with two twins, if you think you're getting a King. Enjoy the crack in the middle. The pillows were PHENOMENAL!!!!!!!! I am a bed afficianado and i slept like never before. Absolutely awesome, weird, lumpy square pillows that were complete heaven. But the room overall was very classy, nice lighting, beautiful cherrywood closets and glass mirrored sections with lighting to enhance. They give you two fluffy white cotton robes and slippers to use if you want. Water in the shower is either scorching hot, or cold. Expect to spend about 15 mins trying to push it, just a tad, oh crap, too far, back a tad... ugh .. cold gain... okay ... just... nudge it ..... AH burning hot .... ok this time two hands so it doesnt bump too far.... GOT IT !!!! Nice hotel. Id stay there over the Hostels.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>