<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="245fcac912edb9f0642153cbed3dd0c6" url=""><![CDATA[Not The Best We stayed at Catalonia Bavaro From Nov. 4 to Nov. 11. Upon arrival we were very impressed with the overall appearance and check-in was very quick. We were in building 19, quite a walk from the lobby but very close to the ocean and the pool. Upon arriving at our room we found the keydid not work so back to the lobby, then back to the room to find the safe key did not work, so back to the lobby. Our remote did not work either but this time they brought us another one as well as a makeshift plug as we did not have an adapter.. Might I say that in the 11 times to the Dominican we have never before needed an adapter. We finally settled in. The room was moderately cool and very clean. For some reason we were left a bottle of rum and two mugs. No-one else we spoke to had received these.POOL: It has a pool bar but was frequently out of items. Not once in our stay did we ever see anyone clean or add chlorine to the pool. There was definitely a scum and lots of dead leaves, bugs etc. No activity at all around the pool during the day. We did not see any of their animation team at the pool all week.BEACH: We spent very little time at the beach. It is definitely not as nice as at the Bavaro beach. The water here is brown, not blue, and there is seaweed. Also because the resort is all on its own thereis really no place to walk and if you did you trudged through seaweed.BUGS AND BIRDS: Lots of mosquito bites, worst ever. Birds in the buffets - yuck. One lady was so badly bitten she spent a night in the hospital on intravenus. One evening on our way to dinner they actually drove by fumigating the mosquitoes. We were left in a disgusting fog. This would be better done later at night.NIGHTLIFE: Karaoke (same 5 songs every night) before the nightly shows. The performances were dancing - every night it was the same. New song - same dance!! After the show it was either the disco or the casino. Most people sweat it out in the lobby bar drinking. It would have been nice if they had a band or some music there. Perhaps even open the bar down by the water.FOOD: I lived on pasta, so no sickness here. Had a couple of mouthfulls of some really bad food that literally had to be spit out. Noticed that I was not the only one, so it was not just me. The a-la-cartes were not great either. In fact we left our lobster on the plateand went to the buffet. People had warned us how bad it was but we decided to try anyway. What a mistake! (That was another spit out food night)GROUNDS: They are lovely and well cared for.OVERALL: Despite several more trips to re-activate our key and some really bad food we did still have a pleasant vacation. We met some great people and had a few laughs along the way. One good thing is I can honestly say this is my first Dominican vacation where I did not have any stomach upset whatsoever and also the first time that I did not gain so much as an ounce. We will be back to the Dominican again but most definitely to a differant resort. As I said, we have been 11 times and this one is in our bottom three. I find the overall rating for this resort should be dropped to about a 3 1/2.P.S. Martin is the best bartender at the pool bar - we miss him already!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>