<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="a0447f76a9d6d20204171c285ef0f74c" url=""><![CDATA[Great Improvements like new! As a vacation club member I have been to the hotel for 5 years in a row. The hotel is in all it's glory, help is wonderful and friendly.The language barrier with help not speaking English is no longer a problem. There are three new restaurants and a new lounge and bar area on the Caribe side. (A fire destroyed the old ones) The grounds were perfect and the marble floors glistening. The food is still about a 7 on a scale of 1-10. One night we went to the American Grill and it was absolutely wonderful, but when we went back it was bordering on terrible. The meals everywhere are very tasty but sometimes can be overcooked or tough. Eat breakfast and lunch at the Tropical Beach side restaurant that's where all the VIP hotel employees eat. The food and service are much better and there are not as many people using the facility. The rooms are extremely clean, but still no wash cloths. Bring your own. A family member who is in the hotel business couldn't get over the condition of the place. If you love the outdoors and enjoy beautiful surroundings you'll love this hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bcccd9ac3b2baea3ea10a8dab18f8628" url=""><![CDATA[Great Time Spent 5 nights at this absolutely beautiful hotel. Everything was perfect. The staff is wonderful and really go out of their way to make your stay everything it should be. Although most staff speak very little english, if you try a couple of the spanish words provided in the book given to you at check-in they really respond. The restaurants are good, not great, but their is plenty of everything to please everyone. The pool is like none that I've ever seen and the sit around in water bar is fun, fun. The lobby bar is also great. A different show each night with same group of entertainers. They are fabulous dancers and the costumes are over the top. Audience participation is a real blast.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>