<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="eea08ed5cc7e2d66a53fd9c17695f309" url=""><![CDATA[Location that cannot be beat We stayed at the Bostonian Sept. 13-Sept. 16, 2007. The hotel is in need of renovation, which according to signs inside the hotel, will commence in early 2008. I, however, am willing to overlook some stained carpet and outdated decor for an absolutely outstanding location. Being across the street from Fanueil Hall and Quincy Market, on the doorstep of the North End and dozens of great italian restaurants, a five-minute walk to the waterfront and aquarium are more important to me than high-end design. The staff was very friendly. I called housekeeping twice (once for a pair of scissors and once from more decaf coffee) and both times there was a knock at our door in less than 5 minutes. Our room would not win any awards for high style, but it was large and clean. When this place is renovated, it will be THE place to stay in Boston.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6afcbd8c1872a24d6664d6c1631fb073" url=""><![CDATA[If location is what you want... Hotel 41 is for you!We just returned from a long weekend at Hotel 41 and were very, very pleased about our stay. The hotel is absolutely, without a doubt, perfectly situated for a tourists visit to NYC. Literally steps from Times Square, Hotel 41 was a clean, quiet and comfortable retreat from the hustle and bustle of NYC. The rooms are small, as other reviewers have said. But I am a large person and I had no problems getting around the room or the bathroom. We stayed in Room 402, directly next to the flashing red RENT sign, and directly above 41st Street. The shade and curtains were enough to block out most of the light - I actually have more light coming in my bedroom window in my surburban home than I did at Hotel 41.The staff was very friendly and accommodating, at reception and at Bar 41 for breakfast and a late night snack. They held our bags for us without charge on our last morning so that we could do some more sightseeing.Although this, for some reason, was a very expensive weekend in NYC for hotel rooms, I loved my stay at Hotel 41 and recommend it enthusiastically to all.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>