<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="1dd3ee4c5d5bc944e4244e55f985534c" url=""><![CDATA[Good basic hotel in an excellent location We booked this hotel through Agoda.com and got a non-smoking, Harbour View Room at the 16th floor. We chose this hotel for the location, relatively good reviews and the free shuttle service to and from the HKCEC (we attended a convention) -- the next best thing to a hotel beside the HKCEC.The overall design of the hotel is simple and dated but generally well-maintained.Check-in: No problem here. We were initially informed that there was no room available until after three hours upon our arrival, but somehow we got one after five minutes or so.Room: As the other reviewers before me mentioned, the rooms offer only a partial view of the harbour and more of the tennis courts below. It was not really a big deal for me personally, as I expected it. Anyway, more importantly, the room was immaculately clean. No weird smells or icky carpets. It was a nice, basic room with in-room safe, complimentary coffee/tea facilities, mini bar and the usual toiletries/amenities. No bathtub, though, and the wardrobe was a bit small. Still for the price that we paid during the peak season, it was good value for money. I liked that they took the initiative of putting an adapter and an internet cable in one of the drawers. By the way, free broadband internet access in the rooms. WiFi in the 1st and 2nd floors.Location: It's not the most posh place in town but there's a 7-eleven and Wellkome nearby, a few small restaurants, bakeries, a bar, some book shops and it's a 2-minute walk to the Tin Hau MTR Station. The MTR is basically THE mode of transportation that you will need in HK. If you fancy walking around, the hotel is very near Victoria Park, Tin Hau Temple and the library. I love the location! Peaceful, but not isolated. I do think there's also a McDonald's nearby (but why when you're in HK), but haven't had the chance to check it out.Tip: When taking the taxi, make sure to specify Metropark Hotel Causeway Bay (as there is another in Wan Chai), near Tin Hau MTR Station. Better yet, keep your hotel keycard handy and just show it to the driver.Service: Efficient and friendly staff. Our cleaning lady was very friendly and cheerful, always greets us with a smile. I've no complaints. I appreciated the fact that they let me use the computer/internet near the lobby even after the Business Center closed at 7pm.Food: Didn't try the food at the hotel as the prices are pretty steep. Guests DO get 30% discount off the regular rate (for intercontinental dinner buffet), but as I said before, this is HK. We just buy some pastries and bread at the nearby bakeries/mini groceries or eat at Cafe de Coral. :) Cheap, good food.Overall: 4 out of 5. No gripes, really. It a good hotel -- great location, simple, clean rooms and good service. Although the prices of the food on the menu are pretty high, there are a lot of cheaper alternatives nearby. It probably just lacks that little extra oomph -- that wow factor -- that would push my rating up a notch.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4ce03cdcfdb0d61b88885334058b646c" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic location! If there's one thing I regret about my stay in Hotel 1898, it's the fact that I only stayed for a night here. I loved this hotel -- from its facilities, the room, the service and the location.Location -- It's along Las Ramblas, so there is a lot of activity going on right when you step outside the hotel. It is a touristy area, so for some it may not be your cup of tea, but it is conveniently located beside MANY shops, cafes and most of all, the La Boqueria (a large public market quite famous in Barcelona. Make sure to go here if you're a foodie). You'll never get bored (shopping and lot of street performers) or hungry here. There's a McDonalds and KFC a few minutes walk away from the hotel, so if you're starting to miss the fast food, you can always go there. Room -- Immaculately clean. The design was very nice. My room was navy blue and white, very classy. Quite spacious for one person, really. They were quite generous with the amenities as well. There's a cool room feature that sort of sets the overall lighting of your room depending on your mood / activity -- for watching TV, for entertaining visitors, sleeping, etc. :)Staff / Service -- Professional and accommodating. Although I really didn't get to interact with them that much except for check in/out and when I asked for an electrical adaptor. But all in all, they were alright.Price -- Got this hotel because of an error made by the travel agent in my booking, so this was a pleasant mistake. But I would say it is still good value for the money. Facilities -- I haven't had the chance to use the facilities, but from what I have seen of the spa and the pool, I would like to go back and try them sometime. Food - Nothing remarkable. Don't expect an eye-popping spread, but it's alright. Overall - I love the hotel for the location, primarily. The fact that the other factors such as the room and staff were great is just icing on the cake.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="304b2754ba3657ec1015f706c8dd01e5" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent hotel! My friend and I just came back from a 4-night, 5-day trip to Singapore. We decided to stay at the Royal Plaza on Scotts because we have heard many good reviews about it and we got a pretty nice deal with asiabesthotel.com.We were not disappointed.Check-in was a breeze and the staff were very friendly. I recommend Karen at the front desk, she is very warm and willing to help out...very knowledgeable, too. Anyway, we were given a room on the 6th floor. We were also informed during check-in that the hotel was smoke-free and the rooms may not have a view. That was fine with us. We all knew this before we came to the hotel, so it was not an issue.The room itself was very clean, I think it was newly renovated. The beds were just right, as were the pillows. I love their slippers, though, very soft and perfect after a day walking through Singapore. Everything else was pretty standard. The bathroom was clean, but no bathtub. Personally, I like it better. I never use the bathtub in hotels anyway and the rain shower head more than made up for the lack of a tub, in my opinion. There had been a bit of a problem with the water heater once, though, but it was immediately fixed, so no biggie.A great touch was the free minibar and the free wireless internet if you have a laptop. If not, there is a complimentary 15 minutes daily use of internet at the business center (2nd floor) for guests. I don't think they're that strict about it, especially when there aren't much people who are waiting to use the computers.The breakfast at the Carousel was good, in terms of variety (and maybe quantity) and about average in terms of the taste and food quality. The ambiance was pretty cool, and the staff as always were friendly and very attentive to your needs (I dropped a fork and was immediately replaced even before I asked for it). As the other reviewers may have mentioned, the buffet does not serve pork. Sausages and bacons are made of chicken, beef or turkey. The hotel is in excellent location. Scotts Road is very, very near Orchard and about 3-5 minutes walk to the Orchard MRT. Beside the hotel is DFS Galeria and McDonalds and other malls just a few steps away. Overall, I would rate this hotel as above average. It falls a bit short on the food (taste and quality). BUT, as we paid SGD210/night including breakfast, we consider this as excellent value for money. So this ups my rating, definitely.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>