<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="7">
		<document id="2844aea06933d356453fe9e1d15b731a" url=""><![CDATA[Beauty in the Desert Sun This is the third Christmas we spent at the Biltmore, but my first review.On this trip, my husband and I stayed in room 3115 from December 23 - 25, 2005. This was termed a Premier room and we had a special promotional rate of $299/night.We arrived at the Biltmore around 12:30pm, well before check-in time, to find our room ready and waiting. We were in the Valley Wing (built in 1979) which was immediately adjacent to the original, main building. Our room had a private porch area with 2 chairs, a table and a chaise longue. A hedgerow seperated us from the pool area (a lovely, smaller pool with Catalina tile, a fountain and a hot tub, more private than the large, main pool).The decor of the room was Craftsman in feel with some desert-color touches and leather and wood touches. Handsome, and plenty of storage for hanging and folded clothes.The King bed was very comfortable and the linens were soft. Bathroom products were present and accounted for, although nothing spectacular. The Biltmore Spa shampoo they provide smells great, though! The shower pressure was very strong and there is plenty of shelf space in the shower/bath to place razors, shave cream, toothpaste, etc., upon.Throughout our stay, the fireplaces were blazing in the public areas (even though it was sunny and 80 during the day, at night it got very chilly) and the holiday decorations were everywhere. This certainly added to the aesthetic charm of the place.We spent plenty of time by the very busy main pool. We enjoyed lunch on two ocassions at the poolside Cabana Cafe (thumbs up to the roasted peach and marinated shrimp salad and the spicy bloody Marys!) which, for two people, was in the $40 range. Waiters took care of bringing us pitchers of lemoned ice water and fresh towels...they were young guys, mostly, and not exactly heel-clicking perfect but sincere, efficient and friendly.Room service breakfast on Christmas morning was delivered at the stroke of the time we'd requested and was exactly as ordered (amazing how many places screw up scrambled egg WHITES and deliver the whole egg -- not the Biltmore, though!).We did not experience any of the hidden fees that some have complained of here -- everything was very clearly laid out on the forms at check-in and being very frequent travelers we are almost (almost...) used to the service/delivery/etc. fees that are tacked onto room service meals. We did not feel the prices for anything were out of line -- it costs $3 for a small bottle of club soda in the mini-bar and while it's no fun to pay that much, we've both stayed places where that price is easily doubled.The only complaint we had (if you can even call it that) is that this is the third Christmas visit we've made in 4 years and it would have been powerful to have heard a welcome back or even to have received a letter in the Fall asking if we planned to return.Although the resort is 75 years old and thus in some places shows cracks and crumbles (it's almost entirely made of formed concrete tiles, so no surprise there), at all times we both felt like we were in an incredibly special and unique place -- almost enchanted, with the ghosts of the famous people who preceded our stay all around us. The architecture, the friendly service, the happy families and couples as fellow guests, the sense that there was no other place on earth but here...all conspired to create a truly memorable holiday weekend for us.I can certainly say that we will return and hope to make a tradition of spending all our Christmases at this enchanted place.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cc3f7f514481da22874d15b987689fac" url=""><![CDATA[Like a Hostel for Cool Grown-Ups This is a review of my experience at the Clarendon Hotel + Suites, from August 25, 2006, to August 27, 2006. I was in room 309...a large suite.My experience with hotels runs the gamut. From suites at the grand hotels of Europe (Le Sirenuse, Claridges, the Adlon, the Crillon, the Goldener Hirsch, etc.) to exceptional US properties (various Ritzes, Waldorf Towers, Auberge, Post Ranch Inn, Bacara, etc.) to boutique hotels, as well (Sydney House in London, Arcotel Velvet in Berlin, Blakes in Amsterdam, etc.). I share this because Clarendon gave me an entirely new experience, which I did not really think possible after decades of travel to hotels big and small, great and good (and yes, some downright lousy).Travelers to the Clarendon should prepare themselves for a hotel that is not sizzling with high-end design (although the rooms are pleasantly appointed and the whole place is VERY clean). But the design that is there is really cool. LED desklights, sliding shades that feature reproductions of the artwork in the lobby, enormous rooms, an exquisite sound system playing big band and jazz standards by the pool, the same sun chairs I lounged on in Positano earlier this summer and the exterior painting and lighting all conspire to delight. You aren't going to get a Phillipe Starck tour de force here, but you will get a feeling that the owners care enough to provide you with far more than the average Holiday Inn.But enough of design, because what the world DON'T need now is a design hotel without the basics nailed.And this, dear readers, is where the Clarendon knocks 'em dead.Service. What a tragically underrealized concept in hotels today. But the staff at the Clarendon could school the buffoons at MUCH higher end properties in what service means. Always greeting guests. Always asking if they can do that one extra step to help? Always producing the unexpected (for instance, with the no liquids rule at airports, we found ourselves without sunscreen. Would the desk have a bottle we could use? You bet they did.).And this wasn't just a bunch of hip young people helping out other hip young people. I observed several much older guests receiving the same level of truly engaged and respectful service and that just made me feel incredibly affectionate toward this property. The ability to experience design and a unique interaction with it should be the province of all ages, not just 20-somethings with the latest Prada swimsuit.The bed was top-notch. We did not use the TV. There is no liquor in the mini-bar (actually it's a mini-snack stack...there is no chilled beverage selection in the room). The A/C worked...not to an icy chill like many Phoenix properties, but it definitely felt much cooler in our room. The shower pressure was perfectly adequate.We did not use the bar or restaurant but peeked in and it looked appealing. The property is very close to many restaurants, bars, clubs in central Phoenix (not to mention museums) so we tried some of those instead.I told the girl at check-out that I felt I had discovered the coolest youth hostel on the planet -- only it was for grown-ups. I still feel that way. It's a lower-budget-higher-design concept paired with the absolute perfect pieces of internal architecture: a genius bed, clean property, and staff who would fit seamlessly into the finest properties in the hospitality industry.I still love my Christmases at the Arizona Biltmore -- I'm a hopeless traditionalist in many senses -- but for any other visit to town, I am going to definitely stay at the Clarendon.Congratulations to manager Ben Bethel for reminding me that it's still possible to assemble a team of flawless customer service providers within the chic walls of a modern hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="625f6ba77f56e9ac582eac8790f1f350" url=""><![CDATA[100% Great Experience This review is for a one night stay (March 3 - 4) in room #1128.Upon arriving at the hotel (friend and I walked from Powell Street BART Station), I immediately noticed that they had finally put a sign on the exterior (metal letters, set discreetly on the front of the building by the entrance). When we started walking past the tree pots set on the outside Geary Street wall of the building, my friend said, I already think I am going to like this place due to the understated but stylish exterior vibe.Upon entering the fantastically designed lobby, we encountered no line at check-in. My friend went off to ogle the spectatcular design elements while I dealt with check-in. The woman handling that was friendly and welcoming...in fact, none of the snottiness pointed out in some other reviews was encountered by us with any of the staff during this visit. But we are smiley, friendly people so maybe that's what we got back? Who knows -- I just felt very welcome the entire visit.We then took the opportunity to enjoy a drink in the Redwood Room before the party scene started -- it's a stunning space, and the redesign of several years ago was sympathetic and successful. Going when it is quiet may not be a party highlight, but it is certainly an opportunity to enjoy the magnificence of this space -- and a good cocktail!When we got to the room, we discovered that the management had delivered a bottle of sparkling wine (Gloria Ferrer blanc de noir) and a lovely flower arrangement, with their compliments. Most kind of them!Our purpose for coming to the Clift this time was to host a 40th birthday party for a friend, including 10 guests, so we had booked a 925 square foot one-bedroom suite with living and dining area. It was spectatcular -- very large, private, quiet and beautifully designed with loads of windows and large wall mirrors to keep things bright and several pieces of custom Phillipe Starck furniture that are unique to that room. There is an 8-place oval dining table covered with a custom cut piece of orange mirror glass. Wild! But very sophisticated, too. It's freaky-chicy as one of our guests said.The room service team arranged everything perfectly -- four hot appetizers had been ordered a week before-hand, as well as red wine glasses, Champagne flutes and iced Champagne buckets (we bought our own wine at the very well-appointed wine shop two blocks away -- Moet Chandon White Star and Stags Leap Wine Cellars Artemis). By the way -- we got NO bad vibes at all about bringing our own wine and the people in room service, in the days before our arrival, were a pleasure to work with. We asked to have everything set up by 6:30pm and it was done by 6:40pm. Pretty good!The room is great for entertaining, and after two hours or so, we all left for the Vivienne Westwood party at the DeYoung Museum. Upon returning close to midnight, some of us enjoyed cocktails and appetizers in the Living Room area, which was dark and private -- the Redwood Room is a great place to party, but we were too pooped to deal with that scene.We slept soundly in the excellent bed and in the morning were shouting for joy over the strongest water pressure from a hotel shower either of us had experienced in quite some time! The bathroom has ample space for personal effects and the dressing room outside the bathroom has a table-with-mirror and huge closets for even more storage.We requested a late check-out at 2pm which was immediately approved. Then we went downstairs to enjoy our breakfast. The Asia de Cuba french toast was amazing -- it had a veritable mountain of whipped cream -- and bravo to the restaurant for also offering design it yourself egg-white omelettes for those of us fat-averse types! Breakfast was not cheap but we had a couple Mimosas, so it was our own fault! LOL And if you want cheap, there are a couple greasy spoons a block or two up Geary that serve good diner food (I think one is called the Olympic Flame and I've had good eggs-toast-and-bacon brekkies there).Check-out was a breeze and there were no hidden charges on the bill. Once again, the staff just could not have been more friendly -- even the cleaning staff one passed in the halls smiled and said Hello.I had some fears about the complexity of the expectations I had of the hotel -- the food, getting it set up, making sure it was a memorable and flavorful 40th birthday for my friend -- and I just could not be more pleased. They got EVERYTHING right.I will most certainly be returning to The Clift....in fact, I have the same room booked for July 6! Good job to everyone at the hotel and thank you for making my friend's 40th birthday truly special.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4dd623067159d189d6b138386585c5da" url=""><![CDATA[Very overrated The Adolphus is a classic case of someone taking a grand old hotel and thinking that if you throw every color, pattern and design element at the thing it will make it even more exceptional. It doesn't. In fact, the interior design of this hotel (aside from the lobby and French Room restaurant, which are magnificent) is like some awful Texas suburban McMansion. The busy pattern in the carpets, chairs, bed linens, art work, etc., darn near hurt my eyes!Better they had done it in neutrals and lower lighting (you could land a jet in fog in the hallways, they are so bright), but there you have it.There is also a serious problem with important structural aspects: the walls are so thin you can hear TVs in the next rooms (more on that in a minute) and the windows overlooking the busy city streets are not double-paned so you hear noise allllll night long.To that point, my neighbor's TV started blaring at 11:30pm. I called and asked the front desk to look into this, and move me if needed. They never called back; after 15 minutes, I finally called them back and was told that security had heard the TV was on from the hall, but that it was not too loud. I responded that I was not sleeping in the hall, I was sleeping in my room. They then offered to move me.The room they put me in was on the 14th floor, overlooking the street! One of the loudest hotel rooms I have ever stayed in in my life. Also, the room's walls had scuffs and dirt stains...definitely not a $615/night experience as the rate card on the door stated!!!The next morning, after a completely sleepless night, I asked to be moved again, and was. This room was on the 8th floor and looked out over a roof and airconditioning units, but was double-paned and quiet.No one ever offered to knock anything off my bill, even though the rooms manager, front desk and security were all aware that my stay was not up to my epxectations.All in all, I would rather stay at a quiet, earnest little Motel 6 than a pretentious, very expensive hotel that doesn't even have the basics mastered. The Adolphus is riding on its laurels, the fact that too many people are cowed into thinking they should not protest poor service, and the fact that most business travelers will just settle for whatever is dealt them.I won't...and so here I am with my one-star review!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1bd4330009ed2631fe9770378651cd7e" url=""><![CDATA[The coolest hotel room ever! I almost couldn't wait to come back to the USA so that I could write this review of my stay from July 24 - 27, so here goes...Plenty of hotels today market the cool-factor of their lounges, restaurants and/or room decor. And many deliver on that one level. But they nearly all fall down when they try to match the design bling with a similarly cutting-edge level of service...many just cannot get their supermodel staffs to deliver super-professional hospitality. Leave it to the Germans (or, in the case of Arcotel, the Austrians) to get the equation perfectly right!The hotel presents a modern front right from the curb -- the photos of the hotel here do not do justice to how shocking (in a good way) the glass facade of Arcotel is in relation to its surrounding neighbors. The chairs of the lobby bar spill out through floor to ceiling door/windows onto the sidewalk and create an inviting integration between building and passersby, in addition to being a great command post for people watching.Check-in was a breeze and very polite. My fumbling German can sometimes be met with impatience but here the desk clerk (at my request) just slowed down her delivery and gave me another chance to get my German answer right -- and I did! We both laughed at my little victory and I was up to my room with a smile on my face......Which soon became a gasp as I opened the door to my sixth floor junior suite (#608). What a room!!! The slanted floor to ceiling window-walls, the furniture, the kitchenette and the trendy bathroom were all just one exciting revelation after another. As a testament to how awesome the design of the room is, I can tell you that the nicest day of my entire vacation was an hour I spent in my room watching the rain from a brief downpour roll down over the giant slanted windows in rivers while thunder rumbled outside...it was incredibly peaceful but powerful. I kept thinking to myself that this was an experience I could have nowhere else but in this amazing space.Some neat touches: the James Bond gadget-style window vents and black-out blinds that open at a touch of a button; the do not disturb sign is your illuminated room number in the hall showing either red or green light; the nifty little cordless phone; the heat lamp in the bathroom; the Ikea kitchen module...and on and on.Breakfast is your typical European extravaganza with meats, cheeses, eggs, pastries, breads, cereals/grains, jams, spreads, juices...god, it was never a temptation to sleep in and miss this feast, I can tell you that! It's served in the Lutter Wegner space adjoining the hotel and is thus a far nicer space than most hotel breakfast rooms.The location of the hotel is right around the corner from the Oranienburger Tor U-bahn stop, so super-convenient and just a 10 minute walk (max) down Friedrichstrasse to Unter den Linden. It's a mere 5 or 10 minute walk to Hackescher Hofe and Scheunenviertel and I walked home at 3am from a club in Prenzlauer Berg and it was safe and actually a quiet and lovely 25 minute stroll.I was wrecked that they were already booked for the World Cup Final next July because I am going to be back in town for that and cannot see any hotel possibly equalling Arcotel. My friends were staying in a room at the Westin Grand Berlin and when they saw my room they were blown away!My bet is that you will also be impressed. This is the coolest hotel I have ever stayed in (and I'm a veteran of the whole Ian Schrager, Christina Ong, Design Hotels, Anouska Hempel scene) and they have excellent service to match -- from the desk clerk to the bar staff to the breakfast room team, all receive high marks and my most sincere thanks for making this a great vacation visit.Arcotel is am besten!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="837b480fe90bca073b71767675e7c285" url=""><![CDATA[Very Pleasantly Surprised I was very pleased with my stay at the LA Omni -- much more so than stays at other Omni properties. I was a guest at the hotel from December 6 - 8, in Room # 923.From my arrival, staff could not have been more efficient and polite. Even walking through the facility on my way to meetings, I was warmly greeted by porters, maids and others.The rooms and public spaces were very clean. The design is nothing fantastic, but neither is it over-the-top or offputting.Room service offered some low calorie options, and the mini-bar is well-stocked. When the batteries on my internet keyboard died, the engineer was dispatched within minutes to replace them.The view from my room was wonderful -- a full-on Disney Hall perspective. Double-glazed windows and solid walls ensured plenty of quiet so I could sleep.Shower water pressure was good, but they should have a shelf in the shower so one can lay their razor and/or toothbrush on it versus having to cram it into the little soap alcove or -- gasp -- leave it on the floor of the shower.Each morning I had a USA Today and an LA Times waiting outside my door...nice. I don't read USA Today so it was great to have something more substantive to read.Wake-up calls are from a real human, not some recorded automaton, and were placed exactly on time.A small bottle of spray starch is in each closet -- a nice extra touch (even if they do charge about $5 for it).I truly enjoyed my stay here and when downtown on business will ensure that I stay at the Omni again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f32a521842dded1473b660b2b5d44c45" url=""><![CDATA[God-awful This tale of woe is in regard to a one night stay on July 15.In the mood for an in-town get-away, I decided to surprise the Sig Other with a surprise night in a W Hotel suite. Upon checking room availability online, I saw no suites were available, so I called the hotel and learned that all their suites were being renovated. Fair enough, so i decided to reserve a corner room on a high floor.I arrived at the hotel 30 minutes after check-in time to process the check-in and get my room keys so that later I could return with the SO and go right to the room. Upon arrival, I was met with huge lines at the check-in desk...it took me 20 minutes to get to the front desk. Now that it was nearly 4:00pm, and having waited in the very slow line, I was stunned to learn my room was not yet ready. I had to be home within an hour to meet my SO and still had to secretly pack a bag with extra toothbrushes, PJs, etc. I was told they would work as hard as they could to get me a room quickly. In the meantime, I decided to arrange for a bottle of Champagne to be in my room upon arrival. I was ushered to the Conceirge, who basically could not have been less interested. When I asked her if she was certain they could have the bottle on ice in the room at 5:30pm, she looked at me as if I were from outer space. I should have known this was only a hint of things to come...Well, I was driving home to frantically pack, and then drive back to do the room key, then drive home to meet my SO -- yeah, I really like him so I go to this kind of trouble LOL -- when the guy at the desk called and said the room was ready. So I threw a few things in a bag and drove back downtown to get the key.Surprise! Another epic line. And people were yelling at the desk clerks and general mayhem was ensuing. Apparently, there was only ONE single bellhop for the entire hotel on a busy Saturday. Genius. Well, while waiting in line I told several people about tripadvisor.com so hopefully they will post here, too.I got to the desk, got my keys, and was running back out the door and said, You won't forget the Champagne, right? And they all smiled and said it was all set.One hour later, I arrived and told the SO that some friends had invited us up to their room for a pre-dinner drink. I entered room 2120 to find...no Champagne. I called downstairs in a wee bit of a rage and was told We knocked on the door but no one answered so we didn't want to come in and disturb anyone. I replied that no one had answered the door, because I wasn't in the room and since there was no Do Not Disturb sign on the door and since I had requested the bottle be waiting for my arrival, I was dismayed, mystified and peeved that they had blown the one most important element of the surprise overnight. Completely unacceptable at any price, but at $300+ it was ridiculous!They said they would have the bottle right up there and I said they were welcome to send it up if they would give me a break on the price, otherwise, forget it. She said she would do what she could.Which was, in a word, nothing. The bottle was delivered with a full price bill. I was insulted. I told the man that I was refusing the bottle and to take it back (it was unopened). He mumbled something and left the room without removing the bottle! I had to call down and ask for the bottle to be collected which it was.We ended up drinking the half-bottle from the mini-bar. After taking showers, we discovered there was only one bathrobe. I called down for one, and it was delivered quickly (albeit on a wire hanger...all the hangers in the closet were wood, so this looked tacky.)The room is nice, in fine shape, and the view was spectacular. I can say that much.At check-out the next day, the clerk was very apologetic and comped the half-bottle of Champagne when I told her of how completely unpleasant the experience had been.The W is very much form over function. I guess Seattle still doesn't have an interesting, cutting edge, non-dowdy, non-business-drone hotel. I would never return to the W and plan to share this opinion with my friends and fellow frequent business travelers.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>