<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="064417643195adc359c3b0426dfcb60c" url=""><![CDATA[Noisy, Noisy, Noisy!!! Never Again!!! They have taken an older, elegant property and painted it the most garish colors imaginable! The rooms are redone in a very haphazard way - they slapped on some paint but failed to refinish any of the wood items like the beat-up 70's era dressers. There is no refrigerator, so you are stuck hauling ice from another floor to keep any beverage cold. The worst complaint is that we asked for a quiet room - HAH! Right under our bedroom window, at 7am the workmen showed up and started hauling metal ladders out of the back of their trucks, yelling at each other, playing the radios in their trucks, and then the air compressor started and stayed on all day!!! When we complained, we were offered an even noisier room (instead of a suite) near the entrance - no upgrade, no discount, no free night. In addition, the highway just below is very noisy; because this is primarily a BUSINESS hotel, the guests themselves don't seem to realize that other people might be on VACATION so when they come back to their rooms drunk or get up at 6am they think it is perfectly OK to yell at their friends; they have outdoor meetings with loudspeakers that can be heard all over the property; and there is a riding academy by the golf course that smells like guess what? Horses! The beds were HARD - this was the upgraded mattress, at a time most hotel chains are changing to pillow-tops. And the pillows were so squishy I couldn't find enough of them to prop me up so I could read. Don't count on getting to eat at the fancy restaurant - it is booked by private parties most weekends and some week nights and is closed Sunday and Monday. The Mexican restaurant is a big joke - $12 for two American-style tacos! They have a captive audience and take full advantage of it.Because this resort is on a steep hillside, you either need to be in pretty good shape or ask for a shuttle everywhere you go. Won't be staying HERE again!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>