<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="5a48b006936ad8842c4909789acd61f0" url=""><![CDATA[Brilliant stay at the Soho We really looked into hotels in London as prices are generally outrageous - especially with the pound so strong against other currencies. The Soho was expensive (305 pounds per night), but worth every cent.The room at the Soho (luxury double) was beautifully appointed and far more spacious than expected. The bedroom had large (openable) windows and a wonderful bed with quality linens. Bathroom was great with a huge bath and separate shower.The hotel's public areas are good and staff are friendly. The room service was of an exceptional quality - though check your order as both times we had room service they forgot something! The location is what makes this hotel one of the best around. It is right in the heart of Soho and an easy distance to everything.Thoroughly recommended. Looking forward to trying other hotels in the Firmdale group.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a4467f1f02107cf22782b48afd692122" url=""><![CDATA[A perfect retreat in bustling Florence Fellow travellers rate this hotel highly and they are spot-on. This was one of the highlights of our 2-month trip in italy. We stayed for 9 nights in the Junior Suite (Iris) on the top floor, which is extremely private - like having your own apartment! We barely heard another guest in the Residence, even though at one stage during our stay the place was completely full. It had two very large windows overlooking a divine garden and with views of the hills surrounding Florence. Inside it is incredibly spacious, clean and well-appointed. The bed is comfortable and the bathroom is huge and lovely with skylights and good ventilation. The kitchenette is incredibly handy if, like us, you are sick of eating in retsaurants after so long away. Angela will give you a recommendation for a local Rosticceria near Piazza Ferrucci which has quite an amazing array of wonderful hot and cold foods, incredible wine and friendly staff.The Residence is located on the Oltrarno side of Florence and is perfect as a cool, green retreat from the centro storico (historical centre), which can get searingly hot in the summer months and is brim-full of tourists. (There is good reason that the Pitti Palace and Boboli gradens were built in this location - even in a time when tourists were more scarce!) The Residence is essentially an old family villa in an aristocratic, garden-filled part of the city and a very comfortable walking distance from pretty much all major attractions. Less than 10 minutes walk to the Ponte Vecchio along the river and easy enough to get a cab back from town (about 5-7 euro) if you need it. The Residence is also, as others have explained, close to the major viewpoint over Florence (Piazzale Michelangelo) - but don't stop here - go to the monastery at the top of the hill for the ultimate views of the city and surrounds. In our opinion Oltrarno also has the best restaurants and nightlife - check out La Beppa Fioraia and Osteria Antica Mescita San Niccolo. The San Niccolo junction is a hotspot for young Florentines on weekends.The jewels in the crown of Residence Michelangiolo are the owners Angela and Cherubino who, true to their names, are angelic and cherubic! They made sure we had everything we needed for a reasonably lengthy stay. They also have somewhat of a sixth sense about privacy - they were there when we needed them and not when we didn't. They live mostly off-site (readily contactable if needed) and you are given your own keys to the villa. Reception hours are till 6pm, but they were often there much later. On our second-last night they surprised us with a lovely chilled bottle of Prosecco and a platter of strawberries with lemon and sugar (as a gift for our 10th anniversary which we celebrated while there).For those of you who are on a working holiday the internet connection here is fantatsic and Angela seems to be able to get any computer to work. There is also a desk and lamp - plenty of room to spread out etc. If you have a car then this is a brilliant location as you can park in the villa's secure carpark and you need not get into the labyrinth of tiny one-way streets in Florence.All-in-all an amazing place in an amazing location with amazing owners and staff. We cannot recommend the Residence Michelangiolo highly enough - they deserve the No.1 spot on tripadvisor. Ciao!PS: A little-known highlight of Florence is the Corrodoio Vasariano - the ancient and private Medici skyway leading from the Uffizi gallery, across the Ponte Vecchio and popping out in the grotto at the Boboli Gardens. It can only be visited with a guide but is well worth the cost. Check out Florenceart.com for tickets.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>