<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="85acd0e7ff91577463c0ff8325a37190" url=""><![CDATA[Not our Favorite We stayed in New Orleans both before and after a cruise in December, 2006, including 3 nights at the St. Marie. The hotel is located in the French Quarter, within easy walking distance of everything. While I hate to criticize anything in New Orleans, given the continuing tragic post-Katrina situation there, we felt that the St. Marie was really showing it's age. The beds were saggy, there were cracks in the bathroom sink (which didn't drain well), they use only 75 watt bulbs, so it's kind of hard to read, the electrical outlet by the coffee pot was coming out of the wall, the hot water was unreliable and the soundproofing was poor. On Christmas day, we realized that housekeeping had not cleaned our coffee pot or given us clean glasses. We asked if they would, and they agreed, but didn't follow through. When my husband went to the front desk to ask for some clean glasses, he was told that they don't change glasses every day, and they didn't give him new ones. The bar--with lots of clean glasses--was right across the lobby. Next time, we would definitely stay elsewhere. The staff was nice, but didn't make up for the poor maintenance at the St. Marie.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e457f127cbc412ed3b8f58cb236d4358" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Choice! We stayed in New Orleans both before and after a cruise in December, 2006. Our pre-cruise stay was at the Maison Dupuy. We wished we had stayed there afterwards as well! The hotel is in the French Quarter, within easy walking distance of everything.We had no complaints about the Dupuy--they are renovating, and our room was bright and clean with a pretty wrought-iron balcony overlooking the street. The room was fairly quiet, considering it was New Orleans, where the party goes on and on. Next time I would ask for a room overlooking the lovely courtyard--there were 3 weddings there the day we stayed. Their breakfast buffet was good, although not included in the price, in a room with great copies of Talouse Latrec's paintings covering the walls. This room/bar also has a big screen tv for watching football games. We thoroughly enjoyed our stay here, and can't understand why it isn't rated higher on Trip Advisor. It is a hotel that is obviously well-managed and well-maintained. Perhaps not enough people have checked it out. We highly recommend it.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>