<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="50864afa372ca4f9442d15803abd87e4" url=""><![CDATA[great resort Upon arrival at the Aston bali my friend was already quite sick, during the stay she grew progressivley worse and the help that the staff provided was wonderful. They have an onsite docter who provided medication and when we were told that we could not fly home on the intended day because of the sickness, they very quickly organised for an extended stay and also on the last day one of the managers gave free late check out as my friend was still too sick to leave the hotel at normal checkout time. Also as my friend couldnt leave they let us choose any of the restaurant food and brought it too our room, instead of only having the room service food options.The hotel is located right on the beach which is great. Also a few minutes walk away there are lots of water activites to do. The hotel also has a lovely spa and a large pool with pool bar.That is the second time I have stayed at the Aston, and I would definatley recommend it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="50c578e793ae844fe4af43f62bb1220e" url=""><![CDATA[great location I stayed for five nights and was pretty happy with the hotel and the service. The rooms were small but so are most hotels in hong kong. Everything was clean and tidy and the staff were helpful. Location was perfect, very short walk and you will find shops everywhere. There is also a train station close by which is very easy to use and will take you basically anywhere you could want to go.Only thing that annoyed me is the extreamly long wait for the life every time you wanted to use it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fa9e5b497739b5fdd0dcf1cb540ca604" url=""><![CDATA[The best property I have ever stayed in I stayed at The Villas for four nights in Febuary this year with a friend. They look even better in real life then in the photos on their website (though i did stay in one of the newer villas). They are completly private, would be perfect for a honeymoon or romantic get away. You also get your own private pool and garden.The villas are cleaned regularly and if you don't want to go to the restaurant for breakfast, they will come to your villa and prepare your food right there for you.The local shops are within walking distance, but to get to Kuta or the main shopping parts of Bali a taxi is needed, but this is very cheap anyway.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>