<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="894624a6d704056055d45de4698cf2e4" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel Myself, partner and son are just back from a nine night stay in New York, and we would definitely recommend this hotel. I booked it thorugh gta hotels and got it for 1123 euro for the nine nights, this was room only but with so many places to eat right on your doorstep, breakfast is not a problem.The Location of the hotel is excellent as its so close to everything. This was our 4th time in New York but our first stay in the Belvedere, and having stayed in the Hilton Times Square the last time , I found this hotel to be much better value although the rooms were a little dated but spacious none the less and the little kitchen is handy if you fancied heating up a snack or just having a coffee.Staff in the hotel were very friendly, and at hand to answer any questions.For eating out there is a great bbq place on 42nd street called Dallas Bbq which was great value for big portions. Ideal for families and people on a budget or long stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f2478da3fb9c5ed47d4d9e6a75f26cf4" url=""><![CDATA[Fab Hotel Myself, partner and Child stayed here for 9 nights in Feb 2005 and loved it. It's called the times square hilton but its actually on 42nd street and not time square so it does deceive people who havent been to Ny before.Reception is situated on the 21st floor where the staff are v polite and helpful. The bedrooms are lovely and clean if a little on the small side considering the cost. The downside of our stay here was that when we were here there was work going on outside our hotel at 7 in the morning and it was v noisy. I know the hotel cant be blamed on this however they didnt even warn us of this and you would think that as we were staying on the 35th floor that we wouldnt be able to hear it, but we could.Also, the day we checked out the only place we could leave our luggage was on the ground floor with the concierge who will only mind your luggage for a fee but doesnt say how much. i think this is poor show after paying a v high price to stay there.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>