<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="24398dd84d0c2ba03632b4216f3f9725" url=""><![CDATA[A little pricey but almost perfect Can't say much bad about this wonderful 4-star hotel. Great location - right on La Rambla just above the Placa Catalunya. Beautiful buffet breakfast (at extra cost). A really nice feature was the double, double-pane windows. That is, two double-pane windows with an air space in between which results in total quiet even though it's on a really busy street.Only one complaint. They had a computer downstairs for internet access which was a pay-as-you-go deal at 50 Euro/cents per minute (!!!). That would mean 15 Euros for a 30 minute session of reading and answering email.. That's almost $40 per hour!! An Internet cafe down near the port on La Rambla charges, I think, One Euro per hour and that's considered expensive. Other than the inconvenience of de facto no internet access, it's a great hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="64345ebc887c3c8fb29b33da52187e99" url=""><![CDATA[mixed review The good:1. Friendly staff at check-in2. nice view of Telegraph Hill, and Washington Square area and Coit Tower3. It's newly redone.4. Good valet service and very friendly and polite.5. A great king bed and v. good llinens. Good towels in the bathroom.6. Free wi-fi in the lobby area. Works good too. 7. New, fast, elevators. One slight catch is that you have to swipe your room keycard before you push the floor button or it doesn't accept your push. The price of 9/11.The Bad:1. Noisy outside. Drunks all over the place when the bars close.2. Five in the afternoon and unable to get clean towels. They ran out(??)3. Generally overpriced. Want to spend $35 on breakfast?The Ugly:1. Parking will be about $100 for two nights (we're still here as I write this). SF is always expensive, but this is out of line. In summary:I got this room for $90 on Priceline. Good deal for that price. If I had paid rack rate or anything like it, I'd really be sore. This is a made over Holiday Inn, and looks like it. The rooms are furnished with IKEA-level stuff. Nice for a young person's apartment, but not for a 4 star hotel. Popcorn (acuostical) ceiling -- they just couldn't spend the $$ to take this out and it looks really dated and ugly. We had stayed here when it was a Hol. Inn, and that's about the level of hotel it still is--only more expensive. Interesting, Hilton is trying to lose the Chinatown identification. Was the Holiday Inn Chinatown -- now the Hilton Financial District. Never mind that all the businesses outsite the hotel have their sineage in Chinese. This place only makes sense at under $100 and it's a good value for that.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>