<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a3fd92a245e118f2d52987725cccfbdd" url=""><![CDATA[Business again... After reading some of the reviews, I was very hesitant to book. I'm an experienced traveler to Hawai'i and know what to expect at hotels.I have to say that those with negative reviews of this hotel are nothing but whiney cry babies that expect Hyatt service for Motel 6 rates.I was impressed.I'm familiar with the Aqua product and how they've upgraded a lot of really crappy hotels in Honolulu. the Marina could use the Aqua facelift but because its a condotel, their options are limited. But they do what they can.Check-in/out: Quick and easy. Advised of computer use, and received a cable.Elevator: didn't have to wait too long at all. I was on a mid-tower floor, and the elevator wait was never longer than a few minutes (if you come to Honolulu and stay at other places, the wait is MUCH MUCH MUCH longer). They also have comfy places to sit in the lobby while you wait.Parking: didn't use.Location: was good for me because I hate Waikiki as a business traveler, I need to be downtown and my choices were this hotel or Executive Center. I'm picking this hotel again because downtown closes up at 7. Its right at the base of Waikiki along Ala Moana close to the canal. Lots of restaurants nearby, and of course ABC on the corner (All Blocks Covered.. heh). 7 bus lines go by, so you are never more than a 10 minute wait. Parking is always tight in Waikiki... dont get a car if you don't need to. Ala Moana is a short 5 minute walk. Kuhio and Kalakua are closeby (main drags). Room: typical for a condotel. Everything worked, no bugs, and the bed was comfy. Had 4 pillows for a queen size bed... ac worked, and there were actual curtains in the room (others have blinds or thin curtains that do nothing to keep light out). TV worked, bathroom was sufficient.. having a stove, microwave, and fridge was very nice...
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>