<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="16407d2b9aa877bafa030437a2bf40fe" url=""><![CDATA[Great value, great location - loved it! We stayed at the Inn after reading a couple of very positive reviews on this site and we were not disappointed. I had looked for something in the area at my price range and kept finding fleabags so I was really pleased to find the Inn.We had just endured a 12 hour transatlantic flight so we were all a little tired and fed-up. What better way to revive ourselves than with the freshly-baked complimentary cookies on the reception desk?!? On subsequent days there was also a fruit basket and freshly squeezed juice, all compliments of the hotel. The location is another HUGE bonus. It was a quick and easy drive from LAX airport, and we were only 2-3 blocks from the beach. So every morning we could take a walk on the beach before breakfast, and stroll on the beach at sunset. The markets (and the endessley fascinating passing parade) of Venice Beach is about a 5 minute walk and both Santa Monica and Marina del Rey are 5 minutes by car. The rooms are enormous by European standards (although I gather pretty average by American standards!) and nicely furnished. We had a queen-sized bed and a rollaway bed in our room and it never felt too crowded. Our room faced the street, so there was some traffic noise in the morning, but nothing too bad. The room was very well equipped - there were more free toiletries than we had at any other hotel over our 17 day trip and they also provided bathrobes, which is an obsession of mine ;-) If silence is a priority, make sure to ask for a room facing onto the delicious little courtyard in the middle of the building. It's a really lovely little public area that doubles up as an overflow for the breakfast room and looks great with the lush plants and little fountain. The breakfast (served in the room adjacent to the courtyard) was good - dry cereals, instant oats, yoghurt, fruit, a selection of hot drinks, bread, bagels, waffles, Philly cream cheese, syrup, jam/jelly etc etc. And nobody seems to mind if you come downstairs, grab some food and eat in your room. The staff were exceptionally friendly and helpful, and credit has to go to the young lady who on our first night recommended Tony P's (in Marina del Rey) for dinner on our first night. We could not believe the view when we walked in - you are RIGHT on the marina! We ate in the enclosed balcony area and had really delicious food (mmmm, clam chowder!) - and it was really reasonable for what you were getting (and downright cheap if paying in Pounds!) The only negatives were the fact that we could not for love or money get our (non wi-fi) laptop computer to work, despite lots of advice from the staff) and the fact that when you are in the bathroom, you can hear every movement in the adjacent bathroom (the staff did warn us about this and suggested we sleep with the bathroom door closed...).But apart from those two very minor gripes, I absolutely loved the Inn and I would definitely stay there again. Oh, and as somebody else has mentioned, the $4 per night parking is really reasonable!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>