<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="be6b4d5d3151e32dddf0498591c273b6" url=""><![CDATA[Wedding at Bahia Principe First I would like to say that this resort has absolutely stunning grouds, is very clean and the rooms are very beautiful. We had a great vacation all together, but I would like to write this review for people who are thinking of getting married here. The review is very long but could be beneficial to some :Me and my husband just got married at the Bahia Principe Feb 1st 2008, and I though it would be very important to write this review for couples thinking about getting married there.We were a group of 50 travelling together for the wedding. The plane ride was very smooth from TO to DR. Everything went well at the airport and the bus ride to the Bahia, they even stopped at a little shop so we could purchase a few drinks for the ride! Very nice! For those who don't know, the resort is divided in two mirror sections, with two different receptions (Bavaro and Punta Cana). When we arrived at the resort, the bus dropped us off at the wrong reception (50 ppl with luggage) The Bavaro side arranged for little trolleys to come and pick us up with our luggage, so no big deal. When we got to the Punta Cana side, we were told that my Grandmother (which is 78 yrs old) did not have a room because the resort was overbooked. They offered to send her at another resort for a few nights, which we declined since we didn't want her to be all alone at a different resort. So my parents took her into their room, hoping the problem would be corrected the next day. It wasn't...When we got to our room, we were expecting a welcome fruit basket and a letter from the wedding coordinator (as mentionned in the wedding package we purchased) It wasn't there, but we though it wasn't a big deal : we were there to have a good time with our friends and family and to get married! We were already on cloud 9! lol... So we didn't mind not having a fruit basket. The next day, we tried to book some a la carte restaurants and some tours for people in our group, it took 1 1/2 hours for a girl in our group to manage to book our reservations. We understand we are a big group (we were booking for 10 ppl) but we still think 1 1/2 hrs is a long time... By then, my grandmother and my dad go to the reception to see if she has a room yet, they tell her she has to deal with the other reception because she was booked with Bavaro instead of Punta Cana. When she gets to Bavaro, they tell her she has to go to Punta Cana...it was like that for all the room troubles we had that week. Nobody was willing to help, and they would always refer us to the other reception, which you could imagine, got quite a bit frustrating.I was able to find Marianna (the wedding planner) and she tells me we should've had a letter from her in our room, and we missed our appointment with her. She asks that we meet with her later that day. Before the trip, I had also sent letters to Marianna by e-mail, that contained all the information and scedule for the day of the wedding,and I asked for her to put it in every room (I gave her names for each rooms) she told me she would do it. That morning, the letters were not sent, I asked her several times that week and it never got done.Later that day (Tuesday), we met with Gaby (her assistant) and we confirmed everything we wanted for the wedding (the restaurant, flowers, cake, music, decorations etc...) We give her the legal documents we need to get married and the payment of 2000.00$ for the wedding package. Everything goes very well and we are very excited.We were getting married on Friday, and on Thursday night (around 7h30) Marianna calls my room to let me know they will be changing the location of the reception to a different restaurant. Now, I'm not very happy with this, because we had to let 50 people know about the location, and I don't have time (on my wedding day) to call everybody's room and let them know about the change... So I ask her why she changed us (I had confirmation for the Garden Grill for more that 4 months ago) she tells me there is a group of 150 people and they need the big room at the Garden Grill. To make a long story short, it took us 3 hours to 'discuss' with her to make arrangements for a new location, and to find out why we were 'bumped' from our location. It was very frustrating the night before the wedding, and put a bit of a damper on our week. ( The next day, after we were married, we got back to our room for a bit before the reception, and we saw that the Garden Grill had a wedding for about 50 ppl, not a meeting with 150 ppl....)Finally we got the Italian restaurant (the food was ok, but not great...) for our reception. The next day (wedding day), I had a hair and nail appointment at 1:00, my nails were perfect! But my hair was a mess... She was done by 3:00 and I was getting married at 4:00, so you can imagine my panic! lol... I still had to get my make up done, my hair redone and my dress on... Finally (Thanks to my wonderfull sisters and bridesmaids!) everything turned out perfect...The rest of the wedding day was wonderfull. The photographer is absolutely amazing (Ernesto), the ceremony went without a hitch, the reception was great (except for the waiters getting drunk by trying to put up a show, more annoying than anything) All in all we had a great wedding day!If you are looking to get married at this resort, you be the judge for yourself, after reading this review. Would I recommend this resort for a wedding? Absolutely not. I would not recommend this resort for any organized events. More than once, we felt like numbers...This resort is great for a couple alone who would like to spend a week to relax and enjoy the beach. But nothing that would involve dealing closely with the staff.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>