<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="b246c6998bdac30e8e34707bb98db2e6" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful Resort but Wouldn't Return My boyfriend and I visited the Bahia Principe September 2- September 9, 2005. This was our first trip to the Dominican Republic and our first time at an all-inclusive resort. We're both 27 years old and we booked through Apple Vacations. FLIGHT:Our charter flight through USA 3000 was excellent. Our flights left on time and arrived early! The planes were clean and obviously new with very nice flight crew.PUNTA CANA AIRPORT:The Punta Cana airport was easy to navigate and straightforward because it's so small. We followed the flow of people and easily found where to purchase the tourist card ($10 per person) and passed through immigration/customs. Our luggage was waiting on the carousel and then we checked in at the Apple desk to get our bus assignment. The bus from the airport was clean and well air conditioned. It took about 30 mins to get to the resort with no other stops.CHECK-IN:Check-in was quick and easy. We arrived at the resort at 10:45am and were in our room by about 11:30am. I didn't feel well from the flight and explained this to the front desk and they were luckily able to check us in early. I tipped the front desk $10 for accomodating our request.ROOM:We were in a first floor room with a king size bed in Villa 8. It was in the Club Golden Principe section and was a 5 min walk to the beach and main pool and about 10 mins to the lobby. The room was spacious and very clean. The king size bed was very comfortable and the bathroom was beautiful. We loved the tub and the air conditioning worked very well in the room. The maids were very good and granted requests in spanish (extra towels, pillows etc.) We tipped daily for their hard work. We rented the safe for $30 for the week.BUGS:Unfortunately we found many bugs in our room. We found mostly centipedes and smallish spiders and figured they were coming under the door. We solved this problem easily by blocking the gap between the door and the threshold with a towel. There were a few mosquitos around the resort and I was bit most frequently in the lobby area. The second night of the trip we returned from dinner to find a huge spider in our room. I wish I had got a picture but I didn't want to get too close!! The spider was approximately 4 inches in diameter and had the biggest legs. We trapped it under a trach can and called the front desk. They responded about 20 mins later and the employee disposed of it and searched the entire room as well as sprayed insecticide. The employee was great but he didn't speak English so brush up on your Spanish and bring along your Spanish dictionary.BEACH/POOLS:The beach was beautiful, nice white sand and clear water. The water was calm and swimmable while we were there. There was some seaweed in the water but it wasn't enough to bother us. There were many chairs and palapas...I'd save one around 8-8:30 each morning before breakfast. The resort wasn't very busy so finding shade wasn't hard. I loved the pools. They were large and nicely maintained. The pools closest to the beach are definitely busier with loud activities most of the day. As others have said the pools in the middle of the resort are somewhat quieter. Each pool has a swim-up bar. FOOD:This was our first all-inclusive experience and we were very disappointed with the food. We found the food to be of good quality but monotonous and not particularly good. The food was plentiful in the main buffet and we had breakfast there most days. We usually ate at one of the beach snack bars for lunch (Las Olas and Piscis), the main buffet and the specialty restaurants at night. The Mexican Restaurant was ok- I wouldn't recommend it. We enjoyed our meal at the Italian restaurant and the Garden Grill (bbq chicken was excellent but very small!) Overall we found the food to be ok- we didn't starve but I did lose four pounds during our week stay. It was disappointing to not look forward to meal times and by day 4 we were very sick of the food.SICKNESS:Overall I felt fine and didn't hear complaints from any other guests. My boyfriend experienced regular diarrhea which was unpleasant but with Immodium AD did not prevent him from enjoying the vacation. The resort is great at providing clean purified drinking water in your room and at the bars.SERVICE:We found service to be good to excellent and most employees were very helpful. They did not expect tips and did their best to communicate. LANGUAGE:Some employees speak some English but it was easier to communicate in Spanish. Look over some Spanish travel phrases and bring a small dictionary with you. TOURS:We did the Marinarium snorkeling trip. The bus picked us up at the resort at 12:45pm and it took about 30 mins to reach the boat. The tour was $72 US per person. It was a nice tour and included snorkeling with nurse sharks and Atlantic Rays, swimming in a natural pool, and the narrated boat cruise. The guide was excellent and she asked which languages everyone spoke at the beginning and everything was in English, Spanish, and French from then on. We arrived back at the resort at 6pm.ENTERTAINMENT:We watched portions of a few shows but didn't find them very interesting. There are activities on the beach and at the main pool for most of the day. We prefer reading and relaxing on the beach so we didn't participate in the activities.SHOPPING:As others have mentioned shopping at the resort is very pricey. Pack all of the things you might need or you'll have to pay the absurd resort prices. Souveniers were also surprisingly expensive in the Pueble Principe area. We did not make any purchases but I would try to barter if you see something you really like!SUMMARY:The Gran Bahia Principe is a beautiful resort with amazing facilities. Good food is an important part of vacationing for us and the lack of good choices was very disappointing, hence the low rating. My boyfriend's sickness also contributed to the low rating. He's traveled extensively in Europe and Mexico and has never had a problem like this. He consumed very little alcohol, no unpurified water, and washed his hands regularly. I'd be glad to answer questions or provide additional information for anyone considering this resort or travel to Punta Cana.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>