<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="fc68a437d7b763023f7adf775d20503b" url=""><![CDATA[Nicely refurbished, very handy location The location is great, opposite London Bridge tube and 5 minutes walk from Borough High Street, where there's a great food market. Another five minutes and you reach the riverbank where there are loads of nice restaurants and the Tate Modern.My room was small but very smart, the bed was comfortable, and the shower was great. I liked the flat screen TV but wasn't impressed with the range of channels. Also, the room service breakfast was only average. There was an up to date Time Out London magazine in my room which I thought was a nice touch.There's a free fitness first gym on site which I thought was good. The reception staff were pleasant and courteous which isn't always the case in London, and there is a concierge to order taxis etc.I would stay here again but maybe skip the breakfast.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1c5983f330755d2eb16b071f9f5b96ff" url=""><![CDATA[Brilliant value for money, thoroughly enjoyable stay I was sorely tempted to give the Hoxton 5/5 and for the we paid for our saturday night stay it really does deserve full marks. However, on the basis that most people will be paying more like to stay here I've only given it 4/5 (but if I could give it 4.5 I would!)I really like the location - it is edgy but shoreditch is really up and coming and there are loads of nice restaurants and bars close by. There are plenty of people around at night and because of that I felt as safe walking around as I do in any other area of London. It's also really convenient for the tube and you can jump on the northern / central lines and be anywhere else in central london in less than 15 mins.The rooms are small but really well laid out - a decent shower, aveda shampoo and pears soap, a fridge, corkscrew and free mineral water and mile all impressed me. And I enjoyed my pret breakfast too.The staff were great (which is not a given in london) and the reception and bar area is pretty spectacular. It was nice to head back to the hotel after a meal and relax with a couple of cocktails.The only down side for me was the noisy bin men (even on easter sunday!). There's probably not much the hotel can do about this but if I'd been staying for more than a couple of days I think it would have started to get pretty annoying. Overall brilliant value though and I'll definitely be returning.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>