<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="2dfc406118449d1769fc28af7ad0fd76" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel, great location, a little overpriced We stayed here in November of 2004 for 9 nights. We were on a tight budget, but wanted to be in the center.We booked this hotel directly from the hotel's website. We were very happy with this hotel's location--right in the center. Right next to the Cathedral, walking distance to the Gothic Quarter, Plaza Catalunya, las Ramblas, etc. The rooms were good, no complaints. The only complaint is that it turned out to be far more expensive than what we originally expected to pay for it. It just wasn't worth it. The hotel administration misled us into thinking that breakfast was included in the price of the hotel, since there were signs posted in the hotel lobby about where when breakfast is being served. We followed these instructions ate breakfast every day, without being told that this would cost extra. Not one of the hotel employees said a single word, warning us about this trick. When I asked them is breakfast being served, I obviously meant, is it included, they would answer yes when in reality, they should've said it will cost you extra at the end. The breakfast was good, I admit, but cost us 20 Euro per day for 2 people. This we found out at checkout. THis was very disappointing because for the price of 110 Euros per night we could've stayed at a better (perhaps 4 star) hotel, with breakfast being included as well. We have done a great deal of traveling around Europe, and breakfast has always been included, even if it was a small continental breakfast. We thought we were getting a bargain, to stay in the center in a budget hotel at 90 Euros per night. We were obviously wrong and very upset--this WAS a budget hotel, except for the price of a FOUR star hotel. It isn't pleasant to get this kind of a surprise on your vacation, especially when you're not expecting to pay this extra money. So, in retrospect, here is my advice: look around for a better quality hotel than this one (it's only a 3 star), find out if they will charge you for extra services, even if it seems logical that they should be included, and then decide if it's worth it. If I were to do it all over again, I would've rather stayed in a 4 star hotel for the same money. (Or if this one were 20-30 Euros cheaper).Good luck!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>