<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="757bddd5d885d60d4627b4f34f36323b" url=""><![CDATA[Go, relax and have a great time!!! We just spent a fabulous week April 30th - May 7th at the Melia Caribe with our 2 children ages 19 22. It was their first trip to a hot resort so we wanted to make sure it was a memorable experience for all of us. My husband and I have been to 5 star resorts in the Bahama's and Costa Rica. We booked our trip through Marlin Travel who highly recommended this location from feedback from other clients who had attended. We were not disappointed. This place is absolutely gorgeous! The gardeners take very good care of the grounds. We saw flamingo's walking in one of the ponds near the Tropical lobby. There are Peacock's strutting their stuff on the grounds and at the beach. Air Travel: Air Transat Toronto Departure 6:15 a.m. Punta Cana Departure 8:00 p.m. On time both ways (Half hour early on departure day)Punta Cana Airport: Please have some patience. Everyone wants to get to their resort and start their vacation. Three flights came in at the same time and they were doing their best to get everyone through.We heard some unnecessary grumblings from some travellers. Make sure you have all your paperwork completed and ready to present.Check-In: We got to the resort about 11:30 a.m. and our rooms were not yet available. Check out time is 12 noon. They just asked that we hand them our reservation forms and gave us our wrist bands and pool towel cards, suggested we go enjoy lunch and a few drinks and asked us to come back around 3 for our rooms. Luggage was being watched by bell boys. Change room was available for those who didn'talready have their summer gear already on. Sol Mei: Watch for the guys in the white shirts. They're reps for the Sol Mei Time Share. If you're not intertested. be stern and tell them. They leave you alone once you start getting some colour on your skin and they look for the newbies.Beach: The beach is absolutely gorgeous - beautiful white sand. Yes, there's seaweed and if you go out early enough you'll notice the workers do rake it up early in the day. They can't control what comesin through out the day. If you go for a walk along the beach, you'll be approached by vendors trying to sell their souvenirs. They're all very friendly... some can be pushy! There are lots of beach chairs available; some of the cabana chairs are taken early in the day. Oh yes, lots of topless sunbathers!!! When in the Dominican, do as the rest of the tourists do!Pool: Beautiful!! We hung out mostly by the pool. Some topless bathers there as well. If you have a favourite spot you want reserved then you need to get out early in the morning to reserve your spot. Please don't reserve if you don't intend to use it. We were beside reserved chairs and the people didn't come for 4 - 5 hours. That's not fair. Food: Lots to choose from. Breakfast and Lunch is buffet and there'sa great selection of foods to keep everyone happy. The a la carte restaurants are fabulous! We enjoyed the American Grill, La Hacienda, La Gondola, Hokkaido, El Guarapo and Ma Maison. My son is a picky eater and he found things to eat at all the restaurants. Service was A+ at most restaurants, a little slower at others, but I'm on vacation, so who cares! Reservations are fairly easy to get providing you're not too picky as to when you eat. Seating is reserved until 2 p.m. for the Royal Service group and then opened up to the resort public. If you call shortly after 2, you can pretty well get in at any time any where. If you wait longer, you'll probably get a reservation at 9:45 p.m. which actually isn't too bad. Just have a late lunch and a little siesta before you go to supper!! We closed Ma Maison one night and ended up dancing with the waiters and having a heck of a great time. Hokkaido is a Japanese restaurant where the chef cooks in front of you. Originally our kids didn't think they would be joining us b/c they were gone on a tour. They did get back on time but we couldn't get them in with us b/c its a group seating of 12 per table. We tried giving the hostess some money but she wouldn't accept it. There truly was no room at the table. So money doesn't always talk as some have previously mentioned. Men, please make sure you bring dress shorts or long pants and you definately need closed shoes. Sandals not acceptable for men.Bars: There's a drink waiting for you pretty well anywhere you goon the resort. Lots to choose from! Premium brands are available. Local beer is Presidente and its actually not too bad. Again, have a little patience. Some people are ordering drinks for their group and it takes a little longer for the bartender to make them all. Tipping the bartender once in a while does go a long way. Rooms: We stayed in complex # 33 which was close to the pool, beach and El Turey Grill (Main buffet snacks). It was a fair walk from the Main Lobby and where the A La Carte restaurants were. The rooms were clean and spacious. We had a King bed and the kids had two double beds. At first they booked us in separate villa's but were good enough to find a villa that could accomodate two rooms. Our maid did a great job and if we needed anything we just left a note and she would have it available (other than liquor or beer). Only water and pop is available in the fridge. There's a coffee maker in the room, iron ironing board, and hairdryer. Tipping: Bring lots of $1.US or $5. US for tipping! They really do appreciate it. A lot of these waiters /bartenders work at different area's of the resort and they do recognize the tippers and go the extra mile for them. Tipping the maid also goes a long way.Golfing: Free?? golf is included at the Melia. My husband and son went out 3 times and did 18 holes. They brought their own clubs. For $5.00 per person you can leave your clubs at the resort for the week. They booked their requested tee time's for 7:20 a.m. before we got to the resort. It was highly recommended they confirm their times with the Cocotal Golf and Country Club once we got in Punta Cana in case their requested tee times were lost. Cart is mandatory.Make sure you pick up coupons at Guest Services so you're only paying $35.00 PER PERSON for your cart instead of $70.00. The course is gorgeous. Bring lots of balls as they're expensive to buy. It gets very hot in the morning so the earlier you can get a tee time, the better. The only disadvantage is if you want to eat before you go golfing, there's basically only coffee and cereal available that early in the morning. Bring some granola bars from home if necessary.Day Trips: As it was probably our last family vacation together we wanted to get out and do some things. We did the Bavaro Runners, Marinarium, Quad (4 X 4) and Horseback riding.Bavaro Runners is more of a cultural tour than a party tour. So if you're looking for a big party, don't go. There are a lot of children expecting gifts to be handed out. We stopped at a school and gave some gifts and also were told when we could throw gifts to kids at the side of the road. The kids did the Marinarium sunset tour and had a blast. My daughter went horseback riding and really enjoyed it as the tour took her along the countryside and galloping along the beach. Our favourite was the Quad tour. If you can afford it, rent a 4 x 4 for every rider. Wear clothing that you can throw out afterwards. It's recommended to wear runners but you don't need to. Again, wear footwear you can throw out. We went through back roads that had puddles all over the place. We went through those puddles and splashed anyone riding in site. Hence taking Malaria pills!!! We road along a beach and were able to stop and walk into the water with everything we had on to rinse off. There's a camera man taking a video of the trip. It's only $35.00 and its a great 20 minute recap of the ride. They drop it off at your hotel the next day. With all the tours, they stop at a few souvenir spots so bring lots of money if you want to buy souvenirs. If you're bringing gifts for children, I would recommend saving some for all your tours b/c there are always children around that would like to get something. We didn't think of bringing gifts on our Quad tour so I gave some of the young children $1.00 U.S. and it definately brightened their faces.Gift idea's: The dollar store is a great place to stock up!Stickers, books, colouring books, crayons, balls, frisbee's, hair gizmo's, bubbles, skipping ropes, rulers, candy, gum, etc. Check Out: Check out time is 12 noon. Our flight didn't leave until 8:00 p.m. and the bus wasn't taking us back to the airport until 4:30 so the resort extended our rooms until 2 p.m. at no charge. You have to ask at the front desk. So we were able to enjoy another great day of sunshine at the resort, check out and have a late lunch.We had a terrific week. We met some really great friends that we hope to keep in touch with. Melia Caribe Tropical is a huge resort. You can walk from the back of the resort to the main lobby at the front in about 15 minutes. There is a train that goes around to pick up people at specific spots. After all the food you eat, the walk won't hurt! It's not too bad walking in heals, but if you're feet are getting sore, what the heck, take your shoes off. Our only regret is somehow we lost our pictures from Sunday to Thursday from the memory card. Too bad, we had some great picutres. We heard some people complaining about their stay but these were the same people complaining if they didn't get their drink from the bartender the moment they walked to the bar. My advice.... relax! You're on vacation with hundreds of others. You'll be back in the rat race soon enough. We will definately go back again to the Melia Caribe. My son is already planning a trip with his friends to go back next year!! Enjoy!!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>