<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="66e7dcbc09259684b81950cac8e38389" url=""><![CDATA[aqua waikiki wave - great hotel Stayed at the Waikiki Wave from 18 May till 13 June 2007. Normally stayed at the Prince Kuhio but since it was bought over by the Hilton chain it has overpriced itself. Found this hotel on the internet which had went through a major refurbishment and reckoned this was the best time to try it out. This proved to be a wise decision as we found this little gem of a hotel just like our second home - this was mainly due to the excellent staff that is employed here - we have never been in a hotel that made us so welcome as the staff - they are ambassadors for the AWW. Special thanks to Josh at reception who always made our day with his lovely smile. Malia who was based at the activities desk and was always so helpful. The guys at the front door were always helpful with their knowledge of the surrounding areas. Finally our maid Julie who always kept our room spick and span and welcomed you with her cheery personality. Well done to the manager who interviewed and took on all of the staff as everyone was a pleasure to talk to.The room is big with 2 queen beds and has flat screen tv, microwave, fridge, hairdryer, ironing board iron. The hotel is sited in the heart of Waikiki and you will experience some noise from the local night clubs. The beds are a dream and if I could buy one in Scotland I would have one the same in my home.Overall our stay was brilliant and we would definitely come back and stay in AWW despite the noise.Only negative comments were it was not much of a pool but we were informed that a new pool is on the cards which would be great for future visits.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0f415f00d661cd2e0dc671ea843f36be" url=""><![CDATA[great hotel with friendly staff Great hotel - very clean with nice big comfy beds. On arrival given juice and biscuits. Complimentary breakfast included which offers excellent choice. Very nice staff.Nice restaurant within hotel Joe Maria's offering anything from sandwiches to steaks etc. The only negative point is it is a bit far out of Boston.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>