<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="db7c50469978db1b5361b0a14de31bc0" url=""><![CDATA[10 out of 10 My wife and I recently returned from a wonderful stay at Anantara, Seminyak in Bali . It was our honeymoon and the entire experience at the resort was nothing but positive. Check in was easy, courteous and relaxing. The staff in the entire resort are very friendly and courteous. The resort is located on the beach and our room had an amazing view of the beach and ocean. When we entered the room we just about fell over. It was huge. Marble everywhere on the walls and floor, a true suite with a living room, enormous bathroom and a giant comfy bed with a view of the ocean even from the toilet! There is a Jacuzzi outside on the balcony so you can lounge in your tub and watch the sunset.The resort had its own yoga master in house which was really great for us as we have always wanted to try yoga. We took two yoga classes right on the beach with him and loved it. A great way to start the day. The breakfast is really nice, with a huge selection of fresh things, fruit, breads and cold cuts. They make and cappuccinos for you and have fresh squeezed juice. They also bring you hot food like omelets and waffles. At night they have a Thai restaurant and the food was really superb and not badly priced for the quality. We did eat out two nights near the hotel but the food was not very good compared to the resort. There is an amazing sun set bar on the rooftop with giant lounge style seats to watch the sunset. We went up there almost every night to watch the sunset and visit with other guests. The resort also has its own spa where we each had a couples massage together. The room was very relaxing and the therapists were excellent. It was our first Balinese massage and I would highly recommend trying one. I give this resort a 10 out of 10 and we will be back again next year for sure!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>