<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="5a0e6043546a34ccdce3bc1a08e12678" url=""><![CDATA[Newly renovated 'It's safe to go back' My travel companion and I had begun staying at The Muse when it opened. Over the years, the rooms and hallways had become drab and worn so we found other accomodations in NYC. After reading that they had renovated the rooms, I decided to give it another try. I was pleasantly surprised at the quality of the renovation. My guest room was bright, cheery and fairly elegant. The decor is somewhat neo-classic and modern. The only drawback for TV watchers (I am not one) was the lack of HD on the flat screen TV's. They have a note in the room that indicates they are working on getting HD into the rooms. Also, I did notice construction noise while I was dining in the restaurant in the morning but did not hear any construction noise while I was in my room. There are 2 banks of elevators in the hotel so the rooms are separated in two different areas. I stayed in one of the smaller rooms (queen bed) so you may want to check the room layouts prior to booking. There is a bar and an adjoining restaurant and the hotel is conveniently located in the Times Square area and the price seemed fair when compared to other hotels in the area.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6fc882ec9d2c29d86b8d2d5a0ee8c74e" url=""><![CDATA[Clean, comfortable and recently renovated The hotel staff (reservations, check in and valet) was very friendly and accomodating. The hotel has recently been renovated, and the room and bath were spotlessly clean. The hotel has a contemporary feel. You can walk directly to the airport terminal very easily. Hotel sheets were not scratchy and the bed was comfortable. We had gotten stranded in the airport without toothbrushes, etc. and the hotel provided a small emergency kit at no charge. I would definitely stay here again....one of the nices airport hotels I have ever visited.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>