<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="11828ffc7ea9db9a6bd821d3bb54a671" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, rooms on small side The location is great minutes from Las Ramblas. I found the staff polite and helpful. Good buffet breakfast. Rooms clean but the single room I had was very small with only a small window, but given the hotel's city location not that unusual. Plumbing was interesting, though I did have plenty of hot water. Would stay again purely due to location.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b32fc353fd91dda323c09677774ed06d" url=""><![CDATA[wonderful hotel, would definitely stay there again This hotel is located on the first floor of a building on Ku'Damm. I was a single room, room 22, which faced the courtyard. The room was quiet and comfortable and quite large for a single room (it is always nice to have an armchair as well as the single bed). the bathroom was massive with bath. As metioned in the other reviews the easiest way to reach this hotel is probably the 109 which runs from Tegel airport to the Zoo via Ku'Damm. The 109 also saves the 15 min walk from the Zoo station at the end of a long day of sight seeing. The staff were very helpful and friendly. The breakfast was very good a good spread of all the usually continental breakfast fare plus a boiled egg.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="552fd460784199e9c19232a0364acc44" url=""><![CDATA[A lovely hotel - great stay A very good hotel excellent service, great room and convenient location. I had booked a single room but had a lovely large room with king size bed. The staff were polite and helpful. An excellent breakfast spread including cooked breakfast. Nice lounge and bar area. With walking distance of the Prado (and other museums) and the Royal Palace, near Sol metro station which makes it very easy if you wish to go further afield.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b1014ee9fb5924f190bb719e137d2eb3" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, nice hotel This hotel has a great location, not far from Las Ramblas, stops for the hop on hop off tourist bus. I had a single room which is not the largest room that I have ever had or however the smallest and was quite adequate. The room was very clean and well decorated, with adequate wardrobing. The bathroom was massive, with a good shower. As mentioned in one of the earlier reviews the door to the bathroom is frosted glass which is obviously no problem if you are single traveller. The room had a minibar with reasonable-ish prices (2,50 Euros for a San Miguel). I had a room on the 5th floor towards the rear of the building which was very quiet. I did not use the restaurant but the menu looked good. The reception staff where friendly and helpful. The air conditioning was good and could be easily switched on and off as required. On Barcelona generally I would recommend the hop on/hop off bus particularly a two day ticket. I would also recommend taking the guided tour at Sagrada Familia, English tour at 11am.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9eba59c1a6f8ef72a7d866a13dbf7ee9" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent location - lovely staff This hotel has an excellent location only a short walk from the Louvre and the Opera House. The staff in the hotel spoke excellent English and were very helpful and friendly, The room was tastefully decorated and furnished and very clean. The bathroom was in excellent condition and had a bath. The room I had (24) was quiet even though it was next to the lift. The room has a mini bar which is always useful. I would definitely use this hotel again and recommend to friends.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>