<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="3ec56ebbe48256876edc053dd08a961e" url=""><![CDATA[Stylish but some irks Based on the pictures and reviews here Flemings looked like a fun little hotel, and it was, but not quite hassel free. Positive details:-sleek and chic decor. Modern clean dark woods with sleek lighting and clean linens. Glass shower and vanity/sink area were a stylish and innovative way to make use of a small area and make it appear more spacious.-free wireless internet. slow connection but most hotels I've stayed at charge $10+ per day to use. -large double bed was a single mattress instead of the usual two smaller mattressed pushed together that seem so common in european hotels. The mattress was adequate, but I prefer a more dense bed.-it was raining during our stay and the hotels offered free daily use of an umbrella. small detail that was very thoughtful and useful.-location is close to the Hauptbahnhof, but area felt secure. Our room faced an inside street so noise wasn't an issue and we slept with the window open. -In house bistro was delicious but expensive ($90 without drinks for fairly routine fare). Seems they have an accompanying deli that has a great selection of raw milk cheeses and cured meats and salads for togo orders.Needs improvement:-some minor and not so minor details with the bathroom area. Minor issue with the toilet room door not locking, door shuts okay but the lock doesn't function. Bigger issue, the shower doesnt seem to drain fast enough and water leaked out all over the bathroom area floor. We had to use all the available towels to soak up the leaking water and also had to wait a few minutes after showering to open door due to not wanting to unleash a flood of water. -In the toilet room there was what appeared to be a tiny smear of dried blood on the wall near the paper dispenser. Normally this would disgust me to the point I'd switch rooms, but for some reason it didn't affect me any more than I felt that housekeeping should pay attention more to details. It was a really small, but obvious stain.-like all hotels it seems, the glasses provided in the room did not appear clean. Mostly dusty or spotty, but one had dried brown fluid.Overall the hotel was comfortable and fun, I'd stay there again despite the few notable drawbacks, but only because the problems seem easily fixed and also fairly common in the hotel industry so they annoy me, but are tolerable.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f3287ee5d254a3fee6524275229a1a6d" url=""><![CDATA[Precisely as expected. This is a great budget hotel in a nice neighborhood in Seattle. I was hoping for somewhere clean, safe, and in a good location for seeing Seattle. I believe it fufilled all those requirements. What it is NOT is a luxury hotel. The rooms are plain, but pleasant and tidy. They provide free bottled water in the mini fridge, along with microwave popcorn, and starbucks coffee. They have basic cable tv, no pay-per-view options but a VCR (! uhm, how about a DVD player instead?) The beds are adequate but strangely hollow feeling, very springy. Still comfortable though. The bathroom is spacious and clean, though the tub is kind of on the small side and the shower water pressure isn't strong like I prefer. The bathroom has a large framed mirror, but it would have been nice to have a full length mirror available in the room. One noticible drawback is that it was a little bit noisy. We kept checking the windows because it sounded like one of them was open due to the audible traffic noises outside.Staff is friendly and helpful. They have laundry facilities along with several vending machines for snacks and beverages. They also offer a free 24hour workout room that was very nice to have access to. (treadmill, stationary bike, elliptical machine, weight machine, they provide towels, apples, fans, and a small tv.) There is a nearby 24hr grocery store, Dick's hamburgers across the street for late night munchies (open until 2am) and really delicious pizza by the slice at Pagliacci's one block down. Seattle Center (space needle, science center!) and Key Arena are both just a very short walk away. The Mediterranean is : Clean, convenient, and friendly.The Mediterranean is not: fancy or quiet.I would recommend it for family or budget travellers, not so much for business or romantic trips.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>