<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="f9abc023d6812961a0c30942b7a7eeae" url=""><![CDATA[Locations, Locations, Locations! We booked the hotel through online agent, and being family with 2 young children, as usual booked a triple room for three. Turns out the hotel have a policy of maximum allowable number of people in one room - but was resolved, and we were helped by adding a mattress. With the price we're paying, we expected a teeny-tiny room with a broomcloset-like bathroom/shower as with other hotels in Europe. I braced myself for having to do acrobatic tricks while taking a shower to cope with the cramped quarters. The room was quite small but not as small as the ones we had in London hotels with the same price, and found - surprise, surprise! - a (small) full bathroom with bathtub, that even have a bidet! It's true that the decors are too pinkish and flowery for my taste but who wants to stay in their hotel room and stare at the wall for too long in lively Barcelona? Furnitures are cloth covered plastic - but we only use them to dump our backpacks on when we were sleeping anyway! We opted for a room overlooking the Ramblas and we're glad we did. The view was magnificent and if you want you can stay for hours looking at the passing crowd and street performers below. Locations is everything for a hotel. Continental Barcelona is at the North end of Las Ramblas, only a few yards away from Plaza Catalunya, Barri Gothic, Metro, El Corte Ingles Dept. Store, Carreour Express, the stop for Barcelona Tour Bus and endless shops along Las Ramblas. Hard Rock Cafe and Starbucks is just around the corner so this one has a perfect location to start your adventure in Barcelona! Being family with children, we love the convenience of having the 24 hour snack and drinks at the hotel. No more rushing to the supermarket for evening milk for the kids while we were there! On Christmas day they even handed out free champagne for guests! The staff are very friendly, polite and helpful and they will go out of their way to make things work for you. Cristina, Peter and others at the front desk will make sure you have all that you need, and help out with enquiries on what to see and where to go in the city, even handed out the brochures for some of the local attractions. They were very helpful and caring, and help with taxi orders even after we have checked out from there! We will definitely stay there again the next time we visit Barcelona after our experience with the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="262a790eae4ba6422de21d8f956fa6cd" url=""><![CDATA[Another amazing stay at Hard Rock Bali Stayed at hard Rock Kuta Bali late August for 4 nights. Been there for quite a few times and found it's still the same old HR Hotel we love. Booking made through hotel website, easy and fast. Got the package that included additional breakfast for children and airport transfer. A good deal. Airport pick-up was fast and efficient. Check-in was a breeze, the staff very polite and helpful. Since we've been here a couple times, they already have my data in their system that makes check-in extra fast! Also a welcome card from the hotel manager was in our room to greet us. Looks like they valued their loyal customers here. Breakfast was the usual crowded affair, however we've always been able to get seats. Food selection is very good, and gets replenished regularly. However the ratio of staff to customers in the restaurant that seems to be on the low side. It takes a long time to get your tea or coffee refilled, since they always seems to ran out of it every couple of minutes. The huge swimming pool was very nice with a sandy beach section and swim-up bar, sand volleyball court and daily activities, and their staff around the pool were as helpful and courteous as always. The cabanas around the pool are just as amazing as we remembered. You can lounge around and relax in there for a whole day in between taking dips in the swimming pool's crystal clear warm water. Food service from the poolside bar is quite fast and tasty. Last year my daughter and I took surfing lessons from the hotel's surfing school. This time we have another go at it and the same people who helped us last year were there to help us having fun on the beach, teaching us new tricks and encouraging us to try some new variations. The bar at the entrance of the hotel, the Centerstage, has a nightly performances by some very good bands. The atmosphere is very relaxed, and it's a great place to just chill in the evening after the children were put in bed. The Hard Rock Cafe is attached to the hotel's swimming pool. The food selection is good and they come in big portions. The best thing to do for lunch there is to dine al fresco in the back patio overlooking the pool. If you want variation, a few steps from the hotel there are gazillions of restaurants and eateries around the place. There are some convenience stores very close to the hotel in case you need additional snack and/or drink. Looks like the hotel tried to add 'funky' gimmicks to attract customers. This year they have just added a wallclimbing facility to the list of their things to do in the hotel. We didn't use the facility at this time, but plan to the next time we're there. Check out was done very fast, the airport transfer left on time and the driver was very helpful with all our luggage (which had expand and even gave birth to some other bags).We've seen quite some familiar faces among the staff from our previous visits. It seems that the management did a good job of retaining a very happy staff, and in turn they are going out of their way trying to please their customers! Staff at the Deli even let us use the internet for free at one time after we bought some ice cream.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>