<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="5e9912e5e668997f7f30378b17a1f0bf" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location The hotel is right in the centre, opposite the Parque de Bombas and the park. The location could not be better. The hotel itself is fine, with large rooms and good bathrooms. Unfortunately the breakfast buffet on the rooftop was located on the terrace during our stay, as the rooftop was being renovated. The breakfast itself is abysmal and to add insult to injury someone had left a box marked tips on the buffet! I'm not sure who the tips were supposed to be for as there was no member of staff in sight on the one day we breakfasted there. There are a couple of decent cafes within 5 minutes walking distance where you can get a cooked breakfast for under $5 for 2 people. Apart from this we had no complaints. We only stayed 3 nights and ate at Mark's at the Melia once. The food was good though not cheap. All in all I would recommend the Melia as a good place to stay for sightseeing in Ponce.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="21ce1974031fe9f680c431486b71a5d6" url=""><![CDATA[Very Nice We were surprised by how nice this Comfort Inn was. Very conveniently situated in the Condado district, within walking distance of some good restaurants. The room was fine - large enough and clean. The bathroom was certainly adequate for 3 nights stay. Top marks to Juan on Reception who was not only pleasant and friendly, but also knowledgeable about San Juan. We asked plenty of questions and he always knew the answer!We did not hire a car until we left San Juan, but there appeared to be adequate off street parking right in front of the hotel and a taxi rank just outside. I would definitely stay there again without a second thought.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5ddae89d300df244b1ff648297c38b6e" url=""><![CDATA[Good Hotel This is a good hotel in a great location. The hotel itself is fine, good rooms, all very clean and pleasant. Staff are friendly and efficient. The concierge was helpful in booking tours, providing a map etc. The restaurant (ground floor) has acceptable food, if a limited menu. The buffet is ok but you'd get tired of it pretty quickly. We didn't use the restaurant upstairs. However, it is not necessary to eat at the hotel as it is well-placed for several shopping malls with food halls and also the Riverside Walk (about 10 minutes stroDll away) with all of its dining choices. Several other hotels, including Raffles, are also within easy walking distance.Our only complaint would be the price of internet access. In the room it was 28 SD for 24 hours plug-in connection (over 10 sterling, 20 USD) and in the public area 12 SD (over 4 sterling, 8 US) for one hour, and this you have to purchase hour by hour - no avoiding the cutoff! Bearing in mind that 5 minutes walk away you can use an internet cafe for 3 SD an hour (uninterrrupted) the hotel charges feel like a rip-off.Overall I would definitely recommend Plaza Park, but avoid using the internet access until they drop the charges!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5896aa6ab7c6f75f7b5f8d005fe88aa0" url=""><![CDATA[Disappointing Check in desk is in a corridor. We had to move out of the way 3 times to let other guests/staff members in and out of the hotel. After check-in we battled our way through the potted jungle (difficult to pass down the passageway without getting your eye poked by palm fronds) to our room. There was a long black hair in the sink, the bathroom door would not latch shut. Having been told that this was a quiet hotel, we were not pleased to have somebody above our room seemingly moving furniture about and a bunch of people well within hearing distance having conversations until well after 11.30pm. The next day we went out and about, returning to our room after 2.00pm to find that the room had not been serviced. The maid finally came at 3.00pm in the middle of our siesta! The third day when we returned to our room we found that the furniture, and all of our possessions, had been moved around the room and the bedside lights had been changed, one of the old ones being left outside the door. As this was our last day it surely would have made better sense to wait 24 hours until we had checked out? Breakfast buffet was ok but not brilliant. On the 2 occasions we requested a taxi/cab one came promptly.On our last visit to San Juan we stayed at the Comfort Inn a few streets away. This was just as conveniently located and was definitely better value for money. If we return to San Juan in the future we will stay at the Comfort Inn.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>