<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="c4af785e5595f8b63ae82648d0b1429a" url=""><![CDATA[Not what I expected from a 5 star hotel Yes, this hotel is close to the Central Train Station and traveling by train from the airport and around the city is great from this hotel. There is, however, construction being done around the station making some detours necessary.This hotel is appointed very nicely and the bathroom is much larger than most European hotels. The bath amenities far outweigh most hotels in Europe and the states, but not having working air-conditioning available in a 5 star hotel even if it is April 27th is not acceptable when one pays such a high price. Even opening the one window gave very little relief since our room faced a courtyard.I had better service at a three star hotel a few days later. Even the free breakfast did not match up to any of the other hotels I stayed in during my month stay in Europe. We were very disappointed and would not stay at this hotel again. The price was just not worth the value! I don't care how many bath amenities were given, they are not worth a/c and a good night's sleep.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1f9066b0072b914104147b19db577813" url=""><![CDATA[What at great location. This is our second time back to the Hotel Relais Bosquet thanks to Rick Steves. It is a little scarey to walk around the area and see Rick Steves' Paris travel guide in most everyone's hand.However, he is right; the location is great. You can walk to either corner to get great pastry to eat in your room with the coffee provided or just walk to the Rue Cler and eat breakfast while the market is set up. You have an ATM across the street and a small grocery a few doors down. If you stay long enough to need clean clothes, you don't have far to walk to a clean laundromat. No one can complain about the size of the bathrooms which are larger than most we have encountered in Europe. We had a smaller room this time, but still facing the courtyard which keeps the street noise to a minimum. Fredricka scheduled a shuttle for the two of us from CDG to the hotel for 36E which isn't as cheap as the metro, but with luggage, it is considerably easier. Oh, you internet geeks, like my husband, they now have WiFi in the rooms. They also have a computer in the lobby for free use if you need to check your e-mail. This place has the basics and is close to everything. No doubt we would go back again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>