<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="c2f62d8f0b012dd660b66207b5e8ab4e" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect locatin for exploring the city Stayed at the Tuscan Inn over the Fourth of July weekend after using Priceline before Christmas to book a room (although I didn't actually think I would get one for only $75/nt over a holiday weekend!).Check in was quick and my boyfriend and I were given a queen room on the fourth floor facing the street. My boyfriend's first response was wow, this is a tiny room, but it was what I was expecting considering the location and that this is only a 3-star property. It was in fact a small room (a King size bed would not have fit) with a tiny closet and 2 drawers for storing clothes. Good thing we only packed carry on luggage and didn't have much to put away!The room was always clean and the maid staff was friendly, saying hello and have a nice day as you passed. We were frequently in and out of the room to change clothes or take a nap and never walked in on a maid (or were walked in on ourselves). One day we had the do not disturb sign on the door before the maid had come so we could rest, and when we finally stepped out for about an hour, we changed the sign for maid service and everything was perfect when we returned!One bad part about the room was that some street noise traveled up, although we were only really disturbed one night when there was a car parked on the street playing loud music with people around it laughing and talking loudly.Pros at the hotel:Staff - Very friendly and helpful. We had to send and receive several faxes during our stay and they were always happy to help. We used the concierge to book theater tickets, which worked flawlessly, and we also called the front desk around midnight our last evening and asked them to arrange an airport shuttle the next day, which they did the following morning when the shuttle company opened.Amenities - While this hotel isn't a luxury property, they have some nice touches like marble bathrooms, mini bar, room service and an evening wine reception every day (which many people attended). The restaurant attached to the hotel is nice, with a great little bar area and friendly bartenders. The restaurant breakfast menu is pretty minimal, but it does the trick.Location - This is the best part of the hotel. Two blocks from Pier 41, one block to the F line street car two blocks to the cable car. This was an awesome area to gain access to many different parts of the city without trying too hard.Overall, I would say this room was not worth the rack rate of $250+ per night, but it was far beyond my expectations at the Priceline bargain rate!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b3fdf9c0e3a2e978cffe29b1c35c547a" url=""><![CDATA[Great budget hotel I stayed at this hotel from May 17th-24th with my boyfriend and another friend. We had a one bedroom suite with a kitchenette which was great for preparing breakfast sandwiches on several occasions and storing beverages in the full sized fridge. The lobby of the hotel is very nice and comfortable with places to sit and read, relax or use the internet. The pool was nice, although it closes at 10:00pm and the hot tub was barely big enough for the three people in my group to fit in at the same time. There are some nice loungers by the pool and even cabanas with nearly full sized beds that give it a spa feel. However, not many people hung out around the hotel since the beach is just a few blocks away. This was a great location for walking around day or night with easy access to the boardwalk and major shopping areas in Waikiki. It was also close to restaurants and nightclubs and there is a full size grocery store just a couple blocks away. Overall, a one bedroom suite for three people including air from Seattle booked for $500 p/p was a steal, but don't expect anything fancy (or even Motel 6 quality) in the rooms themselves. I wasn't disappointed though because we hardly spent any time in the room except for sleeping, bathing and the occasional meal. When looking at the website, 1 bedroom suites go for $177+, which we paid less than half that price.... my suggestion, book through a different site to get a package deal because this hotel is not worth paying full price for.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>