<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="cf1c2c83876bea40b283cc924fd4f32c" url=""><![CDATA[Loved this resort! Have just returned from a week at the Bavaro Princess. Was nervous having read some of the reviews on here but shouldnt have been!The grounds of this hotel are fabulous and the individual suites are quiet and secluded. The resort is extensive and some rooms are a way from the beach and the main lobby area but the transportation is frequent and the grounds are well worth walking around. The food was not the greatest at the buffet (not really good at all!) but there was always hamburgers, pizza hot dogs! There are several other restaurants available although some at an additional cost. Did not suffer any ill effects from the food and believe me if anyone would it was going to be me!Beach is superb, miles of white sand and we walked the entire length of the beach! No problems with any hawkers, they were there but not intrusive. If you want to reserve a palm umbrella on the beach you need to be up early and leave your towels on the desired spot! By 9am there are none left although plenty of lounge chairs without any shade. Forget the 30 minute rule that appears in the hotel brochure!Would not hesitate to recommend this hotel!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="025c28d1ddd2814772ecb514aacee191" url=""><![CDATA[Not bad for the money Just returned from a week at this hotel and must say was pleasantly surprised as the reviews were not too favourable.We had a room in Block 6 which was a Caribbean Spa Suite, two double beds, a jacuzzi tub, double sinks and separate shower. No problems whatsover with hot water or pressure. Was a small leak over one of the sinks but nothing too worry or complain about. Room was made up everyday but did have to ask for beer in the fridge!Check in was a little slow to start but eventually someone else showed up to help and that sped things up. Check out was done in a blink of an eye! Service in the buffet restaurant was slow at times and we sometimes had to catch a waiters eye for coffee, wine etc. Food wasnt too bad, about standard for mass production and there was always something you could select. (great rolls etc at every meal). We never tried any of the other restaurants as we do not like to work to a time table when we are away!Le Cafe had to have the best iced coffees and the Irish Coffee was great. Think we went in here everyday at least once! Barstaff were friendly and drinks were good, not watered down!Beach was crowded and you really had to snatch up the shade early or even the night before but if you were happy to move with the shade during the day you could always find a nice place to relax. No troubles with the hawkers on the beach, if you dont look in their direction they dont even bother you. Would recommend you get a massage, $20 for 30 mins and worth every cent!!Overall we were pleased with the resort. Nice and small and everything was easily accesable and only being 25 mins from the airport is an added plus.If you are looking for luxury this is not the place but good value for money if you are on a tight budget and are not the really picky sort. Go with the flow take the good with the not so good and you will have a great time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>