<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="fbb9f35ae19875fe58349fa04fab7ad9" url=""><![CDATA[Absolutely Loved the Belvedere We stayed at the Belvedere for 4 nights before a cruise and loved it. We were a bit apprehensive because as the saying goes, A 2 star is a 2-star, but we can't figure out why this hotel isn't at least a 3 star. The exterior is very impressive and the lobby is gorgeous. We asked for a room on a higher floor away from the elevator (as recommended by this website) and got a king-size bed in a non-smoking room on the 15th floor, 2 doors away from the elevator. The room was much bigger than expected and perfectly clean. The only complaint we could come up with, and it was a minor one, was the bathroom door was awkward for blow drying my hair. since there was no fan, so I couldn't close the door. The kitchenette was great to have as well. The staff were friendly and accomodating. We walked everywhere from this hotel. I've read about elevator problems but the only thing we noticed is that there didn't seem to be enough of them. Often, on our way down, there was no more room for passengers when the door would open, but we never had any problem because we were almost at the top. We hope to get back to New York someday and will certainly stay at the Belvedere again. It doesn't disappoint!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5c22cf0771fdf2391985440e208de753" url=""><![CDATA[Dive in Honolulu I completely forget to write a review of this hotel after we stayed there last year, but I'm doing it anyway because people need to be made aware of what a horrific hotel this is. We found it on Expedia and are disgusted that they could call this a 3 star hotel. We just came back from a 2 star in Manhattan, the Belvedere, and it was absolutely gorgeous. It should be a 3 or 4 star and the Ocean Resort should be 1. The staff there were awful and rude at check-in and check-out. The room was disgusting, and we wouldn't even set foot in the filthy kitchen. The air conditioner was so loud we couldn't even turn it on, even if we wanted the sickening stuff inside to be blown around our room. The bathroom shower head sprayed all over the toilet and everywhere else. Thankfully, we only had to stay in this dive one night after a cruise, before flying home.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="299aae3047132f4656d83cf55b2d47cc" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel, Great Location We stayed at this hotel at the last minute when we missed our cruise ship out of Fort Lauderdale due to flight delays. We were flown to San Juan where we spent 3 nights until our ship arrived there. It was a last minute scramble to find a hotel and not knowing the area--but knowing Hampton Inns--I booked with them and was happy to see that this property is just like the others we've stayed at. I don't know why this is considered a 2* property, it should be at least 3 IMHO. The front desk stafff were pleasant and helpful, the pool area was great and the rooms were clean. The signature beds were a most welcome comfort after a very long and stressful traveling day. The location is close to some great restaurants, beaches and casinos. Unless you're looking to stay in Old San Juan, I would highly recommend this hotel. San Juan hotels are generally expensive but at $229 this was a bargain.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>