<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="515e8f62afd86912376566cb52201c72" url=""><![CDATA[Fabulous Hotel My son (14) and I stayed at the Sydney Hilton for 6 nights, (20 Feb - 26 Feb.) We were on the executive floor and things could not have been any nicer. Every morning there was a lovely breakfast aand evenings we had light appetizers and drinks. The hotel was spotless, the staff was attentive, informative and friendly and the hotel was situated perfectly - near the bus, subway or you could get a taxi immediately. Great gym and all was perfect. The pool was not as great as the pool at the Hilton in Greece (which is glass sided), but I would not hesitate to recommend this hotel to anyone. We paid a very reasonable rate and certainly feel this hotel is a great value.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8cc792ef23e4b786110af6ec13c3846f" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel with Wonderful Staff I really enjoyed the associates at this property. I would especially like to commend Carlo at Reception and the exceedingly amusing young male Irish bartender. My son and I had an outstanding time and will continue to stay at the International Hiltons. This property did not disappoint. It is about a 10 minute walk from the Arc de Triomphe and you can walk straight down from the Arc de Triomphe to the Louvre. It is also close to the Courcelles Metro station and you can get anywhere from there. Treats by our bedside, very clean rooms and rooms much larger then a typical Parisien hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b112b8c515bf942a3f3f039f20d452af" url=""><![CDATA[Darwin Saved The Day My son and I were in LA and on a very tight schedule. We were leaving the Universal City Hilton and needed to print our boarding passes before arriving at the airport that evening. We would not have access to a printer for the entire day - but the website for the airline was down. I spoke with Darwin Wang at the front desk and he attempted to print them out - and even called the airline for us. Even though we were checking out, he said he would check back on the airline site for us later and we should come back and he would leave the boarding passses in an envelope for us at the front desk......And amazingly enough, he did. This was exceptional customer service. This is what makes people want to return to a hotel. We have stayed within the last two years at Hiltons in Greece, Australia and in the U.S. - and on this trip we wpent the first night in a VERY lackluster Hilton (Mission Valley San Diego) where we would never return, but Darwin Wang restored my faith in the U.S. Hiltons. Universal City Hilton highly recommended for great staffing.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>