<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="a96d232bc5e7fdd8ba5c446d441e4a62" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Location, value for money Stayed at the Star Hotel in Shinjuku from 1 - 6 September 2007. I chose it primarily for its location and it sure didn't disappoint. Paid USD120 per night for our 5 night stay.The hotel is a 5 minute (or less) walk from Shinjuku Station. Those who know Tokyo would know that Shinjuku is a behemoth of a train station that purportedly serves 2 million passengers a day. After having experienced it, I can safely say that the statement is definitely true. If you take the Airport Limousine Bus service from Narita Airport, you will alight right at Shinjuku Station outside the Keio department store and (as previously mentioned) it will be a mere 5 minute walk to the hotel.The hotel lobby is on the second level of the building. Staff speaks decent English to be understood and knew what we were talking about. Staff attitude was pleasant though somewhat mechanical, I attribute it to the language barrier. We arrived just after 11am, but was told they are very strict about the check-in time of 1pm. We deposited our bags with reception and went about exploring the fascinating Shinjuku neighbourhood.We were given a room on the seventh floor. It was well appointed but tiny. The room had:-- queen size bed;- TV with only local channels;- empty mini refrigerator; and- attached rather low-ceiling bathroom with bathtub and bidet.There was no in-room safe, so take care to store your expensive items properly.There was no more room to walk once I open up my luggage on the floor area in front of the window. Despite its small size, the room was more than sufficient for our needs - who wants to stay in the room all day anyway?There is a vending machine in the lobby selling Haagen Daz ice cream and a vending machine on our floor selling drinks. We didn't try the restaurant on the same level as the lobby, our booking didn't include daily breakfast. There's a Pronto Cafe and another restaurant (which name I can't remember) on the ground floor of the same building.The hotel is less than 3 minutes from Kabuki-cho, the red-light district of Tokyo. Despite its less than desirable reputation, we found no trouble walking around the area even late at night. There was no discernible noise whatsoever from the proximity either.Other notable attractions within walking distance from the hotel are the countless countless eateries (there's no bad food in Tokyo!), shopping galore (several department stores ENCASE Shinjuku Station, not to mention the others like Takashimaya and Isetan) and the Tokyo Metropolitan Building for its free 45th floor observatory.A truly superbly located hotel at a great price (by Tokyo standards).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7d6bab38c223582a017295aedb571fbf" url=""><![CDATA[A tragically hip hotel Being less than a block from Times Square, Hotel QT is unmatched in its location. The hip design (a swimming pool in the lobby and a check-in counter that doubled up as a grocery store of sorts) will certainly appeal to the young.The room we stayed in, 1407, was very spacious. The fixtures were really modern and hip in design, it had a rain shower, Neutrogena toiletries, see-through refrigerator, in-room safe, LCD TV, cordless phone and really luxurious sheets.The safe in our room was locked in 'close' despite the door being left opened. It was a full 45 minutes and two phone calls to the front desk before a technician came along to rectify it. The LCD TV, though beautiful to look at, had a constant reception problem on some channels and the remote control was almost totally non-responsive. Perhaps it needed a battery change, but we didn't bother.There were absolutely no hooks of any kind in the bathroom area. Nowhere whatsoever to hang your towel as you're taking a shower. Perhaps hooks didn't match their hip design concept.Despite the minor flaws, we'd still recommend Hotel QT highly, for which other hotel can afford you the chance to have your breakfast at the bar?
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>