<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="386ce1938e48211eab777e6153863678" url=""><![CDATA[Great Service at the Pool - Great Service by Front Office From front desk to back end this was a pleasant and enjoyable experience. I might have done as another and rented a car in retrospec since leaving the resort for any distance is difficult without one. Although, there is a little village just to the north along the parking lot path to some good local establishments, like Tommy's. Back at the resort, the island was very good with great facilities for water sports, good bar and sunning. One in the party did have a day on a hobby cat where the backstay broke, the operators were out in the water to help immedeately. That they were always watching was very good. On another occasion the last shuttle back to the resort was out of fuel anf the resort had to get other boats to transport many back to the resort. The best comment about this incident was by one of the ladies What a shame they have to give us two more hours in paridise. The resort gave a house credit to everyone and the GM was there to appologize to each guest. Very professional approach.Of special note were some of the most professional staff I have encountered at any property were here in the the front desk and in hospitallity.If there is any thing you needed to be done go straight to Ms Torres and Ms Bosque at the front desk, they must get my special mention. In hospitality Mr J Castro makes a really special Mojito at the Spalsh Bar at the pool. He has a wide range of concoctions and just remembewrs each guest. If he is not there be sure to say hello to Ms A Marquez and Mr J Lopez. These are the best hospitality staff I have meet besides those at the Moana Surfrider, my favorite hotel. Last was the casino, a very pleasant mix of locals and guests. It was just enought to keep you interested but a caution to all is that putting a $100 in the penny slot machine will mean you play forever. A couple of suggestions for the Management:The pool bar needs a couple of ceiling fans for summer circulation and one or two televisions to capture those who want the news or sports. Also light it up at night and keep it open until 9 or 10 pm. That would allow there to be anice afternoon happy hour say 3-5p that would keep people there longer. Might also put stools in the pool side. Food service to the pool should come from both locations instead of just the one bythe cabanas. We had an ocean view room with a great view of the entire resort and a direct walk to the pool and two floors down from the lobby. The steakhouse was delicious, beautifully prepared and presented. The Seafood was tremendous, especially the Sea Bass. Al in all it was great , thanks for a great get away - I will be back
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d5b8e537df8adb56bcdb390e0016d922" url=""><![CDATA[Paris - A place to be in the center of things This was a very interesting hotel, as it resides on a small side street just around the corner from The Hotel Ritz and the Tulleries. The front desk personnel were fabulous, knowledgable of the area and exstemely professional. From here a must to visit - a short walk to The New York Harry's Bar whare for bourbon drinkers, they have Knob Creek Bourbon and good hot dogs. For a higher time there is the Hemingway Bar at the Ritz, be sure to get Collin the make you a special drink and empress the ladies. He is one of the top ten mixologists and his mixes will astound you. Besides that you will meet both tourists and locals. They will make your evening interesting at the least. At the holel ask about the little bistros down the street for breakfast and dinner, they are more that happy to introduce you to the neighborhood. That what makes this special along with the Irish Pud just across the street - food and drink is great. The turn down service was perfect, the room had a great bath with lots of HOT water, plenty of towels, a robe and slippers. The best of all worlds was that this property actually takes care of anything you might leave in the room at checkout. I happened to leave my drivers license in the safe when I left. When I arrived in Brussels I realised this and had my hotel call for me. The hotel had the item and forwarded it to me at my next stop in Amsterdam, it was there when I arrived. WHAT A RELIEF!!!!!!!! That makes this my number ONE hotel in Paris from now on, as well as there being this Iris Pub across the street run by Chicagoians. Stay and enjoy.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="12888c09ed8c1beac59a1c30ed026a7b" url=""><![CDATA[The Story Behind the Gables These old merchant houses that have been combined over the years to creat and recreat this Hotel make for wonderful reading ijn the Hotel brochure, be sure to do this. Arrival from the train station was quick and the welcome mat was out the minute I stepped out of the car. The doorman greated me and once I gave my name, remember it the rest of my stay. The front office was very courtious and the ladies are very pretty and polite. I had a package sent to the Hotel, it was waitng at reception with my check-in folio. The room assignment was quick and the room was beautiful and unusually spacious for Europe. Plenty of towels and very clean. This location is just a block from the Ann Frank House and in the neighboorhoods, so walking is a must to explore and appreciate the archectecture of the Old World. I had wanted to see the Heinekin Brewery but alas it was closed for renovation. So the Concierge sent me to the Bols Liquor on this Tuesday. Well, my one complaint, Bols is closed on Tuesday. But a great walk and I found a nice sandwich shop and a cold beer during my trek. One thing I do not normally do is take Hotel tours but the Hotel has it's own boat for a nightly canal tour with on board coctails and the Captian narrates the trip. This is worth every euro and I would not hesitate to take it again, especially if romance were in the cards. On my day of departure the Hotel had transport ready for us and we were whisked reluctantly to the airport. If you are on a tight budget this may not be the place but I found it worth more that The Grand Amsterdam, currently a Sofitel, which has previosly been my Hotel of choice in Amsterdam. Stay here and get out and expore this beautiful city and meet the people. Remember take the small glass for beer after foamed and scraped. Have a great stay.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>