<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="75e141fdc3d5de1ed84d6238fd7c800f" url=""><![CDATA[Not brilliant Just got back from 3 nights in this hotel.Things good:Location - not the most picturesque part of Amsterdam - but only 10 mins walk from the centre.Helpful staff - staff seemed to be trying to be helpful.Free wake up calls.Things bad:No bar - the website we booked with (and several others I have just checked whilst writing this) stated this hotel had a bar - IT DOES NOT! A bar is a good place to meet when there are a few of you - its one of the reasons we chose this hotel over others.We complained to reception - they were not interested and said we should write to the owner.Heat - it was -2 outside but the radiators in the room were barely warm - it was cold.Room size - very little floor space. 2 of us could not get changed or dressed at the same time.Noise - could here exactly what the people in the next room were up to - even though they weren't that loud!Towels - thread bare and with holes.Bathroom - toilet too near to the wall and not enough leg room. Anyone over 6 foot tall can't sit on it!Lift - old style where you manually open the door and with nothing protecting you from the moving wall on one side. Not for kids.Stairs - IMHO not suitable for children at all - wide bending staircase with very small steps on one side that would be easy to miss and fall on.I lost my footing once and grabbed the handrail - it came away from the wall.Breakfast - limited selection continental. Bread and rolls, dutch taost, couple of jams, butter, cold hard boiled eggs in shells, 1 cheese and 2 cooked meats. Some cerial and a couple of fruit juices. Plus hot drinks. Not the biggest selection I have ever seen and very little that really appeals. We only ate here once and chose to eat in town and pay the extra.No batteries in the TV remote control - one of my pet hates as its such an easy thing to get right!Smoky smell - apprently the day before some guests had dropped cigarettes down the lift well which caught fire. Consequently the hall way and lift smelt very strongly of smoke. Apparently they had just got the lifts working - would not recommend this hotel if the lifts are out of order - see comments on stairs.Overrall condition - hotel seemed tired and worn. Lots of things seem to look very used / chipped / cracked / loose etc. Attention to detail in the cleaning could be better. From stories I have heard this hotel is a long way from being the worst in Amsterdam. But there are better for similar money too.We had a great weekend - but that was down to the good company and Amsterdam being a great City.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>