<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="64918fa3dfbac06d352757cb007f2532" url=""><![CDATA[Pleasant and convenient When we arrived for a three-day visit to Toronto, we were told that we had been upgraded to a deluxe suite. This was a pleasant, attractively decorated large room with a kitchen area which included not only a refrigerator, microwave and coffee maker, but a dishwasher and a clothes washer and dryer.The location is excellent. We had come to attend the opera, and the hotel was only about two blocks from the Hummingbird Centre. The King Street subway station is just outside either door, or one can reach it via the extensive underground PATH. The staff were very pleasant and did their best to be helpful, although they were often busy and sometimes did not have the answers right at their fingertips. I have a few minor caveats: (1)If one takes the Toronto Airport Express from Pearson Airport, the stop nearest this hotel is at the Royal York, about four blocks away. (2) Our room had an easy chair with an ottoman which looked as though it would be comfortable. It was decorated with a double row of large nailheads along the sides and back of the chair, which bumped me in the head when I leaned back and made the chair uncomfortable for me. (I am short, and a taller person probably wouldn't be bothered. There were other places to sit.) (3) The booklet in the room describing the hotel's amenities, room service, etc. implied that if a guest needed information about airport bus schedules, where to rent a car, etc. all that guest had to do was to contact the front desk, using the speed dial on the phone. We didn't use the speed dial, but rather asked in person, and we did get the answers we needed, but we usually had to wait while the desk clerk or valet had to look things up and deal with other matters as well. We weren't in a big hurry, but our questions didn't seem very complicated.As I said, these were minor things. Our stay was pleasant, and we found the hotel comfortable and conveniently located.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>