<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="303fa72d759017f3ad92139014244a77" url=""><![CDATA[Remember it fondly months later The City Inn is a spectacular hotel. Its modern design makes W properties feel slightly cheap and over the top. I requested a room with a view when checking in (late in the evening) and the staff informed me that I could have a suite with a GREAT view or I could try a room. I tried my booked Club room, and when getting there was completely stunned, with a view including river, skyscrapers, and the beautiful MI5 building in front. The full floor-to-ceiling windows were gorgeous but just the beginning of a room so stunning a friend, who had been busily telling me a story on the way there, just forgot what she was saying about and went Wow.I had a minor emergency one night: it was 10 PM, and a belt I had just bought was too loose. It was my only belt and I had to dress smart. I let Reception know and, right after I had finished my late dinner, my fixed belt was sitting in my room bed. Very impressive. Walking to the subway is a bit of a hassle (I even miss that though! the area is nice) but you quickly discover an Oxford St bus that also goes past the Houses of Parliament etc and leaves you one block away. It's a very scenic busride.The only thing I didn't like was the restaurant. I only got the end of a mediocre buffet breakfast and was a bit rushed. Dinner was little better. The menu sounded excellent but in the end I didn't feel compelled to finish my meal. My waitress was very enthusiastic but also very new, and spoke practically no English. She knew less of the complicated menu items than me, but in fairness did every effot she should. In general, however, the whole restaurant was quite disorganised, with waiters running around not coping, even with a half-full venue late night, and with everything taking AGES to arrive.All in all, the City Inn was such a nice stay I remember it fondly often. I will never forget sitting by the window my last night in London, after a night out, eating a plate of red fruits and a glass of champagne while looking out the window listening to a CD from their collection. I'll never pass a chance to stay there again, even if I dine elsewhere.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a73736357977d63063db742ad27cef95" url=""><![CDATA[Not really worth it We paid around $350 a night for a suite at the Affinia 50 at a discounted price. The value we got was far inferior to this price even if it's not a bad hotel per-se. In a city like New York there are far better options available.We arrived there late night to find an indifferent check-in and a very large room completely unpopulated of furniture. The problems began rapidly: some of the parcels we had been expected were not there. I had contacted the hotel previously to request my parcels to be held. I assumed they were delayed.Once in the room, we found we had no hot water AND that the toilet was leaking water quite badly. We were so tired we just fixed it with a hanger - the Mexican way - until the next day. Not impressive.The next morning my girlfriend had a really important interview and the hot water wasn't coming. In the end it magically appeared, despite the front desk ignoring us. The toilet was fixed almost 24 hours after reporting it.The rooms do look a bit like the pictures, in a style I personally found quite disagreeable. Objectively, however, once inside the lobby you felt the place was a dump. We didn't see the famous bell boys with the hat until the day we were leaving, and the ridiculously small lobby with the potted trees and the fountain are not awe-inspiring considering the price we paid. If you get a deal, however, this wouldn't be concerning.Finally, our parcels were actually RETURNED TO SENDER by the hotel staff, and despite my repeated mentioning of how angry we were at this to various members of staff, including the manager, we did not get one dollar refunded off our ridiculously high fare. We got into an enormous amount of trouble to rescue some of the ones which were rescuable.In the end we did sleep and were well situated, but I'd recommend the Parker Meridien for a higher-end option if the price is right. There's thousands of options in the Big Apple to have to go through this.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>