<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="ef4d7d13a259409e654c99259cef6e60" url=""><![CDATA[Old World Charm An old spanish hotel with a lot of charm. The rooms were small, but very comfortable, with hairdryers, ironing boards, shampoos, etc. The rooftop continental breakfast was quite nice, and overlooks the hillside of Ponce. The staff at this hotel was very impressive, especially the front desk. They were VERY helpful and up to date on the local information. The restaurant there is a bit pricey and I did not eat there. Downtown Ponce virtually shuts down at 8 pm during the week, and wound up eating at Churches Chicken. I was there for two nights, but one would have been more than enough.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c3f33d87fce8cf754b3a387a75e5304d" url=""><![CDATA[Clean and Nice This hotel is quite nice. The rooms are large, and beds comfortable. They also have laundry facilities on site, which makes it very nice if you're changing hotels every day. The downside is that there are no elevators, however they do have a sign up that if you need help with your bags----ask. Getting morning coffee means walking downstairs and waiting in the restaurant. I tried the Mexican restaurant on site--The Blue Iguana, and found their food excellent, and very reasonably priced. (Under 10.00) The front desk staff was exceptional, and very helpful. I will go back, but will bring a coffeemaker.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d03cd0051fcfb78749077979874cb921" url=""><![CDATA[DON'T EVEN CONSIDER STAYING ANYWHERE ELSE !!!!! Stayed for 2 nights Oct. 2 3. Check in was a breeze at 1:45pm.The ocean-view room was immaculately clean, with refrig. safe, hairdryer, coffeemaker, and upscale selection of shampoos and lotions. The bathroom was very large, marble and mahogany with glass shower. The view from the balcony of room 716 was totally awesome---overlooking the ocean and Old San Juan.ALL of the elevators are working in the hotel, and yes, there is some renovation going on in some areas, but they are being done in such a way that you don't really notice---no inconvenience whatsoever. The pool areas are spotlessly clean, and very well staffed. The main pool area has food service available and beach assess, with a swim-up bar. The entire staff at this hotel is one of the best I have ever encountered. Whatever you need is available, fast, and always with a smile. Joey at the pool bar is a great source of information on the area, and a fun guy. Makes you feel right at home. Guest Services printed out my boarding pass the morning of departure, complimentary, which saved me some time at the airport.The ONLY bad thing-----I had to leave, but will be back !!!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>