<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="a79e2121d35c0b116bce3f563bcaa451" url=""><![CDATA[Mixed feelings about the Savoy We stayed at the Savoy for three nights at the end of April, booked through a Luxury Link package that worked out to about $500 USD/nt including the buffet breakfast. As others have said, the location on Pza Repubblica is ideal for sightseeing, as it's just south of the Duomo and in the exact center of everything you want to see in Florence. (We stayed at the Excelsior on our last visit, which is a long walk to some of the attractions on the eastern side of the Centro). The flip side is thatif you open the windows between 9 AM- 9PM, you will hear a lot of the street noise. Our deluxe double was pretty compact and decorated in the same shades of green as its sister property, the de Russie, in Rome. The linens were luxe, the beds fine, and the bathroom very comfortable with all the ususal amenities you'd expect at this type of property. The only decoration are these Ikea-appearing paintings of shoes in the rooms and public spaces-- it was explained that the Ferragamo family is somehow related to Rocco Forte. After the opulence of the Excelsior, the decor here seemed international bland-- the hotel gives you no sense of place and you feel that you could be anywhere.The concierge and front desk staff are terrific, as are the doormen. In the lower level there is a room with 2 computers and printer, and internet access is free (they give you a code).The breakfast buffet is kind of a cramped affair, with the food and tables in their rather small bar area (with overflow into the also small dining room) With people bumping into each other getting the food, and so jammed in at the tables, it wasn't very enjoyable.Given Florence prices, we probably paid a fair price for what we received. Still, we enjoyed our experience at The Excelsior much more.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c1861854fbb12dd6ffdc6269b7a260cf" url=""><![CDATA[Very, very nice! I can't add much to what the reviewer from St. Paul wrote. It is a magnificent hotel with a gorgeous lobby, gorgeous rooms, huge, fantastic bathrooms, and very helpful and gracious staff. And ..the Heavenly Bed, which IS as good as is touted to be.It is indeed pricey, but we had a 3-for-2 rate from the Starwood website (prepaid), which amounted to about 1100 Euros for 3 nights. I didn't expect much as an SPG Gold, but we were upgraded to a very large room facing the Arno. While the view was sensational, you will hear some street noise from the rooms facing the Arno.The restaurant and bar prices are astronomical, as stated in other reviews here. True in most grand hotels, but there is no shortage of restaurants/cafes/bars in Florence. We have stayed at *wood properties in many of the European capitals, and this is among the best. We will definitely return.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7bb85d5845ddc1fddd3b023469ff960e" url=""><![CDATA[Extraordinary Service at the Hotel d'Aubusson My husband and I just returned from a 7-night stay at the Hotel d'Aubusson. We opted for a grand luxe loft room, offered in their Winter Promotion, where 1 Euro= 1 USD.The location of the hotel is ideal, two blocks from the Seine and a few more to Blvd. St. Germaine.The street runs right into the Pont Neuf, but for the most part we heard almost no street noise whatsoever. Our room was #406, one of the larger rooms, with 2 beds together, probably in total the width of an American King but shorter.... As we are both over 6' tall, they were definitely too short and this was an annoyance. The mattresses are typically Parisian.. hard... but the linens are very high-quality. There was a small sitting area, with a round table and 2 chairs, and plenty of room to walk around and store luggage. The bathroom wasquite large, and well appointed with terry robes, Hermes toiletries, and all the towels you could use.The housekeeping staff are very diligent, and the room was spotless.The public areas are quite attractive, and the Bar Laurent has a great jazz group playing Thurs., Fri.and Sat. evenings. Breakfast is okay, not wonderful nor worth the 23 Euro tab if not included in the room rate. Service in the breakfast room is quite good, and they will make excellent omelettes for an extra charge. The gentleman who runs the bar and sitting room in the evenings is just fantastic... he treats the whole first floor as his fiefdom and makes sure everybody is well-serviced.The real test of this hotel occurred when on day 2 of our stay, I somehow contracted a serious GI problem (food poisoning, most likely) which necessitated getting a doctor to the hotel, prescriptions delivered, etc. The entire staff could not have been nicer of more helpful to us... they were absolutely wonderful. That the desk staff spoke such wonderful English was a real help in communicating the needs we had. When Iemerged a couple days later, everyone inquired how I was, asked if there was anything I needed,and doted on us with genuine care and concern. We would have liked to stay at one of the Leading Hotels of the World in Paris, as we usually do in other European cities. Paris is just so insanely expensive, and the dollar now so weak, that we couldn't justify those prices. While we might have had beds more suitable to us, I doubt that we would have experienced better service than we we had at the d'Aubusson. The entire staff is a family of genuinely helpful and caring people. We will return.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="639ff6e68ed4e04f4b055d40ac1640de" url=""><![CDATA[Still a very good hotel We stayed here for a week in '04, and the reviews on TripAdvisor since then did give us pause for concern in booking again for Feb. '06. We visit Europe 4-5 times a year, and always stay in 4-or 5-star hotels, many of them also affiliated with LHW. I E-mailed them in November with my concerns about the renovation and the complaints registered here. I received a prompt E-Mail back, stating that the renovation would not start until later in '06 and we would be assured of a room in fine condition.We paid 190 Euros/nt for the identical room we had on the sixth floor two years ago. It was great; good bedding, high-quality linens, bathrobes and slippers, nice toiletries, a gift of chocolates and Spanish wine in the room. Everything was exceptionally clean. Yes, there were some dings on the chair by the desk, and a couple of very minor spots on the carpeting. Planning to write a review here upon our return, I specifically looked for the issues that were noted in previous reviews. But for the most part, there is very little to criticize.The service remains exemplary. The doorman, David (from Pennsylvania) is a gem... very helpful with directions, recommendations, and a taxi when we needed one. Both he and the concierege staff remembered us and gave us a warm welcome. The concierge staff are great... they provided wonderful restaurant recommendations. The location, for us, is ideal... several great tapas places within a few blocks, 4 blocks from Plaza Catalunya and the top of Las Ramblas. With the windows closed, no street noise to be heard at all.The only thing you have to be careful about is that the taxi drivers still know the hotel as the Ritz, not the Palace. There are several hotels in BCN with palace as part of the name, and we were taken to several of them by mistake. You have to give the driver the name AND street address.... get the hotel's card when you arrive, and provide it to any taxi driver you use. Is it the Four Seasons in Istanbul, the Grand Bretagne in Athens, or the Grand Hotel in Stockholm?No, it is showing a bit of wear. It needs some TLC to restore its former luster. But it is still a very well-managed, charming, old-world hotel in a great location in Barcelona.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>