<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="58890c3731a1faeecedd7e421b896ab5" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel in the French Quarter I stayed at the Bourbon Orleans for 7 nights, June 25th- July 2nd, and thought that it was a great hotel. I was on the fourth floor in a townhouse suite. I didn't find the noise to be a problem, however I was not overlooking Bourbon street. According to some of my friends staying on the third floor there was some noise from Bourbon but it could easily be blocked out by running the bathroom fan. If you don't want street and party noise talk to the front desk at the time of checkin to recieve a room away from the street. The location of the hotel cannot be beat. It is on the corner of Bourbon and Orleans right in the heart of the French Quarter. It is within walking distance of the Mississippi River, and the St. Charles Street Car to the Garden District. There were only a couple of small inconviences that we experienced while at the hotel. There was only one small trash can in the lower part of the room and none in the bathroom. There was only one phone in the room and it was located downstairs. The phone was cordless however the battery would occasionally die before the wakeup call and I would have to return it to the cradle in order to answer it and have the ringing stop. The wayport data connector didn't work and when I called the front desk they ensured that Engineering would be sent right up. Three days later it was repaired. The room service was decent. We ordered lunch the first day and it was excellent. Based on that experience we ordered breakfast the next morning. The breakfast was delivered 20 minutes late and the eggs were not very good. Besides that, the dirty tray sat outside our door for a full day before I called the front desk to have it removed. Overall, this was a very good experience. It is easy to pinpoint the minor inconviences but they were well worth the comforts of the hotel. The hotel staff was excellent and will go out of their way to assist you with anything you need. When I return to New Orleans I will stay at the Wyndham Bourbon Orleans again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>