<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="8628258e0475947b0b56122a2ce0929d" url=""><![CDATA[We were Robbed!! Occidental Grand Flamenco, Punta CanaMy husband and I stayed at this resort in April 24,-May1When I say we were robbed, I don't mean that the resort wasn't worth the money, I mean that we were literally ROBBED!Somebody came into our room while we were out and stole all of our money (the one and only time I didn't use the safe!!) We were packed to leave that morning, and only wanted an hour or two at the beach before we left.............I had my passports and departure taxes still in the safe, and my hubby had what was in his wallet, otherwise we would have been left stranded!We had been extremely generous with all of the workers so it was very disheartening, to say the least!The resort itself was well kept, the grounds were very nice.The service left a little to be desired.The room was adequateThe beach was beautifulThe pools were greatUp until the last day (only hours before we checked out)the vacation was great!I wish I could say that the managemnt was helpful, but I can'tThe Signature rep commiserated, but could do nothingI won't be staying at the Occidental again!Cuba is looking better all the time!Marilyn
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d8638da6bac916a37c64472696333c1d" url=""><![CDATA[Two Weeks is Too Long We stayed at the Barcelo Bavaro Caribe' Resort from April 25th to May 9th 2005.I can't say enough about the beautiful grounds, they are kept very manicured, by so many hard working people.The beach is fantastic too, with white powdery sand and crystal clear turquoise water.Overall it wasn't a bad resort, although we had some minor problems.Two weeks is really too long though.I didn't find the people there overly friendly, even though we tipped generously, and gave lots of gifts too. At the Mexican restaurant we were left sitting for a half hour after we had been given menus, after that length of time we just left. I don't know if they were ignoring us, or they had forgotten us. We had been there the night before and had great service, and the workers had been very friendly. At our own buffett we found the people to be quite friendly, of course there again, we tipped them at every meal and gave every one of them gifts too.The food wasn't what we were used to, it is their local food, and I have to say our standards for cleanliness are much higher. However the selection was very good, and we certainaly never went hungry. The reception people were very matter of fact too, with hardly a smile.Thank God for Nancy!!, our tour director (Signature)She had answers to all of our questions (and we had a lot of questions)I broke a tooth off my partial plate while I was there and she even got me some crazy glue to hold it in place until I got home to a dentist.We went to the entertainment at all of the resorts as well as the Tropicalissimo Show, which was fantastic!The casino was fun. The train rides were great too.I don't think that any of the bartenders gave me spirits in my drinks (even once), that I didn't have to ask for it :-( and I only had 5 drinks the whole time I was there, and my husband doesn't drink at all.We took gifts for the Outback Safari to distribute to the villagers schools that they support, I think they do a wonderful service!We thought the trip itself would be a little too rigorous for us at our age.So, to sum it all up.........I would go to the same resort again, but just for the beautiful grounds ,the beach, the walking in the park behind the convention center which we did every day, to enjoy the birds and flowers there.Please people, we pay a lot for our vacations there and we know that you work very hard for a very little bit of money, that is why we tip so generously and come bearing gifts for you. A smile is the only thanks we require. We love the Dominican and plan to return at Christmastime.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>