<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="076fe50642a3aac2e80aead96fcd6958" url=""><![CDATA[Truly memorable Selected this hotel based on the previous Trip Advisor reports. It is hard to fault any aspect of our stay. We were 2 couples and had 2 of the larger apartments with views of the canal. Rooms were very spacious, exceptionally clean and the large beds very comfortable.Heating was responsive and toiletries of a good standard.We ate breakfast there on each of the 3 days - a good quality continental style buffet with good supply of fresh fruit.The reception staff were helpful.The hotel is very well located just a few minutes walk from St Mark's Square where you can board a waterbus to most areas.Barry Jones
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a895e6e024d3bf4b72002c35d816a2fd" url=""><![CDATA[Hard to fault this hotel Having read other reviews we were confident to pre-pay with the hotel and secure rooms at a very competitive price. We had looked for 2 city-view rooms but on booking only one was available. This was rectified on arrival AND we were given a free upgrade for the second room.Rooms are clean, beds comfortable and our double was 6foot wide. The bathrooms are excellent with great showers and a good quality range of toiletries. Excellent hospitality tray and generous electric sockets. The public rooms are similarly spacious and well maintained.The cooked breakfast was, perhaps less inspiring and our friends were disappointed at the lack of vegetarian sausages nor was fish of any sort offered. Many people would be happy with the excellent continental style buffet which is cheaper and includes fresh fruit and good selection of cereals, breads, pastries, meats and cheeses. All good quality.The hotel is in a quiet location (valuable in London) and very close to Tower Hill tube station, No15 bus route into the West End with a very frequent service and one of the stops for the Open-top Sightseeing bus tours. As mentioned by previous reporter they will keep cases for you if you arrive early and/or want somewhere to keep them after check-out.Barry
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>