<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="54d7f75396159f1fcd131a7f94569d35" url=""><![CDATA[Great Service / Great view! Aloha! I have many great things to say about The Park Shore Waikiki (Part of Aqua Hotels Resorts)! It's in a GREAT location as it is located near the end the Waikiki Beach Strip @ 2586 Kalakaua Ave in Honolulu. It is steps away from the beach, great restaurants and shopping. Everything you need is within easy walking distance on the main strip. The view is amazing as you can see the Diamond Head Volcanic Crater in its full glory, Waikiki Beach and Honolulu's famous sunsets all from your room (depending on what kind of room you book, of course.) The pool area is very nice and well maintained. You can see the ocean from the pool area as it is located on the 3rd floor of the hotel. It offers a nice leisure, less busy atmosphere than the beach. The best part of our hotel stay was the friendly great service we received! Leanor and Terry truly cared about making our stay as comfortable and as great as possible. They really went above and beyond. Every where we turned the staff was great! It makes a big difference if you feel welcomed. The Park Shore Waikiki's rooms are a bit on the small side however are very clean and in good repair. The balcony was very large and offered a great view relaxation to sit and watch the sunset. This hotel will be updating it's rooms with renovations in the Spring 2009. The staff are very excited about the update! I would recommend this hotel to everyone. It is suited for families, couples or singles. It's quiet at night yet very close to the action if that's what you like! We'll be staying there again for sure! Mahalo! (I will be posting photos soon!)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1fadfb6fd9118fa75aa6b7723e8f3114" url=""><![CDATA[We Loved the Aqua Waikiki Wave We loved the Aqua Waikiki Wave! When we called into the reservations line for Aqua Hotels we were greeted with a very friendly and helpful agent. She ended up getting us a great deal and upgraded us. Once we arrived at the hotel the staff were great as well, very quick and friendly check in process. Our room was very clean and had recently been updated, very nice. The pictures online are exact. The beds were very comfortable and had beautiful white comforters/bedding. The view was great since we were on the 11th floor. We had a view of the ocean on one corner of the patio and the city mountains on the other :). Beautiful! I had read that some guests complained about noise however we did not have an issue and actually found the hotel to be quite quiet. Yes you will hear the odd noise from other guests but nothing to complain about. The patio doors kept the noise from outside out of the room. The location is perfect! About 2-3 blocks from the beach. Very close to great shopping! A fave was Muse that had just opened 2 weeks ago and was directly accross the street. Upscale shops are along the beach. The International Market is literally next door to the hotel. The market has a food court and unique to Hawaii shops and kiosks. It, of course, has an ABC Store for convenience however you will find ABC Stores every half block in Waikiki!! (ABC Stores have everything you need as a traveller.) The hotel is located very close to many restaurants that have great deals for breakfast ($2.99 breakfasts to be exact for your simple eggs/toast/bacon etc). It's great for the budget traveller. There are many happy hour specials that serve $1.00 - $3.00 drinks! The hotel itself is great for all types of travellers. Great for families and singles / couples alike. The small pool is not in a good location however. It is accessed through the parkade and kind of in a back alley between 2 tall buildings - no sun. Very weird. The hotel might as well not have a pool at all really! :) HOWEVER this would be our only complaint and we didn't even want to swim in the pool anyway since you're in Hawaii for the ocean! The ocean swimming and waves are better by far. Towel service is offered at the front desk for the beach as a sign in / sign out. They were very nice about the fact that our towels were covered in sand and sea water! : ) Shuttle service to and from the airport is easy. $9.00 per person. or a taxi would be about $40.00 if you have a family for more than 3 people. We used Reliable Shuttle but there are many others with a simular price point. Overall our stay was excellent! We recommend it to everyone!Any of the Aqua resorts seem great on their websites.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>