<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7051413da2098137e83a92df4b0502a0" url=""><![CDATA[Great Stay, Great Honeymoon Just returned from our honeymoon and it was glorious! Having meticulous read reviews here weekly the last six months touch on some of the popular topics:The infamous drive: maybe because this was our first trip to the Caribbean but we loved the hour drive. We knew be vegging on the resort the entire time so we wanted to see as much countryside and Dominican we could. It could have been longer and we have minded!Once we got there, aka the grounds/service/beach/etc: The resort was absolutely gorgeous. As read, when you (if you) drive to other resorts to drop off/pick up others on your shuttle ride you will see that in comparison to the others this is one of the best. The service throughout the resort is some of the best encountered. It is evident on the drive to the resort why the workers on the resort work so hard to please and appreciate tips so much ($100 in ones was perfect for a week). Everyone acts cheery, attentive and kind. The beach was also great! The best part being the constant breeze that keeps you cool when lounging, and the resulting waves from the wind that provide both a perfect soundtrack and something fun to play in. We live in the Tampa/Clearwater area which supposed to have three of the top ten beaches in the world (according to Dr. Beach) and would take this beach over anything around here any day.Night time entertainment: We loved it. Is it cheesy? Abso-freakin-lutely. what made it so entertaining to us. get me wrong, they are indeed quality when you have an entire show dedicated to Michael Jackson, I mean, really now. We hit almost every show and loved every one. What is not cheesy however, or who I should say, is the nightly Sax guy. Some real quality there no matter where in the world he would be playing. Def. check him out in the Martini Bar before every show. We also loved making absolute fools of ourselves in the Disco almost every night. My apologizes to anyone who had to watch us day full of boat drinks and Presidentes will lead to some interesting moves. :o) But we had a blast every night we went. Speaking of boat free flowing and tasty. I mainly stuck to the Presidente, but we hit a lot of the other stuff as well. The Sammy Sosa was our favorite just the Strawberry Daq. Mix with the Pina Colada mix topped with Blue Cauroco). All the top shelf liquor you can handle, and just request your drink strong if you want to taste your liquor and they are happy to oblige. We pretty much stayed tipsy from morning to night the entire a beautiful thing.Entertainment team: please, applause. We thought be avoiding them like the plague, us not being into silly group activities or the like. But their enthusiasm was so infectious that we help but join in and have a great time. They really do but a smile on your face so go ahead and play one or two of their games or events. Great, GREAT people.Food: Saving the best for last. Oh how I wish that were the case. The only thing keeping this review from 5 stars is that most of the food was mediocre at best for our (not too discriminating) tastes. But that said, others both on this site and that we met there very much enjoyed it so I go into too much detail bashing the food. just leave it as we personally care for it. But even at that, I can honestly say it blemish our trip one bit (maybe one tiny bit) as everything else was great enough to overlook our thoughts on the food. I will say that the honeymoon breakfast in bed and the French resteraunt were the highlights.I see how one could have a bad time at this resort. We did encounter a few people who were moaning and groaning, but they seemed to be folks who would be miserable most anywhere. ;o) My only reservation would be if you are NOT a drinker and are going simply for the fine dining this is probably not the place for you. A few tips: bring your sodas to the outside stores, they are as good as currency; they have $40/70 minute massages at the first store on the left (a name that escapes you have a bit adventure sense it sure beats the resort prices; do the horseback ride even though the horses look rather sad.Have fun, hard not too!! And Stephen/Kim or you read this, big love to you cats! Good luck in love and life!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>