<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="048ca91480e4815d0a994c9327ed05c4" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect location, great value We spent 9 nights in the Luna and Simone Hotel based on the positive reviews on this site. It lived up to our expectations.The Pimlico tube station is a 5 minute walk. We used the Victoria station only when we used the regular rail services for day trips, because the entrance to is on Belgrave Road. The Victoria tube station is on the other side, off Wilton Road, and is a bit farther than Pimlico. We used an internet cafe on Wilton Road which is part of a Subway restaurant.We have stayed in much smaller rooms, and thought the size was fine. We had plenty of room and storage space. The bathroom had a shelf above the toilet to store bath items. The room was always spotless when we returned, and we were messy! Showers are HOT and powerful. Wow. We brought a big bar of soap with us-- recommmended.Our winter rate was 60 GBP, a real bargain. We had room 9 which did not face Belgrave Road. I don't know how noisy a front room would be but Belgrave is not a high traffic street. We made one local telephone call and were not charged for it. When we paid our bill the day before we left, the reception offered to arrange a 5 a.m. wake-up call.I can't comment on the breakfast because we never ate it. We don't like hot breakfasts, and we're vegetarian and don't eat sausages. On Tachbrook Street there is a wonderful bakery and we bought bread and cheese for breakfast. Further up on the street there is a Saintsbury supermarket and on Warwick Way there is a Tesco grocery. We didn't eat at any of the pubs and small restaurants in the area because we had theater tickets every night and ate in the theater area. Restaurants near the hotel include pubs, Indian, Thai, Italian, and French.Belgrave Road is a lovely walk to the tube. There are many small hotels along the street in converted apartment houses. We usually returned to the hotel after 11 p.m. and felt very safe in the area.In Canterbury my husband bought a suit, and we told the salesman about the hotel because he was going to London the next week. He couldn't believe the price we paid. He said he had paid 180 GPB for a hotel recently.Don't hesitate to stay here!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>