<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="c77edf29dbce6e9c02156b6e3c995ffb" url=""><![CDATA[Embassy Suites good for families Our family of 4 went during Easter break. I agree with the reviews. The only problems I had were with the pool and the breakfast. The pool was too small and my kids said it was freezing. Usually we spend every vacation at the pool at some point during our day and we didn't because it was crowded and cold. The buffet in the morning was not for me because I am not a morning person and there were crowds and a mess most of the time. If you are an easy going person this might not bother you because it is afterall free!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="233fa34b3b68641c45a827a37f6c7180" url=""><![CDATA[Intercontinental good for price We were promised a room with 2 queen beds which to make a long story short never happened. After waiting a couple of hours for our room to be ready we were disappointed they gave us a room with two double beds. I had explained to reservation office when making my initial reservation that we were two adults and two kids and needed two queen beds. They assured me we would have them. It never happened which really disappointed me because I picked this hotel because they promised two queen beds!!Besides that, the room was clean, my kids enjoyed the pool and the fellow travelers were very nice and polite. The staff basically lied to us which I do not appreciate. I told my husband wow, people lie here and don't even feel bad! (We were also lied to when we rented bikes with our kids that the ride was easy and piece of cake across the Golden Gate Bridge, which it wasn't but worth it!!)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c095c58f41d8a3bade6051046d19800c" url=""><![CDATA[Okay Hotel for price The hotel is located in a very touristy part of hollywood. The goodnews is if you like shopping, you are right on top of a mall. Also plenty of food court options. The first night we were interupted from our deep sleep by drunk guests trying to knock down our door. I was so tired from traveling that day that I couldn't even get to the door to tell them they were at the wrong room. Finally they went away. After that no incidents. The room wasn't cleaned 100%. Found wrapers on the floor that grossed me out! If I had to do it again I wouldn't stay here.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>