<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="6">
		<document id="0095ebff2a6cd54d67d5a05ed4f766fc" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, decent room Maybe we're too picky, but we found this hotel just average, not great, not terrible. First, the location is excellent - so close to all the sights, but what sort of disappointed us was the room. Yes, it's renovated, but it has a very cold feel to it - tiled floor, and very basic furnishings. The shower (no tub) is tiny and the whole room feels hospital-like in a way. After a day of seeing Florence, with all of its art, history, character and beauty, it was a bit strange to come back to such a stale looking room. I guess for 140 euro a night, we were expecting a bit more when it came to the room. That being said, the staff is VERY friendly; they do go out of their way for you and the hotel has more of an intimate feel to it than any other we've stayed at.I think if we ever go back to Florence though, we'd chose a cozier, more high end hotel with nicer rooms.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="30c3cd2d79c4fe88be0bc7c76e85b2b2" url=""><![CDATA[Best beds ever Incredible beds - can't say enough about them - great pillows and soft comforter - this in its own gives this place a five out of five. Location is very good - close to Times Square (not that you'd want to spend time around there) but far enough to get away from that madness. The staff were all very friendly, always greeting us several times as we entered and left the Hotel. Had room service one night - excellent hamburgers. My only complaint would be that the bathtubs were very shallow - not worth having a good soak. Other than that would 100% stay at this hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7fa4a2f36aa4a7634b7dc52cda40acba" url=""><![CDATA[Great location! Hotel is in a very good location - away from all the tourist traps. Close to Union Square and the Meat Packing District and Balducci's is right around the corner (excellent meat deli there by the way). The rooms are okay - nothing special and not always the cleanest either (in our experience). There were days when the toilet wasn't cleaned and I don't think they even look under the bed (so maybe you shouldn't either). The breakfast area is a nice touch (especially the courtyard at back) and most of the staff are pretty friendly. Not sure if I'd stay here again, maybe for one or two nights max. Not terrible but nothing too special either.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="34328665c62dbf6720f2fa212d25977f" url=""><![CDATA[Central location, spotless room Stayed 6 nights at the Hotel D'Albe and agree with all the positive reviews on Tripadvisor! It was spotless! The bathroom looked like it was brand new, big granite laid shower (but no bathtub) and smart looking rooms with art work and a plasma tv. We stayed on the 2nd floor so it was a bit noisy, especially on the weekend evenings but that was a small price to pay for being in such a central location. We had breakfast included and the woman who works there was the sweetest lady. If I ever go back to Paris I'd stay here again, but I think I'd ask for a higher floor and maybe a room that faces a quieter outlook.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b2a165bf44392a226fe702111c179944" url=""><![CDATA[Terrific Hotel! We stayed four nights at this hotel and couldn't be more pleased with it. First off, the location is fabulous - close to the Ramblas, and very close to the higher end shopping stores. I would not want to stay in the Ramblas as it would be too noisy anyway, so this hotel is perfect to get away from the thick crowds, but at the same time, close enough to walk to all of the stuff going on. Second, the rooms were great - clean, totally modern, smartly decorated, very, very quiet, nice and cool and a big bathroom - so not typical of European bathrooms. The breakfast was also included in our room price and it was very good too - fully staffed and very attentive. The roof top jacuzzis were so cool; great to relax in them after a day of sightseeing. I would totally, 100% stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c87cb7434560d2bc11da46ed3fa4694d" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent location, excellent price We were hesitant to try this place, considering it was only $114 a night for two people. Being San Francisco, we were thinking you'd get what you paid for but we were so wrong. This place was a steal! Very clean, newly refurbished and best of all an awesome location - Union Square is right around the corner with some very good shopping and Westfield Shopping Center is literally a two minute walk away. We were upgraded to a king bed suite (which would have cost even more) and were plesantly surprised by the room. Sure it's small (by American standards), but who cares - it was spotless and newly refurbished with a plasma tv, a stereo system on the wall, and very comfortable bedding. The continental breakfast was very simple - coffee, juice, toast, muffins, crossaints and some oranges and apples. Richard, the concierge, was especially helpful when it came to restaurant choices and the front desk staff were all very friendly.Should we ever go back, we would certainly stay here again!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>