<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="764b9036089ec28d2bfcea082a710191" url=""><![CDATA[Awful in many ways!!not My husband and I spent 5 days at the Princess as part of a conference group. The location is terrible. While public transportation is nearby, the hotel is quite a distance from the city center and all the sights. Each taxi ride into the city cost 11-15 Euros. That very quickly added up to much more than we had anticipated.The room was attractjve but small. The bed was very comfortable but the bathroom left much to be desired. The separate shower was next to the separate toilet and the shower leaked onto the floor into the toilet area. Not pleasant. The view was great.The signs in the lobby forbiding guests from bringing in outside drinks or food made it feel like a dorm or a hostel and not a deluxe hotel. Concierge services were non existent and the front desk staff were not knowledgeable or helpful at all. The breakfast buffet was very limited and unexciting.So it seems that what this hotel has going for it are low rates and a modern design look. I would not stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="18cbdbf1c48214781a89bb59d912a0b7" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Weekend at the Westin We just returned from a 3 night weekend stay at the Westin Grand Hotel in Berlin. First of all we found the location to be excellent and completely convenient to transportation and all East Berlin sights.We arrived early Friday morning and 1 of our 2 rooms booked was ready for check in, which was very convenient. This was the Premium Deluxe Courtyard room. It is traditionally furnished with a queen size heavenly bed. The room was apx. 340 sq. ft. but big enough for a desk chair and a comfortable club chair. The bathroom is small but adequate with good lighting, hair dryer, several mirrors and a make up mirror. It is certainly not a super deluxe bathroom but comfortable. The lobby of the hotel is beautiful with a grand staircase and elegant atrium. The lobby bar has a grand piano and a pianist every night from 5:00 to about midnight. it's costly but a great place to relax for a drink and a cigar. The staff was very responsive and friendly and the concierge took care of all our reservations and touring needs.The second room we booked was a Grand deluxe room and was not to be ready until after 3:00 PM. However, we were told that we would be given a double upgrade to a junior suite. Also a traditionally furnished room. it had the same bathroom as the Premium room. This room was much larger with a separate living room, couch, desk chair and club chair. The bedroom area had a king bed with a closet and dressing table. The room also faced the courtyard and it was very quiet which was great. The pool spa area are excellent with a hot tub, full bar for snacks, sauna, showers, infinity pool, etc. Buffet breakfast was included in our rate and was outstanding. German breads are incredible. The cheese cart was an unusual breakfast treat as was the free flowing champagne, The cost of this buffet is 26 euros if it is not included in your rate. A la carte breakfast can be had at the lobby bar. I would rate this hotel as an excellent 4* property.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>