<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="77fcf1a21acb3ead72adbead4c3dac6a" url=""><![CDATA[Left here rather dissapointed... more a costly budget hotel than boutique. I stayed here with my boyfriend for 5 nights, thoroughly looking forward to my stay in the 'boutique hotel'... especially after the positively glowing reviews here. I have to say however, I was left feeling rather dissapointed. The location is very central- you can easily access all districts from here, however to get down to CBD (Opera House/Harbour) you need to catch the metro (approx 15/20 mins due to change of trains). The nearest metro station is Kings Cross, which is a very shady part of Sydney indeed. In fact it did become quite intimidating walking down 'the strip' during the night time (prostitutes/drug dealers)- however many police were about, which is reassuring. But in the end we mostly ended up taking taxis. The hotel itself was like stated by other users here- very homely, but the owner was not as friendly as I was lead to believe from the other reviews (I felt even abrupt on a few occasions). We stayed in a deluxe room costing $145 AUD/night, which in my opinion is on the costly side, even though it is supposed to be budget boutique. The rooms were an average size,not large, but not small. The bathroom was better (just as in the candid review photographs posted), but the shower did not have a door/curtain and water did get everywhere- there is a drain, but still not ideal at all. Also the fridge is in the bathroom, which I thought could be a hazzard since water got everywhere!I think this is a good place if you are coming with a group of friends and stay in a family room, as these rooms are larger and are overall alot cheaper (in fact they cost only a few dollars more than the deluxe room), but I dont reccommed otherwise. There is also a bar in the reception area, but this closes very early around 6pm.... luckily there is a liquor store next door if you need, and lots of convience stores for food. In the end though the appearance is more budget than boutique. I ended up feeling that I would have been better off staying in a 3/4* near the CBD for the same price.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>