<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="45589493f56ab988e27426db40c6bf6d" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect Location Beautiful Spot If you are going to stay in or near San Juan this the hotel to stay in...Worth every penny..It has its own beach, a clean calm lagoon which is great for kids, (95% of the hotels in San Juan area do not have their own beach, they use public access beaches which are ok but not great) a very good Gym, beautiful swimming pools. (.one with a swim up bar,) very good food, and nice rooms. The hotel bars are excellent..This is where the Pina Colada was invented back in th 50's..The staff is bend over backwards friendly...The rooms are on the small side but not that big a deal since the weather is the main attraction..Views are beautful..If you call ask about the executive lounge feature..It sounds hoity toity but actually it gives you lots of free food options..It might only come with certain floors so ask first how you can get this included with the room price Renting a car is not necessary, as cabs are the best way to go anywhere,.Bus service is non existent...Old San Juan is charming with cobble stone streets and an immense Fort..Beautful lit up at night..There are some eyesores in and around San Juan but if you look past them you will see a certain charm in this area...Try walking to the Coronada area to the east of the hotel along the water and you will find a couple of cafes that have waves that come right up to the windows. We ate breakfast there...Be prepared to spend money on food as this is expensive in this part of Puerto Rico...even just basic lunch food. is high..The Hilton actually had healthy lunch type food that was somewhat less expensive than a lot of the local eateries we tried..Good veggie food cooked by locals is in the Hilton Gym cafe which is hidden away for some reason by the tennis courts..Take a cab ride to Isle Verde one evening and walk through some mega expensive hotel lobbies like the El San Juan which is spectacular(with a casino) and the Ritz Carlton..Good Mexican food sports bar called Lupis in this area..If you like snorkling take the catamaran ( you can book this in the hotel lobby) tour..It goes to an unpopulated Island off the coast .. right out of a post card..Even if you don't snorkle, the ride is great. the water warm,,...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b5bc4bc5cbef5110f05da2535e14c5c1" url=""><![CDATA[Very nice convenint to airport Very nice clean hotel.. actually rooms are suites with kitchenettes..Don't pay full price..I got this room for $76 during prime season Saturday night stay..Do an internet search with a hotel reseller like discount hotels .com or similar..The advantage of this hotel is the location just accross from the airport..Excellent breakfast room for quick on the go..
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>