<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="69aa93b343aa43b137d8d41ad66abc4b" url=""><![CDATA[Would Stay Here Again! We stayed here two days at the end of a nine-day trip to New York in April. I had been unable to get a room at the Beacon for the entire time, so we compromised by splitting our stay between two hotels. I wish I had made reservations earlier so that we could have stayed here the whole time!I was in a funk at first because I had lost my camera somewhere between hotels, but the staff was sympathetic and friendly. The room was very comfortable, and it had a mini-kitchen with basic utensils. It is only a short way to the subway or bus, and there were many interesting restaurants and shops in the neighborhood. You could walk to Central Park!Best of all, there is a wonderful market right across the street that has a large selection of food. In their health food section their granola section was the largest I've ever seen.We were on the eighth or ninth floor, and in the morning I woke up to find sunlight streaming in the window. Seeing this, I suddenly realized that in the previous hotel, where we had also stayed on the eighth or ninth floor, the buildings around us were so high that we never got direct light while we were in the room and we often thought that the day was overcast until we got out to the sidewalk to find that it was actually a clear day. Again, I would like to comment on the friendly staff. When you came into the lobby there was always someone who smiled instead of being annoyed that you were just another tourist. That made a great difference!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7e4304bd41b64a6b151b443db4c607e5" url=""><![CDATA[Basic Tourist Hotel Clean and plain but quite adequate. Our room was relatively small but we had a nice view across Tokyo and we could see Tokyo Tower in the distance. There were many inexpensive restaurants and many shops in the multi-level shopping center adjacent. There was a convenient supermarket across the street from the hotel on one side. For anime fans, there is a tall Ani-Mate (sp?) building across the street on another side and related businesses.This is actually in Ikebukuro suburb of Tokyo, but it is a short walk to the train station.We stayed there two days as part of a package tour, and there were crowds of other tourists there- not just Americans.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>