<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="e527d6a5399e2dc69204e0427bd81e26" url=""><![CDATA[Decent Place - Pluses and Minuses Dreams Punta Cana is definitely NOT a 6 Apple resort. We booked this place on the 6-apple square deal expecting a real bargain. Sorry to say that we got exactly what we paid for. The resort is not horrible, certainly not a nightmare, but it's also not the luxurious experience that they make it out to be. It is an AMstar resort, owned by Apple, which is why Apple rates it 6 stars. Don't be fooled. The ride from the airport was horrible...we took a shorter route that actually took 1.5 hours and involved numerous people getting sick. On the way back, we took the long way and ended up getting to the airport in 1 hour with no one sick. Make sure you tell your rep not to take the short way! Check in was great, but our room was not 6-star by any stretch of the imagination. There was a huge crack in our ceiling that ran clear across the room, and the closet and facing of the furniture was in generally bad shape. The bathroom was OK, but the shower is weird and hot water is sketchy. Our maid was excellent, and we didn't tip until the last day. We also gave her some school supplies for her children and she loved it! Think about bringing them a little something :) We also had a problem with our AC, which was fixed within 1 hour. Very nice. The pool is great, but I did get an ear infection from it and it screwed up my swimming for the last 4 days. You will also find losers gathering rafts every morning to hoard for the rest of the day...such a shame that people act this way. The beach is pretty right in front of the resort, but the water is ROUGH, not clear at all, and there are sharp rocks all throughout the ocean so swimming is hardly possible. No snorkelling opportunities, and others are right---a ton of trash all over the place. A real shame, they certainly cannot tout their beach as top of the line, as I've had better beaches in Jamaica, Dominica, Bahamas, and at Excellence Punta Cana, etc. Restaurants were very good generally, with good food and GREAT SERVICE. The deserts are straight from the buffet, however...very disappointing. The buffet is TERRIBLE...food selection is very limited, none of the food is good, and they run out of everything. Bacon is like gold at breakfast....Patio, Himitsu, and Seaside Grill were great, very good food. Our service was always exceptional. Shows were OK, I don't put much stock into them anyway. Overall, best thing about this resort is the service, and the worst is the beach/buffet. It is not a 6-star by any means, so be prepared. You can certainly enjoy yourself, but don't think you're getting any special deal with the 6-star. You will get excellent service, however!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>