<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7d8e3cb1202e2a5677ea8dcd6b6bb336" url=""><![CDATA[Relaxing Get-Away My Hubby and I stayed at this resort from 05/16-05/23 and had a wonderful relaxing time. We were early risers and pretty much got what ever spot we wanted either by the pull or on the beach. As many of the reviews have stated, there are many Palapalas with shading (more were going up when we left) and the staff was constantly getting us drinks. This all depends on where you sit though, if you are close to a bar, it is most likely that you wont have service, but where we sat we never had a problem getting a drink (tip a dollar or two and service is out of this world). Johnny P at the front bar in the lobby is outstanding and if there is a drink you want he will figure it out.As for the food, make sure to book the Gourmet Restaraunt La Sablia, outstanding. You can also ask for two lobster tails : ) with butter. The steakhouse was okay and so was the seafood restaraunt. We met a couple that loved the Japanese Restaraunt La Padoga?? (please excuse the spelling). As for the buffets, there are lots of choices and mostly cater to the international taste bud, however if you are like me, I stuck with the pasta station and bread, and my hubby stuck with hamburgers and hotdogs.. lol.As for the shops down at the other end of the beach, we bargained our butts off, it was quite funny, to get cuban cigars, oops dominican cigars we got a box for 15 bucks.... T-shirts we paid about 6 bucks and a rather large dominican tote bag for $10. You have to bargain and if they say no, walk away and they will chase you down the strip. DO NOT buy cigarettes from there you can get them at the duty free in the airport for $23, unless you can get them cheaper than that.Hubby and I went on the deep sea excursion with Gone Fishing, make sure to get Manuel, as we caught many fish and make sure to bring dramamine, I lost my sea legs and being an ex Navy girl, that is not suppose to happen.. lolOverall, the hotel and staff were wonderful, tipping the person that cleans your room goes along way for extra water, beer, soda and towels.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>