<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="8321c937b3c100f41d1964ba6f565a42" url=""><![CDATA[Be Cautious of the Bad Reviews--Great Resort!!! We booked our stay as Wyndham TimeShare owners. We were looking for a resort to get away and do nothing. We wanted pool, beach, and great weather. It was a getaway from our kids for my wife and I. We read almost all the reviews over the last year and read many good and many not so good. We felt that people were missing the boat on this resort since it became a Wyndham about 1-1/2 yrs ago. We found out they remodeled every room. Our room was basic overlooking the rainforest, but very clean, flat screen, granite, and great bed! We rented the fridge for $25 so we could cut down on the food costs that we had read about. If you go to this resort expecting a budget resort, you are in the wrong place. This is a high end resort with very good restaurants and service. We did not rent a car. If you want to do activities, rent a car. If not, you can get away without it. We walked to the convenient store (no sidewalks, so for daring people only. Otherwise, take a cab) at the bottom of the hill and picked up groceries and had some great Chinese food (amazing Orange Chicken) at the casual restaurant. The Isamar bakery was great as everyone has said. They have lunch sandwiches that locals enjoy. We bought our own liquor at the store because, yes, the drinks are very high. Also, the bell station might have a cooler that you can use if you ask them nicely. Don't forget to tip for the great service that you will probably get.There is a convenient store gift shop at the resort. Good place to pick up T-shirts and do some Sale shopping. They sell liquor there, but of course, you will pay more. Less than at the bar though.The Pool--Adult pool was great. Kids were having a great time in their own pool. We liked that. NO MUSIC at the adult pool. We knew that and brought our Ipod and docking station. There are some umbrellas but probably wouldn't get them in high season. Beach was great with umbrellas the staff will put up for a small tip. Constant breeze can be expected which cools things down nicely. There are a few Iguanas around, but they are pretty cool and they make sure there aren't too many around.Spa--we did a couples massage for 25 minutes at the Mandara Spa. The Spa services are high price, but it is a very nice place to be pampered. The workout facility is also in the spa and has very nice updated equipment with personal TV's, Nautilus circuit and free weights.The Food--everyone says the food is so expensive. Really, it is not. It is higher than a budget resort, but fairly priced to slighly high. These are some nice restaurants. It is like going out to a nice restaurant in the city somewhere. Palio is great high quality Italian. We split dishes since we didn't want leftovers it kept costs down. The Rigatoni Bolognese was as good as anywhere, including Italy ($18). The chicken wings at Marbella are totally underrated. They are perfectly crisp and outstanding. Many people we saw found this out as well. Great when tossed with the Sweet Chile sauce from the Shrimp Satay! Get this if you go there. Grille Room was a typical steakhouse. Prices were appropriate. Steaks were perfectly done. Take the shuttle for dinner at the Grille Room. It is a nice change of scenery. To keep our money for dinners, we generally ate PBJ Tuna Salad in the room for lunch. Woke up too late for breakfast most of the time :) Don't waste the money on any of the buffets unless you can eat a lot! Muffins, bagel coffee is available at the coffee shop next to the casino. Yes, it is a $4 muffin, but who cares, you are on vacation and it is a big muffin. People we met went to Richie's a few times. They said the food was basically the same price and very good, but the drinks were much cheaper.Golf--great but not spectacular. Ocean course is really not on the ocean. 1 hole is. Go twilight and enjoy golf for $70 or $85 depending on season. Best deal by far. Local told me that El Conquistador has a great course. If you have a car and want to golf, try there. Nightlife--None (except Casino). I shared my concern about this with the GM and he says they are working on that currently. New margaritaville type restaurant will be opening that will stay open late. Tiki bar near the ocean would be great, but it was Turtle season so Island law sets curfew. I believe this will be changing in the future as they have realized it is the one major thing missing. Casino was very small as expected and not worth the time unless you like to gamble.Excursions--You can set up excursions that will keep you busy at the Concierge desk. Ride from the airport--unless you are travelling with a large group and can work out something special, the best deal is the shuttle from the resort. $30/person each way. I called cab car companies and that was the best for 2.Kids--we would bring our kids to this resort. There were activities during the day and the pool was nice with one slide. I would want a car if I had kids so I could keep food costs down. Amigo grocery is a 10 minute car ride or $30 round trip cab ride. Also at the same place you will find KFC, Subway, Burger King.Shopping--we found a place called the Carribean Trading Company that is right around the corner from the convenient store across the main highway. They put together all the local specialties for gift baskets for the resorts. Unique stuff and decent prices. Locally made jewelery, coffee, and hot sauces in addition to many other things. Not some cheap souvenier store so no T-shirts. Wrap-up...if you go here expecting a high end resort with resort pricing and plan accordingly, you will have an amazing time at this beautiful place. If you book on Expedia, get a great deal, and don't plan properly, you are in for a rude awakening which is what I see in a lot of the reviews. This is a great resort with a great staff that went out of their way for us. We will go back here with our without the kids. Sorry, no pictures since we lost our camera on our way home.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>