<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="218838b348d1ec0ca59344e0274682e0" url=""><![CDATA[A Wonderful Week in A Beautiful Place Our group of 10 stayed at the Bahia Principe in Punta Cana from April 16-23. We have read almost every review before going and were extremely happy we picked this place. I can't add anymore to this review that hasn't been said about its beauty and overall accomodiations. I would like to address some of the reviews I have read in relation to being there. Many people have complained about the language barrier and I could not disagree with them more. We found no trouble talking to the people working there. We spoke and understood enough of their language and they did ours as well. Wether calling for service or questions or ordering a drink, we found no trouble. The other issue was the food. Yes, it is a resort, it is not a fine dining emporium. If you are looking for a Wolfgang Puck caliber...then go to his resturant. I sum this all up as....you are in their country, they are trying to accomodiate our tastes in cooking. Give them a break. This holds true to the language too. You are in their country, they are trying to accomodiate our language. Expecting them to speak our language is like them coming here and complaining that we dont speak their language. Think about it.We all had wonderful meals at the specialty resturants. It is a dining experience so dont expect to be out of there in an hour. We ate at the Jap., French, Mexican, and Steak house. All very very good. The buffets were different each evening. Breakfast and lunch seemed to be the same each day. Room Service was also available and very fast.The beach is absolutly to die for. White powdery sand and clear blue water. We stayed there everyday. The pools are massive and plenty to choose from. The water there was warm with a pool bar at each. No problem getting chairs if you were at either place by 8 in the morning.It isnt a bad walk from the lobby to the beach so don't let this stop you. There are plenty of trams running 24 hours a day. We stayed at the Golden Club buildings and is well worth the upgrade. The rooms are beautiful and the cleaning service is excellent. They cleaned the room during the day and then straightened up at night. Close to the beach and pools. While no place is perfect, we found this to be right up there with our other favorites. I would definetly go back and reccomend it to anyone.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>