<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="cd8c6da54e492d7c97dfe55cd08dd4a8" url=""><![CDATA[Great stay! Terrific room and location! My wife and I stayed two nights in October in one of the newly renovated rooms away from the river. The room was both large and very stylishly modern, exquisite, with a large outside balcony. Great bathroom. The staff was friendly and helpful. The breakfast was excellent with a wide range of selections and coffee made to order. The breakfast room itself is large and well lit by huge windows with a great view of the hillside across the Arno.The location is hard to beat, most all sights are within walking distance. The walk is quite short to both Piazza della Signoria and Santa Croce. For gelato lovers, Vivoli is nearby in the maze of small streets. One can definitely have two different experiences in this hotel. I had stayed there two years ago in one of the older rooms on the river side. The room was adequate and the view was great, but I prefer the newer rooms without the view and would request one in the future. I felt it was a better bargain.We will certainly be staying there again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="53e044686e0b19257c1fc338fefdb354" url=""><![CDATA[Great stay during the Biennale! The owners, Stefano and Susanna, and staff really took good care of us throughout our stay. As with other reviewers posting here, they arranged early breakfast for us on the day we were flying home. The photos here and on the website are accurate representatives of the clean and stylish rooms. We had a great view of the courtyard and the Doge's palace. Good breakfast. We njoyed the warm pastries with apple filling. Coffee was made to order. We were always full enough that we never tried the omelletes, though they were always offered.For those debating whether or not to buy that extra guidebook, they had a small library of guidebooks at the front desk. Also umbrellas--though it only rained a bit one afternoon out of 4 days. Early in our visit, we took the Secret Itineraries tour of the Doge's Palace and could see our room and balcony from the top floor near one of the cells in which Casanova had been imprisoned. It was sort of cool looking back at that window from our room. Overall, the location could not be better. We were in the center of everything, but it was very quiet. It was great to be able to come back to our Ca' dei Dogi oasis throughout the day for short rests. We will definitely return!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>