<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="edfd2b32080bbf33d712f32beeccda21" url=""><![CDATA[My Wedding My family I visited this resort in August 2004. This Resort was beautiful, clean, and the beach was everything you could imagen. Front Lobby has two grand stair cases. Exotic flowers and furniture. After traveling and the bus ride, we arrived at the resort and our wedding guest and I were in awe. Staff was very polite, although it took roughly an hour to get to our rooms. When we booked 6 months earlier we requested the honeymoon suite as the wedding couple. But were given an ocean view room with two double beds. The view was breath taking. But our room was nothing special for a Bride and Groom. We spoke with front desk and they said they couldn't help us with a room change. I found this to be of poor service to the Bride and Groom who undoubting should have a honeymoon suite.We had a wonderful time with Family and friends through the first two days. Then on the 3rd day we were informed our wedding which we had booked for 5PM Sunset on the beach for August 25th. Was moved ahead to August 24th. We had planned to have our wedding date on my Fathers Birthday since he had passed away and could not attend. This was disappointing, and again the hotel would not assist us in keeping the same date as planned. Also my identical twin brother who walked me down the aisle was very upset in the change of date. The day of the wedding I went to the Salon spa to have a Gel nail repaired and painted before the wedding while I was getting my hair done. The girls in the spa had not seen a gel nail product before, but insisted they could fix it. The one girl tore the gel nail off but doing so also removed most of my actual nail. This was my RING FINGER. I felt a panic starting to set in, and they continued to tell me it was ok...and they could still fix it. I was in pain, but also worried that as my ring finger was bare of a nail. I asked them to do something. So I placed a small band aid over my open nail bed. And they glued a spare nail found in a vase to the band aid with hot glue. Then painted this to match my other nails. I was Horrified. I really did not know how to react. I left the spa before having my hair finished. This is truely the worst service at a spa anyone could ever recive.Also The morning of the wedding we were informed that the resort staff could not set up the beach for our wedding, as they said weather could turn at any moment. They then decorated the Lobby balcony for our wedding. My uncle spoke with the Hotel Manager and told him we did not fly 20 guests at $1100.00 each to hold our wedding inside a building. So we were able to continue the wedding on the beach without flowers or chairs.We paid $1200 US upon arrival at the resort for our wedding package, which we were told included a wedding coordinator. But of course we were told the wedding coordinator was away on business that week. Everything I picked out from the books was not done for us. Including type of flowers. I picked a local exotic flower in a small bouquet. I got large peach roses that were weaved into a flower display that went to the floor. The hired Judge did not correctly say our names. But we proceeded anyways. We did hire a band for an extra $375 US. Which were worth every penny. They played music on the beach for the wedding, and then followed us to the beach bar where we socialized with family as the played beautifully. During dinner they played the entire time. And also played 5 songs for us to dance too. Although the dinner it's self was great from what I heard. I myself The Bride did not get a meal... and family I all informed waiter staff three times, then was told the kitchen was closed. This was all in an hour and half from the start of dinner The day after the wedding, I went to the safe to get some of my things, and my Austrian Crystal Martini necklace and matching earring, with Emerald and ruby olives on them were gone. This was my wedding gift from my husband. I ran to the front desk to report this, but was told nobody could speak English and I would have to come back later. I kept going back every 10 mins and asked to speak to the manager Rueben. Nobody could speak English when I needed to report the theft. But on a different occasion I went to the front desk and asked for a room key to my room. They handed me one key with no questions asked. This made me very uncomfortable as I only requested a room number and not even by name. This resort was very beautiful and the beach was even more amazing. But hotel staff was impossible and I felt very disappointed even with all the excitement of our wedding. The more time that has passed I feel more robbed of what should have been an amazing trip and celebration. I will NOT recommend this place to anyone planning to get married. OR looking for a place with great staff. If you are looking for a beautiful hotel and beach this is the place to go. DO NOT BRING ANYTHING YOU VALUE, BECAUSE THEIR SAFES ARE NOT A SAFE PLACE TO STORE THINGS EITHER.Other wedding guest staying at the hotel also reported theft of items, high heels, clothing, and money left in shirt pocket from visiting the beach market. My family is very easy going, and despite all this... we still look back and say what a great time. And laugh about all the mis-haps... But in all honesty no vacation or wedding should have this many problems.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>