<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="ff3abb1512978203e48629d12cd7d761" url=""><![CDATA[FABULOUS RESORT!!! I read trip advisor frequently and also travel much.....business and pleasure. I became a bit skeptical after my husband and I had booked an unbelievably cheap deal for 5 nights at the El Con. After reading many of the terrible reviews, we decided not to expect alot. BOY WE WERE WRONG!We are currently on our third night here and are still astounded. EVERYONB has been super friendly, but I believe you get what you give. MY hubby says I could strike up a conversation with a tree!We rented a car and drove from the airport...traffic the entire way. When we got here...heaven! Upon checkin, I sucked up to the front desk person. I asked him if he was the Alex I had read about who was so nice. Funniest thing......both front desk people named ALEX! After laughing, I said it would be wonderful to have a king bed with coeanfront view. He said that was possible, but an extra $70/night. I slipped him a $20, and he went in the back, returned a moment later, and said we would get a special private upgrade from the hotel.Bellman takes us to our room in the Las Brisas wing....and my husband's jaw drops! Magnificent view and very nice newly decorated room. Very large dressing area, sunken tub, walk-in closet. Separate sitting area. GREAT COMFORTABLE BED!Had a massage this morning at The Golden Door Spa....a must do! I had the 50 minute Golden Door massage...best ever. We have eaten at Caribe Cafe twice and it has been fine. Also ate lunch at the Green Iguana on Palimino Island....very good.Palamino island is super and beautiful.Anyone who wrote a bad review was either an inexperienced traveler or doesn't know how to get what they want. Don't complain.....be nice and ask for what you want. Don't come here if you are on a nickel and dime budget....it is not that type of a resort. Enjoy...enjoy.....we will surely be back!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6c4996f33aa9d7003393a623ae27c550" url=""><![CDATA[Nothing to crow about My husband and I stayed here one night, The room was very small with two double beds. There was hardly enough room to open the luggage carrier. I will say the room was clean and nicely appointed. I asked for a king size bed upon check in and was told by a very snooty front desk person that was not possible. No southern hospitality here! Bathroom tiny also.New Orleans is a very very sad place after the storms. We used to love coming to the city before, but will never stay at this hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c2cb816fb701a2aaf2dd24c379b0fda5" url=""><![CDATA[OK...if you are staying there comped by Harrah's The hotel has not been renovated since Katrina except for linens. It is clean but could use an updating. The restaurant menu is limited. Some staff are fine, while others ignore the guest completely. I stayed there complimentary, but doubt I would pay for the room
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>