<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="0dc02c6dd05ac92d65b786411b7b75a0" url=""><![CDATA[Basic Nothing Special I am just back from a visit to Berlin. The city of Berlin is a lovely place to see and I would go back again someday but not to Hotel Agon Frankfurter Allee. I went with my husband and arrived in Schofeld Airport on Saturday 11th Novenber 2006. We decided to get the Train as we felt this would be the closest stop to our destination. The thing to be aware of is that the hotel is in the east of germany and so things there are basic. You will know the difference straight away when you travel to the west. The train station is about five minutes walk from the airport and you just have to follow the crowd, very easy to find it is sign posted in the airport. The train tickets are cheap. You can buya day trip ticket for about 5 to 6 euro per person and it is well worth it. if you want to stay around the city a and b are ok but if you want to travel further then buy a ticket for districts a, b and c. The hotel is basic. I was very disappointed with the false advertising. The hot breakfast is hard bolied eggs and sausages one day and hard boiled eggs and scrambled eggs another day. They do supply a cold buffet and you will manage on that but it's not too exciting. There is no food available in the hotel other than breakfast. The reception desk is a section of the bar. It is really small and there is very little room for a number of guests to sit and enjoy a drink. No tea and coffee facilities in the bedrooms at all. There were two single beds pushed together to make a double and the mattresses are made of foam. If you have a back problem like me you will be in pain I can assure you of that. The temperature in the bedroom is always kept very warm so you will not be complaining of the cold in the room. Most of the staff are friendly and they will order a taxi if you need it. Another thing to be very aware of is that the hotel is stated to be in quiet residential area. The area is rough and you will be very aware of that when you get there. The picture of the hotel on the web site looks lovely. The bedroom on the web site is far from what you will be staying in when you get there. It just does not compair with reality. You have to go off the street through an arch way to find the front door of the hotel. On the street it is filthy everywhere. I would advise you to eat before you go back to the hotel at night instead of going back out to look for a restaurant. In the city you will find many nice places to eat. But closer to the hotel they are not so plentyful. I feel the hotel is certainly not a three staras advertised. I would suggest staying in west side instead. If you do the city trip for 20 euros per person you will see Checkpoint Charlie where you can get your passport stamped for 2 euros. You can also have your photo taken with USA soldiers at checkpoint Charlie for 1euro. Go to Subway opposite Checkpoint Charlie to eat. You can get Pizza or Pasta dishes all fro only 3euros. For those of you who like shopping. Go to the Galeria at Alexanderplaz, it is a huge and wonderful department store, just amazing I promise you. You will see it when you come out of the train station. C and A is also there too. I hope what I have written helps. After all this Berlin is a city we will certainly visit soon again. Pauline
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>