<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="f8c5439e5ddf1c21e9c9a8e946f9b052" url=""><![CDATA[Affinia 50 - Great Hotel My friend and I stayed for 4 nights at the Affinia 50 hotel recently and really enjoyed our stay there. We were in a studio suite which was a large room with 2 queen beds and it's own kitchen area. The fridge was very useful for keeping drinks in and being able to make a cup of tea in the morning was great.The staff were very helpful at the hotel, the concierge helped us book a Sex and The City tour and remembered us the following day telling us to enjoy the tour which was a nice touch. The front desk and bell staff were always friendly and helpful as well.The hotel is in a great location and walking to the Rockefeller Center, Times Square and 5th Avenue was really easy. Don't forget to try the wine and cheese on the 2nd floor between 6 and 7 Mon-Thurs, we were only able to enjoy this once but it was very nice.We would highly recommend the New York Luncheonette for breakfast which is just a few doors up the street from the hotel and served great food for a reasonable price. The continental breakfast at the hotel in comparison was $15 which we didn't bother to try.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c5ea848ebfaaee1cf2de573d65892763" url=""><![CDATA[Great time in Barcelona My mum and I stayed at the Barcelona Universal Hotel earlier this month for 5 nights. The hotel was very nice, our room was modern and clean with a large bathroom. The extras provided in the bathroom, toothbrush, shoe shine, etc were useful. The in-room electronic safe deposit box was a great addition and meant our valuables were safe every day. We had breakfast included so we enjoyed a nice continental breakfast each day, although the it would have cost otherwise was a bit expensive. The staff at reception were helpful and gave us directions to the Ramblas and advice on walking in the area. They also cashed our Euro travellers cheques which was great as nowhere in Barcelona would take them, we had expected a big city like that to have taken them as cash as is done in the USA.I had some concerns about the area after reading other reviews but he had no problems at all. The street that we used to get to the Ramblas wasn't that nice but we walked down it at approx 10.30pm one night and no-one bothered us.We would recommend the La Quinze Nits restaurant in Placa Reial for a cheap, high quality meal, but be prepared to queue for at least 30 minutes to get in at night. Two 3 course meals with wine and juice was around and the food was delicious. Another nice place to eat was Cafe Moka on the Ramblas, very nice tapas! Do not bother using La Poma restaurant which is attached to the Hotel Royal on the the Ramblas. The food is overpriced and we had bread and olives dumped on our table with no chance to refuse them. Even though they were clearly untouched we had added to our bill for them, we spoke to the manager and after some disagreement with us he eventually removed it from the bill, we did not leave a tip!We used the Metro a lot towards the end of our trip, a day ticket was and when you're getting tired walking around it's very convenient to just jump on a train. Most of the main attractions have a Metro stop beside them but the open top tour bus was also a great way to see the city from above ground. We really enjoyed the fountain show just off Placa Espanya, it was very busy and a great atmosphere.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>