<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="403bc886a605827b884ae8c1a7349e70" url=""><![CDATA[THERE IS SUCH THING AS PARADISE Where shall i start.. we were at this hotel 12/06 - 26/06 and have just returned and couldnt wait to write this review as im still buzzing. I cant believe some of the reviews i read on here before going (mainly the americans that complain about anythign and everything). I have stayed in 2 iberostars before (Iberostar founty beach in morrocco and the iberostar tucan in mexico) so i knew what quality to expect and was not disappointed one bit.ok starting with the flight:We flew with first choice as we always do, perfect flight, no delays. we flew premium class and would always recommend this for long haul as the seats are 36 inch pitch, lots of good movies and free food and drinks. Heard many bad reports from people that flew thomas cook and other companies as the seats are very cramped. The airport is lovely, a typical carribean looking airport with thatched roof and locals serenading us as we walked in. Bus journey approx 40 mins to hotel.Hotel:Lovely open reception lobby with lots of marble. Thatched roof. There is a lovely pond area with turtles too.. very nice touch.The hotel shares the facilities with the adjoining Iberostar dominicana, which is identical in every respect, and are connected via the buffet restaurants. The third hotel within the complex is the Hotel Iberostar Bavaro which can use the facilties of the punta cana and domincana but we couldnt use their facilities as that is supposidly a superior hotel, although we didnt think so. The surrounding gardens are well landscaped and maintained with lovely fountains etc. You will also see peacocks and pink flamingoes wandering about freely. The pools are freeform and always nice and warm, and very nice just to sit in with a cocktail in your hand. The punta cana pool is a bit quieter as the dominicana one has water polo and aerobics going on etc. The grounds and hotel were always spotless. It may be nice to tip the gardeners and cleaners as they often tend to get overlooked when it comes to tipping but their job is equally important to ensuring a great holiday.Rooms:After reading reports on here we took the advice of one traveller who advised us to tip the recptionist when getting room. We asked for an upgrade to a junior suite and got one just by asking. I tipped him 10 dollars for it. I was so glad i did too because the room was beautiful Very clean, lovely air conditioning that was quiet (many guests in normal rooms complained it was loud), nice balcony overlooking the gardens, tv, coffee maker, iron, hairdryer, nice bathroom with shower (although the water pressure wasnt great) Also as it was a junior suite, we had a seperate living area with sofa etc.One thing we did notice were lots of minute little ants in the bathroom. Always seemed to apepar after the cleaner had been in, i think it was the roses etc that the cleaner left that attracted them. If you are staying in the dominicana side, you wont get a junior suite as they are only in the punta cana side. They are also much more modern decor wise etc.Food/Drink:Superb - all of it! Cant believe how people find things to moan and whinge about.. what do people expect??? caviar and lobster?? well you can get that here aswell and all free !!The main buffet restaurant was great with show cooking, steaks made to order, fish, pastas, big salad bar, burgers, chips, pizzas, you name it they had it.The speciality restaurants you get 4 reservations for a 2 week stay. We went to the steak house twice which is lovely and on the beach. The sirloin steak done medium was to die for.The mexican was lovely too and the gourmet was beautiful.. we had lobster and you could get caviar on the starter bar. Didnt try the medditeranian one but the japanese was lovely.. never had sushi before and it was lovely as was the thai green curry.The star rock cafe is great and you can visit as many times as you wish. Its air con and you get served by waiters. It is done in an american theme, very nicely done and it opens at 7pm. The earlier you get there the more chance you have of getting in.The drinks were quite good too.. not as good as when we were in mexico or in the riu merengue which is where we stayed last time in domincan (north). but they were still nice. The local beer presidente is nice but can be gassy and loses its head quickly. Cocktails are lovely. The shorts are ok too.. no jack daniels though (gutted) altho Jim Beam, Smirnoff, Gordens, etc are available. Wine was very average (typical cheap wine).Entertaiment:Hmmmm not the best. The Iberostar Tucan in Mexico was far better where they had professional chereographers etc while here they only hired them in once a week. The shows were mainly ran by the animation team where such shows were Mr Iberostar, Men vs women etc. some of the better shows were the michael jackson show and the hollywood movie show. Also the shows are in the outside theatre which gets very hot and humid at night (bring the insect repellant)We spent every night at the air conditioned casino.. 3 blackjack tables, 3 and 5 card poker, 2 roulette tables plus one electric roulette machine, and lots of slit machines. The casino got very busy later on. The drinks are all free in here too.There is also a piano bar playing live music which we prefered to the shows. There is a bar by the beach too which is nice for a cocktail watching the stars. Once a week the animation team host a beach party at night. This was great. BBQ and beach games etcBeach:WOW WOW WOW ! pure white powdery sand and clear turquoise warm seas.. beautiful. Great for snorkeling too as small coral reef a short swim away.. lost of great fish. lots of palapas too to escape the hot sun if required.Daytime activities:water polo, beach football and volleyball, darts, archery, aerobics etc all organised by the animation team. Great if you want to be more active.Staff:Fantastic as all the domincans are. They serve you well and always say hola Tip them a doller here and there and they appreicate it sooo much, as remember its a poor country and these guys work long days for little pay, and still dont stop smiling.Excursions:We did outback safari which we also did last time we came to the dom rep. Its a great day and highly recommended. You get to see the real dom rep and have great fun too.We also did Saona island - save your money guys. Didnt enjot this at all. The island is meant to be pure paradise but the beach at the hotel is better as is the sea. You get three hours stranded on this beach with nothing to do. Its a very long day 6.30am pick up and dont get back till 7pm.Overall:Fantastic and superb. How people can complian is beyond me, although like i said its mainly the yanks. although to be fair most of those liked it too. Check the bad reviews, hardly any english. Trust me you will love it here, if you dont you must either be mad or american.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>