<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="6abf9c7404e5d79bb6f24b393c255a49" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic experience Loved the Marriott!What I liked:1. Very comfortable room. Spacious, had a microwave and a sink.2. Large bathroom .. huge bath-tub.3. Location is good. CBD is a 5 min walk. Hyde park is across the road. Oxford Street, round the corner, has great food and drink options.4. Service is great. I thought my camera was stolen, and I reported that to reception. They went to great lengths to investigate it. Much appreciated. I found the camera in my own bag later.5. Complimentary chocolate, left on my bed by the house-keeper!6. Roof-top swimming pool is awesome, with a great view.What I disliked:1. The room and fittings are a bit dated, though not ugly.What I'm neutral about:1. The gym looked alright, though I didn't use it2. The bars restaurants seemed fine too, but I didn't use them.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e3c12779cba2eba7c9e29c2e050c8e3f" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Service The best service I have experienced so far in Australia.Very courteous, provided full information when asked anything, helped with luggage.Location is fantastic. Right next to Darling Harbour. Perfect for a holiday in Sydney. Also perfect for a business trip (close to CBD office areas and Pyrmont).The room was very nice. Took me a while to locate the bar-fridge though. Internet was good quality too (not free).Room was a bit dark.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b2a58330db39d1e34b5942363b2236cb" url=""><![CDATA[Not much of an *apartment* Positives:1) Nice and clean2) Courteous Staff3) Very good location (for tourists and business-travelers)4) Internet is probably cheaper than most hotels ($12 for one hour, $24 for a 24 hour block).Negatives:1) Floor smelled of cigarettes (I might have been on a smoking floor)2) Apartment only had a microwave and a bar-fridge - not much of a kitchen(ette).3) Bed was uncomfortable - quilt was tucked tight and low ... I struggled to get it upto my chest (and I'm not tall). This seems a common theme across all Medinas.4) Apartment was tiny5) View was nothing to write home about6) Power button on TV remote would NOT turn the TV off. It would just bring me to the Pay-per view menu.What I cannot judge:1) Pool Gym - never went there2) Parking - never used it3) Porter service - never used it
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5b7a91ee9dd95c8ca7a47d985e22c1d5" url=""><![CDATA[Great Place It was a good place. Always got a smile with the service ... which is not that easy to come by in many places!The room was HUGE. Nice balcony ... Spa-style shower ... Free Broadband (yes, FREE! and fast too).The gym pool were tiny ... but there is a fitness first down the road. I didnt sample the restaurant. But every morning, they had $2 coffee in the Lobby (very good 'Vittoria' coffee).Room had a kitchenette. But no utensils. I didn't ask for any, but I am sure they would have brought some up, along with a smile.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>