<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="1e6e86c4a56b85111ebc9a1aa4ce2803" url=""><![CDATA[Just Plain Perfect!!! Me and my boyfriend have just stayed at the Derag Hotel Grosser Kurfuerst in Berlin.... It was brilliant... just what we needed, nothing too over the top, just a great base for our travels. We are students on our summer break, we stayed for 3 nights in a basic double bed room.The hotel is literally next to the underground (dont worry you cannot hear a thing, and we were the closest room to it) which is great when your tired after a great day of sightseeing and all you want to do is chill out :)The hotel is situated in a quiet businessy area, it is easy to access the whole of berlin within a few minutes.The rooms are nicely presented, spacious, comfortable, have good facilites, large bathroom, nice choice of tv channels, and dont smell funny. The overall hotel has nice decor. We did not eat in the hotel at all, but from the look of things, it did not seem too expensive. We opted to eat out in touristy places and sightsee while doing so.My only moans are.......that we had no control over air-conditioning, but to be honest, they are not stupid, we went in a heat wave, so they turned the AC up, when it got colder they turned it down... no compliants really. Oh, and also bring hair conditioner and shampoo, the bathroom facilities are good, but it is just an all in one body wash, and shampoo thing. Also, it was a bit annoying that a 'double' really means two single beds put together, it tends to take away the intimacy, and they just give you two single duvets rather than one double duvet.MY TIPS FOR BERLIN and THIS HOTEL IN GENERAL:1. Check maps - undergound and overground are fairly easy but just check which direction you want to go in.2. Don't bother with Checkpoint Charlie - its a fake! Literally...3. Dont bother eating in - go out and see the world.... this includes beakfast! its cheap but filling!4. Alexanderplatz nearby has some nice hidden restaurants5. Go to the Sony Centre Cinema - english, massive, cheap and rarely crowdedNeway Go to this Hotel its Brilliant.... just what we wanted
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>