<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="93c6f08f61e268de4d16133b477ec69b" url=""><![CDATA[Good choice My daughter and I stayed at this hotel mid October and it was a really good choice. It is in a good location, just 3 - 5 minutes to the main shopping street. The hotel is very good, with lovely bedrooms and friendly service from front-desk to the dining room which is run by two women chefs. We will stay at this hotel again.On the surface, it appeared to be a really quiet area and hotel, but from approx. 4.30 p.m. the hotel bar just came alive with people meeting after work and others starting their evening. The surrounding restaurants were also very busy with lots of atmosphere.We only stayed two nights in Boston before going to New York which we had visited before. Two nights in Boston is not enough, it is a great city with lots of everything, but so much more refined than NY. We will good back to Boston again without a doubt.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="97f633c9f77cb01f201651ef73bc9fd9" url=""><![CDATA[Too big This hotel is situated directly on Times Square. If I remember correctly reception is on the 8th floor, which is quitre a way up to the hotel. Receptionist very nice and efficient.This hotel is like a city, it is far too hectic. It is just rush, rush, rush! The lifts, and there are quite a lot of them, are always overflowing with visitors. However, there is a good system whereby one presses the floor required on a pad approaching the lifts and you are then told which lift to go to, which cuts down the number of stops en-route.We had a delux room on the 40th floor facing Times Square. No noise. This was nicely furnished, and kept clean. No complaints here. Accommodation at this hotel is quite expensive.Had three meals at the hotel and didn't rate the food. However, did not go to the restaurant at the top of the hotel, so cannot comment on this.Would I stay at this hotel again - No. It is too big and no personal touches. Would not stay near Times Square again - it is too busy. Incidentally, I have been to NY previously.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>