<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="b052504aaf76745e592a0685260c16bf" url=""><![CDATA[splurge worthy For our family of four, we booked two adjoining corner rooms and now we are spoiled for any other hotel. Both rooms had endless views and were perfectly furnished. It can be quite difficult to find a hotel in Tokyo to accommodate a family, but the MO did so beautifully. My kids pointed our that their twin bedded room was even larger than our corner-king and technically they were right, but ours was quite satisfactory. The staff knows the essence of service and achieves a very high standard in a country that has perfected the art. The only downside to this hotel is that it's located in a business district and there's not much to do in the immediate area. There is, however, a very convenient metro/JR station on the ground level.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="167244348f2d75e40572b715cec37d62" url=""><![CDATA[A gem Just an ideal London boutique hotel. The right size--so that all amenities are available, the right staff--warm and welcoming, and the right location--overlooking Kensington Park. Our duplex room decorated like a library featured a billards table/dining table (you'd need to see it) and upstairs living area that served as our children's sleeping area. Bathroom was well appointed (though I find those European shower enclosures frustrating). Everynight candy and canapes were delivered and the turn-down service was excellent. Comfy beds. The roll-away beds need some looking after as a couple of them were missing slats. Breakfasts were classic british or continental as you choose. A sweet little bar/conservatory area make a nice nook for a drink or tea. My only significant complaint is that the pool is quite small and seemed over-dosed with chemicals.We'll absolutely return.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eeb4d6aa59e3f90af5a7a9d922ea5de4" url=""><![CDATA[Deserves its high ratings It's like having your own apartment in this glorious city. The famiy suite was very generously proportioned, decorated thoughtfully and with sophistication. It's hard to believe it's just a few minutes walk to Piazza San Marco, but it's quiet and peaceful. The staff is totally professional and helpful. Call them as you arrive by train or plane and they'll give the number of the water taxi that knows their location (it's hidden--but in the middle of everything) and they have a boat-up location so it's worth taking advantage of it. We used the kitchen one night and found it well stocked. Having a washer dryer is helpful too, but since it's a euro-model that uses very high heat, it's best used only for your sturdiest clothes. Breakfasts are a typical European assortment of cereal, pastries, cheeses and meat. They'll deliver it to your room if you like, which is a nice touch. My only criticism is that the desk person on duty after 8pm speaks only Italian, so it was a bit difficult to make arrangements sometimes, though he tries hard. We will be booking this again for our next trip to Venice, but I suspect that we'll have to do so far in advance, because it's deservedly popular.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>