<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="48714a58c0756c130c9d6a04fca2d35b" url=""><![CDATA[It's ok, not a 5 star. Stayed in a Junior suite of which was booked with Sunwing. The rooms was big, but the locations of Jr. Suite are next to the front lobby in a hotel of 2 floors., it's not the same has a suite. For what we payed it was not one of the best I have ever stayed at. The food was ok, not a 5 star. The entertainment was terrible need a big improvement.The Beach was the best I have been to in D.R. We travel 2 trips in the winter, been to Cuba 4 times, D.R. Puerto Plata twice and Punta Cana was are second time. For $3600.00 Cdn per couple was too much money. The service was good. The grounds are very clean and big, lots of walking to do. But the trolley is a must at this resort. Would I go back there? No. If you go, make sure you book a Suite not a Jr. Suite. Sunwing flight was delayed 4 hours in Ottawa of which we where not impress.But overall this hotel is ok.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2bd16f05dd37be68806685bc592e7200" url=""><![CDATA[Great Holiday, lots of fun. Stayed from Feb.10 to Feb. 17/06: We travelled 2 couples with Sunwing. A last minute deal came up for us to stay in Suites which was bldg. #7.The room: WOW!!! the room was fantastic: King size bed, Jacuzzi tub, very very big bathroom, the room decor was beautiful but the floors are ceramic titles (a bit cold on the feet). If you take a regular room we will be dispointed because the are terrible, we saw them. So make sure to get a suite. Sunwing also gave us Golf-shirts and bottle of rum in our room. We paid $1450.00 tax Included each, it was worth every dollars.The Food: The food was all good, no complaints for the quality. But the portion at A la Carte restaurants are a bit too small, even for me. My husband had to order double portions to satisfy him.The Night shows at 9:30 every night were good, do not miss the Micheal Jackson Show it's fantastics.They are 8 bars at this resorts. As far as food, if you go beside the pool bar there is food there from 5:00 to 6:30, all the other restaurants are close during that time. To get ready for supper. No you will not be out of food like people stated.The Vendors: Do not pay the price they tell you. Cut down the price from 2/3 or 1/2. We got lots of t-shirts they wanted $18 US, so we got them for $6.USThe Constructions: Is beside the bldg. #1 and #7, why do people complaint it's not that bad. They are building a Casino and it will be finished in 3 months. The Service: No complaints, the staff are very good and pleasant.My husband and I have travelled a lot, yes we do recommend this resorts. We never go back to the same one.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>