<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="91814d76a030322f6aa70ff0ec5ae393" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic hotel! My girlfriend and I booked two rooms (one for us and one for my brother who was visiting us) for each on their limited offer back in February. We stayed for just one night on 12/04/07 and can say that it is the best hotel experience I have had. Though that may be my relieved wallet talking! :Danyway, we arrived early evening and were warmly greeted by an Irish lady at reception (snazzy uniforms, by the way), and were checked in quickly. We were informed there were free papers (guardian and Evening Standard, lovely), though we were a bit miffed when she told us we couldn't replace our free breakfast yoghurt (we can't eat milk) with an extra piece of fruit each. didn't get why this was, as the fellow we emailed said we could. Ah well, at i can't moan too much. We then went up to our rooms, noting the free internet PCs (5 of them) and roaring fires with comfy seating in the lobby before stepping into the small but funkily tiled lifts (elevators for the yanks). The corridors continued the hotel's funky and trendy feel, though I might [--] that the red lights had the feel of a brothel! (or should I say what a brothel might feel like!)The rooms themselves were of a reasonable, imaculately clean, and furnished to a very high standard. This included a flat screen television with free music streams, radio, numerous TV channels (none foreign) and free internet with the provided keyboard. There was ample storage for somebody staying a night or two, as this hotel is aimed more at the business market, but couples, say, staying for a while may not have enough room. There was a smallish fridge with 2 free bottles of water and milk (not needed thank you!), and a digital safe to store your doo-dahs in the wardrobe. The bathroom. There were plenty of towels (plus more on top of the wardrobe), two free bottles of shampoo/conditioner (not really enough for two people), and an actual new bar of real size pears soap. I couldn't believe this, to be honest. I know it's only a small detail, but having that and a soap dish rather than hotel brand cheap soap made me smile! the shower itself was luxurious, with a separate handheld attachment for your...y'know. Back in the bedroom and the drawer came stocked with a hairdryer, bottle opener with pen-knife and corkscrew, map of the local area with restaurant and bar suggestions and a pad of paper and pencil. In addition to this were the usual coffee (standard and decaff in fresh ground bags rather than instant granules) and tea (twinings english breakfast an peppermint teas) as well as coffee and splenda sweeteners. There were 2 of: wine glasses, tumblers and mugs and a little tea cup-cum-sugar bowl type thing (it got left well alone!).By the large window (which faced out onto the willow street offices (nearly opened the curtains whilst nude - whoops)) was a sofa to recline on whilst watching television. That was until I found out that the TV could be swivelled outwards and to the side to face the bed! the bed itself was quite luxurious with warm, comfy duvets and clean, crisp sheets. The quirky scissors, paper, stone scatter cushions were a nice, and comfy, touch. Back to the point about the breakfast bag. I wrote a little note on it saying about the yogurt situation and was pleasantly surprised when I found the next morning that they had not only gone to the extent of supplying us with an extra piece of fruit (apple), but had also given us an extra bottle of orange juice and another bottle of water! EACH! thanks hoxton and pret!checkout was smooth and fast, with two extra staff coming over to attend the desk when they saw us waiting for a minute. About the area: the area is definitely not the glitz and glamour of Knightsbridge. It is a predominately residential area, whough in the past few years business men and women as well as quirky restauranters have set up shop. Because of this, the area is very fashionable. I would even go as far as to say that because of the residential area, you are in much less danger of being mugged as a tourist here than in, say, Victoria. Also, there are numerous buses that serve the area, with Old Street BR and Tube station withing 5 minute walking distance, and Liverpool Street within 10 or 15 minutes. All in all, a fantastic stay and a wonderful bargain, even if you get it for or a night.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>