<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="84812b57861a13e83f6703fc8202f81b" url=""><![CDATA[If only they did what they said.... All of the reviews of this hotel here on TripAdvisor were fairly accurate. Unfortunately,I experienced a different side of the managment, and was left disappointed and lied to. I checked in on a Tuesday. The following morning, I went out, and left the do not disturb sign on the door. I had all of my legal papers laid out in my room, and additionally, since I was going to be back at the room shortly, the safe was open w/my computer, camera and travelers checks in it. When I returned to my room, not only was the do not duisturb sign gone, but my key did not work. I called to speak to the hotel manager, and explained the problem. After initially not willing to send someone up top my room w/a new key(they wanted me to go down 17 floors in their VERY slow elevator's), a key was sent up. I got in my room, and saw that the staff had ignore my request sign to not enter, and had cleaned the room. All of my papers that were laid out on the bed, in preperation of my presentation, had been stacked on the room's desk. This was not only going to take me several hours again to lay out, but it violated my privacy. I called the manager again to complain...she said she woul investigate, and get back to me. She never did, and then the head of housekeeping called me, and said he would follow-up. He said they would review the video tapes of the hallway, and see what transpired. Then he left another message, and said the maid had already left for the day, and he offered his assurances he'd contact me in the morning. He also left another housekeeping supervisors' name, and said she was looking into it as well, and would let me know why the room was entered into w/out my authorization. I was a guest there four four nights, and during the entire time, none of the three supervisorial people I spoke w/ever got back to me, or followed through. I travel extensively, and mistakes happen. What compounded a mistake into a serious breach of hotel managements' verbal statements blatantly indicate unprofessionalism at its worst. The hotel's management shows an obvious lack of character and integrity. All parties concerned dropped the ball. No matter how nice a hotel's amenities may be, if a guest can not count on management to do as it says it will do( repeatedly I might add) then what kind of reputation is that for the hotel. I am in NYC every month, and have stayed in many hotels. There is an old proverb...I can't hear what you are saying because what you are is so much louder. The management said they would get back to me, but never did. Disregard for guests....no follow-thru.....poor management.....violation of privacy...all elements of a hotel not worthy of patron's time or money.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>