<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="79173b26d6915982ca2cd23279581aac" url=""><![CDATA[SF Marriott Fisherman's Wharf STINKS!!!! I am so unsatisfied with this hotel that I could not wait another minute to write this review. First off, I called the hotel the previous night to confirm the payment and make sure the charges were to be on the specified card. When we got there, Michael (rude hotel staff member) told me in order to check in I would need the original credit card and photo id. The problem is my mother kindly agreed to pay for the stay. So we had to call my mother at work, have it faxed over and wait. Keep in mind we had to catch a alcatraz trip in 15 min. When I asked how to get there, I was told its 10 minutes walking distance. I said well ok that still doesnt tell me much? Then he said oh its pier 39. That type of short service is very typical of the staff here. Even when we got back from alcatraz I asked to speak to a manager (Alexander) which wasnt any better. When I told him of my unsatisfactory service he told me well now that your better and calmed down from earlier you should talk to our concierge staff to show you some stuff to do in san francisco. Yeah like I'm going to take advice from the unhelpful hotel staff. To top it off my mother called the night before check-out to say they charged her WAY too much. I spoke to another manager (from England) who told me in the most blatantly disrespect tone that he knows what he is talking about and my mother is wrong about what is being charged to the room. Now I think MY MOTHER KNOWS what she is talking about when it comes to what is being charged to her credit card. Its a shame I had to deal with this on my birthday weekend especially when I wanted to stay at the argonaut hotel instead but it was booked (for good reason). Avoid this hotel as it has the WORST CUSTOMER SERVICE EVER!!!I wrote the previous posting the night before check-out thinking that was it but I was wrong. The morning of check-out I went to take a shower and was about a minute into doing so when the water from the shower head starting coming out in pulsating spurts which then turned to it spewing out YELLOW WATER. I immediately turned off the water and told my boyfriend to look as the water came out yellow (in addition to the faucet). We called the front desk who said they would send an engineer to fix the problem. Since we had plans for the day we told them we need to shower in another room. 30 minutes later a maid gave us a room key two floors down at the end of the hallway to shower. There was no explanations given or apologies for the inconvienience by the management whatsoever. Due to the ordeal we were unable to do what we had originally planned. I truly hope in writing this review others can be spared from theseexperiences.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>