<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="b6025793d1ce5140b61cf83fec55b2f6" url=""><![CDATA[Comfort My 4 night stay at the Hotel Rex exceeded all expectations. Here is the lowdown:Location - Perfect. The Rex is close to the Theater District and Union Square, but remote enough so that you don't feel like a tourist. Access to cable cars and buses is great. All major downtown sights are an easy walk. Also, the Bart trains are not far; if you don't mind walking 4 blocks and don't have a ton of luggage, I recommend using Bart to get to the Rex from the airport.Atmosphere - Polished and serene, with a european feel minus any attitude. My small, immaculate room on the second floor was completely silent - absolutely no view, but I really didn't care becase the decor was lovely and fun. Nice size bathroom too. Somehow, I lucked out and had a window air conditioner, but I am not sure if all rooms have this.Service - Front desk staff are attentive and hardworking. Cafe Andree has great food at surprisingly low prices. Even room service was inexpensive. The business center is convenient (no charge), and my room was promptly cleaned every day.Price - At $175 per night booked on the Rex website, I received a voucher for a full breakfast each morning and tickets to the Asian Art Museum. Well worth it, no regrets.Lastly, if I am not mistaken, the chain that owns the Rex maintains headquarters directly across the street from the hotel. If this serves as an incentive to keep the hotel running smoothly, it sure is working!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="742c86c39e00f63db7ee23001b285fb3" url=""><![CDATA[Did I Miss Something? We spent 4 nights at the Drisco in early March, which was 3 nights too many for us. I'll try to keep my comments brief. We had stayed at a terrific boutique downtown hotel (the same chain) the previous 4 nights and really looked forward to a change of atmosphere in a residential neighborhood - and boy did we get one. The room was booked directly through the hotel website. We were given a hot, dark room on the 3rd floor overlooking an interior courtyard - the spectacular Pacific Heights views we anticipated were nonexistent unless we hung out in the hallway or on the roof. Through the window, we were in earshot of every noise from other hotel rooms and the adjacent apartment building - frankly, I prefer street noise to flushing toilets, baby crying, coughing, sneezing, and various other bodily functions. We had no fan and no AC, and the room was ridiculously hot even though it was 55-65 degrees outside every day. The bed was like a rock. Yes, the room was pretty and the bathroom was large, but who wanted to spend any time in a hot, dark, loud room? Strangely, every other room on our floor had a theme name posted on the door - ours didn't - and I don't think they would take my suggestion for a name. Front desk hotel staff were aloof. They promptly reminded us that the rewards program we signed up for on the chain's website does not include this hotel; I guess I should have read the fine print. The continental breakfast they serve is on par with any other chain, nothing spectacular, and we felt rushed by the busboys. The business center, while comprehensive, charges you $4 for every 20 minutes of computer time and $0.20 per page to print. I felt nickel-and-dimed, especially since the downtown hotel we had just checked out of included these services at no charge.Pacific Heights has lovely homes and unparalleled city views, but be forewarned: parking is nonexistent on weekdays (resident permits only). Restaurants and shopping on Fillmore and Union Streets are not far to walk to as the crow flies, especailly since they are downhill. However, the return trip is a strenuous, extremely steep climb up a 300' hill. Bus routes are at the bottom of the hill, so be prepared to seriously exert yourself every day. None of this is the Drisco's fault - but it would be nice if they offered some sort of shuttle service. Speaking of shuttles - if you book any bus tours from the Fisherman's Wharf area, they will not pick you up or return you to the Drisco since the hotel is far from the downtown area and situated on the hill. Bottom line: bring money for taxis.Perhaps the Drisco would be OK for a one night stay to see the Pacific Heights neighborhood, but next time I will remain downtown.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0446d3e05a82adbd4b44d248a7240018" url=""><![CDATA[Convenient to Metro Napoleon was superb
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>