<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="1b970d09b26b1201b67bd8ea97fd04fa" url=""><![CDATA[Badley Needs Facelift. Great Staff Just returned from 6 nights at the hotel. After looking at 5 rooms finally got one that was cleaner than the others, The carpets were very dirty with stains and looked very sad and worn. Furnishing the same and looked like thay had not been decorated in years. The room that we finally took had to have a good clean, carpets and remove cob-webs fron ceiling. But on the upside the Reception Staff and Bellman on duty when we arrived could not have been more helpful to try to find us another room. The room cleaning and bed were very good. Location is great. Seasons Restaurant was very good if a bit expensive for travellers on a budget. Executive Chef was excellent and knew all about Customer Service.The Hotel Managerment were also very sorry about the state of the rooms and said that the whole hotelit is due for face lift. They did show us a mock-up room of the newdecorated one and this was realy up-market. As it is at the moment it is below the star rating it has.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eda3f1279bc8dd76b13b87bb9c6c31e2" url=""><![CDATA[Good Hotel Stayed fro April 16- 20th. Booked 2 standard rooms. 1 for my husband myself, another for my son. Felt the standard room was too small for two people. I went to reception and asked about a bigger room. I was offered an upgrade to a De-luxe Room for the price of Superior 30 euro a night extra. It was well worth the extra. The staff at the Hotel were most helpful. It was very clean and the breakfast excellent. The only thing I found having stayed in Florence before that it is quite a walk to the centre and after a long day sightseeing it, and its quicker to walk than get a cab or bus.. Aslo being close the river was a problem with mossie bite in the heat. The room had to be sprayed.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7a966c0c4a3c2e23b69ca0cd78de985c" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel sunrise from suite 38 flr
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>