<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="01f1eb43778c4dc2d8a4b7d10cda3281" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel in great location Having found this hotel while browsing the web for good hotels in Paris, we were impressed by the reviews and my friend and I stayed here for 3 nights. The location is good, lots of Paris landmarks within walking distance (e g Pantheon, Notre Dame, Louvre, Musee D'Orsay) and several nearby Metro stations, but the hotel is in a quiet side road so is quite peaceful. However, despite being an old building with thick walls, the partitions between the rooms must be quite thin as I could hear the person next door cleaning his teeth!! We asked for two single rooms but we each had a small double - my room was very small and also very dark as it looked out over a square courtyard so had buildings on each side. It was reasonably priced and fine for one person but I wouldn't like to share! There are bigger rooms and if I visited again with my husband we would definitely upgrade. The mini-bar was extremely expensive but unusually in a European hotel there was the option of a free hospitality tray, with tea and coffee. The hotel claimed to have a bar in the basement but when we investigated the first night it was deserted - no obvious bar area, although there was a shelf of glasses, no staff, and it seemed to double as a lounge area, but being in the basement it was dark and rather claustrophic, so we didn't linger. The breakfast room was in the sub-basement (!), but we regretted paying for breakfast because at it wasn't good value for money - there are lots of local bistros/restaurants which seem to serve a reasonable breakfast for much less.Reception staff were efficient, if not particularly friendly; my French is quite good but they spoke good English anyway. A request to replace a failed lightbulb in my room was dealt with amazingly quickly! Lots of restaurants in the local area but the quality was variable and prices seemed rather over the top. We found it rather strange that many of the restaurants won't serve sandwiches/snacks at lunchtime, although they're happy to just serve you with a drink! We would probably stay here again because it was a good location, but would go for bigger rooms.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4a31fc933259ae6fab81819f2c84744e" url=""><![CDATA[A very pleasant stay We stayed at this hotel for three nights as part of my 50th birthday celebrations, based on the reviews on Trip Advisor, and we were not disappointed. We went for a deluxe room, which was quite large, with a huge and very comfortable bed. We had told the hotel about my 'special birthday' and there was a half bottle of champagne and fruit in the room when we arrrived, which was a nice touch. Lovely bathroom, with fluffly robes and up-market toiletries (Occitane). Breakfast was served in the basement, which had a character all of its own! We had breakfast there on the first morning, I have to say it didn't seem very well organised. No-one told us what to do, it was unclear as which items were included in the continental breakfast, which was 12 euros, and which in the full breakfast, which was 18 euros; we were offered tea or coffee from a communal pot but no-one came to offer refills although I'm sure we could have had refills if we'd gone to find someone. We decided after that to have breakfast in the room for the other two days and that was lovely, particularly when we were given a complimentary glass of champagne and smoked salmon on the morning of my birthday! The full breakfast at 18 euros was very good value.The staff were extremely helpful and friendly, especially Kathrin, who seemed to be on duty almost the whole time we were there! She speaks excellent English but I was disappointed not to use my French, as I speak it quite well - my efforts to speak in French were answered in English, so I gave up after a while! Room service was excellent - we ate in the room on the Sunday evening and had pizza and tapas, with a bottle of wine. There were a couple of minor problems, one was the total lack of drawer space in the room - there was a bit of shelf space but it was not enough, and the hanging space in the wardrobe was just about long enough for a shirt - not adequate for skirts or dresses. The furniture rather let the room down, it seemed rather cheap and basic.The other problem was the lift. There was only one, which is fair enough as there is limited space, but it broke down on the Saturday and was still not working when we left on the Monday. Being on the fifth floor, we found it quite a hike, and my husband has a heart condition (although to be fair the hotel could not have known that). Had we known the lift was unreliable, we would have asked for a room lower down. The staff were very apologetic though and did everything they could to help, they brought our cases down on the day we left. I felt very sorry for the staff member who had to carry a heavy dinner tray up from the basement on the Sunday evening.I thought the hotel was a little on the expensive side but it's in the Champs Elysees area, so that's hardly surprising; it would have been nice to have had breakfast included for what we paid, but having said that, we did get a few freebies in honour of my birthday!Just a quick word about the area - the restaurants are plentiful (except on Sunday evening, when just about EVERYTHING is closed, hence the pizza in the room!!) but they are very expensive and the ones we went to weren't particularly good either. I stayed in the Notre Dame area last year and it's much cheaper to eat there. Nice area though, fairly quiet, quite close to the metro and within easy distance of the RER.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>