<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="1f969cafef4af92455c074f9d2e37e24" url=""><![CDATA[2nd Stay in 3 months - as great as the first! Not much room around the bed!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="906d476649cc8f5516b3efd7920f0c9d" url=""><![CDATA[Friendly Service Made this our favorite hotel in Italy! My husband and I stayed at the Davanzati in May for 4 nights as part of a 2 week trip around Italy. As many others have written, this hotel rightfully holds their #1most recommended spot. Fabrizio and Tomasso are so friendly that they take a very clean and comfortable hotel in a good location and make it EXTRAORDINARY.5 min walk to Ponte Vecchio10-15 min walk to Duomo15-20 min walk to Academia (overrated - get reservations thru Davanzati - would NOT have been happy if had waited 3 hours in line)10 min walk to Uffizi (also reserve in advance thru D.)To expand a bit on the happy hour - it occurs between 6:30 and 7:30pm. They dim the lights, and light candles and serve free wine and bread. After that, pretty much everyone goes to talk to the front desk to get their restaurant reservation info for the evening.The one issue we had was arriving in Florence on a busy Saturday afternoon IN A CAR. I don't recommend it. There wasn't anywhere to park the car to wait for the garage attendant. This was pretty stressful. Of course, every other day there were plenty of spots outside the hotel so you'd probably be fine on a weekday. It IS difficult to drive through the narrow streets however - and we're pretty adventurous drivers having rented cars in London and Australia.Enjoy your trip to Florence - can't wait to go back (and would definitely stay at the Davanzati again!)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a0562f2822c6b5e4834390976358f44b" url=""><![CDATA[Very comfortable stay My husband and I stayed at the Amsterdam Marriott for 1 night during a stopover en route home from Italy. This was our first visit to Amsterdam.The hotel was a good home base, even though we were only there for a brief stay. We had dinner and then walked over to see the Red Light district - about a 15-20 minute walk. The next morning, we took a canal tour before heading off to the airport. The canal tours conveniently leave from a dock about a 3 minute walk from the hotel. The hotel room itself appeared to have been newly renovated. Very typical and very clean and comfortable.We have gold status with Marriott and so were able to use the executive lounge for happy hour. In addition to drinks, they had both hot and cold appetizers -- and there's a great view of the city from the lounge area.I would definitely stay here again on my next trip to Amsterdam.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>