<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="e5a59fc11631b9f0f2388861221bc5d5" url=""><![CDATA[This was perfect for us! We wanted to stay near, but not IN Boston, and this was great. I had read on Trip Advisor that the hotel had a shuttle, which we needed. It worked GREAT for us, both in going to Boston Common, and to Harvard Square. We used the shuttle only, and not our car.The rooms were nice, the restaurants very good, the staff terrific, the beds comfortable, the room quiet, and we had a nice view of the Charles River. We would definitely stay there again. Boston was thrilling and we're glad to have taken the Trolley tour; great meals at Legal Seafood in Boston, and Sandrine's at Harvard Square.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0decdd26d71a9cfcf547a6ae22571461" url=""><![CDATA[Highly recommend This hotel was simply wonderful. Designed to look old, but only about10 years old, the hotel was beautifully decorated and set a veryNew Orleans mood. The location is terrific. It does not have a Fitness Center or laundry, but we didn't care. Their breakfast servedthe best fruit we had at a Hampton, on a long trip. We had great service from two employees in particular: Manager Charlene Martinez was extremely helpful, and Rose, who was serving breakfast, was a joy! (Hi to you both!)New Orleans is still a great city, yet it's one in extreme pain. We were so glad to visit there, to spend our money in a place that desperately needs support from business and individuals. The French Quarter was great, as always. But we drove all around the surroundingareas, and the tragic effects of Katrina are evident everywhere. The devastation was so extensive it will take years to come back. Here's a place where we can really make a difference.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="61a2e79c585023518f1cc2858c2c195e" url=""><![CDATA[a Rare 'five' Thanks to Trip Advisor reviews, we stayed at the Silver Cloud for 3 nights. It was one of our favorite stops in a month long trip. It has it all ... it was quiet, comfortable, roomy, great beds, spotlessly clean, lovely lobby, free parking, free internet, free and accommodating shuttle to downtown, extra nice continental breakfast in a large, lovely room, and helpful staff ... we even paid extra for the beautiful view of Lake Union. We honestly hated to leave! We had a great meal at Duke's nearby, also Daniel's which was VERY expensive... also a great meal at Anthony's downtown.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>