<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="06b9041e0f5c38a9100744ac6786c115" url=""><![CDATA[Overall a safe bet My wife and I stayed here the weekend of Feb 2 thru 4th '07. The hotel was easy to find and the parking situation is very good. We were able to park on the second floor of the garage each time. Parking is a steep $18/day but it is nice to not have to worry about finding a spot.Upon arrival we found we were booked in a 3rd floor room but they offered us the 15th floor when I asked. The 15th floor room only had double beds but that was a reasonable trade off.The Ohana East is right in the middle of the action. If you want to stay in the heart of Waikiki there really is no better location. You're not on the beach but it is a short walk.I give this property a 4 out of 5 stars for the following positives reasons: The room was very clean as were all the common areas. You can't really see any signs of excessive wear and it looks like the property is reasonably well maintained. The bathroom is on the smaller side but no big deal for us although some reviewers obviously differ on this opinion. (I'm 6' tall.) High speed internet is included for free- nice. As mentioned, the location and parking are both outstanding. We walked to Zanzabar nightclub a couple blocks down at around 10:30 PM on a Saturday. Based on some reviews I was expecting that we would want a cab back for safety reasons at 2 AM. Not the case- there were lots of people on the well lit street. This part of Waikiki has some prostitutes, but for us that didn't matter at all. Prosititues, due to the nature of their job, are usually friendly and harmless. They don't stay in business long if they mug people. The hotel also gives you access to the pink line trolley which alone is worth $8 for a single round trip ticket for 2 to the Ala Moana mall. The negatives: Our hallway had an odor at times. We never smelt it in the room thankfully. We're not sure what it was and didn't complain to anyone. Secondly, the internal walls of the hotel are apparently very thin. We could hear people talking on occasion.Other traveler considerations: As with any hotel in this area, there will be a certain amount of noise from outside. We were on the 15th floor and you could still hear traffic but it wasn't bad at all. However on a lower floor it might be unreasonable for some travelers. The property has AC so at least you won't need to leave your sliding door open at night- that would be a nightmare.Overall I consider this a safe bet for anyone like ourselves. We don't need pampering or spa service but we do often stay at more expensive properties (we're not rich... I'm just good at getting discounts and using priceline.com.) So, we're used to a certain level of cleanliness and upkeep. For people like us it can be a terrifying experience to look for a less expensive property- images come to mind of cockroaches, spiders, bloody sheets, ripped up walls, no hot water, etc.The world could really use more hotels like the Ohana East- less expensive with no major frills yet still clean and maintained.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="87b1ebb0ff210689f11ce8bbf1c6f212" url=""><![CDATA[Consistently Good I've stayed here a few times for business and most recently for pleasure. They sometimes have good rates for Hawaii residents, which was the case for the recent pleasure stay.In all cases the rooms have been consistent. I've never had much of a view in the P tower, but I've visited rooms in the K tower that have a phenomenal view of the beach. I assume these rooms are out of my price range by a long shot, which would explain why I've never stayed in one. The rooms are similar in quality, the main difference is the view.The rooms are relatively quiet for the location, all things considered. The beds are comfortable. The bathrooms aren't anything exciting. Personally, I think the rooms at a place like the Hawaii Prince are a good deal nicer, but it is unfortunately in the marina district and not really walking distance to the main part of the Waikiki strip.I enjoy the pool deck and especially the hot tub. This area is spacious and is actually a terrace. There is something about being perched up a few stories high that makes it pleasurable- can't really explain it.Their restaurant, Sansei, is my favorite place to eat in the entire state. If you like sushi, or even steak or normal seafood, it is hard to go wrong.Overall, assuming you get a decent price, this is a good place to stay for anybody who wants a slightly nicer property.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8e23c20080948bd82645b32dfbcdf655" url=""><![CDATA[Decent hotel- but reserve a high floor We stayed here for three nights. We are Hawaii residents so we got a discounted rate.The hotel is recently remodeled and is, in general, in good condition. However, an extra 20% effort in the rooms would have went a long way... for example replacing the old, dirty air vents or maybe some bathroom upgrades. Overall though, the room was clean and the bed slept well.This is not a resort, it is just a standard hotel, so you are basically paying for the room. The price includes easy, fast, free WiFi which is really nice considering the big resorts will really ding you for this.Many have said they had parking problems. We actually didn't go in and out a lot, but we never had issues parking. In fact, if you find a spot in their garage, it is really nice. This is the closest I've ever been able to park to my room in a Honolulu hotel. Perhaps, if you come back late you may have trouble getting a spot.Basically this is a good place to stay if you can get a good price and you don't need resort amenities. Don't underestimate some of the things the larger properties offer though. Even active folks who don't spend a lot of time in their rooms might enjoy being able to relax in the hot tub for a half hour under the stars at night in the warm tropical air. No can do this at the Wave.One other, MAJOR consideration. We were on the fourth floor and it was LOUD. I wouldn't stay here again if I couldn't get something on a high floor. Otherwise, check a property like the Ohana East and see if they have something on a high floor.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>