<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a980f6bdeee828f3528b1015ac1d0898" url=""><![CDATA[What are they talking about? I read these reviews before my departure a week ago and frankly was apprehensive, as in: What have I got myself into?. My main purpose in posting this is to clear up some of the BS that has been posted below. This hotel is clean, spectacularly beautiful, and (imo) decently maintained. My room was spotless, the shower was hot, the A/C worked fine, the maid was courteous, the grounds and the beach were immaculate. The variety, quantity, and quality of the food offered on the buffet was excellent. Although personally I would like to see some spicier items on offer, this is a Dominican Republic problem, not an Ocean Bavaro problem. These folks like bland food,period. On a negative note, there should be a toaster available in the main dining hall every morning, not just when someone thinks about trotting it out (there is one in the secondary dining room - this is a merger of two hotels). The beaches are beautiful and well-maintained. and are probably among the nicest in the D.R., certainly compared to the Puerta Plata complex. OK, lets talk about your fellow guests: Yep, there's a lot of Francais-de-France (as opposed to Francais-de-Quebec - a totally different person, not necessarily with the same points of view. Yeah, you may consider them rude, but this is a cultiral thing and how does this become the establishment's fault? Is the fact that you find your fellow guests might have different values than yourself something we need to read about? If I had to find a major fault, it would be the gift shop. It's pricy, when there are marked prices they are in US dollars. This hotel is not in the United States, and at least 90% of the clientele is not from the USA. A rip-off, as there is a supermarket a five-minute walk from the hotel with a mixed trade of locals and tourists that treats all their customers equally, prices are marked and are in pesos. I made the mistake of trying to buy an after-dinner cigar here one evening. The clerk attempted to sell me a cigar for US$25. Even after I explained that all I wanted was an after-meal smoke, the reply was Well, how much will you offer?. No prices were marked on any of their cigars. Solved the problem by visiting the supermarket and not buying so much as a newspaper from the gift shop. With this noteable exception, this place is a four-star facility with three-star pricing. I'd be happy to spend another spur-of-the-moment holiday there.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>