<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="a9afa501589b906370c09903a631135c" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel Bathroom
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="33fb59db3dda71338c82017e8506aa04" url=""><![CDATA[Service how it should be We booked this hotel for our final 3 nights in tokyo and wow we loved it.The hotel isn't that great to look at from the outside.But from the inside its beautifull. We got an amazing rate on Expedia. We had an executive room on the top floors with a breathtaking view of tokyo tower. Room category included free champagne every day from the minibar. The bathrom was big with jacuzzi. It also included free executive lounge , lounge a little disapointing. Breakfast was good.Only niggle the computers use was not free. The hotel was huge and had a shop too with reasonable prices.A great hotel if your looking to pamper yourself.The service was excellent !
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ed5c649bc02eae898dd99d678cb04979" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic Hotel 15th Floor Room
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4af5b7996b184b00dd43b005db3a7ce9" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel Great Location We stayed on our first 3 days in Tokyo and this hotel is a well suited nice stylish hotel perfect for all your needs.We booked a premium king room. The room was georgious and quite big. However my one complaint about this hotel is NONE of their premium rooms have a view of facing Tokyo tower. Only standard and corner rooms have a tower view (or so I was told , when i enquired) so bear this in mind when booking. You would think premium meant not only larger room but also better views, sadly not so. However the city view from our room was adequate.We had breakfast each morning , expcept on final moring when we had to catch a shinkansen to Hiroshima. The breakfast was ok not huge but satisfying.They have 2 computers and a laptop with internet connection which was free of charge. The lobby is beautiful and nice for a drink or two late at night.The hotel is well connected to the JR and Metro lines. However can be confusing arriving for the first time. I recommend arriving at shiodome metro station , its closer.We also found the family mart on the ground floor of great help.Please email if you would like to know more about hotel e.t.c I am happy to advise from my experience.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>