<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="f92649ae7a5afc2200dbe2c661c10234" url=""><![CDATA[Outstanding service Stayed at the Jays based on other reviews on Trip Advisor. This place does not disappoint. We have stayed at other top hotels, including many Four Seasons, Mandarin Oriental's and Ritz Carltons. The service at the Jays is the best I have ever seen. Before we even arrived at the hotel, we communicated with Judy, the owner, and her staff to set up museums and a side trip to Versailles. They could not have been more helpful. In fact, when we inquired about a Paris restaurant, Judy said she hadn't eaten there, but that she and her husband would try it out before we got there so they could give us a recommendation. When we arrived they had a booklet waiting for us with the itinerary that we had worked on over the preceding months. Very professional. Before we left, we needed a train to Amsterdam and they went out of their way to assure we had the right train and time. With such great service, it may be easy to forget the room, but we were on a three week tour of Europe, and the room was the biggest one we encountered. It had a large four poster, king sized bed. The mattress was a pillow top. While it may have been a little more pricey than a typical boutique hotel, the level of service that was provided made up for the cost. Absolutely loved the Jays.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="87f2389b0a34ecb8409d4a4744275452" url=""><![CDATA[Outstanding hotel We stayed at this hotel for 2 nights in June, 2008. They have a few rooms in the main hotel and a few in the building across the alley. We stayed in the suite on the top floor of the building across the alley. The room was fabulous. It was extremely clean and quite large. The bathroom was spotless. The suite had a separate kitchen area that was very large. The only downside was that the room was on the sixth floor and there is no elevator. However, the staff of the hotel took care of all of our luggage, so the stairs were never a problem. In addition to the room being so great, the hotel is right behind the Doge's Palace and about 100 yards from the boat docks at St. Mark's Square. I can't imagine a better hotel in Venice.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>