<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="d225ead0eea4c877e7f08879e3020c59" url=""><![CDATA[Outstanding Hotel This is a three star that is much better than the rating would suggest. It is one of the best, most friendly, clean and well located hotels you can find in any city and definitely in Madrid.The hotel staff is helpful, eagar to offer suggestions, directions and quick to respond to any request. Most speak English and all employees appeared to love their jobs, giving good service and the hotel. The owner is available in this family owned and run hotel and is involved with employees and issues and the staff spoke favorably of the management--always a good sign of a well run operation. The rooms were larger than could be expected in a 3 star, the decor was modern (the name) and well appointed, the bathroom was large with lots of light and hot water (always a plus for me) with fluffy robes (yes, robes in a 3 star). The room, the halls and the entire hotel was well maintained and extremely clean. The lounge and meeting rooms (also breakfast room with reasonably priced food) on the 2nd floor were spacious and very attractive--an excellent place to meet friends and/or business associates. Maid service was both efficient and done with a smile showing geniue concern for the guests. A minor maintenance problem was reported and within minutes people arrived to examine and fix the issue. In fact, this was a hallmark of everyone with whom I interacted--great and friendly service. A very well run and managed hotel. The hotel could not be better located. It is in the heart of many of the 'must see' tourist attractions such as the Plaza Major (tourist office located in this plaza), the Royal Palace and the Opera House. Even though the hotel is in the heart of the Puerta del Sol area the noise level was quite low for sleeping. However, the excitment of the area with lots of shopping, bars, eating places, etc. is great fun. There are always people on the street, performers exhibiting their talent and good people watching. The Metro is just steps out of the front door of the hotel which makes travel everywhere in the city easy, convenient, safe and inexpensive--even to and from the airport.I have only been home a few days but I have recommended this hotel to my friends and family and I plan on returning as often as possible. The whole hotel experience was one of the highlights of my visit to Madrid. Don't miss the chance to enjoy this special place, Hotel Moderno.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>