<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="f47eef877bead9cefea7caa39a05855f" url=""><![CDATA[Lovely Hotel Wasn't sure what to expect from the sprawling metropolis of LA after reading various reviews so I picked a fairly central hotel in Downtown. The Omni is primarily a business hotel but it was perfect for us road weary road trippers too. Beautifully set out with very helpful staff - the concierge was particularly helpful in answering our queries regarding transport attractions. This hotel is in a great location for exploring LA, particularly if you don't have a car. As it's in the business district there's not many shops nearby but the underground to all the prime sights is a 5 minute walk away and the area felt a lot safer than much of the city.Bedrooms were expansive and comfy with big roomy bathrooms. Lots of drinks and sweets available from the mini bar - though at a price too rich for us! Morning buffet breakfast (not included in price) was also a treat, fresh made-to-order omlettes and and fuevos rancheros. All in all this felt like a real luxury hotel experience and a great way to finish our California trip.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9923b178512d98bf52529a99d8517939" url=""><![CDATA[No Room At the Inn... We arrived at this hotel at 11pm, worn and weary after a long flight from the UK, only to be told that the hotel had overbooked and there were no rooms left. This was somewhat disappointing given I had booked and paid for our accommodation in full over a month previously. In addition, I had called earlier in the day during our stop over in Philadelphia to say that we wouldn't be in until about 11pm and check everything was OK - I had been assured it was...And so we found ourselves shuttled off at 11pm to a what we were told was an equivalent-standard, family run hotel nearby. This turned out to be a tired and grotty motel in the red light district that was crawling with prostitutes and drug dealers. We were put on the first floor which had patio doors with a dodgy lock that was easily accessible. We spent a very uneasy night then headed with our luggage straight back to the La Quinta in the morning. We demanded a room or an upgrade to a better hotel rather than one of inferior quality to what we had paid for. Fortunately they now had a room available and the rest of our stay there was fine. I must say the staff did apologise for what happened and were nice enough trying to sort things out. The error had occurred at central booking and wasn't their fault, but it did create a pretty poor start to our holiday. If you make a booking here you'll really need to make sure the hotel is ready to honour it!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>