<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7afd9a65db52050bf7fa97abe36285bc" url=""><![CDATA[Great all around upscale family resort I read alot of mostly favorable, And some mixed reviews before my visit to the Rio Mar. Here is my take. The rio mar has 5 star, 4 star, and 3 star aspects. Here is my breakdown: ..... PLANE TRAVEL: 5 stars- Four hour direct flights from N.Y.area with many flight choices on many airlines, no connecting flights to smaller islands (which many on my plane missed because of the ny ice storm) my roundtrip was $240 ...... HOTEL LOCATION AND PROPERTY: 4.5 stars- A 30 min. car ride from the airport, set on beautiful grounds with 2 nice golf courses, lots of tennis courts, Grounds are nicely landscaped. HOTEL STRUCTURE- 4.5 stars- tasteful, rustic, lots of terra cottaearthtones. Lobby is big, simple and beuatifull, not all white and marbleled like a four seasons, reminds me a larger version of the old Dorado Beach lobby ...... ROOMS- 3.5 stars. The rooms are a bit of an enigma to me. fairly small and rustic. BATHROOM was a bit tired looking, rust stains appearing around most fixtures, far from luxurious. BALCONY was great, held a table with 2 chairs. great for having breakfast. BED was awesome, slept better than @ home. MAID SERVICE was there by 10:30 am every morning. ........ POOL- 4 stars- One of the thing I hate most about Vacations is getting up @ 7 am to get a poolside chaise w/ umbrella. The rio mar is no different. get there early for a choice spot. pool is nice, w/ a 4 leaf clover shape, big hot tub, fairly lame water slide for a hotel like this, kids seemed to like it though. seperate adult pool was very nice and fairly quiet..... BEACH-4 Stars- no powdery white or pink sand in Puerto Rico,Just nice soft brownish sand. beach must be a mile long and 50 yards wide, lots of chaises. fairly big waves, lots of fun for adults and kids. Can get a bit rough depending on the wheather. need to comb the beach a little better! .... FOOD- 3 stars- Restaurants are very nice looking, good ambience. Prices are not unreasonable in my opinion(similar to new york restaurants). Food was mostly awfull. stick with fish or pasta. I don't know where they get their beef from, i doubt it's from cow. Even the burgers taste bad. Kids menu was actually good. everything was $6 on it. Aqua Luna had good Seafood, Palio was the best spot, pretty good Pasta. Ate at Shimas Twice(no other choice) it Was just plain bad. Went local twice, Richies(great views) and La Parilla(lots of bugs)both highly recommended from the staff. I found the food to be no better then the hotel food....... SERVICE: 5-Stars- Staff was very Accomodating, never rude. very cheerful. In my opinion 5 star staff abd service, prompt maid service a big plus...... THINGS TO DO:-5 -Stars- every hour they have different activities for those who don't like to sit. Hair braiding for kids, aqua robics, iguana feeding,kids bingo, P.M. bonfire w/ smores making, Poolside kids Movie at night. 2 golf courses, tennis, lots of excursions, they are pricey if you do through hotel(i rented a car(saved alot of money)..... OVERALL- Great family resort, not for a romantic getaway..... VALUE- While not cheap, I feel the hotel is priced right for what you get. P.S.-$70 resort fee is completely obnoxious, but i think most big resorts have this charge, it's a hoaxy charge, all the stuff you think is free is really not(complimentary room coffee,beach towels,shampoo,shuttle service,plus any thing else you think is complimentary is paid for for via the resort fee.) I Will be going back, overall great experience, but manage your expectations. Go for a family vacation, not for the food.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>