<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="ccc8acca8aa2dc687718ec068e213720" url=""><![CDATA[Decent Business hotel in the heart of the financial district I stayed at the Marriott, New York Financial Center from 8/22/06 to 8/25/06. The best part of the hotel is its location. Right in the heart of the financial district and opposite the World Financial Center. The rooms are strictly okay, appears old. The lobby is small. They have a Starbucks in the hotel. Cabs were easily available, and there is public parking behind the hotel. The closest Subway Station is the Rector St station on line 1. The other convenient subway station is R or W line station at Rector St and Trinity Place. The stations are couple of blocks from the rear entrance of the hotel. I also had breakfast and one dinner at a small, charming bistro called George's Sons at 89 Greenwich St, minutes from the hotel and close to R-W subway station at Rector St. Good cooking, prepared fresh.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9b11e3c02d3bec54a8ee78df54c3cf83" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel at a great location I stayed at the Courtyard Marriott Midtown East, 866 3rd Avenue from June 19 to June 22, 2007 on a business trip. The location is great from my office which is on Lexington Ave and 53rd St. and bang opposite the E,V Subway station on Lexington and 53rd St.It is clearly a no frills business hotel it delivers strongly on its promises. The free Wi-Fi worked very well in the room and the room itself was big, airy, modern and clean (much bigger than some of the other NY hotels I have stayed in). The check-in was smooth and hassle free. They provide complimentary USA Today in the rooms and a limited number of complimentary WSJs at the concierge desk in the morning. While the restaurant serves breakfast in its in-house it has tied up with a nearby Outback Steak House for delivery of in-room dining. A colleague of mine who was staying in the hotel at the same time said that she had great difficulty ordering in-room dinner through this process and after being put on hold a number of times, simply gave-up and walked out to have dinner. This being Manhattan, there is a wide variety of restaurants and bars around the hotel. I liked Solera (216 E 53rd St at 3rd Ave) which is expensive and focuses on Spanish cuisine and Grand Sichuan Eastern (1049 2nd Ave) which is moderately priced. Majority of the patrons at Grand Sichuan appeared to be Chinese, which in my mind is a vote of confidence in the restaurant.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>