<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="97f59932f1991352082c1e8197987bd8" url=""><![CDATA[Very nice stay I recently went to Seattle to meet up with some friends. We wanted to stay downtown and none of us were familiar with the city. We settled on the Max based on reviews and availability. It was a great choice for us. The location is really great, near everything. The staff is most helpful and informed we found. Yes, our room was small. It was also well appointed. The mini bar is a small frig which was easy to use for our stuff. The beds and bedding are first rate. The bathroom had a great tub, something I love! One thing I found odd is the windows were not sound proofed. It is city hotel with city street noise even on the 6th floor. The windows do open for fresh air. I loved the original art and the hallways. They are dark but not unpleasant. One evening we ate at the Red Fin, the restaurant within the hotel and enjoyed it. I would stay again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="af2dae5d1264b45d603596453cdf1d7a" url=""><![CDATA[Close to Cultural Venues My husband and I stayed at the Omni for a one stay for a birthday trip. The staff and rooms were great. The location, one block from the Music Center and Disney Auditorium was the real reason for our choice. The museum next door was also nice. Our room was spacious, the bed was so comfortable and it was very quiet.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7c29b70aecd5fc68f0ffb1309c1761c3" url=""><![CDATA[Gracious Stay My husband and I went to Mexico City for the first time over the Thanksgiving weekend. We stayed at Gonzalez because of the reviews here and were not disappointed. I booked a suite, which turned out to be an extra large room with king bed and bath. The room was large enough to contain a sofa, easy chairs, desk and wardrobe. Although on the ground floor we had no problem with noise. We ate breakfast every morning there. What a treat! Not only was the food delicious but the company of other travelers was wonderful. We also had supper there a few nights and it was very good. There is a coffee shop, book exchange and small library. The property is in a walled compound which made it very safe. The owner/manager Jorge could not have been more gracious and helpful. He helped us with arrangements and directions. The place is not perfect. The linens could be nicer, the king bed, which was firm, had a double sheet which kept pulling off on the bottom. The towels were of vintage swimming pool variety and the upholstery and drapes could be fresher. The floors were wood which was wonderful and the place kept very clean. Filtered water is available.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>