<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="63b72e7045ea6e0510f7edcd7e37f21c" url=""><![CDATA["Don't Bother With This Hotel!" If you have never been to Hawaii before, I do not recommend you stay here!I totally agree with I have been to Oahu over 20 times and have always wanted to stay at the Hilton Hawaiian Village. Well, I finally got my chance when I received a special offer to check out their time share. At check-in, after waiting a long time in a long line, I found the staff was very indifferent and not friendly. They barely look at you and hardly give you eye contact. They could have cared less if I was there at all! The property is so big, it seemed only like a convention hotel the guests in and out like cattle.The first room they gave me was very average and over-looked the roof of the shops. Even though I requested a non-smoking room, when I first walked in it smelled of smoke so I immediately had my room changed. They just gave me another very average room, also with no view at all. No apologies or mentioning any kind of better room. They seem to care that I was a prospect for purchasing one of their time shares.If you self-park, it is a mile to your room. And, if you want to walk to the center of Waikiki, you have a nice little hike ahead of you. The hotel is at the very beginning of Waikiki. There is nothing near the hotel to walk to - only the Wailana Coffee House across the street (which by-the-way has excellent food) or the Kobe Japanese Steak House with the little bears in front.I had a voucher for The Bali Hai restaurant. Otherwise I have eaten there because it was overpriced. But it was lovely. I had complained at the NY Deli, but the owner was in and he was very nice. The shops are over priced, as well. Other reviewers said there is an ABC store on the hotel grounds, but there are about 30 in Waikiki alone!The smaller swimming pool is tiny and the big pool is just average.There are other better hotels in Waikiki, I understand why the Hilton Hawaiian Village gets such rave reviews. It seems to me that some reviewers had never been to Hawaii before and this is their first impression of it, so they think the hotel is wonderful. If you want a great hotel, I suggest the Moana Surfrider, the Royal Hawaiian, the Outrigger or the Outrigger Reef. They are all in the price range of the Hilton. The Kahala Hotel is also a wonderful hotel, but it's around the other side of Diamond Head. If you really want something special and romantic, the only hotel to stay in is the Halekulani. In my opinion, it is the most grand and elegant hotel in Waikiki with superb service and a friendly, accommodating staff (no, I am not an employee, just a big bother with the Hilton Hawaiian Village.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>