<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="c539337c24b7b96f10257e6d3ecda46f" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent hotel We stayed six nights at the Intercontinental from March 14 to March 20, 2008. It was our first trip to Singapore on a package deal to Singapore and Hong Kong.The hotel is lovely - truly a first class experience. The staff was bright, experienced and helpful. Our room was large and comfortable with luxurious towels, linen and dressing gowns. The breakfast buffet was a delight with a choice of freshly cooked eggs, sausages and bacon, fresh fruit and juices and much more.The staff arranged our visit to the zoo - a must see in Singapore - are were very helpful in suggesting things to see and do. We highly recommend the Intercontinental and it will be our choice on our next trip to Singapore.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ea4cf189a67e5b36bbd0ea4bcf9113fb" url=""><![CDATA[Stay here if you can We stayed at the Casablanca for nine days from May 18th to May 27th.Our flight landed at JFK after 11:00 PM so we did not arrive at the hotel until almost 1:00 AM - after a wild ride from the airport by taxi. It was a relief to be booked into our room, not large but certainly adequate for two with the features that we love - luxury towels and linen, hairdryer and in-room safe. The next morning we enjoyed the complimentary breakfast of fresh fruit, fruit juices, pastries and bagels, cereals and a variety of coffees. Breakfast is served on the second floor where a 5:00 PM offering of wine and cheese is also enjoyed. We especially looked forward to this feature after long days of walking, shopping and shows - we saw four plus a taping of the Dave Letterman show. (Spring Awakening is an amazing show, with adult content). We overheard several guests commenting on how much trhey loved the hotel. The staff were friendly and seemed happy to greet us each day.They arranged for a 5:00 AM car and driver for us for our trip back to JFK - a bit of a luxury but so calm and relaxing. Our driver commented that The Casablanca Hotel is one of New York's hidden secrets. We would have to agree.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>