<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="311779bbc575e06173af1ecde2fc1c6c" url=""><![CDATA[WONDERFUL BOUTIQUE HOTEL My sister and I just returned from a three-night stay at the White Swan Inn, and we both just loved it! The rooms were spacious, and the fireplace in the room was such a lovely extra. The breakfast buffet was delicious, and I thoroughly enjoyed the afternoon wine hour. If you're a walker, there couldn't be a better location. It's half-way between Nob Hill and Union Square, with China Town an easy walk, and public transportation close by. The sink in my bathroom had just a very little counter space - I could barely fit my toiletries, and if there had been a second person he or she would have been in big trouble. But my sister's room, right next door, had a lot more counter space, so the bathrooms are not all the same. I will definitely stay there again, and would recommend it to friends. The decor is definitely Victorian - think a lot of wallpaper with floral/stripe/etc. prints, so if you're looking for a soothing zen room, this isn't for you. But my sister and I sure did like it!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="036eb297ac2bcad4aca9e7539682ac0a" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Hotel! My husband and I stayed here for four nights, from 4/11 - 4/15, and we could not have been happier. This was our fourth trip to San Francisco, and our fourth hotel. The room was large and nicely decorated, bathroom was fine. The entire staff - front desk, bell captain, and especially the concierges Peter Chuck were friendly, professional and helpful. Two small points of disappointment: There is a nightclub just down the street, and the noise bothered my husband, but not me. Just bring some earplugs if you're really sensitive. The continental breakfast can definitely be skipped, but there is a crepe house half a block away with a wonderful breakfast, or other places within 2 blocks.The restaurant next to the hotel - Postrio - is a Wolfgang Puck restaurant. It's pretty pricey, but the food was incredible beyond belief. Also liked the Daily Grill, a block and a half away - an old fashioned steak chop house. Fun good medium priced.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>