<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="55f772f49905fd6a4539967d4fb16513" url=""><![CDATA[Great stay at Royal Grove We spent a wonderful week at the Royal Grove. It's not some fancy resort, but it offer CLEAN rooms, good beds and a good shower. Those were the important things! The location is grest, two blocks from the beach, close to many restuarants, grocery store, and shuttles. Paid parking ($12 a day) at the hotel across the street. The kitchenette has full-size refrigerator, microwave, coffee pot, and four burner stove, plus all the dishes, pans and silverware. We stayed in room 208 overlooking the pool. Free use of beach mats, snorkel gear and beach toys was a plus. It was nice to get the free paper from the lobby and have my morning coffee while reading it on the lanai. I felt like this hotel conveyed more of the real Hawaiian spirit than the big resort hotels. As long as you aren't expecting a big resort with lots of activities, you won't be disappointed when choosing the Royal Grove! At $400 a week, it costs less than you could pay per nite at some of the other hotels in Waikiki. We're already planning our return!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ad811286a3e62336d5a016fa08ffdd3f" url=""><![CDATA[Loved IT We just returned from a week at the Resortquest Waikiki Beach Tower! It was awesome! The view from the lanai, the great staff, free valet parking, twice daily maid service, in room laundry facilities, full kitchen, and great location combined to make this a dream trip for my husband, myself, our adult daughter and my 80 year old mother. This was my mother's first trip to the islands so we wanted to make it special. The staff were very accomadating of our few specail requests. Our room wasn't quite ready by three but they gave us a bottle of champange, Godiva chocolates and a $100 in-room dining credit so we didn't mind the delay, just went next door for a snack until it was ready! Every staff member we encountered was friendly and willing to help with anything we needed. We had a two bedroom partial ocean view on the 17th floor. It was certainly better than most partial ocean-view rooms! We watched the surfers and swimmers every morning as we enjoyed our coffe on the lanai. The condo was a little dated and needed a few repairs but the beds were comfotable and everything worked so that was minor. We never had to wait long for the elevator even though one was being used by the renovation crew. We would recommend this condo to our friends and will definitely stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>