<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="ae398f2a82284a701303b5bdd844d161" url=""><![CDATA[Another nice NH property. This property is convenient to the Rijksmuseum, Leidseplein, tram stops, the Heineken Brewery tour, and the Albert Cuyp Market. It is a rather new (2001) property, and hosts many airline crews. The walls were thick and curtains dark enough to promote a good night sleep. There's a lounge, restaurant, and it is a stop on the conexxion (KLM) airport shuttle bus. There's a PC available for rent in the lobby. The property is functional and elegant, without unecessary flourish. Well recommended.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f9039106cea15c10ecbe9b8d1db31fb2" url=""><![CDATA[W in SF This W property is in the South of Market area; not renowned for tourism but across from the Moscone Convention Center and near the dot-com business area and SBC Park (baseball). It has a trendy euro-asian aesthetic, from the apparral of the staff to the decor and vibe. Inside, it is dark, stylish, with audible techno music and valets wearing wireless headsets (almost a cliche). It does feature an expansive lobby and bar area, populated by the dot-com crowd in an area still lacking many evening attractions. If you need to be close to shopping and tourist attractions, look again. If business or staying in a W is warranted, this is your place. Note that the BART light rail is a few blocks away.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="45a8248356c9b27d0d970392f8ff8aac" url=""><![CDATA[Classic San Francisco We recently enjoyed a weekend stay at The Fairmont San Francisco through Disney Vacation Club points usage. As a quintessential San Francisco property, there is much to this property as well as nearby.We stayed in room 590, the Dunkirk suite. It is a corner accomodation with great city views. It is well appointed in the classic sense; elegant Napoleonic decor along with modern touches like large flatscreens and two full baths. Along with numerous lounges and restaurants, I would recommend the Tonga Room. It is a Polynesian themed lounge and restaurant replete with thatched roofs, tiki iodols and rain falling from the ceiling accompanied by thunder from the loudspeaker. A true nostalgic experience!This hotel is ideally situated at the intersection of two cable car lines, and walking distance to Chinatown. It boasts an enviable location atop Nob Hill, and the service aspect from the staff is one of total service.This hotel is ideal for couples or families on a holiday, all the way to conventions. As it is a classic hotel, it will not have all the wired amenities of newer properties like a W Hotel, and Nob Hill is a bit far from the airport or Silicon Valley. However, if you enjoy classic hotels, this is among the best.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>