<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="afa426e09382d151af0652aa5ffa5f0a" url=""><![CDATA[It's now a great place to stay! I stayed here two nights, one going to and one coming back from the Marshall Islands in March 2007. Forget any prior bad reviews. This hotel is now a fine place to stay. The hotel has one wing completely renovated and recently closed the other wing for renovation. Everything is new. You beat the location. Literally 5 minutes or less from the airport via their shuttle bus that runs every half-hour. If you want to save dough on cab rides, take a bus outside the hotel. $2.00 to Waikiki vs. $30-40 for a cab. Highly recommended, even for stays of a week or more.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="144c165b231aaa3fd8f4e4a25d670ed9" url=""><![CDATA[The Drake is Great! My wife and I did a four day trip to San Francisco to take in a few baseball games and the City. We have been to SF several times and stayed at various places around the city. I found a great rate at the Sir Francis Drake on their web site and reserved a room. Great rate and no money up front. The Drake is a fine classic hotel in the perfect location. The staff is extremely friendly and helpful. The rooms are a bit small, but all have been refurbished and are quite comfortable. Since SF is a great walker town, a right turn out of the front door leads to three straight blocks up, up and up before you start going down, down, down towards Wharf. Excellent way to wear off breakfast. For those who want to pass on the walk, the classis cable car line goes right in front of the Drake, so just hop on! The light rail train to the ball park is a short 6-8 blocks away and a great, cheap way to get there. The staff at the Drake arranged for a rental car (Napa Valley trip) that was picked up and returned within 6-8 blocks from the Hotel. Very convenient in a city that is hell to drive in. We both highly recommend the Sir Francis Drake.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>