<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="05e6b14625c1991c599de2bcf00a15ca" url=""><![CDATA[Great Value for Location This hotel is a former Holiday Inn and completely renovated in European Style. Decor is the latest Brown/Blue suede with outstanding comfortable beds and pillows. Extremely well appointed with nice touches such as a plush terry cloth shower curtain and monogrammed towels. The latest style of faucets have been put in. Because the hotel is so conveniently located off the freeway at Sunset Blvd. you will get freeway noise on that side - turn on the air conditioning unit in the summer and you would never know. The hotel is circular and at the top is a fine dining restaurant with a nicely appointed bar. Great views of the Getty Museum and of UCLA and Westwood. Just up the street slip into the Hotel Bel Air for a drink without having to pay the price of their rooms. Extremely convenient for any business traveler into the West LA region and certainly acceptable for the vacation traveler also.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c8a826c97130ef5cb42a3c638b2e9d51" url=""><![CDATA[Fine Boutique Historical Hotel The hotel is tastefully renovated with fine art and furnishings. Rooms are extremely comfortable with fine linens. The staff make your stay more than pleasant. Experience the Library restaurant where they serve one of the best breakfast French Toast I have tasted worldwide. Hotel is close to everything if you enjoy walking a city. Charming and quaint best describe this 1889 built hotel that has recently been renovated. The hotel is owned by Kimpton Hotels and they have put a lot of money into their recent renovation with no skimping on anything.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1719e19d87bc5ccc0479478050add7fc" url=""><![CDATA[A must stay! Absolutely delightful boutique hotel in Amsterdam. If you don't mind being out of the hustle and bustle of the city hub this is the place. The hotel is located on a precious quaint street with lovely trees. Easy to get to from the central train station - just take the number 2 or 5 tram right outside the front of the station. You can purchase your ticket for the tram on the last car. Large rooms at this fine establishment and the services are all of the comforts of home. Exceptionally clean! Non Smoking! Family owned and they take pride in their business.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>