<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="43ee15af5bc6a594e00e41c1da241a04" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful hotel in the busiest part of town My wife and I stayed here for a conference. Excellent hotel. I grew up in NY, thus, never stayed at a hotel there before. This was an amazing first experience. As a New Yorker, I tend to stear clear of Time Square, but for my wife's first time, it was exciting. There is always tons to do. The hotel itself was extremely comfortable. We loved our room, very clean, with views and everything. I don't know how the cost was because our trip was paid for, so it was great to me. If you want to visit New York and stay comfortably in TIme Square this is the way to do it. We were able to retreat to our room to escape all the madness going on outdoors. Check it out if you can.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="818981a6b6b09f12a35bca54b109fd22" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel, nicer island Stayed here for my first trip to the island and enjoyed it. The beaches were beautiful, the pool was awesome, and the rooms were pretty good too. I have to say, I was so excited for my first trip there that I could have stayed anywhere and would have love it. This hotel was pretty nice though. The concierge was very friendly and helpful (a puerto rican who grew up in canada?) and the hotel offers many fun tours at reasonable prices. I was there in November, so the weather was gloomy for most of the trip, nevertheless, it was very warm and the ocean was like bath water. The pool was very nicely designed and I made good use of the swim-up bar. The casino was alright, kinda small, but my comparisons are to Vegas and the Indian casinos back in SD. The hallway to our room had gotten wet and was being dried with huge air driers. There was a very strange odor out there. The rooms were fine though, they had not gotten wet at all. I think the hotel could use some sprucing up. All in all, I had a great time and enjoyed a very nice, clean, fun and exciting hotel, with very helpful staff. Try the Pina Coladas at the piano bar!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>