<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="60196ecc24f456ceecb58f13c78c89ef" url=""><![CDATA[decent hotel good location Stayed at the Sydney Mercure over 26-29 November 2006 with no problems whatsoever. If you have limited time in Sydney you would probably enjoy being closer to the harbour, but this is a good location for getting around the city as it's quite close to the central station. There was a queue for checkin but this went quite fast. Staff were great and outwardly friendly to guests. Breakfast was a bit too chaotic and overpriced for me, but there are plenty of alternatives nearby. Hotel is close to transport and also there is a 24 hour shop next door...very convenient for travelers.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="767533f63e22591a371066677d1ba9d9" url=""><![CDATA[Ok for by the airport I booked my first night in Sydney at this hotel. It is nothing special but is reasonable if you need to be near the airport or don't want to go into the city your first night. I wouldn't book an entire vacation here or anything. The property is definitely dated and is undergoing some renovation in the lobby. The rooms definitely had some wear on the carpets and around the edges, but the bathroom and bed were both fine. I arrived early and was allowed to use the hospitality lounge before the room was free. However it didn't seem like many people use the lounge as there was no soap available and just one towel. Another drawback is that the deli next door is only open during the week for the business workers, so there are not many food options except for the on site restaurants which are rather expensive.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b50360c80dc621fcfba4a2eb289bfb0a" url=""><![CDATA[No complaints I stayed here on a weekend special rate. Very nice architecture building with modern interior quite a bit nicer than your run of the mill tourist hotel. Upon arrival the service was prompt and friendly, however there was s miscommunication between the front desk and housekeeping and I was given a room that had not been cleaned yet. I reported it back to the front desk and was immediately upgraded to a deluxe room. So that pretty much made it up for me since the room was a really nice one up on the top floor. I would agree with the other reviews that for the price it's about as good as you will get in Sydney. It's also reasonably quiet given the central location. All services were above average. It's in a great location for seeing the city although there's not much of a view from the rooms themselves.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>