<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="92b30a2a3290983ef19eb49d1f5c540e" url=""><![CDATA[Don't be fooled by pictures My friend and I stayed at the Royal Garden from 4/19-4/29/06. The pictures on the Hotel's website paint a different picture of what you will actually get. The lobby is decked out in marble and fancy furnishings, and it is clear that this is where the hotel chose to spend it's money. There is no internet access on the premises or coffee in the morning.First I will address the rooms. We had their basic room, on the eighth floor. The balcony offered a good view of the city, the Ala Wai canal, and the mountains in central Oahu. The carpet was dirty, so dirty I wouldn't even lay down on it. The bathroom tub's drain didn't hold water properly, and the bathroom door was slated wood that you could see through. The beds are small single beds and the two lamps in the room had problems working. We had to unsrew the bulb to turn it off. The furniture is all very cheap-deco, probably early 80's and very worn out.There is a female manager at the front desk who is very unpleasant, but the remainder of the staff, to include the maids, bell staff, and security officers were all extremely friendly. Unfortunately, most of the maids have trouble speaking English, so don't bother. The bellmen and security officers were very helpful in giving driving directions, and pointing out places of interest. We found their service superior. You will have to pay full price for a newspaper though, nothing is complimentary here.The exercise room leaves a lot to be desired. Only one electrical outlet worked in the room for equipment and the bathroom-whoa-I was not prepared for this. I opened the door, and the toilet was cracked open, there was black mold everywhere, and a huge hole in the ceiling above the toilet that had been caved in from water damage. The exercise room is actually a defunct guest room, and I cannot figure out why the hotel didn't lock this bathroom door shut. It was frightening an dprobably representative of bigger problems.You can walk from the hotel about 15 blocks to the beach. There is a TGI Friday's one block away, just don't do breakfast there, it was gross. This hotel is also very close to upper-end shops like Gucci, Prada, and Chanel, and an easy walk to the beach and the Waikiki strip. All in all, this is your basic, run down hotel. The room safe was free and parking was $12 a day. You really don't need a car if you stay in Oahu, the bus transportation is great. If you are planning on spending most of your time outside of the hotel, like we did, and are looking for a cheap and safe place to stay, this is it. Just don't expect much.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>