<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f7c6414bf222f96e200b5318d9371c03" url=""><![CDATA[Good Hotel but bothered by the worksite The hotel is conveniently located and is very near the Sants Station stop of the Blue Line of the Bus Turistic (i.e. the hop on and hop off tourist bus) which we spent most of the time in sightseeing in Barcelona. However, one will have to take the subway to Placa de Catalunya or a taxi to a nearby transfer point at Francesc Marcia-Diagonal in order to take the Red Line.The breakfast is a buffet style with lots of food; the smoke salmon is even better than what we have in the cruise ship which we have just left. The magnificent view of Barcelona one can enjoy during breakfast is beyond comparison.The staff is polite and friendly. The bellboy is particularly helpful. He explained the various switches of the room when he delivered our luggage to us.The hotel should have been a very good hotel but for the work site situated right in front of it. We arrived the hotel after leaving the cruise ship early in the morning and arrived at the hotel some time after 9 a.m.. Despite my request to have a room at a higher floor, the girl at the front desk said I could only check into a room on the 3rd floor immediately, or I would have to wait until 12 noon, the regular check in/out time. for another room on the 8th floor. There was also a condition that I would not be able to change my room once I had checked into the 3rd floor room. Since I have only 2 days in Barcelona, I wanted to settle down as soon as possible so that I could start my sightseeing earlier, I decided to accept the 3rd floor room and was fully prepared to take this as a room without a view. However, we had overlooked one thing or had we been alerted at all, i.e. it faced the worksite in front of the hotel. At 4 in the morning, workmen started talking loudly outside the worksite and heavy machines were clanking up and it was just impossible to continue with our sleep. We did not negotiate with the hotel for a change of room because we would have to get up at 3 a.m. to catch a flight home on the second morning. I wonder whether the hotel will allow us to change our room even if we asked. Another problem is the partition between the bathroom and the living area. Part of the partition is made of translucent glass. When I had to use the bathroom during the night, light came out through the glass partition and shone directly on the face of my wife and this woke her up. I cannot understand the rational of using the glass partition nor its location. If the designer wanted something translucent to create an ambient or what not, he should, say, use a translucent glass door, which faced the closet.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>