<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="ed2b937cb0f224e64791b8084b2d8659" url=""><![CDATA[Brilliant Hotel We really enjoyed Hawaii and the Moana Surfrider is probably the nicest hotel i've ever stayed in. It has the perfect mix of modern luxury with an almost colonial historic atmoshere. We had a superb stay. Everything about the hotel is luxurious. We were on our honeymoon and the staff couldn't have been been more helpful. We were offered a free upgrade to a room overlooking the Banyan courtyard. The rooms while not the biggest (its an old building) were spotless and very luxurious. Possibly the most comfortable bed i've ever slept in!Location: This hotel is right on Wakiki beach and is within walking distnce to everything worth seeing and doing in the wakiki areaWhile the pool is quite small the fact that you are right beside the beach means this hardly matters. The hotel has its own private section of the beach. Even during the hight of the day the pool/beach area never felt packed- we could always get a sun lounger- not something i've ever experienced in Europe.The food and service were excellant in the restaraunt with a very nice breakfast buffet. The food isn't cheap but then it is a luxury hotel.The pool/bar area is a brilliant spot to sit in the eveings and watch the sunset. There is live entertainment every night although it tends to be Hula dancing or local musicians. Very nice but not really my sort of thing. One evening we took a sunset catamaran cruise from the beach directly behind the hotel- an excellant idea (two hours of free drinks and turtle and whale sightings for $25)I can't recomend the Surfrider highly enough. If i'm ever back in Hawaii i will definitely be back.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9d96c37b12d752c6fea1537e11cf3f79" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel, Great City This is a beautiful little hotel in a great location in san Francisco. We were staying here for a few days at the start of our honeymoon and absolutely loved it. The staff were all really freindly and helpful and the hotel is very nice- all mirrors, marble and four poster beds. We booked a basic room intending to upgrade to a suite on arrival but unfortunately they were all booked up. The basic room was perfectly fine but a little on the small side.Location: the hotel is about 15mins walk from Union square but is right on one of the main bus routes for getting to Pier 39 and Fishermans warf. The public transport is the best way to get around (you could walk but the place is ALL hills) and is very reasonable if you by a multi day ticket.Overall a great start to the honeymoon and we would definitely recomend the Majestic to our friends.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>