<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="4b96376eea805c9a3198dd6394c7effd" url=""><![CDATA[This Takes The Cake!! My friend and I travel alot and we always try to find the worst hotel in town to stay in just too see how freaky it is. We've stayed in alot of dumps and have seen it all - the bums, drug dealers, pimps and hookers hanging around, from poop on the floor, blood stains on the walls, the ever-present urine smell and those un-identifiable stains...you know the deal. We always love it when something we never would have expected actually happens. Well, in this hotel, all of the above happened, and more. In our horribly grungy room, while we were laughing about how this hotel was one of the worst, we got a knock on the door. It was some sleazy drug girl, with a needle hanging out of her arm, looking for her boyfriend. We said he was not here, and then she proceeded to try and sell us some heroin. We said no. She then offered us her services so she could get money to buy some more. We said no. She then ran down the hall screaming, threatening us that Dwan was gonna find us and kill us. Well, Dwan never showed up. But we both agreed.... The Renoir definitely ranks as one our top 5 worst hotels in the world. This place is not for the meek. It is not a place for romance. It is for people in the fringes....those you see in the shadows. Good Luck!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c41279eada4ec8bc623152fa0d9356e3" url=""><![CDATA[Great Place To Stay in Boston Being a former Bostonian and having worked in some of the area hotels, I can surely tell you that Chandler Inn is one of the best values in town. Yes, it is not fancy, but it is spotless, nicely located, and within walking distance to almost every attraction in town. Not only that, but the subway and Amtrak stations are just footsteps away. Yes, there is no parking at the hotel, but only a block away is a huge public parking garage that is fairly inexpensive. There is a gay bar on the first floor and it is very friendly and all are welcome...almost like a gay version of Cheers. The area restaurants can't be beat....Chandler Inn is in one of the trendiest neighborhoods in town. Lots to choose from. So anyway, if you like high-priced chain hotels with all the amenities, this place is not for you. But if you like a nice, inexpensive hotel in a great area of the city, then don't hesitate to come here. This hotel is great for the sightseer and person on a budget. I always stay here every time I'm visiting Boston. I mean, I could stay at a fancy hotel, but why? I'd rather spend my money having fun in the city than sitting around in some overpriced, generic hotel room all day. Wouldn't you?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ce0f880e052e49f3656990b10bed403d" url=""><![CDATA[Good Budget Hotel Having stayed at alot of budget hotels, I can honestly tell you about the good, the bad, and the ugly. Adante Hotel definitely falls into the good catagory. Once again, this is a budget hotel.....so if you're looking for luxury, this is not for you. But if you're going to be out sightseeing all day (like me) and stop by the room every now and then, and want a good place to crash at nite, then this is the place for you. I was pleasantly surprised when I arrived at the hotel. Check-in was a breeze. The front desk clerk was friendly and very helpful. The room itself was spotless, although somewhat small....ok for 1 or 2 people, but that's it. I liked the funky paintjob. The bed was very comfortable and the bathroom was exceptionally clean...looked brand new. The room also included a large closet with ironing board and iron. Internet acess was provided as well as coffee pot with selection of coffee/teas. Bottled water was provided at extra charge and was clearly labled as such. Cable TV also provided. No AC, but there was a large ceiling fan that did the job. Continental breakfast was included from 7-9am at no extra charge. There is an elevator, but it is somewhat slow. My only complaints....bathroom towels were kinda cheap, maid service will knock on your door at 8am...loudly... if you don't hang the do not disturb sign on the door, and the view from my room was that of a brick wall. So except for these few minor things, I would definitely stay at the Adante again. A couple of extra notes....Adante Hotel is in the Union Square area, not on Union Square. In fact, it's quite a bit of an uphill walk from Union Square and the Bart/Muni public transport stations. This can be kinda annoying if you've been walking around the city all day. There is a bus stop right in front of the hotel, so you may want to take that instead of walking. The cool thing is that the Powell street cable car line is very close. And yes, the neighborhood has it's share of crack [--] and street people. But if you're used to large city life, you won't care. When I was there, these people mainly kept to themselves. I'ts not nearly as bad as you might think by reading some other people's reviews. So, all in all, Adante Hotel is a good place to stay for the budget sightseer or student traveller. I would go back again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="49160d3dcc9eba1e8cb7d8c242ccba0c" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Little Gem I stayed here a while ago and made some petty complaints about outside noise and such (street noise and there was construction going on...no fault of the hotel's). This was my first time in San Fran and have since stayed at other hotels in the city around the same price range. I have discovered that this hotel is the best for your buck. I't's clean, very cozy, centrally-located and cheap. Plus, the staff is very friendly. I have learned my lesson, Edwardian. I think I can deal with a little bit of street noise for the value. I would definitely like to come back.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>