<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="0dee4ac9b7ebf598d65af9c10338ac0d" url=""><![CDATA[Big and brash-but sometimes even beautiful The Americans really are masters of the large hotel universe. Not for nothing does Las Vegas have 7 of the10 largest hotels in the world-and the Hilton Hawaiian Village, with its over 3000 rooms , is by far the largest hotel in Waikiki.Three things are essential to running a really large hotel successfully. Superb efficiency and systems. We have stayed at this Hilton 4 times over the last two years .It really runs smoothly, whatever the weather and however many tourists throng the complex. Everything works and ,if you have reason to call down for anything, the staff normally come quickly. The check in lines move reasonably fast and the penguins in the fish ponds are happy to perform for the kids.Secondly a massive hotel like this has to appeal to all sorts of people. A small boutique hotel can be targeted exactly at a niche market of potential guests. A very large hotel has to appeal to everyone. So they will have a massive range of rooms. So in a hotel of this size and complexity it is useless to talk about room sizes or types There will just be too many.. All you can say is that even the worst and cheapest room will still be a Hilton double- and the best room will probably rival anything in Waikiki- and most rooms will be somewhere in between. And the hotel has to have a wide range of restaurants running from fast food type burgers at one extreme to Hilton style haute cuisine on the other .The Hilton has 18 food outlets including those in the main towers and the attached shopping arcade.Thirdly a very large hotel, if it is to make money, has to attract large organised groups, whether they are tour groups, conference attendees, or those just enjoying corporate junkets. This Hilton, whenever we have been there, has always had plenty of guests sporting various kinds of labels round their necks and / or pinned to their breasts clearly not shy to announce their identities to the world .The Hilton advertises itself as being on the beach. But if you are in the Tapa or Kalia towers then you would probably be physically closer to the beach if you were staying in hotels not actually beach side like the Embassy Suites or the Waikiki Parc. Location wise then it may indeed be on the seas shore but it is not that close to the centre. It is really a bit out of the way , right at the end of Waikiki beach next to the Alii Wai yacht harbour. Not nearly so handy for downtown as its competitors the Sheratons and the Hyatt. But Waikiki is so compact, everything is still within walking distance.Land is of course highly expensive in Waikiki . So all the hotels are high rise and most of the Hilton Towers are over 30 floors. Few of the hotels will have any kind of garden-but the Hilton does its best with cleverly planted trees and shrubs. And none of the hotels can afford to have a massive swimming pool .But the Hilton , as befits its status as the largest hotel, also boasts the largest pool .This is still on the small side if the hotel is full. But who wants a pool anyway if the beautiful Pacific is just a few steps away? And anyway, if you mind swimming in the shade, there is another smaller pool by the Tapas towers.The five major Towers do differ somewhat. The Alii tower,( which we have yet to be invited to grace with our presence) has its own swimming pool and private entrance complete with frock coated porter at the door to keep the ordinary public out,.. The Rainbow tower has great views but is showing its age a bit. In the Tapa tower the higher floor rooms also have good views, and the Kailua tower , the furthest from the beach and , I hesitate to say, shared with time sharing condos, is probably the cheapest. Most of the time sharers however are concentrated in the fifth building the Lagoon tower with their own pool etc .But it is of course open for them to partake also in any of the main hotels amenities .And as always in Waikiki, although it may not be yet quite as bad as Vegas , there is building going on everywhere. So, be warned, by the time you read this review, it may be out of date.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="325e98622330a10444261f07169094be" url=""><![CDATA[Downtown Designer luxury Knowing we were using Hilton honors points for a free stay we were expecting the smallest room looking over the dustbins at the back.. What we actually were given was a superb suite on the 31st floor.Large bedroom with a super comfortable super king size bed. Hi tech hi spec bathroom, all glass, mirrors and marble. Two person Jacuzzi bath right under a picture window. Great view of the Sydney skyline as you sip your evening champagne and watch the flat screen TV in the bathroom wall. Walk in shower with 5 separate heads. Two hand basins and separate toilet.Next to the bedroom, an equally large and equally impressive lounge and hall area with another toilet and in all 3 flat screen TVs scattered around the suite. A telephone and communications system that you probably need a pilots licence to operate.And all this done in exquisite simple modern taste.The Hilton is downtown whilst most of their competitors cluster around the harbour. But downtown is great for shopping and restaurants and it is only a 10 minute walk from the ferries.Undoubtedly the Hilton Sydney is, for me, the queen of the Hilton group in Australasia.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f31a7ec5fe4bd2eba9f23982fb58587d" url=""><![CDATA[Good but not great The Conrad is good. It gives you a large room, for Singapore luxury hotel standards. And the room has everything it should have including a flat screen TV and a good sized bathroom with loads of luxury goodies. It does everything it should do efficiently.But to be great a hotel either has to have a superb unique location, or exceptional facilities or food, or exceptional people.The Conrads location is fine in the CBD. But then so are most other luxury hotels. The facilities are perfectly adequate. A smallish infinity pool, and a spa health club as good as any other. The Conrad food we tried is standard rather than sublime. So to be great the staff would have to be exceptional. They are helpful and efficient. But they are more formal than friendly. They seem to have a job rather than a vacation. And next week they might be working at get me wrong. The Conrad is a very good hotel. But not quite a great one.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>