<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="92f65fff00078ba2a251d1fce47c6c05" url=""><![CDATA[I just don't get this hotel - So terrible I just got back from this hotel today Feb 1st 2005 after staying there for 6 nights. I try to be as objective as possible so that you guys will find the facts not my opinion.I have stayed in Amerisuites, Comfort Inns, all the way to Ritz Carlton or other high-end hotel chain. Although I have never stayed in a european based hotel, so there is the flaw in my comparison.Here are the facts that I find this hotel is lacking:1. No refrigerator, microwaves, or even coffee maker. If you need coffee in the morning, the hotel restaurant downstair will conveniently pour it for you for a small fee of $2.16 a cup (no refill, nice try). This might be OK for some travelers. But when you have small children this can be a quite inconvenience. Forget warm milk....2. Their welcome booklet says: Tap Water is not drinkable. They do provide a minibar with a bottle water that cost about $3.00 (small one).3. No iron - but they do have a dry cleaning service sheet that I won't even dare to see how much it would cost.4. If you are lucky to stay on 5,7,9th floor you can get to the ice machine on the same floor. Otherwise, you need to wait about 2-3 minutes on the elevator just to get the ice.5. Yes sometimes the elevator does take 3-4 minutes to arrive at certain times of the days (check out times, breakfast, and dinner time). Even the cleaning lady wants to get a piece of the action by crowding the guest elevator too.6. No lotion in the bathroom. Yes, I realize a lot of hotel chains do not give out lotions, but if they call themselves resort - I expect a small bottle of lotion can come in handy especially after a day under the sun.7. The room looks old. This might be subjective, but it does look worn out to me. 8. Oh, if you pay more they do give you a nicer room with balcony (I had that). Here is the lacking part: your neighbor can jump out easily from his balcony to your balcony. There is a dividing wall about waist high. Just enough to hide your head if you sit down - no privacy at all. 9. Related to #8 - the balcony door from the room sticks and DO NOT lock. Now, what's stopping a criminal from the other room to enter your room? Perhaps not much. Oh, but the sunrise, sunset, and the full moon is beautiful from the balcony.10. Pool towel - Make sure you ask for 4 towel cards if you are going to need 4 towels at the pool. Otherwise, the pool tower 'personnel' will give you a hard time for asking more towels than your towel card, as if you are going to steal their prized towel.11. Speaking of towels - so many clean towels that I had got stains on it. I did not even want to think what the stain was from. Just closed my eyes and used them.12. To be fair, some employees are nice, some needs a lesson in cutomer relation (pool towel personnel included). The receptionist with red glasses is nice, the other older one - got a major PMS.13. You cannot check out before your room is completely empty. I just never had that experience. I always check out a bit earlier while my wife is finishing up with the kids. I was confused....Those are facts. I cannot prevent myself from being sarcastic a bit after how they treated us. I just don't get their philosophy. They call themselves a resort, but they are operating a cheap level that I have never seen before even compared to a budget motel. At the same time they pride themselves with their excellent restaurant service (with overpriced everything). I tried their food - mediocre. Not worth spending $25/person.Here is the greatest thing we found about 2 blocks south of the hotel:Cafe Migas. Highly highly recommended. Very modest cafe with excellent cuban coffee and espresso, real orange juice, heavenly ham-and-cheese croissant, full hot breakfast all for under $9. Do yourself a favor don't fall into the hotel's hyped buffet. I read the good and bad reviews about this hotel, and now I believe the bad one. I did not expect a 4 or 5 stars when I got in, but this hotel is lower than 2 star in my humble opinion. Sorry, I have to give my opinion at the end...
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>