<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="4f3d5a63166b6b7e498a6874e9678895" url=""><![CDATA[Customer Service was Amazing!!! Aloha All, I had the distinct pleasure of going to this property on my honeymoon and was absolutely derailed by the customer service i received, immediately at check in i was greeted by a Lemon scented moist towel and a glass of lemonade. The Bellman escorted us to our room and gave us a first class tour of the room and showed us how to work everything. We had breakfast at The ShoreBird Restaurant and it was absolutely subherb, any kind of hot breakfast food imaginable was at our delite. They had a great activities desk to help us plan out all of our activities for the week. Finally a vacation that i didn't need a vacation from!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="677623200b84cf6b7ad5e45fcf06395a" url=""><![CDATA[Great Service I have been to Waikiki a couple of times and this is by far the nicest place i have stayed at, not just because of the property itself but also becuase of its service, amenities, and its LOCATION!!! It is on the right hand side of waikiki with majestic views of diamondhead crater, only about a 3-5 minute walk to The Honolulu Zoo, and The Waikiki Aquarium. Kapiolani Park is also right next door. And oppisite the direstion of park is The International Marketplace also in just about a 5 minute walk. If you come here you definately do not need a car. Because you won't use it, almost all of the local activities provide shuttle service and they pick you up right in front of the hotel. The property has 4 restaurants located right on site, a beautiful pool area in the shade of the Tiki Bar Grill. The property also offers a 2 for 1 luau in their coupon book at check in, we had a chance to go to this luau and it was well worth it... me and my wife got in for like 70 bucks and it included a buffet dinner a show, and a fire knife dance which was just out of this world. This was our honeymoon and if you call the hotel before hand they will usually do something for you....For us we got champagne. And don't miss their FREE breakfast on the beach every morning.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>