<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="4f4dcb54bc1c16e918ee44f8646ff842" url=""><![CDATA[2nd Trip to Excellence and not the last! Service was beyond our expectations! Let me start by covering the basics briefly. The grounds are immaculate and gorgeous, the beach is breathtaking, the pools are awesome, the rooms are perfect, the food delicious, the service everywhere, excellent. Everything was as perfect as it was last year when it comes to the basics. We are getting married at Excellence next July and we knew this was our wedding location before we even got engaged! And when we did get engaged, we didn't have to compare resorts or feel like we were stuck between two places. This place is it! Easy decision.However, I recently found out I have a serious food allergy and I was very nervous about eating anywhere, let alone outside of the country. I was very nervous that a resort would not be able to accomodate my food allergy. I did figure because of the excellent service last year, that they would be the most likely to come through for me so that eased my mind. So I brought special sauces to cook my food in, special food and snacks and guess what? We barely used any of it! It was not necessary. The staff at Excellence went above and beyond to ensure my health safety and enjoyment of my trip. There are some people I must give a compliment to for their outstanding service:Chef Berthold ~Chief Executive Chef ~ I can not thank him enough for everything he did for me during my stay. He went above and beyond my expectations regarding my food allergy. He came to our lunch and dinner everyday before and after our meals to make sure the food was safe for me. On top of that, for the weekly beach party and pool soiree, he would walk me through every buffet station to go over what was in each dish. I ate like a queen. He even had a cook cut up a lime for me to put on my bug bites at the beach party! They also bought a special pan to cook my lunches and dinners in so I would not get sick!!! Talk about 5 star service! I never even felt restricted with the exception of dessert but we were too full every time to even contemplate that! I never imagined I would have such personalized and friendly service and I doubt I would receive that kind of service at any other resort. He is a kind and an amazing man! I know he truly enjoys his job. Excellence is sure lucky to have him!Elvira ~Head Concierge~ She was so accomodating even before I arrived. We spoke so many times over the internet and she answered all my questions. Everyday I would let her or one of the other concierges (thanks Carolina and Fior!) know where I would be eating that afternoon and evening and they would have someone bring my pan and sauces (the ones we never even had to use) to the restaurant. She is very sweet and always wanted to know if everything was going okay.Roberto~Club Manager~I never actually got to meet him because we did not stay in the club, but he was also extremely helpful prior to my arrival to make sure everything with my food allergy was being taken care of. Thanks!Rosaura~Hostess~She was so sweet and really understood my need for special attention and always got Chef Berthold right away for me. She even gave me a special gift for us to remember her by. Thank you!Now, as for our wedding, Ana the wedding planner is awesome! She took the time to show us pictures while we were there and help make some decisions and arrangements with us. She was very concerned about my allergy as well, and was very happy that everything worked out so amazingly. She is definitely a sweetheart because she put up with me emailing her everyday with questions about the wedding prior to our trip and even still! Thank you so much Ana! She sets up amazing weddings and makes them really special. I can't wait for our wedding day! The beach party they have every Tuesday is exactly how I picture the wedding reception. They really know how to set up a beautiful party!Also, Domingo the saxophonist is out of this world. We are definitely hiring him for our wedding and we even bought two of his cds. Soon he'll be famous in the United States and Europe. He is really the best saxophonist I've ever heard. Make sure you take the time to enjoy his beautiful music after the nightly shows.Luciano, the entertainment manager is so nice. I loved the circus music and asked what it was, and he made a copy of the cd for me!!The one and only thing I would complain about and I hope the resort hears this is how they shut off the lights in some walkways way too early and its so pitch black out there you dont know where you are walking or who is around you. It's one thing tto do it after everything has been closed for a while,but several times, we were either at the Cafe Bar or at the Sports bar and closed the place and as soon as the bar shuts the lights down, all the lights surrounding the area and beyond shut off too. They should considering leaving the lights on for at least 15 minutes so people can get back to their rooms safely. Otherwise, someone could get hurt. I think they want people to use the lobby area for walking at night for safetyreasons, but sometimes it just doesnt work that way depending on where you are at the time, and it ends up defeating the purposed about trying to keep the guests safe! Hope you hear me, Excellence!!!I can still not get over the outstanding, specialized service we received our entire stay. I've been raving about since we got home. This is what makes Excellence stand out above the rest. (can't forget the breathtaking beach too!)We can't wait to return next year for our beautful wedding and fantastic honeymoon! Yay!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>