<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="d721efb09e6f44253c44708f90973b08" url=""><![CDATA[Best Hotel Value In Hawaii Although this hotel hardly needs another 5 star rating, it was such a surprise and great experience I will try to give a different perspective.I was a Vice President for one the largest hotel chains in the world and have stayed in many hotels throughout the world over 30 years. I also have a second home in Hawaii and have been going to Hawaii since 1968. The first comment that comes to mind is that Aqua Resorts have really got their act together. I have not seen a such a combination of value, decor, friendliness, amenities and service.This hotel use dynamic sales, much like airlines, so your rate will vary depending on demand but it will remain the best value in Waikiki since demand is essentially seasonal and will affect other hotels as well.My first impression was the striking decor of the lobby and four employees at the front desk in about a 150 room hotel--you would be lucky to have that many in a 1000+ room hotel.Then to my room which was tastefully decorated as I've seen in a long time. Many of the few negative reviews complain of small rooms. I found the size well designed and more than adequate. The amenities were first class and the refrigerator, microwave and coffee are rare to find in hotels costing three times the price. The bathrobes were unique and the most luxurious I've seen anywhere--not the usual terry short white robe if they are provided at all. Also unique was having live anthuriums. The lanai was large and a view of the Ali Wai canal and the green mountains of the Monoa valley. . The beach is only a few blocks away and it is a bit quieter at this hotel location and has the only super market in Waikiki next door. The only thing I would add to the room would be a night light and small reading chair--but you can use the lanai chairs.The desk staff was always extremely friendly and the engineers , Craig and Mark, were very helpful in setting up my own dvd player and replacing a defective phone. Again for the few negative reviewers it's to be expected that sometimes things go wrong but what is important is that it is corrected. Try to get this kind of service in 2000 room hotel! It' s obvious that the employees enjoy their jobs are truly examples of the Aloha Spirit.Two other extras are the free broadband connection(hotels on the beach charge up to $20/day) and the free continental breakfast.The bottom line is that you will not find a better value in Waikiki, maybe not anywhere. Of course, if you must be on the beach prepare to pay 3-4 times the price with 1/2 the experience. I am telling all my friends and neighbors in Hawaii about this hotel and since it is relatively new, most do not know about it. My friends and I rarely go to Waikiki but it is much improved over 10 years ago and I would definitely pick this hotel again.David C. Johnson
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>