<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="885424021e17aa9713f596b8dfbb7365" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent experience We have stayed at several 2-3 star places on the Upper West Side and would definitely stay here again. Great location with clean, comfortable rooms. Europeans who are used to smaller rooms will be pleasantly surprised.We chose a suite just because we like the extra living space (3 adults in 2 doubles). Never opened the sofa bed so can't comment on that. Furniture in living room a bit worn, sort of like your grandmothers apartment. Great location as others have mentioned with lots of affordable very good restaurants nearby including the adjacent Viand. Staff was very pleasant and responsive to all requests. Plenty of closet space, bathroom clean but small. Full kitchen was nice especially the toaster for all the bagel places nearby Add this place to your list whenever you need a reliable hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb267be9e0e43d3e2318b4888187ada5" url=""><![CDATA[Surprise and delighted For less than $200 a night incl all taxes and fees, this place was a steal. Very large rooms with full kitchens and lots of closets. We had a queen bed and a sofa bed opposite it. With the sofa open, we still had room for a dance floor in between. Bathroom was ok and clean, as was everything else. Not a suite in the separate bedroom and living room sense, but just a very large room with a full kitchen and dining areaYou don't have the restaurants nearby like the Upper West Side places but who cares since this place was a good $100 less than those places for similar furnishings. A good and safe area with decent options on 3rd and 2nd. Also a great jumping off place to Long Island since the Midtown tunnel and Long Island Expressway (I-495) is a block away. Staff was professional and friendly, plus the adjacent public garage takes the car from you right at the hotel entrance so no hassles dropping the luggage and finding a place to park for the nights
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>