<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f56453df2a53f95720deeacb6084c6e0" url=""><![CDATA[didn't want to leave... My best friend and I were slated to stay at the new Majestic Elegance from November 8th to the 15th, but due to opening delays resided instead at the Majestic Colonial. I myself had never been to the Dominican Republic, where she had been numerous occasions to the different tourist areas throughout the country. I think we were both equally impressed with the resort and area alike. To me there could have been no better ambassador to the Dominican than the Majestic Colonial; every member of staff I met was extremely and genuinely friendly (not to mention incredibly hard working). I found this to be true elsewhere in the area as well (just in case you are thinking of excursions). Amazingly enough the great attitudes of the people working at the Majestic rubbed off on our fellows tourists; we made many new friends Dominican and American. The hotel itself is beautiful, perfectly echoing its natural surroundings. The grounds are impeccably landscaped and facilities are well-maintained. Rooms are spacious and very clean (love the big shower and Jacuzzi tub). Each room also has a balcony or sitting area which is nice for relaxing in the evening. The pool, though second to the beach in my opinion, is one of the hotels greatest assets. It is refreshing and large, spanning just about the entire length of the hotel. There is always a place to rest in the sun or under the palapas. Drinks are never far away whether walking to the bar or swimming. We tried all of the restaurants including the two a la carte, and always found something we like. Desserts were always fabulous; the local fruits were especially delicious (as is anything covered in chocolate!). The best place by far is the beach. I highly recommend snorkeling. There is a vast array of beautiful fish swimming around the coral reefs that dot the shoreline of the property. *While you are on the beach, say hello to the wonderful beach concierge Denny. He is very sweet, attentive, and will make you feel right at home. I miss him already!!!Do not hesitate to stay at this property. If you are easy going like myself, you will find nothing wrong. I think even the more discerning clientele would have to agree, the tiniest of problems are greatly overshadowed by the gracious people who are there to welcome you and assist you in your stay.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>