<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="124691b7caccf949a05bc62dfc31d1f7" url=""><![CDATA[A Great Stay Myself, partner and 2 friends booked 2 rooms in the Langlois directed through their website after reading reviews on TripAdvisor. We paid about 100euro for each room which was excellent value. The rooms were spotless and perfectly sized (our friend's bathroom was huge!).Trinite metro was a mere 1 min walk away which was convenient for getting around. A taxi was less than 10 euro to the Lourve. We walked to the Moulin Rouge which was no more than 10mins away, with Montmarte a mere 20 min walk.We would all definitely stay there again as it was a terrific Parisian hotel and great value for money.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1d7d7f7056a95623337115a5dc697ce5" url=""><![CDATA[Mercure Sydney a Great Surprise Bed
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7182b44ef0cf3c78e975a1c54599d370" url=""><![CDATA[Superior Swissotel Bathroom
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0bec8927a219d0972691be42cbe7f68f" url=""><![CDATA[Centre of Barcelona! We stayed here last weekend for 4 nights and had a very good stay. We booked directly on the H10 website after reading the reviews on TripAdvisor. We requested a large room and got a decent size room at the back of the hotel wich was very quiet. Whilst the room was not as big as we had hoped, it was a little bigger than some that we happened to see (but not as big as others).The hotel is very trendy, modern and friendly. The bathroom is huge and probably takes up a third of the room. The location is fantastic being a 1 minute walk from the Plaza de Catalunya and La Rambla!We had the breakfast which we were very happy with. There were lots of hot and cold options which were all very tasty! Also available were some English language newspapers and free internet at the 2 terminals in the lobby. All in all we had a great stay right in the centre of Barcelona.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d9f72d308778dcfd6ef04fe54ea40b69" url=""><![CDATA[As good as everyone says This hotel is definately as good as everyone says. We were not disappointed at all. The location is absolutely fantastic being right on Union Square with all the shopping you could possibly want and a cable car stop right out the front (which takes you down to Fisherman's Wharf). Chinatown is a short 5-10 minute walk away with Japantown being a bit further away and easy to get to on the bus (great for Japanese food!)The rooms are very nice. They might not be huge by American standards, but by European standards they are a good size. Everything was spotless and very nicely furnished. We asked for a high floor room and got the 11th floor which looked down towards Union Square. It was very quiet, even with the window open.We booked a package deal which came with parking which was located around the corner (a minutes walk away), as well as a voucher for food/drinks. This paid for our breakfast which was delivered to our room and was massive! A great way to start the day! The price was fantastic at about $150 per night for the parking and $25 voucher.The staff were very friendly at all times and very helpful. I would definately stay here again next time in SF.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>