<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="fa2b881f8edd10fbabaefa79e468bd2f" url=""><![CDATA[A Well Run Hotel in a Great Location By New York City standards the Hampton Inn is reasonably priced, and for what the hotel gives you, almost a bargain [again, by NYC standards].LOCATION: Located on 8th Avenue between 51st and 52nd Street, the hotel is close to theaters, subways, delis, TKTS, and the bustle of Times Square. If you like to travel via taxi, if not one waiting at the door, there will be plenty driving by on 8th Avenue. Eighth Avenue is bustling and at no time does one feel unsafe.THE ROOM: The room with one king bed is a comfortable size. My wife and I have to coordinate our movements to avoid bumping in to each other. In addition to an iron/ironing board and hair dryer the room had my three necessities: a safe, a clock, and a coffee maker. Drawers and closet space are adequate. There was a full length mirror. USA Today is included in your room price. If you bring your computer, high speed internet access is available in the room and is included in the room price. The TV was a flat screen. We watch TV so I comment on picture quality or station selection. The shower spray is adjustable and the water temperature remains constant; the water pressure, however, is unsteady. The shower is a shower/bath combination. The bathroom has a nightlight. Housekeeping was dependable, friendly, and performed their duties well. The beds were comfortable. We were on the 11th floor overlooking 8th Avenue; my wife, who is a light sleeper, never commented on any street noise.ELEVATORS: Very efficient -- never an unreasonable waitSTAFF: Pleasant, helpful, and accommodating INTERNET ACCESS: If you have your computer with you, the hotel provides two computers with printers off the lobby. The cost is included in the price of the room. There is a 10-minute time limit before you are logged out -- a good policy that prevents discourteous guests from treating them like their personal machines.SECURITY: I noticed no security cameras in the hallways and elevators. A security guard checks room keys after 9 PM, but no one was checking on Friday/Saturday nights when we went to our room. In any event, the checking of room keys is not very effective. Instead of turning in the plastic key card when one checks out, an ill-intentioned person can retain it and use it to show the key checker when he wishes to access the room areas at night.FOOD: Like all Hampton Inns at which stayed, the guests have access to a buffet breakfast which is built into the price of the room. Cereal, sausage, eggs/French toast/waffles, yogurt, breads, bagels, pastries, fruit, milk, juice, coffee, hot chocolate, and tea are standard. The breakfast crew does an excellent job restocking. In addition, apples, coffee, hot chocolate, and tea are available at any time in the lobby [as are cookies if you time it right]. When looking at the price of the room, be sure to consider how much money these food features will save you.All-in-all, a well run hotel in a great location which offers you value for your money.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>