<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="23f0a6a19aebfcf332ca30b504c6d538" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic place to stay! After reading a couple of very recent reviews from visitors I was concerned that my vist to the Argent would not be a good one - there were a number of complaints regarding the upgrading to a the Westin chain and the impact it was having. I have to totally disagree. The staff were fantastic, my hotel room was stunning, clean, well appointed and obviously a completed part of the upgrade to the Westin. I was visiting San Francisco on my own and the hotel was the perfect setting for shopping and sight seeing with an excellent location and felt very secure. My only criticism would be the automated mini bar system which made it impossible to keep soft drinks I had purchased myself cool due to the sensors designed to generate charges for mini bar purchases. A minor irritation though in the grand scheme of things. Would definitely recommend this hotel to anyone.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="944565c10b4e00b121f034ae0e4623c0" url=""><![CDATA[Let down by housekeeping Lovely hotel badly let down by the housekeeping service. When I arrived, the first room I was shown to, on the ground floor, had a broken blind leaving the room open to the boardwalk and people strolling back and forth right outside. The staff very kindly swiftly moved us to another room on the 3rd floor which was spacious with high ceilings and overlooked Walsh Bay. The staff we encountered (room service, front desk, bar staff) were exceptional. The slightly odd and noisy plumbing was slightly irritating but certainly not enough to put us off the hotel. Unfortunately the whole experience was marred by the terrible housekeeping service. Day one (we stayed for 4 nights), the room was cleaned adequately but not to a standard you would expect from a hotel of this level. Day two, I requested a change of sheets (request required in keeping with hotel's green policy) as there was a hole in one of the sheets. When we returned in the evening the bed was made to look like there were clean sheets but discovered the exact same hole in the sheet when I went to bed. Nothing else was cleaned in the room, bin were not emptied, drawers left open, toiletries/glasses/washcloths not refreshed and the towels left on the floor for replacement were still there. Day three the room was not touched at all - unfortunately we returned too late in the evening from our day out to raise it with the front desk. While 1-2 day sheets and towels can't be considered a hardship, it is certainly not what you expect from a 4-5 star hotel. While the hotel itself really was lovely and was nice to stay out of the CBD but still in easy reach of the city, the housekeeping experience has put me off returning to this hotel or any other in the Sebel/Mirvac chain.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>