<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="04df0bd05b4ddfa198d0f31f729c1d8a" url=""><![CDATA[Astonishing Architecture and Ambience This is a most unusual hotel and experience. The rooms are the slickest contemporary rooms I have experienced full of textures and with fine view over the harbour. The hotel is situation inside a VAST structure that is more than cathedral like. The consequence is that the communal inner space has a marvelous industrial feel but is so vast it is mostly unusable. There is a bar and cafe - breakfast in the cafe was a poor affair characterised by poor service and mediocre food - once experienced not to be repeated. There is a swimming pool\ but few people manage to find it in the building and there is no guidance in the rooms (perhaps due to the new ownership?). Overall the experience is positive. The location is convenient being right next to the Botanical Gardens and there are a variety of local eating places either on the dockside within the building or vicinity. The hotel seemed out of style for a Taj Hotel and one wonders if such an unusual space can be made to work effectively as a business. But try it and enjoy..its certainly a wow.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="526dc941502b04ba2f45f9b7a49b9555" url=""><![CDATA[Not up to scratch Having booked two rooms for two nights we were pleased with the efficient and personalised pre-arrival emails but on the ground there were several poor features of this stay. First the reception clerk was very cold, unwelcoming, slow and seemed more concerned at trying to sell me up to the next class of room (Club Level). Secondly, the rooms were ok but showing signs of wear (desks, room items such as trays, wardrobes) and incompletely kitted out with amenities. Thirdly the pool area was slightly scruffy and it was hard to find a pool towel that was not torn.I was most surprised. Finally, being off-season there was no pool bar but a telephone service..the problem was the phone worked once then went dead. So the negatives out of the way, the location is good and main lounge area has a sense of gravitas. The breakfasts were fine.I will not be going back. Verdict: Must do better!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c0cafb19dd0f854771c5b1956be51eca" url=""><![CDATA[As good as ever..the best! Interconnecting Garden Wing rooms were ideal for the family. As ever, we were looked after famously and everyone enjoyed eating out at The LIne. This remains the best Singapore city hotel in my view, since it has the most attentive staff and best quality food around. Another strong recommendation!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b7d3d8d9dfaca78e1d13f74d1439a0bc" url=""><![CDATA[Outstanding... as usual Bathroom trinkets
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>