<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="37c611100a97e0d6b1394f66c66dad88" url=""><![CDATA[Tips fom a 3rd-time Visitor Background: I'm 28yrs old, I have been to San Juan 3 times in the past 2 years - twice at the El San Juan when I was single (next door) and once at the Intercontinental with my girlfriend (this visit).The Hotel: My first impression was that the hotel was very nice. It is centrally located in relation to popular tourist attractions (Old San Juan and El Yunque Rainforest). It is right on a beatiful beach. The lobby is quite small and not much going on. If you are looking for action the El San Juan is right next door. Overall, the pool and the lobby is much nicer at the El San Juan but for a family, couples, a relaxing vacation or elderly people, the Intercontinental is a better choice as it is much quieter and well lit. The El San Juan is very trendy, dark and loud (think night club) - but if you are single and younger (under 35) the El San Juan is a better choice.The Room: I originally upgraded to a room with an ocean view but when I got to my room on the 7th floor I noticed that most of the view was obstructed by trees. I immediately called the front desk and they gladly changed rooms to the 14th floor...that view was SPECTACULAR!!! Moral of the story - make sure you call for a higher floor because ocean view is pretty much anything on the side of the hotel that faces the ocean...it doesn't necessarily mean that you can see the ocean LOL! My only complaint was that the walls were paper-thin and you can easily hear people in the next room and it can be hard to sleep at night if you have loud neighbors. I had to call security all 3 nights I was there - it's not the hotel's fault that these people were really loud but just keep in mind that the walls are thin.The Hotel Staff: The staff is extremely courteous (much more than at the El San Juan). There was always someone to open the doors to the hotel for you no matter what time you entered or exited the hotel (and they never asked or expected a tip). The concierge was very nice and helpful as well. My only complaint was that the service at the front desk was a bit slow. House keeping was very quiet when cleaning other rooms- they were like ninjas - you dind't even know they were there. I left my room for breakfast, put the sign on my door to get my room cleaned...came back 45min later and my entire room was clean.Rental Car / PARKING!!!! : This was the best part for me...right accross the street is a self-parking area...it costs $16 per day and you can go in and out AS MUCH AS YOU PLEASE! This is such an advantage if you are doing any sightseeing. DO NOT waste money on organized tours...all the signs in San Juan are in English and easy to follow. Rent a car and you will save yourself a TON on money (including a $15 cab trip each way to and from the airport). I reserved a car from the airport on priceline.com for $15/day tax inc.!!!! That's $93 for a 4-day, 3-night weekend for parking and the car - You can't beat that! Old San Juan and the Bacardi factory are 15min by car and the rainforest is 45min away. If you take an organized tour this will cost you at least a couple of hundred dollars per person...for something that can easily be done on your own! However, make sure you bring a GPS - it will really come in handy - if you don't have one, most rental car companies can offer you one at a marginal rate. RENT A CAR, RENT A CAR, RENT A CAR!!!!Where to eat: Right across from the hotel there are tons of restaurants (Burger King, Pizza Hut, Wendy's, Subway, KFC...). My suggestion would be Mi Casita it is fairly authentic and relatively inexpensive and the food is good...BUT BEWARE the service can be long. I have eaten at this restaurant 5 times, dinner usually takes at least 45min for you to get your food and breakfast is around 25-30min. However, the last day we were there, dinner came out in 15min and breakfast came out in 10min...so I would say it's hit or miss but prepare for the worst. Don't go when you are extremely hungry because chances are you will wait a while. Try their Signature Mofongo dishes (mashed plantain topped with a tomato based sauce and your choice of chicken/beef/shrimp.) Overall, the wait is worth it - both for the quality of the food and especially the price. If you eat at any of the hotels, don't expect to get out of there for under $100 for 2 people (wine not included). Another option, is there is a grocery store within 5min walking distance from the hotel - you can't see it, so ask the concierge how to get to the Pueblo grocery store. There you can buy water, drinks, and even prepared food for dirt cheap prices. Also, there is a Walgreens 5min walking distance as well. Beach: The beach is very nice but can be crowded in peak seasons. It is a long beach - I'd say at least 5 miles. The sand is groomed every morning. The water can get rough if there is bad weather but generally, it is really good. The good thing about this hotel is that the beach chairs are free. Some other hotels charge $4/day for beach chairs!Things to do: If you like booze, the Bacardi Factory is nearby, you can go on a tour once you get there with your rental car =) Old San Juan is beautiful - make sure to bring a camera. There are a few old forts that can be visted that will give you a great view of the ocean and the city as well as a history of the island. Also, there is a path that you can walk on right by the ocean that takes you all along Old San Juan.El Yunque rainforest: This is a must! Take your rental car and drive to the rainforest; there are many well marked trails that are paved. You do not need a guide or to go on a tour. If you go by yourself - it's FREE!!!! All you have to do is print out a trail map from the internet first. On my first trip in 2005, I went on a tour that cost me $60...we walked for an hour and we were done. This time I did some research and did the La Mina trail and the Big Tree trail and that was amazing - nothing like what the tours take you on...breath-taking scenery and a gorgeous waterfall at the bottom. The rainforest opens at 7:30am; if you start hiking before 8:30am you will be fine otherwise expect crowds, especially at La Mina Falls. Both trails I took were about 40min of hiking...the La Mina trail is MUCH nicer than the Big Tree trail but it is also a bit harder to do. If you are in any decent shape, I suggest the La Mina trail down to the falls and the Big Tree trail back up. I hope this helps you out, I really love Puerto Rico and it is clear why it is called La Isla Del Encanto. I am set to go back in May and visit Culebra, home to Flamenco Beach - rated by Discovery Channel as one of the nicest beaches in the world. If you have a week in PR be sure to check this out - I am sure that you won't be sorry =)Wes
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>