<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="059b6e17ebe7356d3c68a722d734731e" url=""><![CDATA[an enjoyable holiday We have returned from the Occidential Grand Flamenco, Punta Cana 2nd August we stayed there for 2 weeks. It has beautiful well maintained gardens and pool areas, a fantastic beach the sea is lovely and warm. I have seen complaints about the food, these people must be very fussy eaters. The food was good during our stay, there is a wide choice, the only problem we found about the food is was not always piping hot. We ate what we fancied and none of us got any up-set stomachs during our stay. Sometime it was busy in the main buffet at certain times, which did mean you might not get a drink straight away, but chill its a holiday no need to rush. There were some nationalities thet don't know the meaning of 'wait your turn' and would push in front of you whilst waiting for you omlette to be cooked they would especially push in front of our children (HOW RUDE!!! that is all i will say on that matter)The room's are of a large size and the decor is a little dated however, they are kept very clean.We always had hot water and the A/C was a little noisy but it work very well. We had a junior suite which is fantastic for a family, which we are. We left between 2- 5 $ per day and I took gifts for the staff e.g tooth brushes, make-up, false nails, toiletries, pencils and crayons etc which i gave out don't and forget the gardeners, they work very long hours to keep the garden looking fantastic. In return we were left spirts, wine, beer and lovely flower towel decorations. All the staff were friendly, apart from the staff on reception, we found them to be rude and they did not speak very good English (or they made out they didn't). Don't go there if you do have a problem, go to the guest services near the amusement area in the lobby. We tried all the different restraunts we like the orential the best (no children allowed under 18 yrs though) Luckly our children are old enough to be left alone for a hour or so. They went to the pizza place and the waiter was aware we we were in the orential and he said he would serve them and watch them, which he did. Even though they are old enough and sensible it was nice of him to offer.Go and visit William the bar man in the beach bar hut, he his a GREAT man. You can see he enjoys his job, which is great for a man who is away from his family for long periods of time. If you treat them how you want to be treated they have a great deal of respect for you. I have read on other trip advisors reviews that they had things stollen, I was worried about this, but we had nothing taken and we heard of no others having any problems, during our stay. The evening entertainment was poor and mainly in Spanish, we were expecting professional shows, it was the day enterainment staff that also did the evening shows, they worked hard and well to their ability. It is the hotels fault they need to bring in professional acts of an evening. Luckly we met some great people therfore, we spent most evenings chatting and made are own entertainment. We all enjoyed our time in the Dominican and i would go back to this hotel, happy holidays
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>