<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="9f5176c3a746120adb7c108ceded5a4c" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel for the Price We are bay area locals staying in the city for one night, and wanted a decent hotel for a good price (which is hard to come by in SF, especially this time of year!)...I did a lot of research, and decided that based on the reviews here on Trip Advisor, that the Hotel Carlton would be worth a try...I was right...from the moment we walked in the door, we were greeted by extremely friendly front desk and bell staff... who made us feel at home right away. Valet parking was a little steep- $30...but worth it for the in out privileges... We stayed on the Everest floor, in a deluxe room, which I think is just a tad bigger than the regular floors- and it also had a flat screen TV, which was nice. The room was clean, and well appointed... the bathroom was small, but very clean...The only thing I would say that is partially negative about this hotel is that the walls are indeed VERY thin...so if you are a light sleeper, it may not be the best choice for you...All in all- a great stay!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b07acd8d3641832fd9e0e4203b5cee05" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Pacific Heights Gem We stayed at the Hotel Drisco (sadly, only for one night)... for our friends' wedding.. We easily found a parking spot outside when we arrived (before check-in time)... which is so rare in San Francisco... were greeted with hot towels, and quickly shown to our room. The room was beautiful, with a small separate sitting area. Light filled the space and bounced off the crisp white linens as we entered the bedroom . We only had a few minutes to spend in the room before heading off to the wedding, but when we returned, the bed had been turned down, and light jazz was playing softly from the bedside alarm clock radio. There were also a couple of cookies and a little card on the tv table, indicating the weather for the next day so that we could be prepared (it was unseasonably warm, but beautiful)... which I thought was a nice touch. The bathroom was small, but efficient, and the rug was super plush. There was also a bathroom amenity basket filled with many thoughtful items for sale, which can be a life saver for some guests, I'm sure! The actual bathroom amenities were wonderful, as well- it's nice to get something other than Gilchrist Soames for a change! The only ding I have to give this property is one that many people already know and accept about staying in older, boutique hotels- you can hear EVERYTHING that's going on in your neighbors room- above and to the side-... In the evening luckily, we were so tired, we only noticed it right before nodding off to sleep, but in the morning, were awakened in the morning by a previously set alarm clock (5:45am) , and the guests next door to us using a hair dryer. We did partake in the complimentary breakfast, but opted to dine in our room, since we had the sitting area- it was great. The food was simple, but hit the spot. The dining room area was spacious, and filled with light, people were quietly reading the newspaper or having their morning coffee- it was very mellow. I can't say enough about this neighborhood, it's so nice to stay in San Francisco, and not have to deal with the crowds, haggling for a cab, or waiting for a valet to bring your car- we checked out, leisurely walked to our car, and agreed that we'd return very soon!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="040c80445745be2a5475f69331529942" url=""><![CDATA[Ok stay, nothing special- kind of weird We stayed here for the San Francisco Marathon... and it was a great location for that... I can imagine this place is good for business travelers who are in the financial district... but it left much to be desired in the way of warmth. Everything is VERY sterile here... and the rooms are the oddest shaped I've ever seen, and had we not opted for the superior room, we would have been staying in a hole... all the lighting is very institutional... I also felt very itchy in the bed, perhaps the sheets were too rough, or perhaps there were bugs- not sure.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="34ff7e1e3dcb06978eeb6b97078d8e33" url=""><![CDATA[San Francisco Gem! We stayed at the Westin one night for our friend's wedding. I made a reservation through the Rooms Reservations Manager- and he was wonderful about a great rate, and he attempted to upgrade the room. HOWEVER- at check-in- the front desk agent decided to void the upgrade to speed us through the line! I was very disappointed that he never even asked us if we'd like to wait for the upgraded room!! When we arrived at our room on the 11th floor, the door was OPEN! The room was clean and ready for us, but it was VERY disconcerting that the door to our room would be OPEN! The room was nice- the bathroom was typical San Francisco- VERY petite! The chandelier in the sleeping room was a nice touch.. The heavenly bed was a little less than heavenly- but it did the trick. For the location in San Francisco, if I was a tourist, this would be an impressive place to stay- but being a local, I expected a bit more!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>