<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="ba8b01ea266fc492e3df7cf18bfa6cb3" url=""><![CDATA[Good Value Four of us - 2 adult couples - stayed at the Hispanos 7 Suiza (H7S) for 8 nights 12/28/08 - 1/6/09. The hotel is about 10 blocks from the center of Barcelona, but a subway is easily available. (Ten rides cost less than 8 Euros and rides can be shared.) The hotel is 5 floor high and consists of 2 bedroom, 2 bath apartments. There is a front desk that's staffed 24/7. A free breakfast (cold cereals, yougurt, fresh fruit, pastries and breads, juice, and beverages) is provided in the upscale restaurant on street level. The apartment is about 400 sq. feet. There's A long living room with a separate kitchen area at one end. The appliances are modern (d/w, built in oven, 2 burner range top, undercounter refrig,. with small freezer, microwave, toaster, and washer/dryer). The furniture is basic - upholstered coach and easy chair, small TV, glass top dining room table for 4. The living room - kitchen is about 11ft wide x 20 ft long. There are 2 small bedrooms, about 10 ft x 10ft. (Each has its own closet with hanging space, shelving, and drawers.) One has a queen bed, the other has twin beds. (The twins can be pushed together.) There's a hall bathroom (small tub with hand-held that doesn't mount on a wall) bidet, toilet, sink and lots of mirrors. We assigned that bath to one couple. The other bath is attached to the twin-bedded room. It has a small shower, toilet, and sink. It's tight, but it's certainly functional. The apartment has it's own heating and a/c system. It worked well. There's also a front balcony - probably 11 ft x 3.5 ft. There were a couple of problems. Thin doors and walls make privacy within the apartment an issue. One can also hear conversations in the adjoining unit - but this wasn't as serious as it may sound. There are supermarkets around the corner and places with prepared foods within a block or two. We didn't prepare meals but it was convenient to have cooked food and drinks available. The place was small for 4, but it suited our purposes. The modern bathrooms and kitchen were far from depressing. The rate was 230 euros a day plus a 7% tax. That's reasonable for 2 couples. We were there during an expensive time period. My guess is that discounts are readily available at other times of the year.. We found H7S a good alternative to a 4 star hotel. And during this holiday season, two rooms at a 4 star hotel would have cost significantly more.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>