<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="fd6ab6e83f79ad8f97f77dd4e18d8dfe" url=""><![CDATA[Overally satisfying experience We stayed at Club Quarters Boston from April 25th to April 27th 2008.We arrived in Boston at 6:30 in the morning of the 26th. We went directly to the hotel because we wanted to leave our luggages there until check-in time - but surprisingly, the room was already available ! It was a very appreciated opportunity since we had just made an exhausting 7 hour bus ride.Otherwise, two things could have been better : the staff and the noise. The staff isn't the friendliest in the world. I don't have any souvenir of a smile or anything like that. They do their job - but that's it. As for the noise, we could easily hear conversations in the bathrooms on other floors and in the corridors. But overally, considering the location daily rate, negative aspects just aren't that important.If you're staying at Club Quarters during the week-end, keep in mind that you'll have to walk a little to get to restaurants and stores. Since the hotel is located in the heart of Financial District, everything nearby is closed on Saturday and Sunday. But Boston being a relatively small city, pretty much everything is in a reasonnable walking distance.The room size was just fine for two people. Although the bathroom could have easily been a little bigger even to the room's lost, if was very comfortable. To my surprise, there was a fridge and microwave in the room, which happened to be very useful in my case. The room was clean and neat.The proximity of the pub is handy - drinks and beer are great and cheap. Food is pretty good but don't bother getting the brunch on mornings - it's $18 per person for not so many choices. They have a breakfast special - two eggs, a huge sausage, potatoes, beans and toasts for $10. The staff is mostly friendly. Overally, I'd say we had a very good experience at Club Quarters. We recommend it for businness travelers or couples. Not really appropriate for people travelling with children. We'll certainly return to one of the many Club Quarters in the future.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>