<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f6aff898e995c7455124a88a853d585c" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel, Good Location Spent 5 nights in Barcelona, wanting to see the sights and stay at upscale hotel at a reasonable price. If you are looking for European Old World elegance, this is not for you. If you are looking for a modern, clean, better hotel, that is on the water, close to La Rambla, this hotel is for you. At $176 US, Priceline awarded us with a stay at a comfortable hotel. Arriving on Saturday evening after a full day of traveling, and a layover in Madrid, we pleasantly greeted at the reception desk and given a very nice room overlooking a not so nice office building. We were offered complimentary glasses of Cava in the lounge. Being it was Saturday, we were lucky to see that the lounge featured Opera night, which showcased four very good performers. We ordered some tapas, an additional drink and called it a night. The prices were in line with what you would expect at a better hotel. Not outrageous by any means.The room was nice, bathroom had a jacuzzi, but the bed was a little hard. With all better hotels now offering plush bedding, we were surprised. The hotel is about a 10 minute walk to the top of La Rambla. We are walkers and found we were able to walk to many of the areas most tourists would want to see. La Boqueria a short walk on La Rambla is great way to start your day and load up snacks for the day ahead. The On and Off Tour Bus stops by the hotel. I suggest if you are staying a few days, to get the 2-day pass. It will take you to the places that are too far to walk to.Now for the best part of the hotel...Felipe, the concierge. Felipe was like a local tour guide for us. He advised where to go, where to eat, and how long to spend at each site. He even advised us where to rest, take out our snacks we bought earlier, and just take in life. Felipe made sure to ask us, on our return from sightseeing, how our day went. If a 5 star hotel is based on services, Felipe might be the reason (maybe the only reason) this is a 5 star hotel. We would recommend this hotel as a good place to stay for seeing the sights.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>