<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="a92159308d1edeaeab4b6ee0c29d8671" url=""><![CDATA[Some Additional Details.... The other positive reviews have already said it all, and I agree with them. In particular, the rooms are among the most beautiful and functional of any hotel I have stayed in. I just want to fill in a few details that might help others....What you want is a water view on a high floor with upgrade to Regency Club (27th floor) if available. Regency Club includes cont b'fast, evening appetizers, coffee/water almost 24/7, free internet access, nice space to hang out in.The Concierge can arrange very good Limo to/from SeaTac for around $50 each way.Hertz Local Addition Car Rental is RIGHT around the corner and shares a garage with the Grand Hyatt. Very convenient and open weekends. Check Hertz website for HLE (Hertz Local Addition) deals.At least two different city tours pick up at hotel. Concierge can arrange.Also Starbucks in Hotel Lobby.10-15 minute walk to Public Market. 20 -30 minute walk to WA State Ferries Terminal.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b93ea068738090585aa9c3793c7bea75" url=""><![CDATA[Great Pre/Post Cruise Hotel I enjoyed being able to see the cruise ships come and go from my room before my cruise. It really got me psyched and also a bit more prepared.My room request recommendation would be for a room WITH a full balcony (w/table and chairs) on the cruise terminal side of the hotel as close to the water as possible on a high floor. Note: the rooms with the most expansive bay views - - which the hotel charges more for -- do NOT have balconies....although they have a sliding glass door opening onto a tiny railed-in ledge and those views are indeed the best.The hotel was very accomodating to my need for any early check-in (10am) after my cruise, and a staff member told me that they try to be very responsive to this.Finally, they have a self serve laundry for guests and a business center with pay internet access.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2e1b5b2372fa0e3a363ddccf5a55c9f3" url=""><![CDATA[I love the SF Hyatt Regency I stay in hotels in San Francisco often, and I enjoy the SF Hyatt Regency the most. I want to say right off the bat that this assumes I have a king room, bay view with balcony -- which IMHO is absolutely worth the price to upgrade. (I'm a Hyatt Gold Passport member, and I have had very good luck getting upgraded.)I find the architecture of the hotel fascinating and the somewhat Zen rooms extremely comfortable and efficient. I love hanging out on my balcony in the evening, or watching the boats and world go by in the daytime. Any service or store you could ever want is in either the Embarcadero shops or the Ferry Building marketplace....and all these places are used by locals so you are plunked down in the middle of a part of real San Francisco...not a tourist area per se.BART, the Cable Car, and a host of other public transportation options are right at your doorstep.I also like the level of service I have received here. It's not overly intimate and personal, but that's fine with me.Big Exception: I hate paying $38 for Valet parking. It seems like a crime.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>