<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="6b817b7379e719608159640019f54827" url=""><![CDATA[Outstanding! We stayed at Residence HIlda for 4 nights. We were a group of 5 - my husband, mother in law, and our 2 daughters. The apt. was very spacious, composed of a large master bedroom with a TV (minimum satellite channel choices), lots of closet space, another room with a small, functional kitchen with a dining area, and one luxurious bathroom. We stayed at a Superior Apartment, and the sleeping accommodations were as follows: One queen/king bed in the master room with a twin bed; a larger twin bed (coverted from a sofa) in the kitchen area; and another twin bed in the hall to the bathroom. Although I found the accommodations a little crowded, and would have liked a 2nd bathroom, my preteen/teenage daugthers loved having twin beds, vs. sharing a bed. In fact, they said it was their favorite hotel in Italy (we also visited Rome and Venice). The room was decorated in a modern, yet sophisticated style, with beautiful wood flooring. The only negative about the room is that the acoustics were not the best...we had a family with young children above us and they kept running around pounding on the floor. The situation got so bad my husband had to go upstairs and ask them to keep it down. We still could hear them the next day, though. There was an internet connection in the room, although not wireless. The windows were pretty soundproof as we couldn't hear much coming from the street. The location was excellent - - literally 2-3 blocks from Piazza Dei Duomo, 2 blocks from L' Accademia (where you can see David) and a 10 walk to the Uffizi Gallery. Tons of shops and places to eat around. We drove from Rome and took day trips to Pisa and Siena, which we highly recommend. Overall, it was a great experience and we would stay at this hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9239fcad8a25e44de053bbc785764182" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic! My husband, 2 daughters and mother in law stayed at Corte Grimani for two nights in Jan 08. We stayed at a wonderful, cozy apartment composed of a very large bedroom with a queen/king bed, and a pullout queen bed. The master bedroom was luxurious. The other room had another pullout queen bed and it's own bathroom, as well as a small kitchen with all amenities, a plasma TV and a dining area. We had quaint views of the canal. The room was sparkling clean and perfect for our group...lots of space. The customer service was A+. We decided to have breakfast at the hotel, and the buffet was very complete. There is also complimentary internet in the room (but not wireless). Besides its comfort, the best asset of this apt. hotel is is location. It is in a quiet corner, only 2-3 blocks from Piazza San Marco, close to all major attractions, restaurants and shops. We recommend taking a water taxi directly to the hotel entrance and also back to the airport if you're flying out of Marco Polo airport. Overall, it was a perfect experience....we would definitely stay there again when visiting Venice.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>