<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="211cc47c52c3a46dff2c6c901a52f3d6" url=""><![CDATA[not great...... We picked the hotel as we wanted to be near the beach but not too far away from the centre of things as we were staying for 5 nights.The location was fine, the beach and port (with all it's bars and restaurants) just a 5 minute walk away, but other than that the hotel was really isolated - but at least it was quiet at night.Check in was short and sweet, but they forget to tell everyone that you need to use your hotel key card in the lift or you won't be going anywhere..... luckily some other guests helped us out.The room was ok, but the bathroom door didn't shut, it took a few hours and phone calls to resolve but as the hotel was full and we couldn't change rooms, they did send someone to fix it pretty quickly. We had to go down and spend a couple of hours by the crowded pool area while we waited (it's VERY small, even smaller than the pictures on the websites so don't expect to get a sun lounger). Otherwise the room was ok fittings new, just don't look too closely and so you don't notice the bathroom ceiling had a damp patch and the bedside cabinet tops weren't properly clean.... they do provide tea and coffee, but no milk and the plastic tea spoons disappeared after day 1.... be prepared to bring your own!! On the 3rd day there was a problem with a burst pipe so we had no water for a day - we called to complain and reception explained no one had water (hadn't had it all day, not that they bothered to tell anyone) and then brought us one 1litre bottle of mineral water to wash with (between the two of us). When the water came back on it was slightly yellow, so we decided not to use it.Breakfast was very mediocre (hot food limited and cold) - ok I think pretty atrocious for a 4 star hotel (coffee tasted like watery instant, and only herbal tea as an alternative) - the rest was disappointing, suggest you head to the local shops or the port for a much better option (and cheaper!) So, to the main complaint, after day 1 we decided to cancel breakfast which we had pre-booked for one of us - and were told by an incredibly rude man at reception (he kept answering the phone without a single apology while talking to us), who told us we couldn't, it was included in the price (no it wasn't) and only when we got annoyed would he check our reservation and realise that we had ordered the breakfast separately and yes it could be cancelled. Reception in general were rude and unhelpful, not interested in helping or providing good service. We asked about the theatre tickets (as per the leaflet in reception) and they told us to go to the theatre ourselves and buy tickets..... the one notable exception was the very nice lady who helped us check out very quickly and ordered a taxi as our flight had changed, she was quick and efficient.The hotel is just about ok, although I think VERY expensive for what you get, I think you are better off paying a bit more for the hotels nearer the port/town - they are also that bit nearer to things as it's about 30 min walk to the old town from the hotel icaria -or picking something more reasonably priced nearer town - the public transport system is fantastic cheap (don't go on the tourist bus, get on the metro/use taxis - it actually worked out much cheaper and far more flexible)Barcelona however is fantastic, worth the trip, but probably you should pick another hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>