<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="0844343475c6f75ca0e955cba03d24a2" url=""><![CDATA[Brilliant hotel My husband and i stayed at Hotel Lungarno for 3 nights and we found this hotel to be a great find.It is located a short walk from the shops and restaurants.We booked a suite room and were pleasantly surprised by the size and the decor was lovely throughout the hotel not just our room. We had a huge balcony (although we did not use it due to it being too cold) which would have been perfect for breakfast with views over the river.The staff were freindly and efficient, the bar excellent and i can say the restaurant was one of the best meals we have had and we travel frequently and have sampled food all over the world.I would recommend this hotel as a great place to stay in Florence.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="63ef9f6ed06edd34fa5b537f659fbed2" url=""><![CDATA[Was ok We stayed at this hotel for a week over christmas. We found the location very good, great restaurants and bars on third avenue which is a blocks walk away.The staff were extremely friendly and informative. The rooms were big but the bathroom was on the small side. We could not help but think that the kitchen was space that could have been but to better use say a bigger bathroom.Overall we found our stay at the Affinia |Dumont to be pleasant but not as good as other hotels we have stayed in like Omni Berkshire.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fec665ef2b4d5319658a774271e5e736" url=""><![CDATA[First class hotel My husband baby and i have just returned from our week trip to New York and would recommend that if you are visiting the states then stay at the Sofitel.We have been to New York 4 times and have stayed at different hotels but none compare to the excellent service we received at the Sofitel.There is not a kettle in the room and i phoned reception to request one so that i could use it for my son's milk and within 10 minutes one appeared in our room.The concierge recommended several excellent restaurants that we would not have visited if not for them.We had breakfast at the hotel on the day we were leaving and it was so good we wished we had gone there before.There were no negatives about this hotel. The business room was enough for the three of us including a cot. All in all we all had a wonderful stay and will be back next year.I must also say that the staff in the bar are excellent.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>