<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="89e1d3c34b56676a19f0e110cb46d71c" url=""><![CDATA[Good value in spite of limited room size I booked four rooms for a group of four couples, including me and my wife, after visiting Tripadvisor. At the time of booking, Hotel Ares occupied top rank. Moreover, the room rate was within the group's budget, while mapping the hotel confirmed its central location.Room: The room had attractive state-of-the-art decor. The main problem was the tight room size of about ten square metres (excluding bathroom and lobby). There was absolutely no space for luggage. So this was opened on the bed and then replaced on the floor which made it uncomfortable to manoevre round the bed. Hanging space in the wardrobe was hardlly sufficient for one person. To make matters worse the hair dryer located in that compartment competed for space with hanging clothes.Amenities: An extensive choice of TV channels was available. The internet facility advertised on the Quadriga system turned out to be a joke and effectively unusable in terms of speed and userfriendliness.Service: Reception staff were extremely courteous and helpful. Housekeeping staff were totally inconspicuous, but their performance left nothing to be desired in terms of cleanliness and room turnout.Breakfast: One member of the group tried out the buffet breakfast and reported that the offerring (including eggs only in scrambled mode) was over priced at 15 euro. So we opted for a more varied breakfast for 10 euro at a coffee bar round the corner.General: The central location is indeed a boon. Nearby boulevards Suffren and Motte Piquet are full of shops, restaurants and bars. The Motte Piquet metro station, five minutes away, effectively connects the hotel Ares with the rest of Paris. I recommend Hotel Ares as good value for money, by Paris standards, especially on the strength of its location if not of the room size.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>