<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="41990e6f033f1612b8edb93d23d9a03f" url=""><![CDATA[Not a hotel it's a Garden Inn This hotel (actually every complaint I made was answered with this is not a hotel, it is a Garden Inn) looks quite attractive in the lobby and bar but it stops right there.They had our reservation information incorrect.There was no two bottles of water provided But they would sell them to us.there was no shaving cream, tooth brushes, toothpaste shampoo etc providedThere was no concierge. The front desk covered that job but they repeatedly did not know the answers to my common questions.They did not know the length of the tour for which they sold ticketsThey charged $95 for a tour that their own literature indicated $90. They corrected the charge when I brought it to their attentiontheir General manager refused to answer six different phone calls.their elevators were inoperative on three occasions (Once because of extended cleaning, once because the service elevator was inoperative and they took over the passenger elevator to move baggage)On three occasions my card key did not workthe printer on the computer PC did not work. Eventually they summoned a geek who came in and got it working againthey failed to make one wake up callThey did not know of the nearby banks operating hoursThey did not know of a nearby hairdressers location, hours or even if it was open They were unaware of a nearby supermarkets operating hoursWhen asked about transportation to Ponte Vecchia etc they said we should hire a taxi ($22) even though there was a trolley a short distance from the hotel.The dining room was supposed to be open for service until 2230 however wwhen we showed up at 2225 they refused to allow us in even though there were several people still eating.The hotel charged extra for breakfastWe finally left the hotel two days early because of our repeated disapointments.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>