<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="eaafa7b80747e2b0ebcc0aca0e916ff5" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel, great location, no elevator problems This is the best location in Times Square. And, it is one of the few NYC hotels that is completely void of street noise. There were hotel employees at the elevators assuring that everyone got to their floor in a timely manner. All of the employees were very friendly and helpful.I will definitely stay at this hotel on future NYC visits.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="549a6d7b680c204498c8c8e06c30c8b9" url=""><![CDATA[Duck and Cover! Here comes another jet through the room!!! I had a jet fly through my room every 10 minutes. The loudest one was at 5:15 am. I gave up on sleeping then. They just kept coming.This is an older property. Probably early 1970's. The neighborhood must have been much nicer back then too. The location has gone down hill.The bed was extremely small, but reasonably comfortable. One roll over on either side and you would have fallen off.There were stains in the bathroom from the years of wear. Not dirty, just very old. A black streak here and black flecks there.The front desk was nice.Very close to the airport.The breakfast was okay.I did like being able to buy a Coke out of the machine for the bargain price of $.75 per 12 ounce can!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1f960cb2dcf631e9483b26aed24886a1" url=""><![CDATA[The Omni was a little disappointing 1) I tried to get an early check-in at 2 pm. The room was not ready until 3:30 pm. 2) I checked my luggage with the bellman and went outside to wait. When my room was finally ready, the bellman was gone. I waited at the bellman's stand for ten minutes and no one showed up and the front desk was not concerned. Finally I hunted around and found my own bag. It was sitting by the hotel entrance with six others and nobody was paying attention to the luggage. I helped myself to my bag and went up stairs. What is the point of checking your bag if it is left out in the open with no attendant???3) The whole floor I was on had BAD BREATH! P.U. It was a horrible last week's pizza and beer smell. 4) There are no restaurants in the imediate area except for the hotel restaurant. The hotel restaurant was okay but, I was there for three days and would like to have had a choice of restaurants.5) Some of the staff at the front desk were nice. They must have had a 5 pm shift change and that group was rude. 6) The mattress was old and sank to one side. Otherwise, it was your average two star hotel. Do not get your expectations up and you will be fine here. If you expect $125 worth of hotel room, you will be disappointed. This hotel is a good value at the $75 per night price if you can live with the negative features mentioned up above.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>