<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="b3a133f72e3a05b012e585cc439a8ad3" url=""><![CDATA[Great vacation! We stayed at the Bahia Principe for a week - from Sat. Feb 9th through Sat. Feb 16 2008. We booked online through Apple and left from Philadelphia for a direct flight to Punta Cana. Our original reservations were for the main resort, Bahia Principe Punta Cana, but we arrived after 10 p.m. and were told we were upgraded, which we found out meant they were overbooked. So we were taken to Ambar, which is the newest section of the resort, BUT were told we had to use the restaurants, bars and pools in our original location - and they were quite far apart. My husband asked - nicely - and we were given privileges to use everything at Ambar. Another couple who were arguing and yelling at the manager, were NOT accomodated, so please be nice! Anyway, the entire resort grounds can be confusing - there is Punta Cana, Bavaro, Ambar, Diamond, and they are all separate, but there are common areas. Trying to figure it out took all week. But instead of worrying about it, we just enjoyed where we were. There is SO much there, it would be impossible to use it all anyway, so just go out and enjoy. The grounds are immaculate, the beach is beautiful. All the things others have said are true about reserving beach chairs or palapas - I swear people go out in the middle of the night to stake their spot. We did get a palapa every day, but it was not easy. Beach towels are provided, and plenty of towels in the room. Ambar rooms are serviced twice a day - maid service in the morning, and turn down service at night - with more towels, chocolates and little bottles of liquor. Minibar was replenished every day with beer, bottled water, soda. If you use washcloths in the shower, bring them - we bought 15/$5 at Walmart. The rooms are lovely, the mattress was comfortable, and so were the pillows. The pillow service and bath service are extra at Ambar - you can order scented pillows, and scented baths, but I can't see the point myself. There is a lovely balcony where you can sit at night and have a cocktail - be careful - our porch door locked behind us and we were stuck on the balcony until our shouting got a maintenance man. Making yourself understood is difficult - hardly anyone speaks anything other than Spanish. But they try very hard.The food was wonderful, particularly at the buffet. So many people complain about hot not being hot - cold not being cold. Aside from the cold cuts ( which we don't eat) we found everything to be as would be expected. There were plenty of choices, a theme every night, and beautiful selections of salads and desserts. Coffee is served only at breakfast. The specialty restaurants are a nice idea, but there are many servers running around in a disorganized fashion, and the food is not really reflective of the theme. We had reservations in the Italian restaurant, Portofino, and there was NO pasta on the menu that night. Nothing remotely Italian. Also, we sat and waited there for 45 minutes, got water and bread, but never got anything else. Some tables were getting excellent service and some were getting none at all. We left and went to the buffet. The staff on the grounds, the buffet, and the cleaning staff are very efficient. So are the barmaids - but we usually went to the lobby bar at Punta Cana - much livelier. There is also coffee and tea service every day at 4.Drinks are OK - many not like what'd you get in the US with the same name. Margaritas are good, blended drinks, and Irish coffee. And don't forget to try mamajuana - the aphrodiasiac that makes mamma wanna. It's made with rum, branches, spices, etc - and you drink it as a shot - loved it! We saw one show, Lion King. Very cute, kind of amateurish, but this is not Broadway. The shops at the little village were OK - mostly cheap souvenirs. Be sure to bargain - a lot. Casino costs extra- didn't go. Didn't take any side trips.All in all, we had a wonderful vacation - we went to relax, and we did. We spent our days on the beach reading and walking and just enjoying the beautiful weather. At night we dressed nicely for dinner and had a nice dinner with wine. Got tons of beautiful photos.For all the complaints we read, we would still go there again, and just realize that nothing is perfect, and the people here try hard to please and they are very nice and friendly. Exceptions were a couple bartenders who had an attitude, but you will find different people everywhere. We tried to tip people who don't usually get tips - like the drivers of the shuttles that are available day and night, and the housekeepers. Just GO and enjoy - be sure to take insect repellant ( our room in building 69 was on the edge of the jungle and I am covered in mosquito bites), sunscreen, immodium in case of diarrhea, books for the beach, insulated mugs to keep your beer cold on the beach, and some hats. Don't overpack - you don't need more than lots of swimsuits and some nice clothes for evening - we could have gotten along with HALF of what we took. We would highly recommend Bahia Principe - it's a work in progress, but we'd surely go there again anyway. We have been to many other all-inclusives and this one is very, very nice. Enjoy!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>