<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="e29940238aea841cdf00f7fe7f2da39e" url=""><![CDATA[Mixed Reviews of the WESJ We have gone to this about six years now. It has many pros and many cons. They seem however to equal each other, and why we keep returning.Ill start with the Pros: Restaurants are really good but quite pricey. Lobby is amazing, and the staff does give the general can help attitude. The grounds are what the make the hotel so special, the two pools are really nice, big and clean. let the ads fool you however; when it says three pools, one is only for certain guests. The adjacent beach is quite long and the ocean water a perfect temp.CONS: Rooms, Rooms, Rooms. The rooms are in dire need of repairs, they are old, and dirty, and have some serious mantience problems. The most serious being as we heard from other guests one water pump was the top floor of the hotel receiving no hot water during prime hours. (4-8PM.) The front desk just told them go to a different room and shower, and they were given a key to that room to use for an hour. Hot water is always a problem though in the hotel during those hours as is water pressure. We had the same room the last two years, and the broken doorknob last year, was still broken this year. We had two rooms; in one room bathroom towels were repeatedly dirty. Most shocking however, was the stained sheets left one night. They were immediately changed upon request, but this should not happen in this first place.I probably would return to the hotel, but all in all in needs a major facelift, as the price they are getting does not match the rooms they offer.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eef3cce283195e165f1629e7eb63a2d6" url=""><![CDATA[Amazing Relaxing Thanksgiving View from the balcony
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="08140b54e97f6deda522120b44a40299" url=""><![CDATA[Yuck Not the best of hotels. I was in one of the wings. Hotel is old and visably unappealing. It says its on 35 acres, but they literally use all that area. Parking gates to get in and out of lot. Very big hotel, not very good hotel though. If I returned to Seattle, I would most likely skip this place.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2368624047957317d2bfadba7371934d" url=""><![CDATA[Great Find Ca Dei Dogi makes you feel like you live in Venice. It is a tiny six-room hotel that has excellent hosts who welcome you in their city like family.It is located in an amazing location, off some small alleyways near St. Mark's Square and from there everything is in walking distance. There is a water bus stop right at the end of the alley, so access to the airport and train station is also easy.I stayed in the single room which was tiny, barely enough room to walk. But for the price in Venice, it was fine.Breakfast was included and a good chance to relax. Likewise, the hotel has a rooftop garden that is a nice place to relax from the heat of Venice.The hotel does not have an elevator, but they help you with all your bags. Venice is an amazing city and Ca Dei Dogi makes it even more enjoyable. Pick this place--you will not regret it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f87b0577a5c8cebf6aced14b632309e3" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel, Location TV and desk
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>