<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="e8abaf429d245ff3dd485c9076b99568" url=""><![CDATA[Good bang for your buck The Hotel Metropolis is located right on the edge of the Tenderloin neighborhood which, if you can get past the dirty streets and menacing-looking residents, is a great location convenient to public transportation, shopping, theatre, live music, restaurants and the MOMA. Although the surroundings are intimidating the good news is that there is a lot of foot traffic in this area, even at night.The hotel itself is clean and very modern in design. The front desk staff was friendly at check in and they made sure to advise guests of the fitness room, meditation room and free wi-fi and breakfast. My very clean standard queen room was TINY - there was about 2 feet of space between the side of the bed and the desk and the foot of the bed and the armoire/TV. The bathroom was impressive for its size, relative to the sleeping area. Waiting for me in the bathroom was a care package with chewing gum, a Quatro razor, moisturizing cream, shampoo/conditioner and - totally cool touch - a thin romance novel!I was very happy with this room for which I paid $100 (incl. tax). I knew exactly what I was getting with the neighborhood surroundings and small room yet I feel that the hotel delivered exactly as promised. This hotel is an excellent value for budget-minded travelers or younger people that want to be close to SF nightlife without breaking the bank on a room. Keep in mind that it can't be stressed enough that the cheapest rooms are very small - even a couple that gets along well would find themselves climbing the walls with claustrophobia in no time.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="85ac6ea47cac4ffeb7dbc494105bbb67" url=""><![CDATA[Will Never Stay Here Again The rooms here are large and nice, and the views are remarkable but not nearly enough to make up for the awful service I received 2/15-2/17/07. Upon arrival the doorman did not come to the curb to assist me with my luggage - normally this wouldn't be a big deal to me but with the wind gusting and snow on the ground, it irked me this time.My room was large, clean and well-appointed. All was well until I attempted to open the mini-bar, which was stuck. A call downstairs informed me that they had problems with that particular room and would send someone right up. Maintenance arrived within 10 min but it's annoying not to be told of the problem in advance when management knows about it.On my second evening I had trouble establishing an internet connection; again, a call downstairs informed that particular room doesn't have internet connectivity and they offered to move me to another room. At this point I spoke to the manager who denied that anyone had any prior knowledge of the lack of internet connection in that particular room - whatever - I went ahead and moved rooms. I checked out Saturday morning at 6:30am and asked the desk clerk whether I would be able to hail a cab at that hour or if I was better off calling for one. I was told that the doorman (who was nowhere to be seen at that moment) could hail a cab for me. It's 6:30am on a SATURDAY, there is NO ONE else in the lobby, yet the desk clerk seems to feel it's beneath his station to accommodate my request for help in getting a cab.I will never stay here again - the service and attention to detail is minimal at best, and the staff is barely apologetic when their lack of attention causes disruption to their guests.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="df3a35bb0a30bbd7e689dde7ea8a9582" url=""><![CDATA[Great Experience We enjoyed a Saturday night stay and had a wonderful experience. Nice lobby. The clerk at check in was friendly and efficient and went to the effort of searching for the room upgrade we asked for. Our room looked dead-on at Coit Tower with partial bay views. Room was extremely clean and decent-sized although the bathroom was small. Furnishings and decor appeared to be in excellent condition, not worn out or tired looking at all. Noise in other rooms and the hallways was pretty much non-existent (although there was some construction going on next door that resulted in a generator going off at 6am on Sunday morning!). Sunday morning we had an awesome breakfast in the hotel restaurant - fairly reasonable at $35 for 2. I would definitely recommend this hotel for either a business or a leisure traveler, although simply due to the relatively small size of a standard room it probably wouldn't be the ideal hotel for any longer than a couple of nights.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>