<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="56ec142a2a571b5314e2318aa86b3311" url=""><![CDATA[Great place to stay! But keep in mind... The Westin was a beautiful hotel with friendly, courteous extremely helpful staff. Upon arrival, check in went slow we did get offered a below average room... however, after asking for an upgrade, we received one of the BEST rooms possible at no additional charge! The beach was private beautiful however there is brown sand not white so those of you who feel it's dirty - it's not! It did get a little littered by the end of our 8-day stay but NOTHING to complain about. The pools were perfect - with the exception of no swim-up bar although the tiki bar was great VERY relaxing the hours were too limited. The food/restaurants at the hotel were well-above average - except that they were not always open so if you are looking to JUST be at the hotel the ENTIRE time you may want to take that into consideration. We rented an Avis car at the hotel (good price cheap parking) and explored the island which we HIGHLY recommend doing! Don't expect 4-5 star areas or restaurants as you would find in the U.S. Mainland - but if you give it a chance you WILL find 4-5 star quality in both food places to visit - ESPECIALLY with the people of P.R.!! The hotel is isolated so, for example, to get to San Juan is at least 40 minutes with a bit of traffic. We explored El Yunque which is a MUST! (GREAT tour through the Westin with Harry the tour guide!!). The East Wind Catamarran trip to Culebra is also HIGHLY recommended out of Fajardo. Luquillo beach is great but NOT in the public area of the beach!!! You must go INTO the area of Luquillo where seafood like King's Sandy's are AMAZING that area has the beautiful beaches. The kiosks off route 3 for Fast Puerto Rican Food seems scary but if you can get past what you are used to you will be in for a REAL TREAT!!! The Pina Colada's at La Roca Taina (#53 -#58?) out of the kiosks is awesome esp. for $3!!! And Hacienda Caribali for sunsets in Rio Grande overlooking El Yunque Rio Mar was breathtaking! The food incredible - the service outstanding again! THe Pina Coladas ROCKED!! Also - if you can muster up the energy - Old San Juan is truly magical... We ate at a local hideaway called El Jibarito (recommended in Frommer's) and it was some of the best Puerto Rican food we had on the island... For 2 meals 4 Medalla's (Puerto Rican beer) the bill was under $35 with tip. The main drawback to staying at the Westin Rio Mar is the lack of nightlife. If you don't mind driving a bit - the El Conquistador is good for some nightlife Isla Verde is about 30 minutes away GREAT for nightlife. For golf the Westin seems wonderful (we don't golf) again, if isolation is a factor for your trip it's a TERRIFIC place to be! We were able to get both - relaxation adventure we can't WAIT to go back to Puerto Rico! Also for those people who we've read reviews of that complain about things like the humidity bugs sporadic rainstorms... It's a CARIBBEAN ISLAND! IT'S TROPICAL! DON'T GO IF YOU EXPECT TO FIND THIS OASIS OF PERFECT WEATHER! IT'S NOT POSSIBLE! And to us the weather was pretty perfect! Also, please keep in mind - Puerto Rico's MAIN language is SPANISH! 90% of the people speak english well but it helps to know a little spanish.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>