<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="ad59d9e4f452f52e8e4b5b3a9689cbb4" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent anniversary trip-just a few tips... My husband and I stayed at Secrets Excellence for our 10th anniversary from November 3-9. I really appreciated all of the reviews on this site and others and I always like to know what to expect so this will be pretty long. We have stayed at the Xpu Ha Palace in the Mayan Riviera and liked this better because of the architecture and it wasn't so spread out. (this is the only other all inclusive we have to compare to but we loved both)Overall, our vacation was wonderful. I knew the resort was on the Atlantic but thought surely we would have calm blue water. This was not the case but on the last couple of days it calmed a little and we were able to snorkel just 4 minutes to the right of the resort (there is a reef there). THIS IS MY BIG TIP our rep, Prieto Tours gave an orientation on our second day which I thought would give a lot of helpful info. Really, they are just trying to sign you up for excursions. Before you book anything, go to Scuba Caribe (we had never read anything about this) at the watersports area or at the pool cabana. They have tons of trips; scuba, snorkel, snorkel offsite, even deep sea fishing for much less money and they take you by boat from the resort so it doesn't take up your whole day. Unfortunately, we discovered this on the next to the last day. The snorkel trip is a 25 minute boat ride from Secrets to a reef and it is only $25pp. (it is $80 from the tour operators and a 1-2 hour BUS ride). PLEASE check here first!!!!We booked deep sea fishing thru the front desk and it was 1 1/2 hour ride to Bavaro and we caught no fish. it was fun being on the boat all day, though. Were with 4 germans and the 2 dominican captains. $90 per personWe found the food to be fair but there was usually something we liked at each restaurant. I think this is just indicative of the all inclusive because we experienced it in Mexico also. We were much more adventurous the first few days. One of us ordered a safe meal that we could share if we didn't like the adventurous meal the other chose. We loved the breakfast, pizzas, and pastas at Higuey, caeser salad, mixed grill for 2 (served on a hibachi) at dinner in Texas restaurant, and french onion soup in the Quisqueya. The deal with the carribean lobster is that it is mushy at the top. Just cut that off and eat the end of the tail-it is firm like Maine lobster. Look for the sports bar in back by the cascade pool-they have great chicken wings. We had a complimentary anniversary dinner at the mediterranean restaurant that was nice atmosphere overlooking the beach (We were going to book the $160 on the beach but I think it was the same steak and lobster just more atmosphere). Overall, we didn't mind that the food wasn't fabulous-if it had been we would have gained 10 pounds!!!We brought bubble bath and candles for our room and were glad we did. The resort is very romantic and there are hot tubs in the rooms as well as hidden all over the resort. My husband loved the Playboy channel!!!! We went to the beach in the morning and spent the afternoons in the pool. We never had to wait more than a minute for a float-if you look like you need one people will give them up. I saw people stealing them from under other chairs which I think is fine. The palapas for 2 on the pool deck are a great place to hide out during the short rain storms.The drinks are great-they can put anything in a coconut-lime daquiris were great and Presidente. One couple told us to ask for a bucket of beer in ice if you want them colder. On the last night we discovered Cosmopolitans-we needed a change from frozen fruity drinks. The casino is fun and the disco is too-Julio and his group get you riled up with audience participation before the show and at the disco. We thought the shows were pretty entertaining and the theater is nice and comfortable.Overall, we loved Secrets. We would not go back again just because there are so many other places to try. We would recommend it to friends so go and have a great time. We couldn't understand why people had so many complaints.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>