<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="8b50ea2b4211f3056ea2a49932b92caf" url=""><![CDATA[Nice place, but very crowded We recently stayed at this hotel for one night, before our return home. We had originally booked the room for our first night in Puerto Rico, but our flight from the US was delayed. We were told by Expedia that our booking was non transferrable/refundable, but the hotel was understanding of our situation, which was out of our hands, and agreed to change our booking at no cost to us. What a relief!The hotel was nice, but very crowded. We waited quite a while to check in, only to find out that our room was not ready as promised. We were upgraded to a villa, which was lovely. Our villa neighbors were very noisy. Upon our complaint to the front desk, someone was sent to calm them down immediately and we had no further problems. I would probably look for a smaller, less crowded hotel the next time I am in San Juan, but the Hilton is lovely if you don't mind a crowd.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d45816a323a6b2abbbde82a96ac0ec73" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel As a member of the Kimpton Group's frequent club (or whatever they call it) Hotel Palomar was a no brainer when my mom and I decided to visit San Fran.Like the other Kimpton hotels, Palomar is very modern and I love the decor. Our room and bathroom was smaller than what we would normally expect, but maybe that has something to do with the location.I ordered a $12 sandwich off of the room service menu and the charge to our room was almost $30, I guess with all of the fees and everything. I find that to be ridiculous and the sandwich wasn't even that good!Overall we had a pleasant stay and liked the location.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="518bff768b862fd6bd601edf1195cea9" url=""><![CDATA[3 Star We wanted an inexpensive getaway for the holidays this year, and Rincon Beach Resort came up on Expedia, under the package deals that include flight and car rental. It was in our price range, so we decided to try it. The resort is really beautiful and was just what we were looking for. It is very relaxing, if you want to hang out at the pool. The restaurant is 5 star with a price to match. We thought it was worth it though, considering the room was priced very reasonably. The room itself is what makes this hotel a 3 star. There were small bugs on the counter every time I went into the bathroom, and as we were on the bottom floor, we kept waiting for a lizard or other creature to visit us through the gap under the door. The rest of the hotel was more like a 4 or 5 star though, and we weren't in the room much. Very friendly, helpful staff. We will visit again and request a room on one of the higher floors.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>