<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="7312478d9d00ab143a462c0f2fb13aaf" url=""><![CDATA[Lovely hotel, great situation Westayed at the Keppler hotel September 2008.When we arrived at the hotel after a long trip from Japan, we appreciated the quick and efficient check in.The room was nice and clean and well decorated but extremely small. I think that most hotel rooms in Paris are small, but this one was so small you could hardly open the wardrobe door as it couldn't clear the bed.The bathroom was very nice and clean and very pretty.I have 2 complaints about the bathroom:1. The shower only dribbled out and we asked them to fix it. It was fixed the day before we left and we were there for 6 days.2. The hairdryer was permanently attached under a shelf so you have to bend down to use it if you are over 5ft tall. I am 5ft7.The location of the hotel was great, close to the Arc de Triomphe, the Eiffel Tour and the Champs Elysee and there were lots of Metro stations around.Try and get a deal that includes breakfast. Do NOT believe that there are lots of nice little cafes around where you can get a good, inexpensive breakfast. There are not.On the whole the hotel was clean,comfortable and safe and the staff were really nice and helpful.We loved it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6624ef74b5c37ac2b1e203e6c6038a76" url=""><![CDATA[We loved it! We stayed at this beautiful hotel in September, and thoroughly enjoyed the experience.We arrived a little early for the usual check in but were quickly and efficiently shown to our room.The room was quite a reasonable size, very clean and tastefully decorated with period furniture sloping ceilings and beautiful french fittings in the bathroom,The bathroom was marble and even though the shower was over the bath it was easy to use and the water pressure was good. The soap, shampoo and other products in the bathroom were french and of a very good quality.The staff were nice and very helpful. On the day we arrived we were tired and hungry and the receptionist directed us to a restaurant just up the street which was excellent.The location of the hotel was fantastic, just across the road from the beautiful gardens and only a short walk to Blvd. St. Michel and St. Germaine. Musee D'Orsay, the river Seine with the artists and souvenir sellers, Notre Dame and many other places of interest, shops and restaurants.The metro and RER train stations are only a short walk away and easy to use once you get the hang of it.Take the RER train to Versaiiles, it only takes about 40 mins and is a really interesting trip. The palace itself is unbelievable, you really have to see it and the grounds are huge.We really loved the hotel and wished we had more time to spend there.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>