<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="acab0cba3816948548ea41ef309d2523" url=""><![CDATA[Good value but lacking amenities Hello fellow tripadvisors,Having recently returned from a 5 night stay at the Novotel here is my opinion of this resort. Firstly 8 members of my family stayed here. 5 of us in a 3 bed unit and 3 in a 2 bed with private pool. The pool unit was fantastic and well worth the extra paid. There were no 3 bed available with pool when we booked and when we saw it we were even more disappointed. All in all for the price we paid, pppn I can't complain about the accomodation.On arrival at 2.45pm only the 2 bed unit was ready so we all made our way there and surveyed the unit. It was clean, spacious and of course the pool area was wonderful. After leaving our cases we went to the hotel restaurant for a snack. The menu was pretty good but unfortunately despite there only being 1 other table with 6 diners we waited about 30 minutes for our food to arrive and it was, at best, mediocre. Needless to say that was the last time we used the restaurant. We booked a room only package and thought we would check out the breakfast on offer before committing. My husband went over the next morning and said not to bother, at a head it just wasn't worth it. There are plenty of little restaurants less than a 5 minute walk with an abundance of choice. At the resort it just seemed to lack a holiday atmosphere, it was very quiet, probably due to the inflated prices. The beach was lovely and it was a very short shuttle ride which was frequent and you could have a drink or some lovely fresh fruit baskets which were very refreshing. Again it was quiet which was probably a good thing as i could imagine a shortage of loungers if it was busy.My sister stayed at the Melia on her last visit to Bali and we did use their facilities one day. It was definately a much superior resort and what a difference it makes being right on the beach, this hotel was busy, had a very good lunch menu with prompt service and there was a good selection of watersports available on site. We also had dinner here one night, it was a spanish buffet with a fantastic selection including champagne with plentiful refills at a head.To conclude, the novotel accomodation itself was great but the facilities and proximity from the beach let the resort down. Next time i'll pay more and stay at a beach resort.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>