<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="24ef74589a135ad8c0ea3a3eac479927" url=""><![CDATA[A lovely boutique hotel My husband and I stayed at Hotel des Grande Hommes 18 years ago and we loved it then. We originally found the hotel in Karen Brown's book on France. This summer we traveled back to Paris with our two teenage sons and we stayed once again at the hotel. It was so lovely! This is a high-end 3 star. Very old world and elegant but not over the top fancy. It is very small, the elevator only holds two and there is only ever one person at the front desk.The hotel is located next to the Pantheon and is close to the metro as well as wonderful cafes and restaurants. At first we thought the charge for breakfast was too expensive at 12 euros but after tiny cups of coffee for 5 Euros at the cafes, we gladly paid to have unlimited delicious coffee. Overall The Hotel des Grande Hommes is a great place to stay in Paris. It is an excellent value, extremely clean and the staff is very warm and helpful. I can't wait to go back!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b0478d1bad10f34a8d6ecf211319a322" url=""><![CDATA[Awful! We booked this hotel because the Boston College website listed it as a local place to stay. We planned on staying two nights and we had booked two rooms at a rate of $169.00 per night. When we arrived my husband commented that it looked like The Bates Motel. Once inside our room - we were horrified. The room had been decorated in the 70's and had never been updated. It was extremely shabby and the bedspreads and carpet were stained. Worst of all was the disgusting smell of smoke and stale air. It was so bad that we told the front desk clerk that we didn't want to stay there - the clerk informed us that he may have to charge us anyway. We told him fine, knowing that we would stop our credit card payment and make a formal complaint against the hotel. Our trip to the Boston area ended up lovely. We checked into the Doubleday Suites and were very happy there. The rate at this hotel was actually less expensive because a two room suite was $199.00 and accommodated our family just fine. The bottom line is DON'T stay at the Best Western Inn in Boston. There are so many other options of great places to stay!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="94f4536e7d19533b18e5342ee747c57d" url=""><![CDATA[Extremely comfortable welcoming I booked this hotel because of the great reviews. It is all true. The decor is lovely, the beds are really cozy and the fitness room is adequate. Best of all is the welcoming staff that is always available to offer suggestions or provide directions.We also really liked the location.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="80721349ad5e157e9e85e205856c0475" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Hotel The Mexico City Marriott is a a great hotel to stay in because the staff is so kind and accomodating. When you walk in the hotel there is a lineup of staff waiting to assist. Although we loved visiting Mexico City, it can be a scary and daunting place and we really needed assistance with our daily plans. Also - the hotel is very comforatble and was a great place to relax after a day of touring. The workout facilty pool are outstanding and the bar is a lovely place for a margarita. The food was just ok. but there are numerous good choices in Polanco for food. One tip for Mexico City travelers: take the hotel taxi cabs car service. Even when you are away from the hotel - call them to be picked up. My husband and I had a terrfying experience when we jumped in a taxi waiting outside a museum. The driver seemed fine at first but then we realized that we were headed in the oppisite direction from our hotel. The driver brought us to a VERY SCARY location near the airport to buy goods from a store. We thought we were being kidnapped. My husband firmly told the driver to please bring us to our hotel and he did but we had about a 5 mile (very tense)drive back.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>