<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="6">
		<document id="f3e0b1de269a89e4bdc3e2ca4ab82cc8" url=""><![CDATA[Good Value for Money I have lost count of the number of times I have visited Singapore - lets face it, if you like food, this is the place to be! I have to admit that when I choose a hotel in Singapore, I often let the price decide, because the quality of all of the hotels I have stayed in here has been excellent. I reserved a deluxe room at the Pan Pacific for two nights, paid around 290 Singapore dollars for the experience and have no complaints. I felt looked after from the moment I arrived ( which included an in-room check-in) until I left (a 30-second check-out). The room was comfortable, well-furnished. The position of the hotel itself is great if you want to be in the colonial district; there are several large shopping centres on the doorstep, loads of restaurants and food courts (don't overlook Singaporean foodcourts - they are really excellent and totally spotless). I got what I paid for ...and then some.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d7dd4e11e4324de81db0888ab26c418a" url=""><![CDATA[Singapore Hotels Just keep Getting Better Having spent the summer in Australia, I was due to fly directly back from Brisbane to Norway, but decided at the last minute to stop in Singapore. I have stayed in so many hotels in Singapore over the years that I have lost count! My last stay was at the Oriental and I was more than pleased. This time I booked last minute and there didn't seem to be too much available, but being a memeber of Priority Club, I decided to give the Intercontinental a go. WOW! Just as good as the Oriental, and for my liking, a fine location. The hotel is situated in Bugis, about 5 mintues walk from Raffles Hotel and major shopping centres. Orchard Road is 15 minutes walk in the opposite direction, and the Boat Quay (prepare to be slightly hassled by throwers-in)/ Robertson Quay (nearly finished, impressive, slightly more expensive) restaurant areas took me around 20 minutes to walk to. Singapore is renowned for being conducive to those who like eating and whichever direction you go from the hotel, there is a plethora of diverse eateries.The hotel itself was spick and span, the staff welcoming (I managed to book a room with one bed instead of two beds, but they changed my reservation on the spot within seconds), and the facilities great. The rooms are large (especially if you are used to European hotel rooms!), the furnishings seemed new, the bathrooms large with a good range of cosmetics and a deep soaker tub, and the rooms have flat screen TVs.I'm going back to Singapore in April 2007, and I feel that I am spoiled for choice as far as hotels are concerned, but the Intercontinental is definately worth the price you pay, and I will return!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="95a0479ff5dfec0493f8cd3e03bd85d6" url=""><![CDATA[Good Location and Price for Sydney Sydney is not the cheapest place in the world to stay, especially if you want a property that a reasonably central and clean and comfortable. This hotel is 5 minutes walk from Darling Harbour - cross the road and go around the back of the bar on the other side and from there on it is pedestrians only. The hotel itself is midern, well-equipped and well-run. Clean and comfortable, offering all you need for a stay in the big city. Prices are low if you book in advance and represent good value. I would not hesitate to return.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1a3484cac93f5f239c50843f0055467e" url=""><![CDATA[The Problem with Singapore... ..OK, so it's one of those problems you might prefer to label a luxury problem - and that problem is, where to stay in Singapore if you really appreciate quality. Not because it is hard to find, but because there are so many 5 star hotels in this wonderful city that you may not know where to start. I've recently tried the Oriental and the Intercontinental and now this trip stayed at Raffles the Plaza - just to try something different, as I have no complaints at all about the aforementioned hotels.Raffles the Plaza lived up to all my expectations - and then some. The hotel is in the colonial district of town, leaving you 5 minutes walk to the marina area and 15 minutes to Orchard Road (although it is hot in Singapore and all that bag carrying on the way back from the shops may wear you out....and oh yes, you will be carrying bags because you won't be able to resist the choice and prices...). The rooms are calming; light brown walls, a liberal use of textiles as panelling keeping noise in the room to a minimum (and you won't hear a squeek from your neighbours). I was in the South Tower on the 11th floor; my room had a balcony, a flat-screen TV and a funky bathroom with huge showerhead and toiletries from the spa at the hotel. It goes without saying perhaps that the room was spotlessly clean. Most of Singapore is spottlessly clean. A dream for us clean freaks.The hotel also has a hospitality lounge where you can get a shower before your flight home. A nice touch, particularly when you are so lucky as I was to have a flight at 0100. Breakfast was served in the Stamford Hotel next door which is reached via an inside link. The selection at breakfast was enormous - local specialities, western favourites - you name it.So now I have a problem - and that problem is, which hotel should I stay in next time I go to Singapore. Raffles the Plaza is way up there - one of the big boys in town. I think that it is the price of the stay which will help me make my decision.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ce19dc85b24cfcb225494d6a024bece1" url=""><![CDATA[No Complaints at All I have stayed in Singapore on numerous occasions - never in the same hotel twice though, as the choice of great hotels in the city seems limitless. However, I would most certainly return to the Orientel given a chance, not only because of the excellent standard of accommodation, but also because of the area surrounding it; convenient yet much quieter than Orchard Road. The rooms are faultless and of a good size, the staff accommodating and welcoming.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1a85b4868bfe4bee5771d2922280ebf3" url=""><![CDATA[OK for the price Good location within easy reach of all of Berlin's major sights. However this didn't compensate too much for the step back in time. I lived in Warsaw for a while in the early 1990's and was transported back to my younger days by the interior and smells of this hotel. There was something strange and somewhat surreal about the whole experience. The corridors smelled as if they hadn't been aired - a kind of musty / stagnant water smell. The wide corridors also reminded me of East European public buildings of a bygine era. Once into the room however, the smell and ambience disappeared. This is one of the more standard Holiday Inns I've stayed in, although for a price of 79 Euro in the centre of berlin, I suppose you get what you pay for. I got no recognition as a Platinum Card Holder - the hotel may well have been fully booked or something, but no explanation was forthcoming (I speak fluent German, so it wasn't due to language difficulties).On the plus side; the room was clean and functional. Nothing more, nothing less. No tea/coffee facilities (am I getting to demanding in my old age?), and a minimum amount of towels in the room (or was there just one towel - I forget) but there are plenty of cafes and restaurants in the area, mostly Turkish / Asian, but the ones I tried were good. The hotel is a 5-minute-walk from the train station at Gesundbrunnen from where you can access any part of Berlin. Would I recommend it? If you're looking for a fairly basic, but clean hotel, in what seemed like an OK area of town and can get a good rate, then go for it. If you're expecting anything unusual, extraordinary, spectacular or rememberable, then go elsewhere.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>