<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="e8b37fb058117b2dd7a5298d84ff78fe" url=""><![CDATA[Gorgeous views, but not everything its cracked up to be We booked the hotel based entirely on Tripadvisor reviews, and one recommendation from a friend who stayed there 2 years ago.We stayed for 4 nights from March 1st. We arrived at midday and were checked straight into our room, and having been up since 3am in the UK to fly over we decided to have an hours nap before heading out into the city. This was impossible - our room was directly outside the main lift and we were woken by the lift whining and a maid came into our room. The final straw was some very noisy people holding a conversation outside our door while waiting for a lift. The decor in the room was very shabby - we were given the impression that a facelift was long overdue.To the hotels credit they moved us immediately, and gave us a room on the 40th floor, room 4032. The views of New York from here were incredible, both at sunrise and during the evenings. The decor was less tired than the first room too. Both rooms were very spacious, and the beds were very comfortable. We didn't have any problems with the room temperature as mentioned in previous reviews.Our tower had 3 lifts, though only one was working throughout our stay leading to some quite long waits - about 5 minutes on averageWe didn't eat breakfast in the hotel, choosing to walk to the end of the block to eat in the excellent Johns Cafe. The service here was fast, friendly and helpful - the waitresses were happy to give tips on sights to see and the cheapest ways to get round the city.The hotel staff were very friendly, and couldn't do enough to help. We'd highly recommend a trip to the reflexology section of the fitness club - Rose is a star and really knows how to relieve tired feet that have been walking the streets of NYC!One last word of warning - we didn't have a guest pack in our room so were unaware of the cost of phone calls. As I'd forgotten my mobile we made two 5 min calls back to the UK and would have been charged $60 for this had I not complained.Summary - great views, friendly staff, adequate but not spectacular rooms. Probably about the right value for the price we paid - $229 a night booked on the internet, which was $70 cheaper than I was quoted by the reservations team on the phone...
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>