<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="25e0bf9908903c55019cf746ca3b2f8e" url=""><![CDATA[Will never stay anywhere else but Conrad in Miami comfy bed
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ddc81d132412324b097dc882303fa371" url=""><![CDATA[Overprice for a dump I'm glad I didn't have the reservation for this hotel. I made a reservation for my friend who decided he wanted to come to Winter music Conference in the last minute.I booked this hotel because I couldn't find any other hotel avaiable (winter music conference and sony erricson tournament at the same time in miami). I booked thru hotelclub.com, paid and got a receipt and a confirmation.I did read the bad reviews, but I was just going to have my friend use his room to sleep but hang out with me at the Conrad most of the time.We arrived at 6pm, we got lost because the hotel didn't stand out, and there are so many hotels along that road. And their sign was Ocean Breeze with a paper that's said Bay Breeze taped on the window.There were 2 people working behind the front desk, but apparently 1 guy couldn't even do anything. He just stood there. The other guy was helping the person in front of me. There were only 2 guests (together) in front of me and my friend, but it took the front desk guy 30 minute to help them. And then after that we saw the guests were leaving. I wasn't sure what happened because they were speaking spanish.I asked the guy that was just standing behind the desk doing nothing if he could help us, the other guy yelled at me very rude: Can you please wait?What's the point having 2 people behind the desk if only 1 person can help guests? So after 30 minute wait, it only took the guy 2 minutes to look through his reservation papers (there is an old computer but I think that's just for decoration) and told us that he couldn't find my reservation. I showed him the receipt and confirmation email from hotelclub. He didn't even look at the code, instead he wrote down a fax number and told us to call hotelclub and ask them to fax over a confirmation page. I WAS HOLDING THE CONFIRMATION PAGE!!! I was so mad, we left the hotel. We couldn't call hotelclub because their customer service closed at 5pm. So we couldn't take care of it until the next day.We left the hotel and called intercontinental hotel and luckily they still have rooms available (I would've booked intercontinental if their website didn't show fully booked). So my friend stayed there for 1 night and the rest of the weekend he stayed with me at Conrad.We called hotelclub the next day and the customer service was really helpful. She immediately processed the refund for my friend's credit card. She actually called Bay Breeze hotel to find out what happened and got yelled at by the front desk person that answered the phone. Bay Breeze hotel should be closed!One more thing, the lobby area smells horrible.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24d68ae35c9770637196f9c39d3a05d1" url=""><![CDATA[pleasant stay the room
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b40242419d1a7fb3f35e9c804c8ce37e" url=""><![CDATA[perfect....beautiful villa pool and breakfast area
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>