<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="127d889c3618f4cb3d38238117440b2f" url=""><![CDATA[Blue Hawaii fun in the sun! I had read so many reviews about this property - so many unhappy people saying it wasnt worth it - but I can say all the bad are totally set aside once you sit by the pool and soak in the sun!Same deal as everyone else - wrong room at check in - but we refused what was given and had it amended. Loved our Hilton Honors membership as it got us free breakfast daily which was continental only and although basic could be upgraded to hot meals. Had a high room in the Rainbow Tower building with Diamond Head View which I booked and paid extra in advance to secure. Was worth the $$ as nothing like waking up in the morning and looking out at the beautiful scenery. I would sit out there and read my book while waiting for the rest to wake up. Rooms are tired but are fine and clean. Bathroom could do with a revamp. The services at the hotel are amazing! You dont need to venture far for anything as everything is there. The beach is gorgeous - only hotel with such a large beachfront in Waikiki. There was so much activity for the kids - hula dancing - ukelele lessons - lei making - they had a ball. We bought some sand toys and off they went. Rented paddle cycles which they had fun on in the lagoon. Evening entertainment by the pool every night. Dont feel you need to buy the big Friday night show package. You can see it for free by standing behind the ropes. We bought the seat with the cocktail - but would have been just as happy seeing it from another position. could have also watched the show from our room balcony. Fireworks made it special!The animal life is also amazing. They have penguins!! The village shops are great - lunch by the pool fun - dinners were average. Great bookstore - also a second hand one. Suggest reading something written by a local. There is always something to see or do - or just relax by the pool. Was a much needed rest after a long trip on the mainland. I highly recommend it for some serious RR - especially for families. We will be back!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>