<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="00b5a9c68727c0558213aeed654aef04" url=""><![CDATA[A quality stay at the Affinia Dumont I highly recommend staying here...it's number two on tripadvisor for a reason!As soon as you enter the hotel, you are struck by the relaxed atmosphere and pleasant staff. Nothing is too much trouble and the staff will go that extra mile to ensure that you have a great stay. For example, when we arrived at the hotel we asked for a room with a view, if possible and sure enough we got a fantastic corner suite on the 30th floor that had an amazing panoramic view of the skyline.We got a Junior Suite. It was incredibly spacious. From my past New York experience I was expecting a cupboard but it was impressive in size. The kitchen has a family sized refridgerator, coffee maker, microwave, oven etc...We ate some of our meals and snacks on the sofas in the seating area which had a big coffee table.The bed is huge (King sized and then some!), comfortable and a pillow menu is on hand to guarantee a good night's sleep.The desk area is large and I would imagine great for business visitors although we hardly ever used it except to store stuff on.The TV has all the channels you could want including HBO etc. The only gripe I had was that you couldn't really watch it in bed unless you physically turned it round....The bathroom was okay - probably the least attractive room. The shower had a propensity to go from hot to cold unpredictably and the worst point was that the bath didn't drain properly. However, the Aveda toiletries went some way to make up for that!The hotel also had fitness facilities and a spa. I didn't actually take advantage of these but I imagine that they, like the rest of the hotel, were of a high standard.Next door to the hotel is the Barking Dog restaurant, a neighbourhood place, that serves good standard dishes. We ate there a couple of times and thought it was good value.All in all we enjoyed our stay. Would we stay there again? Definitely.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0ef97ba4de8342e069061e8c316892a6" url=""><![CDATA[Well its okay... I really wanted to title this review W stands for... but couldn't find an appropraite word for average beginning with W....From the time I arrived at this hotel until the time I left I was comfortable. And thats about it.Our taxi drew up and the first thing that strikes you as you walk in is the pleasant smell, and cool, dark atmosphere. Now when I say cool I don't mean it in the Fonz sense. The crowd was ageing businessman. What I mean is the temperature was cool and refreshing.Check in highlighted the first major problem. Parlez anglais? My partner and I are British. We speak clearly, we have no funny accents or colloquialism's yet everytime we approached the front desk we found ourselves repeating everything we said. No where else did we encounter this problem except at this hotel. I can only think that they weren't listening the first time round....needless to say this was tedious and made the checking in process drawn out.Our room was on the seventh floor, just above the pool area. Not a bad location and the sound proofing was good. The room itself had two double beds, a large TV with CD player etc, coffee maker with selection of Tazo teas and W blend coffee, a large desk area and a comfy day bed. Here there were some nice touches; quality dressing gowns, Bliss spa products in the bathroom (and the Maids replenish generously!), a good selection of pillows on the beds and a day bed by the window to relax on.It is all very comfortable and I had no complaints. Ok, so the phone didn't work properly. After a protacted exchange with the front desk, where we had to repeat had to repeat had to repeat what we were asking for, it was fixed within a day.Now for the rest of the hotel...Both of us wanted to check out the gym and were pleasantly surprised. The emphasis here is on cardio. There are about 4 treadmills, all fitted with tv screens, a couple of bikes, crosstrainers and a selection of free weights, yoga mats and ab balls. Jet lag meant that we were down there at 5am. It seemed to get busy at 6am so time your visit carefully.Bliss is adjacent to the gym (both on the fourth floor). Now I am not a big Bliss fan but I did try and find out if they had any massage appointments available and they didn't. If you feel like spending $120 on a facial then make sure you book ahead. We didn't eat in the hotel for dinner but we did have breakfast in the XYZ (gettit?) restaurant one morning. I was thoroughly underwhelmed. Ordered cappuccino which came in a cup that I can only describe as Dolly sized. The fruit salad was okay but anyone can chop up melon, drizze Vanilla yoplait over the top and charge $13+ can't they? Mentally decided never to bother with that again....as an aside they have a less format buffet just outside XYZ and this looked better. Muffins, cereals, bagels and a barista are on hand to deliver a quick breakfast.The hotel is located in a decent area. They are lots of casual dining options nearby, you can walk to Union Square in less than ten minutes and it feels safe round there. Plus art lovers will love the fact that Moma is next door.Now to the rating. The W is a good hotel - but its not great. It charges high prices and bills itself as a cool hotel. But the fact is, it just misses the mark. I feel that it was probably at the top of its game 5 years ago. Now the convention crowd have moved in and the coolness quotient has moved on.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>