<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="dd0fe87ef60e1df3184573bd40f819cd" url=""><![CDATA[Great Service, Value, Location, Great Hotel My fiance and I stayed there one night over the weekend. We have nothing but praise for the hotel. The employees go out of their way to help their guests. We got in at about 11 am and asked if we could have them store our bags until the 4 pm check in time. Instead, they let us check in early. We put our bags in our room (14th floor) and we went spent the rest of the day Christmas shopping and playing tourist. The concierge was very helpful when it came time to recommeding restaraunts.The hotel's location is great. As my fiance put it, we could have paid at least $200 more in a hotel right on Times Square, or stayed here and put that money towards a show; which we did. The hotel is only about a 5 minute walk from Times Square. There is also a subway station about two blocks away from the hotel. During the Christmas season, it is easier to get around Manhattan by subway than it is by taxi. The room was clean and modern. It had a refrigerator, microwave, coffee maker and two tvs. The closets could have been a little bigger and we could see where someone might have a problem storing clothes if they were staying there for an extended period of time.The elevators were a little slow, as some of the other reviews have mentioned. One trick is to go to the east or west end of the main corridor and use those elevators.For breakfast we walked around the corner and grabbed some bagels from the local deli. There are a lot of restaraunts in the blocks around the hotel,(including the omnipresent Starbucks) One thing that we did hear were sirens from fire trucks, ambluances, police cars, etc. The hotel is situated between two major north south streets in New York. What makes the location convienent for the guests also makes it covienient for the Emergency Services to travel from one part of the city to another, especially with a fire station nearby. However we did not hear any sirens after midnight.Would we stay here again, definitely. As we were leaving, one of the bellmen wished us a Merry Christmas and said that he hoped that he would see us next year. We told him we could not wait to come back.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>