<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="881187617e5cb15737d5a27d4bdef92d" url=""><![CDATA[Pros and Cons We stayed at the Hotel Milano in Feb. 2007 - 1 night pre-cruise and 1 night post-cruise. The main advantage of the hotel, in my opinion, was its location. It was great to be within walking distance of so many of the sights in Old San Juan. Also, there is a free bus to El Morro, which we took advantage of while there. The hotel is also within a few blocks of 2 of the main cruise piers. Unfortunately, our ship departed from the third! However, it was a short taxi drive, and not a problem.We booked a room in the front of the hotel, as we had read that the rear rooms were smaller and some lacked windows that could be opened, which sounded a little claustrophobic to me. The room itself was quite adequate and clean, though a bit small, as we expected in an older hotel such as this. Our main problem was the noise from the street, which continued until 4AM both nights we stayed. Part of this was our own fault, as we left the windows open. However, the air-conditioner was just 'On or off' - with it off, the room was very hot, but with it on it was frigid - so we opted to leave it off. It may have helped with the noise to have the unit turned on, but I'm not sure we had enough blankets for that!The restaurant on the roof was very nice, although the views are not as scenic as the photos, as there is a lot of construction in the area. The food was good, and so was the service - so it was enjoyable. However, the complimentary morning breakfast was very minimal - beverages, packaged donuts, and boxed cereals. It was a start to the day, though - and we found several nice restauarants nearby for a more substantial meal.I would probably not stay here again, but I would recommend it to anyone wanting a reasonably priced comfortable room in Old San Juan. The staff is friendly and helpful, and it's a great location as a base for sightseeing.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>