<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="354e1dc3c87efd569872a7cb5606fec2" url=""><![CDATA[Good basic hotel, central location We stayed one night at the Citypark Pelayo in July 2006. Overall, the experience was positive. Positives:+ easy access from/to the airport+ close to Placa de Catalunya+ price was ok (around 93 euros through Destinia incl. breakfast)+ beautiful building+ quite spacious bathroom+ efficient air conditioningNegatives: - the room itself very smallI would recommend this hotel to anyone looking for basic, clean and modern accommodation in the heart of Barcelona. I would try to get a corner room in the tower, it could be nice.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fd45728f40b43e14e90b0f292f6596c9" url=""><![CDATA[Very cool and stylish We spent one night of our 5-day stay in Barcelona at B-Hotel. I made my booking based on the reviews here and was very pleased. I had quite a good deal through Hotelclub (113 euros incl. breakfast). Positive sides: + modern design, spacious room+ nice bathroom and toiletries+ varied breakfast+ location: first I was a bit sceptical about the location (Placa d'Espanya) - thought it would be too far from Placa de Catalunya. But it's just a few metro stops away, and it's also at walking distance from Poble Espanyol. Also close to Eixample and its nice restaurants. I prefer this location to Ramblas, which seems too crowded and touristy. + no traffic noise as the room faced a shaft (which on the other hand meant that we had no view)+ easy access to airport with busNegative sides:- some noise from the corridorThe lighting system was not as difficult as I had expected, and as a tip: the blinds in the bathroom can be shut and opened from two buttons situated above the wash basin (if I remember correctly).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2a01180e1049616d2463f9b2504910d2" url=""><![CDATA[Grand Marina - the best so far I stayed at the Grand Marina with my husband who was there for business for a couple of days. Overall, the experience was really great!Positive sides: + beautifully furnished, modern, spacious room (even though it was a standard room)+ the view towards the city+ big bathroom with separate shower and bathtub+ wonderful and varied breakfast (especially the iberico and fresh fruit were great)+ good sound isolationNegative sides: difficult to find anything major, but some small things: - the jacuzzi did not work, but we didn't bother to contact the reception- the roof top swimming pool is small- on mornings the ferries make some noise- this hotel is maybe more of a conference hotel, but it's suitable for tourists as wellThis was my first 5-star experience, and I enjoyed it very much. =)
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>