<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="09724d041c940433070d2d20be092a70" url=""><![CDATA[The best views in the Bay Area. We stayed here because of the height of the hotel and the views we would get. The hotel is on a busy street and as it is in the top half a skyscraper it doesn't have a pulling in area to unload, but the vallet was helpfull and took our car for parking. Check in was easy and the lobby was nice, but not spectacular. The suite was lovely. A seating area, a double bed, plasma screen, large bathroom with tub and shower. Three huge windows with views from the Golden Gate to the Bay. They brought us free tea to drink in the suite on arrival. The concieage reccomened the best eating areas for dinner and provided us with a free Mercedes S Class limo to ferry us around town. He dropped us off at the restaurant and picked us up later. Nice touch. The next morning the conciage suggested a nice place to get Sunday Brunch, and it was great. Very helpfull people. When we checked out after a two night stay we left our un stamped post cards in the room. I called the hotel and they put stamps on an mailed them Free. I thought this was a nice gesture. Overall San Fran has many nice hotels, but I can't think of a simple one that is both Five Star and has these views. It is expensive, but deals are to be had. Or you could book a standard room and ask for a free upgrade, maybe slip the front desk staff a $20 bill, and see what happens. Usually works for us.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="85630f56b6a125a6ec1ada8fbf457fe7" url=""><![CDATA[A good hotel but no wow factor. Was in Amsterdam for one night with friends. The Marriott had the best price on expedia for a 'five' star. I would classify it four star. Located in central Amsterdam we found the hotel easily, although the lack of a porte coche with a valet was confusing. Eventually somebody took our car from us and we were able to check in. The lobby was small and had no large centre attraction that I like in a hotel. The staff were friendly. The corridors upstairs were confusing and of okay decor. The room was nice, no view but two large beds and a small but clean and elegant bathroom. The TV was pay per view only. Rip off. The concieage was helpfull. I got the impression they get alot of trouble at the hotel. Not long after checking in a man knocked at the door asking if we were using drugs, as the stench of weed on the landing was massive. We were not, but I did think 'when in Rome!'. Also you need a room key to get in the elevator, probably to stop the outcall business that is so popular in this city. We didn't eat in the hotel as the American Hotel over the road had a spectacular dining room, that was much nicer than the Marriot. As it was Xmas it was decorated and felt very festive. As good a place as any to stay, so long as the price is right. From what I saw of the American Hotel I would try and stay there next time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>