<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="469fc00c15554204aefcd581cf618d6a" url=""><![CDATA[A True Gem When I was planning our first Bali trip, I listened to my Indonesian friends and changed my reservation from Nusa Dua to Ubud and Jimbaran. What a pleasant surprise Maya Ubud was!Arriving at the hotel was a trip itself - Ubud is inland and far from the touristy areas of Kuta, Legian, etc, so arriving at night and going to Ubud means you get a taste of the local life - limited traffic, locals sitting out in the streets eating, chatting. Serveral roads had few street lamps and our taxi drivers even got lost when a religious procession blocked the main road, so we meandered through some rice fields, and finally arrived at our resort. It is set outside of the town of Ubud high on a hill between rice fields and river valley, completed with its own nature walk.There were many things we were impressed, so I must start slow - first - the whole property is designed with one word - Care. It is reflected in the infinity edge pools that overlook flowing river below, the affordable flower baths in room, the western and japanese breakfast buffet that is included in the room and virtually two buffet in one, the ever caring staff - just such a sweet and neat place. What a great first impression to bali! We enjoyed this place way more than the big Intercontinental in Jimbaran.The experience starts with the great breakfast the first thing in the day - although we almost missed half of it - the Japanese, or the Western portion is hidden behind a wall depends on where you were seated. They have all the juices you can think of in Bali - orange, mango, apple, Papaya, guava, even banana, They also given you Champagne for free to blend with the dazzling variety of juices to make your own mimosa mango mambo maga-sa-s that you want.Then, take the free hourly hotel shuttle and head to the Ubud palace and market. One word of caution. the shuttle will pick you up but usually at 15 after the hour, even though the printed hour is 20. Spend the afternoon at the nature walk down the slope, and then swim in the infinity edge pool that looks down to the river valley. You can also have the hotel car take you to a local Ubud spa for a cheap massage and scrub.At night, use the $12 well and make use of the in-room milk and flower bath all set up in your own room to relax and warm up. This feature is not availalble in the bigger resorts in Jimbaran and Nusa Dua, and if available, no less than $25 a pop i hear.HIring a car from an Ubud hotel is cheaper than the south island options. For the same 8 hour day, we paid about $75 USD and our friends in Jimbaran paid $150; Sure they had a Mercedes, but for the 35 MPH bumpy roads around the island, an airconditioned comfy roomy Toyota will do the same job. Our driver from Maya Ubud is Dewa Taman and he is so polite and sweet, and knowledgeable and told us everything from meaning of the dances to the time of the offerings to the volcano eruption stories. It was simply wonderful. The fleet of staff is ever-smiling and sweet, and genuinely interested in their guests' welfares, from exchanges to designing daily tour routes, they are caring, enthusiastic and real (unlike the Jimbaran smiles that disappears way too fast sometimes). The hotel bar was excellent, try the drink called Bodyheat, local drink with pinapple juice, or One for Two, the honeymooner's version of local twist on Cranberry Vodka. Afternoon tea is always free and everyone gets tea, coffee and three pieces of well-made dessert, usually a western style cake, a Japanese dessert, and somethng fresh. On the day we went the hazelnut cake of the day was excellent and melts on your tongue, and we had a really soft mochi ball and some fresh fruits. Overall, we loved this place and my husband said i could stay here a few more days! LOL. We honestly loved everything about this hotel. A recommended place for anyone visiting Bali and want to stay in Ubud for a day or two in order to order the art-central of Bali and the northern volcano and lake, and rice fields.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1e6de9809072c10006159a5c56128a04" url=""><![CDATA[Too Big and Buggy To Be Personal Intercontinental Bali, or what the local drivers fondly refer as The InterCon is no doubt a superb luxury property with lush setting and prime location, however, since the review is based on the experience upon the hotel's established rating, I must say the experience is so so for a 5 star hotel.I will state the bad experiences first, then the good, then my personal statement for our anniversary stay. Being a travel agent with a IATAN card, we also had our fairshares of experience at other 5 star hotels around the world (Fairmonts, Ritz, Four Seasons, etc).First, the checkin encounters were a real turn-off- When we checked in, they could not find our reservations till we produced our reservation document with Travelocity, then we were refered to a different desk, where a lady went to a telephone and spoke for quite a long time holding our Travelocity reservation papers, which I suppose they were checking with Travelocity's hotline. Then we were told (quite seamlessly) that as first time visitors to InterCon Bali, we were automatically upgraded to the Club Room (which I am pretty sure by now they lost our reservation - i booked the cheapest room on sale, and was upgraded to the highest tier room due to first time visit? Never happens to oany other first visit, nice gesture though. ) However, my gratitude lasted as long as the moment where she kindly forbid us to visit the Club Lounge, Club Pool and Club Breakfast. TWICE, as if we were sneaking kids. Then, the next day, the removed the Club Red Carpet from our door (working in the travel industry this seems like an old school service trick), and viola, we are no longer getting daily grapes, crackers and fresh fruits while they are still going to our REAL CLUB neighbors. So this whole pretentious sorry we lost your reservation so we lie about upgrade you to royalty then constantly reminded your of your real status thing, a real disappointment. I rather just have any room, thank you very much.The BAD:Top of the list, bugs. Lush setting and fish pool et all is great, ponds near guest rooms - bad idea. We stayed in the Club room, the highest tier of the rooms, and over our first night, doors and windows tightly closed and aircon on cold, we killed 5 mosquitoes within 3 hours. No wonder a bottle of RAID comes in handy in every room and a nice fine-paper note reminding guests to close the doors tightly after 5:30PM. We sprayed the room every night after that waking up with 3 itchy unsightly bites each. Well, the smell of RAID really countered any soothing effect of the nice AVEDA toiletry items.Then, like a second plague there comes the flies. We visited the lovely buffet, which was really great with so many items, but we soon realized that at least one person should guard the food and drinks at the table at all times as flies are constantly visiting all guests at the Breakfast restaurant room - inside too because the door of the restaurant constantly opens to the outside for the guests dining on the beautiful porches. We didn't know this at first and returned to our table only to find two flies crawling over our first plates and coffee cups, which to our dismay, we had to waste the food and resorted to only eating one plate at a time for the rest of our stay.Bugs aside, another bad experience was with the Beach. At higher tide in the afternoon the experience is fine, but in the morning, the portion of the beach immediately in front of the hotel is riddled with trash, I boogie boarded onto a plastic bag and then a flattened drink box, and then a couple balls of tangled sea weeds with plastic debris in the first two minutes. As I packed up to leave, the lifeguard (who was very polite and nice btw) told me that the beach off to the side of the hotel is cleaner - he was right and I ended up walking off to the side, and stayed another hour, minimizing my additional trash encounter to maybe three of four and enjoyed the beach then- thanks to the lifeguard.Like the stereotypical tropical celebrating couples, we like resorty drinks and had many good ones else where in Bali, but we simply could not find one good tropical drink - sweet and just right at the pool bar -- Our two selections of featured menu drinks were out of ingrdients (bars out of 3 of 5 ingridents on a not busy day? No white rum? Instead we were offered strong mixed drinks that tasted bitter and at least 4 shots in each drink for a few days - We are younger couples barely 30 and could hold our drinks, but getting drunk is something we planned to do in Kuta, not in the hotel pool swimming intoxicated with swimming infants around. How about more honeymoon like, sweety-weakie drinks? Also smoking of cigarettes and cigars are allowed around the pool while little kids are running by, just a note.Lastly, no irons or iron board in room, and if you special request one, you get an old iron, a small board, and for only two hours. As a result the first two hours i spent in heavenly bali was ironing clothes, then returned to the first service staff who came back to collect them, then got two more staff coming to collect the same items which was returned in the next hour. Iron really was a precious commodity at this hotel!The Good: The food was great, price is about $25 for buffet breakfast which has just about everything you want (Japanese guard stew! Balinese Curry! Noodle soup bar! Made to order omelettes and pancakes and waffles!) , or you can get a great deal for $15 for one of the breakfast sets in-room, which the polite staff set up oh-so-patiently and maticulously. In room Dinner items are typically $15-20, cheaper than its US or Europe counter parts.The service is excellent by any standard, twice-a-day checks (regular housekeeping and 8:30 night run) Ever smiling friendly staff, items always replenished with the slightest use - Although tipping is discouraged since all balinese hotels include a 10% service fee already, but we just always had to tip for the service was always so fast and attentive.The pool itself is vast and the swim-to-bar feature is cute, pool is perfectly-heated - never a cold moment!One side observation from a dumb tourist, but i enjoy seeing the locals celebrate their culture even in a hotel, fresh hibiscus flowers were offered to the big and small statues throughout the hotel just like we've seen in farm houses and endless puras (temples) in Ubud and the south. Location is excellent on Jimbaran beach, walking distance to the south warung center (beachside seafood dinner centers with many little restaurants) (just to the left of the hotel), and a sunset that delivers on the Jimbaran promise.Overall, there were shining moments and good qualities, but the bug factor makes this grand resort seem cheap.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>