<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="278e3fe45838bc13ef735c9a9354c58d" url=""><![CDATA[Not up to Sheraton standard We stayed in this hotel for two nights in July 2007 and were very disappointed with the lack of professionalism of the staff, both at checkin and the restaurant/b'fast area. B'fast buffet was okay but dirty dishes were left on the table for unacceptable amount of time as staff wandered past and kept going without picking anything up. The room was okay, bed comfortable. Bathroom was clean. The lounge bar was very expensive. We did not think the hotel was up to Sheraton standards and found it very overpriced for what we got. Very hard to find at the airport terminal with virtually no signage to point the way. We would think twice before booking in there again. Airport is easy access via train from the city and would probably look there first for better value.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dbb794db732cdcd4f18ebda3a616cadf" url=""><![CDATA[Great but uncomfortable room We stayed at the Swissotel in July t2007 for four nights and were very pleased with the cleanliness of the rooms but disappointed in the smallish queen bed. Aircon was intermittent between no air at all and then full blast. Asked for, and received, a blanket because the one doonah was far too heavy for that time of the year and lack of decent aircon. Staff were very pleasant and polite except for the bar where we had to, at one stage, wait 25 minutes for a glass of beer even though we were the only ones in the lounge at the time. Expensive, too. B'fast is fabulous. Starched white tablecloths and napkins, huge variety of quality food - and, yes, FRESHLY squeezed orange juice - not the tinned variety. Restaurant staff very very helpful and quick to remove dirty dishes. All in all would stay there again but would ask for either a room upgrade to a larger bed or twin, and would be more forthcoming re the aircon problem.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>