<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="c910bdd2ad66a03424ffb6f228c93f2e" url=""><![CDATA[We loved the Majestic I spend one week for my honeymoon at the majestic and it was incredible. My wife and I got married in Dec 15, 2007 and flew to Punta cana the 16th. When the shuttle we had schedule took us there we had to see different hotels of the people we were letting off and let me tell you just the receiving in the majestic is different. They have a cold towel waiting for you, they have a fruit punch or something so you feel welcome. If you have a Premium room, you make the check in in a special place of the lobby, if not the line that bad.We stayed at the Colonial Suite (I think the name) and it was awesome. We had a huge living room with tv, sofa, loveseat, a small table, fridge and it was really nice for romantic nights out of the actual master room. From there we had to sliding doors, one to the private, Jacuzzi roof top balcony, and another for the double size traditional balcony. This balcony also connect to the master room. Obviously, it had a King bed, but we had a whirlpool for two waiting with roses an bubbles on it, plus a champagne bottle. The bathroom was incredible too.The food the best I have had in my life but it was a lot, and different variety so you can choose. The pool was amazing, it was so big, we never felt claustrophobic feelings.The only problem occurred because one day they decided to replace some furniture in the room, and we had to stay out of the room for a couple of hours. After a while I thought it was to much time, so I went to the front desk and in half an hour they were out of our room. But to our surprise there were fruits and Champagne waiting for us in the room. The other weird thing is there is no way of locking employees out of the room. There is no old time lock that can only be opened from the inside. So if you are doing something private in your room of in the private balcony I will suggest that you hang a sign in the door or at least close the door between the living room and were you are.They have an animation team that was pretty cool, but we were more in a romantic mood. So every night they have live music outside with bands of jazz, merengue, oldies, and others. We appreciate this a lot because we could dance romantically. My last comment, if you want to have fun and be in a party hotel, this is not the one for you. But if you want a romantic getaway this one is perfect. We are going back for the first anniversary in December.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>