<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="0f02db0ff4ef88ce55f7c0b1d1148594" url=""><![CDATA[Great Beach but.......awful resort Well, to say I was dissapointed would be a drastic understatement. Please, please, please read this review and then decide if you want to spend your hard earned money, a week of vacation time which you look forward too and realise that you cant get back that time or money.First lets put my review into perspective. I'm ex-military, and used to roughing it. I've stayed in hotels in Eastern and Central Europe. I've been to Hawii, Bahamas (x2), Croatia, Hungary, Greece, Bulgaria, Malta, France, Germany and countless other places. I consider myself easy going, and extremely easy to please. Give me some sun, some sand and a decent nights sleep and I'm happy. But this resort is EASILY the worst place I have ever stayed in. Yes the beach is nice, and yes the pool is nice (a little dirty, but still nice). But please read on...1. Our Room. We checked into a bottom floor room (Room 2107) late at night after a long flight. Immediatly we were overwhelmed by a horrible moldy rotten smell. i do realise that we are in the tropics and we could be subject to damp smells due to high humidity etc, but our room was just plain filthy. The phone didint work, so we couldnt phone out to our travel agent. The phone smelt of dirty BO on the receiver. The bathroom caulking around the tub, and toilet, was black with mold. The sheets smelled as if they hadnt been changed in weeks. (Pillows had that dirty hair smell). Mold around the walls, cracked ceiling, dirty fixtures, tub faucet hanging off the wall. Other problems to numerous to mention.I went straight away to change our room and after lining up at the front desk was told not possible (Bear in mind we had booked the new SUNQUEST SELECT section which we had been told was open, but wasnt). come back in morning. So sure enough i went back in the morning and waited and waited for help on another room. when I talked to the supervisor, i had a smile on my face and an agreeable attitiude, as I felt that rudeness wouldnt get me anywhere. His answer.. Not possible, come back in the evening So back again i went in the evening, only to be put off again. That night my wife was sick with the mold, my 6 year old couldnt sleep, and still our phone hadnt been replaced. the next morning after a very firm talk with the supervisor, he threw a key to a new room at me and turned and walked away. The new room was on the second floor and a little better. Here we stayed for the rest of the trip. 2. FOOD. There are 2 buffets. one is in the main area by the beach, and 1 is in the new select area. The one in the main area, reminded me of the Vegas Vacation buffet ( give me some more of the yeller) the other one was much better. and served all kinds of not bad food. But since they rinse the veg and fruit with the same water that you cant drink, you do spend more time on the toilet than you normally do. The al acartes. Book as soon as you can (first day there) or they will be booked up. They ranged from terrible (the grill) which took over 2 hours to get served, to good. (The Dominican, La Tiana). The waiters seem to forget what you were drinking, so you end up getting your drinks yourself. (Often we would order 2 cokes and a beer, and the waiter would come back after being gone for 1/2 hour with one beer. So if you made the mistake of repeating your order to him, then you may end up not having anything to drink at all.The snack place at the beach served the same burgers etc all day3. BEACH and POOL The Beach and Pool are both very nice. And if you get up at 6 and reserve a nice spot under an umbrella, it makes for a great day. OVERALL. The clientle seemed to be mainly French from France and some from Quebec. I meet some really great people from Montreal, but other young guys from Quebec in our cell block seemed intent on yelling and screaming obsenities at the top of their lungs every night at 3. Management didnt do anything until physical violence was threatend by some hotel guests. The service ranged from very nice in some of the restuarants, and in the swim up bar at the club, to absolutly awful at the front desk, and in the little gift shop. At the front desk, they were rude, ill mannered and not helpful at all. They tried to charge me an extra $20.00 for using the phone (for connection charges). I say tried, because I pointed out to them that the words NO CONNECTION CHARGES were printed very clearly on all the phones.When we went to check out, they had recieved a fax from our airline at 06:35 that morning, notifying us of a delay of our flight by about 12 hours. They didnt tell us about that until 8 that night. so we were stuck in the lobby from 1:00 pm after room check out until after 8 that evening. It wasnt until one of our group complained bitterly to the staff, that they got 2 rooms for about 18 people to share so that the kids could get some sleep. Bottom line...Take heed of what you read about this resort. I read all the reviews, but had the opinion that reviews are very subjective and varied as the people writing them, so I thought I would be safe in the new area. Please believe me when I say that all the bad reviews written about this resort are very accurate, and you could end up throwing away your money and time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>