<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a46d105bed3f874d84dee83cb8a507b2" url=""><![CDATA[Lovely Beach, Lousy Food My family and I (4 of us) went to the Riu Palace Punta Cana the week of May 13 - 20. Overall I can say we had a good time at this resort, but if we were to compare it to other resorts we have stayed at either in Mexico and Domincan Republic, this resort would be in the bottom.Check-in - Went by really quick. We had an early flight and they actually gave us our rooms early. It was very organized unlike other resorts we have previously stayed at and before you knew it, we were in our room after a long day of traveling. Pool - It was very tiny and crowded at times, especially around the pool bar area. Although, they did have nice little jacuzzi sections that you were able to go to and relax at. There were plenty of lounge chairs spread across the pool area, but you have to get there early to get a shaded spot.Beach - The beach was lovely. Gold sand and crystal blue water. The waves were good and everything about the beach I loved. I always found somewhere to lay at (most of the time being in the sun). Weather - Amazing! I guess it was a great time of year to go. It only rained twice and that was at night time. I got a bunch of sun and when I came back, I was very tan.Grounds - The resort was beautiful. It was luxurious and felt very ritzy when you first enter the palace'. If you go they're, you will know what I am talking about. The grounds were kept clean at all times.Rooms - Very cozy. I didn't like the fact that they had a firm beds, but got used to it. They have a liquor dispenser and mini bar in the room that they keep stocked if you want to have a few drinks when you go out or get back from a busy day. The maid kept our rooms nice and clean; overall she did an amazing job cleaning up the rooms and there was no complaints.Entertainment/Nightlife - Terrible! The only good show was a Michael Jackson show they had and that is probably because the person that was impersonating Michael Jackson didn't work full-time at the resort. There was a lady entertainer named America they had (part of the entertainment staff) that had absolutely no clue what she was doing the whole entire time. When they would dance up on stage, she didn't even know what to do. The only good part about the entertainment were the icebreaker/audience participation shows they had. The dance club they had there was not that fun (spent five minutes there). Casino - Not that much fun, very small. It felt like they stole all of my money each time I played and I only played on slot machines.Drinks - Very good. I would reccomend a Bahama Mama; very tasty. If there is not enough liquor in your drink, I would reccomend just asking the bartender for more.Food - Terrible, terrible, terrible. Same selection at the buffet each night i t seemed like. The Italian Restaurant was just beyond disgusting and the service was horrific. The steak house was pretty good; had a good ribeye there as well as the brazilian restaurant. ---- I would recommend those two restaurants. We tried several times to eat at the Gourmet restaurant, but each time we tried to get a reservation, they only had 9 PM available. Who eats at 9 PM? The food made some of my family members sick, I on the other hand was fine the whole time (thank God). Sports bar - About the only nightlife they have at this particular resort. There are some slot machines in there and the staff is very polite. Orlando (the bartender at night) was awesome. He knew what my brother and I wanted everytime we sat at the bar and did a great job. It is open 24 hours, so if you want a late night snack, they have hotdogs, nachos and cheese, etc. for you to eat.Overall, I did have a decent time at this resort. I don't think I will go back to it, but it was nice to just get away and relax. I just wish the food and entertainment could of been a bit better. Hope I helped out in some way to some of you and if you go to this resort, I hope you have a great time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>