<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="f46c1d04d6c88fad460dbf70a078524c" url=""><![CDATA[Good - But Not Great Have just returned from a week's vacation at the Majestic and while it was enjoyable, I honestly cannot say that there was anything special or unusual about the resort. I have stayed in Punta Cana many times and always at 4 1/2 to 5 star resorts. The best resort I've stayed at was the Paradissus, which you would expect considering the price. However I have paid less at other resorts along the strip and found them just as good and better than the Majestic. I am not sure why there is so much hype about this resort. It does not have the best stretch of beach, in fact there are rocks (many) in the water to the left of the resort, so if you want to swim you must move over to the left. I have never seen rocks anywhere before on Bavaro Beach. Most of the restaurants are just ok, the asian one is the best. The buffet definitely leaves a lot to be desired - food wise and atmosphere. The beach restuarant is positively awful - cannot even serve hot french fries - I just got tired of eating pasta every day. The rooms are large - furniture not particularly nice, kind of cheap looking and for the length of time this resort has been operating the covers on the bed and furniture are terribly shabby. There were large stains on the furniture in my room. Also the bathroom setup up would not suit most people - too open - who needs to hear your partner in the bathroom! The shows are pretty awful, the only good one was the Michael Jackson show, the rest of the shows were just awful and I am not hard to please. On the positive side, the pool is lovely and the service is good. You would not starve at this resort, of course you can always find something to eat and you can have fun in the pool and on the beach - but for the extra money they charge it is simply not worth it. This resort is just an average four star, but that's just my opinion.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2d02fa50baf048427e6fa90b7e2d76d8" url=""><![CDATA[Not a four and a half star!! We stayed at the Palladium with two friends for two weeks in January. It was our third trip to the Dominican Republic but definitely not our favourite. First of all, when you take Air Transat from Manitoba you do not take off until late afternoon (which we found out after we booked). That means you get into your resort in the early hours of the morning and believe me, that is not good. We had made three requests for our rooms to be together, at least in the same building. They were not even in the same building. The next morning took a lot of perserverence with the front desk people to try and get our rooms changed. They promised us rooms in the same building two days after we arrive - so we lived out of our suitcased until then. After we got our new rooms, we discovered my friend's room had a horrible sewer smell, I mean really bad despite spraying it daily with a spray she got from housekeeping. Forget trying to get another room. It never got any better and anyone just walking into that room could smell how bad it was and nothing was done about it. I thought the rooms (Jr Suites) were very shabby, the beds lumpy and uncomfortable. The bathrooms were very large but made little sense. There were no fans in the bathroom, but there were two very large windows with blinds over them and a window that opened inwards. In other words, if you wanted the window open, you had to leave the blind up and then everyone from every angle could see right into the bathroom!! Also there was a huge hole in the corner of the hot tub and you could see right down into the ground. I put a wet towel over it every night just in case anything nasty crawled up. We never found a towel folded nicely, like a swan or anything or any flowers left which we experienced at other resorts, even 3 1/2 star resorts make more effort. Of course we left tips, but it makes no difference, they simply don't go in for nice touches at this place. The service was usually poor, especially the a la carte restaurants, which we found to be terrible. The food in the buffets was very good with lots of variety, we have no complaints about that. However at one of the a la carte restaurants, they wanted $32 us for lobster!! (each) Last year we stayed at the Iberostar and they had a lobster night every week - no extra cost. Also the service was so much better, they could not do enough for us. We should have gone back there and I am sure we will in the future. The Iberostar is rated a 4 star and the Palladium is rated a 4 1/2 star. Don't believe it. The Iberostar will cost you more, but is worth every penny, the Palladium is a 3 1/2 at best. We would not recommend it, there are too many other superior places for the same price.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>