<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="30a35e925318284c19c95ff624cf58e9" url=""><![CDATA[Loved this hotel Our family of 4 stayed here for 9 nights and loved the hotel. We had booked partial view with the possibility of being upgraded to ocean view because of 50+, depending upon availability. We were upgraded on the second day to an ocean view on the 23rd floor. The balcony was much bigger and the view was absolutely awesome. We had a great view of the ocean and the pool. This room was much smaller than the first room and we were rather cramped with 4 of us, but the view made it worth the difference. The rooms were lovely and had obviously been refurbished recently. The whole property was very clean and well maintained. We had no problem with the elevators. They were fast and our card worked every time.The kids loved the large plasma TV for down times. You could hook up to internet in the room for an additional cost, but if you have wireless, you just take your lap top down to the pool deck and use it for free. The only wireless hot spot is on the pool deck. Our favourite restaurants were the 2 at the hotel, Tiki's and Wolfgang Puck's. The meals were delicious and quite reasonable in price. The service was fast as well. All the staff at the hotel was very friendly and accomodating. If you called for housekeeping or bell service, they were there immediately.The cooler bag breakfast was great and we could always pack enough for lunch and put it in the fridge in our room. Having to buy only one meal a day really was a saving. We tried Cheeseburger in Paradise, but were not impressed. Also, avoid Planet Hollywood. That was the worst meal we had. We had the early bird special at Chuck's Steakhouse at the Outrigger and it was very good. We did the 2 for 1 luau that comes with the package and the show was excellent. Be sure to go early to get a good seat. When the hotel advertises that kids stay and eat free, it is a bit of a misnomer. The kids eat free at 2 or 3 restaurants that are not at all close to the hotel. They do not eat free at the hotel restaurants. However, with free breakfast and lunch for everyone, this was not a real concern. The kids loved the International Marketplace and we visited it several times. It is about a 10 minute walk. They also loved the beach because there were always waves to ride. Take water shoes, because there are some stones and rocks in the ocean. We loved this hotel and we would go back in a minute!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>