<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="ecd3861838d910c2519ef5dbe599271f" url=""><![CDATA[Great location and view but noisy We just returned from a Hawaii trip - this was one of three properties that we stayed at. It could be a good location as long as you have the right expectations - which I didn't ! We had a room on the 20th floor in the tower. The room was updated and nicely appointed. The bed, as all Westins, is super comfortable. The view was astounding - we watched the full moon rise over the mountainscape and the city lights below. It really is spectacular. The downside that led to our early check-out was the noise. Everyone told me Waikiki is busy, but I had NO idea. You are smack in the middle of the beach action - if this is what you like, then this is a great location. If you want a quiet beach escape, this is not the spot for you! The noise of the city seemed to bounce off the concrete buildings and it was like having a helicopter hoovering outside your room. The hotel staff offered us another room, and was very considerate, but we decided it was just not the place for us so we moved to the Kahala (FABULOUS). The Surfrider has a great entertainer in the Banyan Bar - the staff was very welcoming. Plan early if you need your car from valet parking - it took 30 minutes !
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="55a9b75cf7bf71f939a7c902b95fc8ac" url=""><![CDATA[Solid - but #1 ? We recently spent 3 nights at the Sofitel in NYC and had a very enjoyable time. It is a great location and an oasis of calm in the midst of the bustling city. My only compalint....sorry...is that the beds here were not quite up to par with the Sofitel in SFO where I stay a couple weeks per year. I'm a comfortable bed fanatic and these mattresses have seen better days. The linens are great. I loved the bathrooms. Huge for NY. Everything else was fantastic. Is this the #1 hotel in NYC ? Guess it depends on your budget. We had one meal in the restaurant and were not impressed. The SFO Bay Sofitel has a little restaurant where you can buy the BEST pastries made in America. We wished that the NY location would have this, too.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b904e3b8df2e4d68d68818a244828152" url=""><![CDATA[Heaven on Earth We left the Moana Surfrider after a crazy, noisy night to arrive at the fabulous Kahala for a restful, fabulous stay! We have stayed for years at the Hapuna Prince on Hawaii, but the Kahala will be our new Hawaii getaway. Where to start at this perfect spot? Our ocean front room on the 7th floor offered a beautiful view of this coast and the property. You'll sink into a deep sleep after relaxing to the sound of the in -room CD featuring Hawaiian slack key music. The deep pillow top mattress guarantees a great night sleep. The room furnishings are a nice mix of contemporary style with classic island architecture. Great in-room coffee, cozy robes - they have every detail covered. The dolphin experience was incredible and even if you don't do it, you'll pass hours just watching these amazing creatures. The pool is on the small side and a bit over-heated - not a bad problem, eh? Loved the cushioned pool and beach chairs - no signing in for towels as if you'll be charged if you don't bring them back - a nice touch of respect compared to other beach resorts. The service at this hotel is impeccable. No one ever says no. We loved at the contrast between this property and Paris where the favorite saying seems to be this is not possible. Great concierge - very friendly and we enjoyed the dinner recommendations. Printed car directions to the restaurants was a nice touch. The food was very good - breakfast seemed expensive, lunches were very good, dinner at Hoku's didn't live up to our expectations. Did not use the spa. Wished I would have brought some dressier outfits, but never was treated any different even though we were very casual.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>