<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="2f3d2316efef28e59ff6bca9d10f4c37" url=""><![CDATA[Good location. Service is decent. Rooms are comfy! This is my first time staying at this hotel. My usual hotel is the Hyatt across the road. I managed to get an extremely good rate for this hotel, 50% of what it costs at the Hyatt. Now the outcome.Check-inCheck-in in was quick. I upgraded myself to the lounge for a minimal fee. Somehow I regret putting myself up at the lounge. Service is alright, but rusty compared to the Hyatt Grand Club Lounge.RoomsRooms are very comfortable. I am a member of IPrefer, so I got an upgrade. Upgrades are good! The beds are the same as Westin's Heavenly Bed. I felt so refreshed waking up the next morning.Bathrooms are very nice, marble and good fittings.FoodFood in the lounge is good. It is mostly catered for the Indonesian, Malaysian and Brunei crowd. Very decent selection.LocationRight at the crossroads of Orchard and Scotts, where most of the shopping is located. Plus there is a cinema in the mall next door. OverallStay at this hotel. It has good value for the location it is in. The rooms are very comfortable.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a83b995ca22b8e454a5d489f3fb44543" url=""><![CDATA[A Cheaper Alternative bathroom
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bcd609f797b3d6b29c299e1bbe2e891f" url=""><![CDATA[A Great Hotel with an excellent location This hotel has been one of my favorites since the early 1990s. I have always stayed on the Club Floor providing access to the lounge facilities including free internet, breakfast and cocktails. I suggest potential guests at this hotel upgrade to the club floor. Location:The location is excellent as it is at the the Scotts and Orchard crossroad. This is where most of the nicer shops are located. Taxis are abundant, giving you easy access to anywhere in Singapore.Rooms:I cannot say much about the regular rooms, but the grand deluxe rooms which is a Jr Suite is an excellent place to stay if you want extra space or a family tagging along. The bed linen and towels are very plush!Service:The front desk attendants were very polite and helpful. They even called up to check if the room was alright. That is good service! Little things matter a lot. Also, parking is free which is a great plus! Food:Food was good, but there are so many restaurants outside, that I'd suggest you try them rather than the hotel outlets. The lounge breakfast is great, although it is not an American Breakfast.Conclusion:If you are short on time and would like to shop and do business, this is the perfect place to be. If you bring your kids along, upgrade. They'll enjoy the extra facilities. *ahem* Just tell JR to go easy on the free alcohol in the lounge.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>