<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="be5e57a1813e9438bc116a808545ee2f" url=""><![CDATA[Great value in Paris My wife and I just returned from Paris where we spent 8 nights in Room 26, a standard double which looked out over the courtyard. Rate 146E. I researched the Parisian hotels extensively prior to booking. Try to find a 3 star hotel at this rate in a fairly central location where the rooms and bathrooms are relatively large, well decorated and clean, and come with a small refrigerator (great for storing wine and picnic items), an in room safe, a flat screen TV with 3 english speaking channels, and a shower curtain. There was no alarm clock but you can program the phone to give you a wake up call. I'd bring an alarm clock for back up though. The room was very quiet with respect to outside noise. But the walls are apparently pretty thin. The phone in the adjacent room was easily heard in ours. That said, we rarely heard any voices. I think everyone must have spoken in quiet tones. The prior reviewers were dead on with respect to the location of the hotel. For those wanting to walk out of the hotel into a street of action, stay elsewhere. Such a street is a good 15 minute walk or so. Nevertheless, there are plenty of restaurants, a grocery store and everything else you'll need very close by. ATM is just down the street. The nearest metro is an easy 5 minute walk. Most of the top attactions are within a 15-30 minute walk.The staff was for the most part reserved but very helpful. This is not a BB type place where they fall over themselves to help you but I believe that's the norm for Paris. There are about 6 people who staff the front desk 24/7. Not all had restaurant recommendations. They give you a xerox copy of a map showing some French restaurants in the 7th but they don't seem prepared to make other recommendations, which is probably not unusual. So come prepared with your own list of places to eat. They will gladly make reservations, call cabs and do all that stuff. For you Mastercard holders, you might check with the hotel to confirm that they take it. We tried to pay for our stay with one and it was not accepted. The receptionist didn't know why but said it was a problem on her end which was clearly the case since I'd been using that card all week, had notified my MC company we'd be in Paris, had gobs of money left on the credit limit, and were able to use it immediately when we got home. So I'm not sure what the problem was. Fortunately we had a Visa card which did go through.We would not hesitate to stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>