<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="d23c71a981c1b207fa6a4e52a2aeaac3" url=""><![CDATA[Horrible Night! My boyfriend and I booked a room here last minute to attend a wedding in Scottsdale. I was really excited because i had heard that this was a really nice place. WE were really excited when they assigned us a condo type room with a covered parking space. WEll, when we drove back to our room, which was a duplex, with one more larger room below us, we were upset because all of the four parking spots were taken, by who , I don't know. SO we parked on the street. This was fine. So let me get to the horrible part. When we were ready for bed, at about 10pm, we heard very very loud rap music apparently coming from the room below us. I called the front desk once and they called the other room and the music stopped. OKAY fine, right ? NO WAY. At about 12am we were awoken to very very loud music and a bunch of kids screeming HAPPY BIRTHDAY. I called front desk, they sent out security and the music stopped. ABout 20 min later, the music started again. AND SERIOUSLy, it seemed like our walls were paper thin. We could hear these kids cussing and yelling and we even smelled pot. I was SO furious by this point, its 2am now, I called front desk and asked for another room. THEY REFUSED and said they would call security again. Security did nothing but made all the kids leave the room. SO now the kids are standing outside our window cursing and breaking bottles. WAS this the HILTON OR WHAT?? I called the front desk yet again and demand a new room or to call the police. They still did NOTHING. Let me tell you I was even afraid to go outside to check on my car. Well, I called and got the managers name, obviously an inexperienced kid, and in the morning when I spoke to the manager, he again did nothing. OH wait, he took $20 off our BILL I WAS SO FURIOUS!! I will absolutely never ever stay here again. I cannot believe a hilton would allow this. ANd I didn't even mention that these kids came back in the morning about 6:30 am and began slamming doors. PLEASE, don't stay here if you want peace and quiet.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5a50a1b2539b697a760827cc50b2af9d" url=""><![CDATA[location is excellant BUT.......... Stayed at the Drake for 2 night s in mid January. While the location is excellent be aware of certain issues. First, we got a great rate on a hotel website, only $89 a night, what a deal! BUT parking $90!!!! $45 a night...! I expected the parking to be expensive, maybe $20 a night. $45 is just way too much.. The check in was easy and the front desk staff friendly. Our room... VERY TINY, especially the bathroom.. seriously, there is barely room to turn around... but the room we thought was very nice and classic looking. Another plus, the bar/restaurant on the top floor (oops forgot the name)... its very very romantic and the views are beautiful.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>