<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="c19f2663903284c13c0fe5f521e8d710" url=""><![CDATA[Second Time Around ... Stayed at The Oriente several years back (before it was a Husa, I think) so decided to have a bit of an homage on this weekend trip in July. Bang in the middle of everything, so full marks for location ... easy access to most things and plenty of eating choices on the Ramblas. Beware though - restaurants on the Ramblas can be very pricey ... two course dinner (not that great a dinner either) with half a bottle of red wine was - that's about GBP60. Ouch! Our room was modern, fresh and clean. It was very quiet as it faced the rear of the property, so no Ramblas rabble to keep you awake at night. The down side of course, is no wonderful view ... we looked out at a brick wall. Hey ho ....Overall I'd recommend The Orient, but avoid the overpriced buffet breakfast.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6357a10674ef360bd83f3244719356a7" url=""><![CDATA[When Is An Upgrade Not An Upgrade? This was my second visit to the New York Sofitel this year. Being a big fan of Sofitel and a Privilege card holder, it was the natural choice for my 50th birthday bash in April 2008. Though there was no usual Sofitel Privilege welcome drink offered, we did get fantastic, upgraded rooms on the 22nd floor, with views out over Rockefeller Centre. It was super ....!So, this time I once again booked online at Sofitel.com and I specifically booked the (more expensive than standard) Queen Room, 15-29 floor, in the hope that we'd again get a room high up in the building. We arrived Friday around 9.00pm and the desk clerk advised we'd been upgraded to a King room. Great, I thought, until we got to the room on the 5th floor and realised it looked out over an air shaft into the back of the Iroquois Hotel next door. Not so impressive. Whilst the room was undoubtedly bigger, it was rather dull, with little natural light during the day. All in all, I'd have preferred the room I paid for, with less space and more view.However we did get our welcome drink this time!Notwithstanding the debatable upgrade, the rest of the hotel was pure Sofitel - professional staff, comfortable rooms, great beds, super pillows, lovely bathrooms, nice amenities .... all to rave about. The Gaby Bar is a great for a pre (and post) dinner cocktail.Will certainly return, but will be wary of any upgrades offered!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>