<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="59ec21c9ec53c12a08761ddabf974de0" url=""><![CDATA[Basic but location makes up for it We stayed here for 3 nights at the beginning of our trip and then 2 nights at the end before flying home. The location is fantastic and right in the heart of Hollywood.Rooms are very basic and smell rather musty and old, however, they are well equipped. We had the two king suite and used the spare bed to lay all the suitcases on which was useful!The kitchen was huge.There are some restaurants nearby in the Hollywood and Highland but the steak grill place turned out to be a disaster. Some people mentioned the Wolfgang Puck place was better. There is a small store nearby selling breakfast items.Although the rate we paid was good ($129 and tax per night) I do feel that it is highly priced for what you get due to the facilities being so old. Although if two couples were sharing the two king suites it would be a bargain. The location makes up for this. We did not have any problems during our stay although they do clean the rooms late in the day (3pm).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6b0de7cbba7bdbbb8c1ff6df99faf654" url=""><![CDATA[Not recommended We arrived and checked in to a room which had been used by a previous guest. They did not seemed surprised by this but did move us immediately to a clean room. The bell staff jump on you (literally) to get your luggage and we politely declined help on three occasions. Still they came to drag it away from us and in the process made us trip over them and send the luggage flying. They fight amongst themselves to get to the guests first so they can get a tip which is rude and intrusive. This only seems to happen in the States and I believe that gratutities should be at the guests discretion. I believe in rewarding good service. Also I do believe that it is their jobs to provide a service to guests and this service (if it is good) should be rewarded. If I want to take my own luggage then I should be able to do this without feeling that they want a tip for just opening doors or smiling. One of the concierge answered an outside call when we were in the middle of talking to him. The rooms are adequate but without a fridge. Beds are very comfortable. Housekeeping turned the air conditioning on and then left the windows open. What is the sense in this?! Location is good. Staff appear disinterested and lacking in common customer service skills. If you must stay here then I advise:Do not park here. They charge $50 a night PLUS TAX and you can't take your car out and bring it back in the same day without being charged another $50. Park at one of the public car parks which are close by and significantly cheaper (5th and mission or gardens)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1657cd64bff6b8f4d65ca19b51928830" url=""><![CDATA[Over-rated hotel I totally agree with the previous review. This hotel has lots of issues. We stayed from the 27th January for three nights. The hotel is about a 5 min drive from the train station (take a train from Schiphol not a taxi as it is only 4 euros each and the trains leave from the airport every 15 mins). The hotel is 20 mins from the centre, the walk is fine and that was not a problem. It was the access that was the problem. There are no clear walkways and you have to walk under dark, un-lit bridges at night to get back to the hotel. It is really frustrating as you can see the main entrance from the bridge but you then have to walk for another 5-7 mins to the end of the bridge and the walk back in the opposite direction (there is no walkway or staircase available). Taxis are way over priced and best to avoid or agree a price before you set off. Hotel staff are not really friendly (bar staff are very nice though) and we only encountered one smiling face on check in and that was the guest standing next to us!! The concierge are non existent. We had to drag luggage to our room only to find we were not given the right type of room, then to come back down again with luggage in hand.Rooms are clean and adequate BUT be aware if you book a king bedroom, you get a kingsize bed with two small single duvets. They do not provide one king duvet. This meant cold feet all night and this style is totally couple unfriendly. You might as well book a twin bed and sleep separately. I asked for a king duvet and the guest relations just said well this is our style. I said well we are both cold and with a king bed you would expect an adequate sized duvet and all she said was well you can turn the room temperature up. Apparently this is a normal procedure for a Dutch hotel. I can't honestly believe it and I think the world has gone mad if they really think that a couple can sleep adequately together in a king bed with a single duvet per person. I think the hotel is totally over-rated and would only be suitable for business travelers traveling alone who really need to leave the hotel during their stay. We will highly recommend using the trams and buy an I amsterdam discount card from tourist information as it gives you free entry to loads of attractions, free bus and tram travel and also discounts on other attractions and restaurants. Restaurants to recommend; Restaurant Brasserie Di Poort (part of Di Poort Van Cleve Hotel), is near Dam Square and serves gorgeous meals. It is fairly pricey if you go for three courses and wine and come to about per person but it is worth it.Amsterdam is a wonderful city and very beautiful but try to avoid the Movenpick.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>