<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="f0590ae0a73affb3e77c211a3af63c3d" url=""><![CDATA[Harborside nice and convenient to the city I booked this room through Hotwire, and like usual, I was quite pleased in terms of money well spent. The hotel, while next to the airport, is also conveniently close to the city, and it is easy to take the T in and out. The best thing about the hotel is the view from the rooms if you are on the harbor side, followed by its convenient location. The worst things are that it is isolated, so you have little choice in terms of food, and that it still takes a bit of time to get from the airport to the hotel as the shuttle makes all sorts of stops. Also, the hotel is remarkable in that there is almost/virtually no airplane noise, in spite of being at the end of the runway, but you can hear people in adjacent rooms a bit more than usual. On the whole, I would not hesitate to stay here. Oh, if you stay out here (or maybe anywhere in Boston), get the pass for the T. It is going to be worth it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6c0c4960204352ddda5a9ce2378063d7" url=""><![CDATA[Solid hotel, reasonably located. While some of the reviews found issues with the Parallel, we found our stay here to be quite reasonable, and the staff helpful (though their English was variable from very good to a bit limited). Probaly the two biggest dislikes were the parking (which is across the street) is expensive (24 Euros/day), and they need to provide better instructions on how to get to their property, e.g., from the airport. (Take the train to Sants, switch to the subway.., though I forget which one, but it is obvious as you just go to the Parallel metro stop, or there is a direct bus: which they say take a bus, but provide no bus number. Providing the details would help A LOT!!!)On the plus side, the rooms were quite comfortable (even for three), as noted above the staff is quite helpful, and it is very well located. While it is not in the historical district, that is only a few short blocks away. The subway is two blocks away. The fruit market is a 5-10 minute walk. Getting to the beach takes 20 minutes. Reasonable resataurants are around. The train station is 10 minutes.For breakfast, there are some quite reasonable cafe's within a block that serve a solid breakfast. At night, the cafe's on the street behind the hotel is very popular with the locals, but if you do not get there by 10:30 pm (or so), it will be difficult to find a table outside.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>