<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="0991d6c0f418df5a80de588ed1e71ac8" url=""><![CDATA[Good location but noisy Room 304. Mid - March 2006.Superior spa room. Cost on wotif - $140/nite.When the Legion cab bearing yours truly pulled up at the Haven, I frankly didn't know what to expect. The reviews I'd read of the place conflicted wildly and I hadn't set foot in trendy Glebe since Star Wars was on at the Valhalla. So I'd come prepared for anything. OK. First impressions. The Haven isn't going to win any prizes for architecture. I'm tipping that the rash of heritage orders in this area didn't get going til well after the Haven was already up. With its off-white brick exterior and early 70's decor, it's not a particularly attractive building from the outside. If you're looking to take in the Victorian ambience of Glebe's streetscapes, I suggest you take a walk down Glebe Point Rd with the Haven behind you at all times. 1/5 for external appearance.Once inside though, the place doesn't seem too bad. The girl on reception's friendly, efficient and helpful. There's no waiting to be checked in and no leave-a-credit-card-or-$100-cash-to-cover-your-mini-bar-rorting formalities either. Guess that's cause there's no mini-bar. There's no lift either and I'm on the top floor, but the offers of assistance with the bags are coming thick and fast. On top of all that, I can get free DVD for the night, so happy days. 5/5 for check in.Up the stairs and into my room and it's cold (YES!!!) there's air conditioning and it works a treat. Despite the sub-tropical Sydney funk of the day outside, I have to turn it down in the end because it's just too efficient. 5/5 for air conditioning. The room's reasonably sized and clean enough, but the balcony is quite small and spartan and at no time during my stay do I get motivated to venture out there. The room decor's like you used to see in country motels - in fact the whole place reminds me of the Flag Inn at Holbrook circa 1988. It's clean and it's comfortable. It's not 5 star. There's a small fridge with tea and coffee making facilities and an iron and board as well. 3/5 for the room.The bathroom is OK, but quite overwhelmed by the spa with shower over. The sink is also pretty small and awkwardly located under a shelf, causing me to headbutt the shelf when I was brushing my teeth. 3/5 for the bathroom.Across the road is the Toxteth Hotel - a fine drinking establishment even if the punters DON'T like my jukebox selections. What's wrong with some people anyway? The Ramones are SEMINAL, man. Glebe Point Rd is littered with eating establishments so you won't go hungry, ever. It also boasts the highest proportion of Tarot reading places per square mile in the southern hemishere. 5/5 for local activity.Night time. Noise. Oh deary me. How's the serenity? Well there isn't any. Glebe Point Rd has a surprisingly high volume of traffic late at night. The double-glazing mentioned in an earlier review was not in evidence and this is no place for the light sleeper. 0/5 for serenity.Brekky. The price is right at $5, but don't expect a wide selection. A bit of fruit to go with the cereal would've been appreciated. 2/5 for breakfast.Overall I'd recommend the Haven for budget travellers and those with powerful sleeping drugs or narcolepsy. For $140/nite, I've found better places in the city on wotif in the past.The Haven staff are quite good but the building is a bit dated and could use some maintenance. Glebe's a fun area and close to the city too, but next time I think I'll try somewhere new.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>