<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="ed8deeafd8bde678f825f2b8078563c7" url=""><![CDATA[Superb hotel Superb hotel, great location, friendly staff. Couldn't fault it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="08e141ddf5d7dba530b8dc4920e1c39c" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful hotel I booked this hotel on the strength of it's TripAdvisor ranking and I wasn't disappointed. It's so central, staff are amazing and the room was fabulous. This was the most comfortable bed I've ever slept on. Bathroom wasn't huge, but was more than adequate, and the room was big by Manhattan standards. No problem getting a late checkout.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d099d73bbf2de539b8c9f798819d775d" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel The Preciados is in an excellent location, close to Grand Via, but in a quiet side-street. Rooms were also soundproofed. Immaculately clean, pleasant staff, not the biggest room in the world, but perfectly sufficient for a short stay in Madrid. Free mini-bar is a bonus.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b516529a0acae98385e36f13191d1048" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent hotel This is a great hotel in an excellent location, just off Playa Catalunya. Our room was on the 8th floor, and had a nice view of the city. Bathroom was spotless, and had a good selection of toiletries provided, including toothbrushes, razor shaving cream, and body buffer. Didn't have breakfast there, but had food at the bar, which was excellent, although a bit expensive compared to what's available in nearby tapas bars/restaurants. Staff were pleasant, and most spoke English. I would definitely stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ea20ba0848da0dd6bd4cd7dee08d3fae" url=""><![CDATA[Above average I won this hotel on priceline for just under a night including taxes etc., and was quite worried after reading some of the reviews on this site. However, I was very pleased with the hotel. The staff were exceptionally friendly, our room on the first floor (smoking floor) wasn't huge, but was very comfortable, and looked to have been fairly recently decorated. The bathroom was a good size, and water pressure in the shower was excellent. Breakfast was a little expensive at per person, but there are plenty of places nearby for a good breakfast, and a cup of coffee at the bar was outrageously expensive at over however the food available at the bar was very good valueGood points: Location; clean, bright room; airconditioning; friendly helpful staffBad points: Expensive breakfast coffee at the bar
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>