<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="5fa4d975c6f3b05b71582bc3bd9a7145" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful vacation I wrote an extensive review of this hotel over a week ago but as I have not yet seen it I am now doing a shorter version.My husband and I stayed here from October 29 - November 12. We were very pleased that we booked the Platinum package through Air Canada Vacations. Their Representative Mylene was fantastic. The Guest Services Manager Armando Vargas was also wonderful.The check in was done in the Platinum Lounge so there were no long line ups. Check out was the same. I will not go into details about the beach except to say that we never had any problems finding chairs. The gardens were magnificent. There is a very nice ecology walk. Ask the trolley driver to let you off at the Mangrove Bridge. We had a Continental Breakfast in the Platinum Lounge. We ate so much during th day we did not need a big breakfast. You could go there for drinks in the afternnon and evening. In the morning you booked your a la carte dinners there. We tried all of them the first week and picked our favourites the second week.They were the Sakura, Chopin and Bella Vista. At 8.30 in the Chopin a small boat appeared on the little lake. There was a piano player in the boat. He played for about 1/2 hour.We also had a free dinner at the Licey Gourmet Restaurant through the Platinum package. The food was very good and very well presented but we did not think that it was worth the $25 surcharge.The soups in the beach Buffet Restaurant were the best that I have ever had in a hotel.Many of the reviews mentioned the lack of water pressure. We had a lovely room close to the water. The first week we were downstairs and the second week upstairs but that made no difference. This was our only complaint. We rarely got face cloths so if you use them you would be advised to bring your own.The suites were large and very clean. In addition to the fridge which contained beer and pop we had a dispenser with 3 bottles of liquor.My husband really enjoyed the 4 Dives that he went on. We also went on 2 snorkelling trips out to the reef which were included. You got a good view of the coastline from the boat. The fish and coral were terrific. Unfortunately the waves were very high.We were delighted to find out that there was Mass at 5.30 on Sunday evening. There were not many people there possibly beause it was not well advertised.The Duty free place at the airport was closed on the Sunday evening. A small gift shop finally opened. It sold beer and rum. The local rum was $25 for a 26 oz.We will certainly go back to this hotel. We have been travelling to the Dominican on and off for the last 25 years. The staff, food etc were the best yet at the Bavaro Princess.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>