<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="3431a11804a25a9861a9a2c39dc86169" url=""><![CDATA[Dont believe everything you read!! Wow, Wow, Wow!My family and I have been yo many all inclusive resorts, in the past our goal was to try a different Country each time we travel.I will start this off by saying that I would go back to the Iberostar Bavaro in Punt Cana in a heart beat! I read and read the reviews here on trip advisor, reading through the lines we decided that you cannot make everyone happy 100% of the time. Lets start with some of the more common complaints. This is not a 5 star Hotel, if your comparing to a USA $500 a night room you will be disappointed. Remember you are in a third world Country not the USA. The room was great, how much time do you spend in a room when you are on the beach? I am 6'4 300lbs and if I did have a complaint it would have been the room we had with 2 beds the bed was small, a double maybe? I have one child and when we go again I will book a king room with fold out couch bed for my child. Musty smell, yes there was a every so slight musty smell. We took scented candles and never lit one. Nothing to be concerned about! The air conditioning, no thermo but I would sayit stayed a nice pleaseant 72-72 degrees the whole trip, no worries. The food, Wow we made resos at several of the special resturants and never made it. These resturants you must set a time for dinner and wear long pants (no denium). We found the Buffet at all meals to be amazing! If you are picky I promise you will have no problems with the food, everything you can imagine for breakfast and lunch, dinner was from steak to lobster, fish and more fish, fresh sliced turkey, pork, beef. Pizza and hamburgers with fries at every luch and dinner for the kids.I ate sushi and all the above without one bit of stomach concern. The reviews about the bad food? They were not staying at the same resort as we were!! The food was A+. The beverages, if you are looking for top shelf booze you are more or less out of luck. The blender drinks are mostly with rum, the rum is made there in the Dominican, it was good. The beer Presidente on draught was actually quite good. At night the bar next to the stage has your better call labels. This bar is open all day but away from the beach and pool, no complaints. The pool was not the biggest I have ever been in but more than adequate. We spent most of our time on the beach but the pool was great never felt crowded.The beach was awesome, Aruba was the only other Island that I could compare the sand to, powdered sugar fine and white white.The water was cool enough to feel refreshed after being in the sun ( pool also ) Both were crystal clear. The palm leaf covered cabanas were wonderful, I stayed in the shade and my girls were right next to me in the sun. The weather was about 85-90 degrees each day, humid. Topless sun bathing is here and thereso be ready or explain to your children ahead of time. About 200 yards from the Hotel is a small gathering of make shift buildings where the locals sell there hand made items along with cigars, paintings, jewelery and so on. No prices are marked, If the price stars at $40 say NO THANK YOU and start to walk away the prices will drop in half to $20 and if you are in the mood you can barter to $7-10 dollars. We bought allot of stuff for $100 US.The tours, we did not do any! This was our first trip to do nothing.The Hotel will let you sail ( Hobby Cat ) for one hour free each day or snorkeling gear was also free one hour per day. Most days there was bingo, dance lessons or something going on.The shows were not Broadway for sure but the costumes werefirst class, they we Ok and I will leave it at that. Now lets get to the working staff at the Hotel, first class! Never saw anyone without a great attitude or a big smile A+. These people work 12 days on 12 + hours per day and then 3 days off. They make a whopping $5-7 US. per day!! We took down allot of stuff for the locals to give away. Cash works best, Take a few hundred dollars in $1 billsand hand them out. These people are among the hardest working I have ever seen, they do their very best to make you vacation wonderful. The Hotel has a Disco that is OK, opens at 11PM. Right next door for you cigar lovers is a great shop, the man that owns the shop hand rolls cigars out front almost every night for $5 each. The store has a great selection with REAL Cubans at a fair price. DONT buy your cigars from the beach vendors as they are all fake. I have said enough to give you some idea that we thought this Hotel was a good bargin for the $$. We spoke to other people on the beach that were paying double what our Hotel charged and they were not getting anything more, maybe the same or less? If you have any questions dont hesitate to write me @ nugman.net Big Joe
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>