<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="b4da8835038f3debc6fc0f031c684f6d" url=""><![CDATA[Good, but not GREAT experience We -- two adults and a near-teen -- visited Squaw Peak at the height of the spring break/spring training season, so it was packed. For the most part, we had a great time, but there were some annoying gaps in service/quality.The hotel is all suites (although small with no fridge), most seem to have been done over very nicely, with very comfortable beds and solid quiet construction. But if you have a bad back, get three people to help you unfold the fold-out couch!The River Ranch water complex was great, with mulitple pools, tennis, fairly boring miniature golf, and faux lazy river and waterslide (with great smoothies at the pool bar). However, at opening time, there was a long line of people waiting to get in, and the gate was understaffed. Concierge staff was incredibly knowledgable and helpful (thank you, Dave, Joan and Carol), with good advice on trips to Sedona and local sites and restaurant choices.The biggest disappointment was the on-property dining, which was mediocre and overpriced. We had opted for the bounce-back breakfast. The vouchers covered only a couple of menu items. The staff at both the family oriented Hole in the Wall and the fancier Lantana Grill kept trying to direct us to the pricey breakfast buffet. At the Hole in the Wall it was awful -- soggy french toast, cold eggs, a few pastries -- more like school cafeteria than good resort. (We DID love the Joshua Stone Band, local bluegrass group that plays Friday nights... worth seeing)The Lantana buffet was better, but more expensive... we would strongly recommend not buying the breakfast plan, and visiting some good local spots, like the 5 Diner nearby.It was annoying that while there was free wi-fi in the lobby, internet access everywhere else was an add-on.All in all, we had a great time... this is NOT a luxury resort, despite the pix, but a middle of the road family resort with nice rooms and a laid back atmosphere... just fix the restaurants!!!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>