<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a7a5e19da83599f8cec4afbee0964af8" url=""><![CDATA[Two thumbs up...way UP!!! Hola! My husband and I just returned yesterday :( from our week-long stay (6/6 to 6/13) and we're definitely having withdrawl! This was our first trip to Punta Cana, and our first All-Inclusive. We loved everything about our trip except the fact that we had to leave! I really wanted to write this review because I know how I looked forward to reading them. We booked through an on-line site and it was an Apple vacation out of Cleveland on USA 3000. Everything went smoothly with with our reservation. I requested an oceanfront room, second floor. That's not what we were given upon arrival, but I just asked for one, and, though it wasn't oceanfront, we were re located just behind those that were, on the second floor. We were in suite 2403...loved the location near the beach and pool...a good walk to the lobby and the breakfast/dinner buffet, but really appreciated the lush grounds and beautiful surroundings along the way! The room was just as pictured, nicely renovated-especially the bathroom! We had a new flat-screened t.v., but not one of the new clock radios that I've heard they've been installing...no big deal...brought a travel alarm clock. We had great maid service, with beautiful red flowers left in the bathroom towels each day! We tipped each day for the great service, but I think it would have been the same, tip or not! We always asked for extra water each day because we used the coffee maker each morning...we'rereally early risers, and enjoy our coffee! We found the food to be really good...the breakfast buffet had a great variety of choices, we always found something we liked...the dinner choices were wonderful, too! We always sat near the water where we enjoyed watching the water fowl...and we loved the great service we were given by Juan and Jairon!!! We always ate lunch at the beach/pool buffet and, again, we liked it there, too. Lots of choices...I really liked the pizza and the salad bar, and the ice cream was always refreshing! As far as the drinks go, I really liked the Bahama Mammas, and my husband liked the rum and cokes. We ate at 3 specialty restaurants, the Steakhouse--loved it...the Mediterranean--liked it ...and the Gourmet--absolutely LOVED it...the lobster salad appetizer was to-die-for as was the steak entree and the pineapple sponge dessert w/coconut ice cream! We ate pretty much what we wanted and never felt sick our entire trip!We met many nice vacationers...hola Natalia, Gloria and Philleman from Chile...we miss your warm, friendly smiles! And the Star Friends, who run the activities at the pool each day and the shows at night, do an awesome job making everything so much fun and everyone feel so welcomed! You don't have to do any of the activities...we did the horseshoes, the archery, and the air rifle shoot...I won the horseshoe toss one day and my husband won the archery on another day. When you win, you are invited on stage that night and they present you with a certificate and a t-shirt and everyone sings We are the champions... and though we weren't sure we'd like all that attention...It was great fun!We were very pleasantly surprised to find almost no bugs, and only a few flies and a mosquito or two. We had just one complaint...we had cold showers most of our days there...though we spoke to others who always had hot showers...could have called the desk, but didn't. Absolutely no mold anywhere, no smell in the room and always had a good working airconditioner!!!I realize I'm going on and on...but there's so much to tell...we're looking forward to our next wonderful vacation...hopefully next year! We would highly recommend this resort in a heartbeat!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>