<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="78ca146316f2c2508a55e4736a0c9953" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel, nice location but best for short stays With an Embassy suites style design with an open atrium and 7 floors this hotel looks very nice. The rooms are the usual two rooms with a small kitchen and living room.The property is located across from several nice although moderately priced restaurants and for the casual experience there's also a Hooters. However beyond those if you want other dining options or even fast food you will have to drive. This place is great for a short visit or weekend. But the long term business traveler may want to look for hotels closer to downtown.My only real complaint I had was the Internet service was very slow. I was unable to remedy this with technicial support and my own networking expertise. One would think that Seattle hotels would not have this kinda of problem.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1248f6dd773f4282b0c0e5a77ffd69ae" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, superb service, excellent rooms! This former Wyndham hotel is Hilton's gain. In an absolutely superb location close to Quincy Market, Thaniel Hall, a T station, the Aquarium, along with many pubs and dining options of just about any variety all within walking distance.The rooms are superb. Hilton Diamond members this is your place. The suites, although not equipped with pricey furniture, are very large. Almost too large considering the very reasonable rate. The bed was quite comfortable. Not too soft, not too hard but giving.The staff are very polite, professional and helpful. But the key here is the very nice location and the superb rooms!This Hilton is a deal! Way to go Hilton.The only downside is what I experience at many Hiltons sadly including this one. Its Hilton's repeating canned commercials over their cable TV service. They repeat and repeat and repeat the same ads over and over again. Many of them are politically driven but made to appear as PSAs (public service announcements). HIV ads with Michael Douglas' narration, breast cancer and colon cancer ads running repeatedly become old quickly. If you are like me I like to leave the TV on while I do other things in my room. But hearing HIV infection statistics every 20 minutes is a bit depressing. Come on Hilton, just run the regular commercials everyone else watches please.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>