<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="69c216d318a0243acc2eaac3dadff66c" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location, Over Priced and Bad Service. Look Elsewhere Singapore is Expensive. Regardless of your currency, this beauty comes directly from the Taxes you pay as a guest. Nothing is the price it seems, and Hotels are at least 15% more plus there is Goods and Services Tax on everything, pretty much. It is a nice and safe place but the money will start leaving your pockets as soon as you move through Customs and it won't stop until you leave.The Intercontinental is in a great location but that is all it has going for it. Everything else about this Hotel is smoke and mirrors. You don't have to look too hard to see it looks ok but it being neglected and will be very ordinary in a few years. I stayed for 12 nights, pre paid through Priority Club where I am a Platinum Member. I am a simple guy, I like clean, neat and secure. I'm not fussy and I don't write many reviews but I felt strongly enough about this stay to comment.The driveways staff is friendly and helpful and the reception is neat but the staff are very mechanical in their approach and it very personable. I was taken to my room but the staff member was just going through a routine and didn't seem interested The room was neat and tidy but where it stopped. The room service and housekeeping was terrible. They missed many things including replenishing coffee and cleaning the tiles in the entry. I had to call them back on a few occasions to do tings they had missed. Actually they didn't replenish the coffee for 10 days and missed the mini bar many other days too. The fridge wasn't cold enough and I had to order ice for the whole stay. At $280 a night (discounted), I have had to do this.I asked for direction at the Concierge Desk and they gave me the wrong directions on 3 separate occasions. I thought it might be my accent but I asked in Chinese (I'm Australian and I speak a little Chinese) NO I don't sound like the Crocodile Hunter ;-) my accent isn't strong so I was surprised. Even the Indian guy gave me the wrong directions. I said SUN TECH CITY, they heard something else. Anyway I went to the map and found out for myself, only after walking around the City in the heat but I got there in the end.The Internet service is about $30 a day and SLOW!!! They say it is broadband but It was horrible and I had to make a number of calls to get it sorted. Problems on their end BUT not the issue. It was more about the attitude of the receptionist who answered the phone at the Hotel when I complained. I was treated like some scumbag who was trying to get his money back, scraping to use the service and get a refund. I simply said the service broadband but it was resolved only after the IT Manger came to my room and called the Internet Company. The problem returned but I The breakfast was expensive, $27 plus tax for the cold buffet (cereal) and $37 + for the hot. When you arrive into the dining room the staff automatically generate an Invoice for the full buffet, I got caught out on this on a number of occasions and nearly signed off on it before I got it corrected.Overall, the issues I experienced should NOT have happened in this Hotel, not at this star rating and at this cost. I be staying at the Intercontinental Hotel Singapore again and I urge you to consider another Hotel, read the reviews and look elsewhere. Thanks Kristian (Shanghai China)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="666b632d395c5ad4b1baa2e8db4722fc" url=""><![CDATA[CAN DO BETTER The City Garden Hotel is comfortable but it is under renovation (Sept 2008) on floors 5 and 6 and moving up to the 15+ floors. I booked through Wotif and while I can often get a good deal from that engine they are so big now they are slipping with their discounts. I took the is booking a Hotel without knowing which one it is. I fgured it was City Garden as the description was exactly the same as the listed City Garden but I saved HK55. On arrival my deal said I would get the complimentory fruit basket and free drink but that never happened. Normally I mention it but I let it go until I cheked out and the receptionist went to a draw a got a few coupons. Something I use anyway as I was leaving, this was typical of the service, it was very lapsed. On arriving to the room I had a look around. There was a few black hairs in the bathroom and around the floor. A half full bottle of moisturizer was on the sink and when I went into the bedroom there was another black hair on the pillow, For a minute I sure the room was actually made up from the last guest. Apparently it was and this is the best they could offer. They really need to step up in the housekeeping department.I was told I have been upgraded to a suite but this room was NOT a suite, it was the only Non Smoking floor available. expect any views as this Hotel looks into the local neighbourhood. The MRT (subway) is 2 blocks away and a short walk. There are several 7 11 stores, Starbucks and a few other places to grab snacks and coffee. The breakfast in this Hotel is HK130 which is very expensive.Hong Kong is expensive in any currency, on par with Singapore. You really pay to be here so getting the best rate on a room is important. Best to shop around and look for an all inclusive deal. If you can get a room that is HK200 more with everything like breakfast and Internet then take it as the Internet in the City Garden is HK200 a day, the room was only HK550.This Hotel 4 star by western standards, more like 3. Be careful, shop around, you can do better then this Hotel. KP
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>