<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="999a2133bb23a189694034593f03f0c1" url=""><![CDATA[Disappointing Stay in Seattle Nothing fancy, in fact a bit cramped, not well laid out and located out of the way. Definitely not a walking destination to/from downtown or the seattle center. Was disappointing for a Marriott product.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6aad072a7af0c126071d6953f5ffe265" url=""><![CDATA[Shopping, Dining The Grand Hyatt Seattle is one classy place. My honey and I stayed 3 nights and enjoyed everything about it. Clean and wonderfully appointed. The enormous bathroom and soaking tub, the fitness gym, on-site restaurants and location next to shops and cafes galore couldn't have been better. The brief walk to the bay and Pikes Market - wow!!! Highly recommend this one to couples needing a break from the rat race.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="451dccd8cd84ca3dee095f008cbafa2d" url=""><![CDATA[Stretch out at the Stanford Court A wonderful place for a romantic get-away. Don't bring your car. Take BART from SFO or OAK to the Embarcadero Station. Walk 1/2 block to the California Street cable car line. Take it to the top of the world's greatest view and, alas, the hotel is on your left. Great, attentive service. 12,000 restaurants, amazing walks and Giants baseball just a taxi or cable car ride away. I suggest the Cosmopolitan Cafe and Morton's for dinner.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1e08b690995de2904896f6be83b9ce22" url=""><![CDATA[Monte Carlo Suite Wow -- from the moment you enter the spacious suite and find yourself smiling at the bright colorful draperies and linens, comfortable furnishings and wonderful touches with Aveda products, mint chocolates and leopard print robes -- to the peace and quiet the room and its placement afford -- you know that you have chosen well. What a great place to spend with your honey. What a great, central location to shopping, theater, restaurants and the stadiums. I would do it again in a heartbeat!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>