<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="2ddb1fff25dd928dd04dacc29b1dc95b" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect The selection of a Tokyo hotel can be tricky given the size of the city. The Cerulean Tower Tokyu Hotel is located in Shibuya and after having stayed here for 4 nights I believe it is perfectly located for exploring Tokyo's neighbouring Wards.All that has been previously written about this hotel I totally agree with. Firstly the hotel is easily accessed from Narita by the Airport Limousine Bus - its a door to door service and it took roughly 1 hour 20 minutes in each direction. The Cerulean is one of only 2 hotel drop off points for Shibuya. The Cerulean has an impressive entrance and grand foyer which is ultra minimalistic in its design. Huge windows look onto a formal Japanese garden - it all makes for a wonderful first impression. Check in is brisk and efficient. We also used the Concierge several times and the staff were all friendly and knowledgeable. Rooms are located from floors 19 to 37 and this is the selling point for this property - all have incredible panoramic views from large windows. All of Tokyo seems layed out before you. They are nicely fitted out in the less is more Japanese style and are quite spacious by Japanese standards. The bathrooms are also generously proportioned. Lastly - the hotel is within quick walking distance to Shibuya Railway Station and the famed Shibuya Crossing which has be seen to be believed.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2f28709087ee68fcb740a35a4ec0bd4b" url=""><![CDATA[Understated Some years back I attended a wedding at the Santika Beach Resort and decided that one day I would return and stay there. This hotel is delightful - it occupies an absolute beachfrount location in Tuban and it the thing I liked most about it is that it has a relaxed and understated feel about it - unlike the hotels that sit either side of it which are done in the Balinese more is more style.Much has already been said about the Santika gardens - they are indeed beautiful and well kept. I stayed in a Premier Room - these are housed in a seperate wing from the main complex - its very quiet. The rooms are furnished simply yet are tasteful - I loved the split level design. There are 2 pools - one in the Premier Wing and a main pool that looks to have been done recently. My only negative comment is that breakfast was just ok. I have stayed at several properties in Bali and all offered a way better breakfast selection. But this in the scheme of things is a minor fault. My onl
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9ebe67d810e4d89cded11bc737a40036" url=""><![CDATA[Great Value Lets just put things into perspective. You get what you pay for. Having visited Sydney more times than I can count and stayed in all manner of hotels with varied star ratings, I can honestly say I liked the Kirketon very much.I had a Standard Room and yes it was small but stylish nonethless. The bathroom was particularly interesting with creative lighting. Having a cd player, video and walk in wardrobe was also nice. Lobby is small and the bar and restaurant are currently closed which is no bother cause you are in Sydney's best dining precinct. Staff were fantastic. Friendly and well informed. For what they are charging you cannot beat it.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>