<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="e73920aa3ceae68a50fd70ba9e44577a" url=""><![CDATA[Good Hotel. Great Location My wife and I have just returned from a weekend break at this hotel. The location is great. Step out through the hotel entrance and you are right in the centre of this energetic and stylish city. Step back though the door to escape the same! We booked a Superior Design Ramblas View room. These are on their own Royal floor. They are modern and stylish, but the room we had was small. There was no separate bath tub, but the shower room was excellent. Overall for our short stay we were happy with our room. Noise insulation from the bustle of Las Ramblas was very good, which had the downside of making the internal noise of the hotel more noticable on ocassion. On the Royal floor is a small lounge area of a few tables and chairs with some complimentary Cava, Tea, and Mineral Water. We enjoyed a glass, or two, of Cava before we went out for the evening. We had breakfast in the Hotel, which unsurprisingly is more expensive than you can find at local cafes. The breakfast room over looking Las Ramblas was pleasant, and the buffet breakfast offered a good choice. The staff were polite, professional, and very helpful. When we return to Barcelona we will stay at this hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="173f67d1694796c697220602552e3db6" url=""><![CDATA[Good Quality Hotel in a great location We stayed at the Sofitel for a long week-end, our first trip to New York. Whilst acknowledging the Hotel's French ownership, I found being greeted in French upon our arrival in New York in the early hours of the morning, a little bizarre and pretentious. But then I'm English so French is not going to be my cup of tea! The Sofitel is a good quality hotel with a sense of style. The rooms are modern, and well equipped. The bathrooms are very good with a separate shower stall, and bath. The baths are a bit shallow for a good soak. The beds are very comfortable. The rooms are quiet, albeit the air-con was a bit noisy when it cut-in. Staff are very helpful and polite. The Bar is very pleasant, with good service. We did not dine in the restaurant, prefering instead to go out and choose from the many, and varied restaurants within easy walking distance. Like others we would reccommend the Red Flame Diner, just a few doors a long the street. You may have to queue for a few minutes at breakfast time due the its popularity with both locals and visitors - but it's well worth the brief wait. The waitresses are great and work hard, so tip them well. The Hotel is situated adjacent to the Thearte District between 5th and 6th Avenue so it is ideally placed for exploring. We walked from the hotel to Times Square, Central Park, Maceys, Bloomingdales, and the Museum of Modern Art, amongst other places. As I have not stayed at other New York hotels I cannot say how it compares to them. However, compared to other hotels I have stayed at in other countries it scores well, and we would have no hesitation in returning to the Sofitel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>