<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="9a104420273f9e9b8393008f8071c12d" url=""><![CDATA[Won't stay here again When we arrived at the hotel around 1:30PM, we were told there was no early check-in and we'd have to wait until 3:00PM for check-in. Ok, that's reasonable, so we went to lunch. Arriving back at the hotel, we were told they didn't have a queen, which we reserved, but only 2 doubles. I really wanted a queen, so we were told we'd have to wait even longer. Around 4:00PM we were finally shown to our room. The air conditioning was not working at all in this room and it was unbearablly hot. When we complained, they said they had no other rooms available. After much arguing, they finally let us stay in the model they had available. It was on the street level and right on the street. There were no curtains in this room, only blinds which were broken in places. This meant people on the street could see right into the room, not a very secure feeling to say the least! We had to keep the bathroom door closed as the odor coming from the bathroom was intolerable. Overall, this was one of the worst experiences I've ever had in a hotel. It was not a clean hotel, shabby and moldly smelling in the rooms and halls and the staff was not at all pleasant.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="31833bb73f8cc76037b6a2f0add637f5" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel We stayed at the Holiday Inn Port of Miami one night before our cruise. The hotel is very clean and the staff were friendly and helpful. There is free internet access.. The beds were quite comfy. The smallish pool area was also clean and a pleasant place to sit and enjoy drinks. Drinks were not available until 5:00 PM. Breakfast was available in the hotel restaurant, the buffet was $10.95 per person. There is also a McDonald's a block away in back of the hotel. The only complaint I had was that the coffee at the hotel was terrible! We were 3 women going on a cruise so we got a room with 2 double beds and an extra cot. The cot was $10.00. Our room was very large and easily accommodated the cot. The best thing about this hotel is the location. It is right across the street from Bayside Marketplace. A nice spot along the bay with many restaurants and shops. There was live music playing on the Sunday night we were there. It was a nice way to spend an evening before our cruise. I would recommend this hotel to family and friends and would stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>