<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="3f26e2c3692b1a2e7032cb1242847dc0" url=""><![CDATA[FABULOUS and FUN family resort!! My parents treated our whole family of 14 to celebrate their 55th wedding anniversary at DREAMS from August 10-17, 2008. Ages ranged from 77 yrs. to 11 years old. We flew direct from and everything went off like a hitch. We were greeted at the airport with an air conditioned bus that took all 14 of us and our luggage to the resort. Yes, the roads were bumpy but we quite enjoyed the trip there and seeing the TRUE Dominican life. It was an the kids. Once there we were given champagne and mimosa. (I drank both!) No cool face clothes which I really needed at that point as I attempted to check all 14 of us in. We had 7 rooms and had emailed Eileen (manager) ahead of time with some room requests as we wanted to make sure the children were safe and adjoined with their parents. Unfortunately that didn't happen and they were placed in rooms next to their parents. It all worked out but we did wonder why we couldn't have been accommodated when the adjoining rooms were unoccupied. Oh well! Michel, at check-in, was truly giving us his best service and trying hard to please. We were housed is 5122, 5120, 5112, 4124, 2203, 2204 and 2226. The rooms were clean, decent size for two people in each room, the air worked well, and the fridge was fully stocked with water, juice, pop, and beer. We had maid service 1-2 times a day based on our schedule and cute animal art on our bed on several occasions. No one in our party had any complaints about the rooms.I was disappointed at the lack of face clothes. We receive them for the first 3 days and then we ended up with 6 at some point later in the week. Go figure!The pool is AMAZING!! It is the gem of this resort. We all loved it as only 3ft. deep throughout. There is a swimup bar at the beach end and another pool bar (on land) way down. The chairs are plentiful and there are palapa huts throughout too. There are a few cabanas beds which hold many people at once. My family loved chillen under the cabana together when a sun drink break was needed. Guests did not really reserve beds. We saw security remove items if they were placed on beds unattended before 8am.I was disappointed by the poor quality of the poolside chair cushions. The cushions on the poolside chairs are in MAJOR need of replacement. It appeared to be black mold or something and on them. I covered the chair well with towels.The ice berg was fantastic fun for kids to play on. Rafts were available too. We brought several with us and only ended up using 2. Many mornings the rafts would clog up in the pool by building 2. We called it the we were able to get a raft first thing in the morning.The beach was BEAUTIFUL!! The water is turquoise blue and the sand is soft and tan. We were there right before Tropical Fay rolled through so the water appeared to be a little rougher than I remembered. We all brought water shoes and made sure we swam to the left. It was absolutely gorgeous. We brought our boogie board rafts out to the ocean and rode the waves in. We also brought our own masks and snorkels. It was FUN!! There are rocks as many people have posted. Just be aware of them.The chairs and palapa huts were plentiful on the beach. The beach service was GREAT!! We brought our Bubba Kegs and they kept ice water COLD for hours. They were a BONUS for the beer and mixed drinkers too. Never had a problem keeping them full.The restaurants were incredible. have to be CRAZY to not find something to eat. It when people say the food was HORRIBLE. What planet are they coming from??? We did bring our spices but rarely found it necessary to use them. We enjoy eating bland food but obviously that was NOT the case.The World a HUGE variety from breakfast, lunch and dinner. At breakfast you can get made to order eggs and omelets. The smoothies are die only ate lunch twice in the World The pizza is wonderful. They also had a make your own pasta bar where you pick the noodle, sauce, etc. It was delicious. The El Patio was a with a certain food being served. (ie~ Dominican night with Dominican far, Asian, etc..) the food was VERY good with A LOT of variety.The Seaside Grill was closed for renovation part way through the week to have the thatch roof repaired in this open-air restaurant. We ate there the first night and had great steaks, veggies and desserts. Drinks were plentiful too.The Oceana was very convenient for lunch. We spent A LOT of time on the beach so you just had to throw a cover-up on and head to this open-air beauty. The sandwiches were pretty good. One day we ordered a version of a club sandwich as stated in the menu but got a ham and cheese sandwich served to us. Not sure why. They also had a fresh fruit and dessert bar.The outdoor beach grill offered fresh fruit, fresh salsa, chips and cheese. There was a grill with hotdogs and hamburgers and ALL the fixins to go with them. The pop machine was nice too.The Bordeaux was truly the hidden diamond in the rough. It is located above the Seaside Grill and Oceana BUT it is enclosed and air-conditioned. The view is stunning as there are windows wrapped around it and you can see the gorgeous blue water. The food was very tasty. We loved the seafood shell appetizer and the beef tenderloin and steaks. The best part was the bar located right next to it. Often we were the only people frequenting it. The views are SPECTACULAR!!! The bartender, Aquino, was so efficient and friendly. My dad asked him one evening, you like your Aquino replied, you like your ALL laughed as he had made THE BEST bloody sisters EVER!!The Himitsu was a very fun Asian grill restaurant. The chef was very entertaining and allowed my daughter to partake in the cooking. She had a ball!! The food was VERY delicious. We were STUFFED by the end of the meal that we had to skip dessert. The view was beautiful too.We must have missed the Da Mario. I imagine how but we did. It is an Italian fare.The bars offered plentiful liquor and top-shelf when you asked for it. The drinks could be as strong or as weak as you wanted them. After a while the bartenders often knew what and how you liked your drinks. It was INCREDIBLE!! miss the hidden gem by the Bordeaux.The entertainment team worked EXTREMELY hard everyday to prepare the very entertaining programs. Many people participated had a lot of fun. On Friday when Tropical storm FAY rolled through they had a variety of activities and food to keep everyone entertained.No one in our party had kids that used the Club. It looked AWESOME and the kids we did see were having the time of their lives being entertained by the staff there.The Core Zone was a hit for both the teens and a few adults in our party. They offered a mechanical bull, pin-pong, pool, internet (fee,) a snack/drink bar, batting cage and a few other things. There was a lot to keep the teens busy.The Casino is VERY SMALL and fairly smoky. My mother won several times and came home with more money than she brought. (BONUS for mom!!) There were approximately 30 slots and 6 tables.The grounds were IMMACULATE and the wildlife roamed the resort. (Peacocks, babies and the flamingos.)The vendors attempted to get pushy but we FIRMLY set them straight and it worked. Be firm and consistent and you have a problem. only when people continued to converse with the vendors that they became frustrated because the vendors let up.A few minor renovations to this resort would truly make it EXCELLENT! We felt an above average rating was in order.Last but not The staff worked VERY HARD to serve the guests of the resort. It truly showed.I am sure there is so much more to comment on but I feel as though I have covered the things. DO NOT believe the negative reviews. Those negative reviewers must be hard to please. funny how many negative reviewers post only ONE time. Hmm? Makes me wonder. Enjoy your stay at DREAMS if lucky enough to vacation there. HAPPY TRAVELS!!!!!Jan :)
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>