<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="102a212928f570354871772f1e39afe7" url=""><![CDATA[Overall good, some problems Stayed for one night, and was generally pleased. We arrived on a late-night flight, so did not check in until about 2am. The front desk clerk was friendly, and the room clean and spacious when we arrived. Unfortunately, when we attempted to go to bed, the sleep number bed would not inflate. After changing rooms at 3am (not really a pleasant thing to have to do), the new bed worked. Once in the new room, called the front desk to request a wake-up call and a late (2pm) check-out. We did not receive our wake-up call, and our late check-out was not documented. Overall impressions: The public areas and rooms have been recently renovated and are attractive and spacious. The rooms are clean. The pool is located next to a freeway offramp, and the deck area around it is very small - not the best experience, but acceptable for an airport hotel. I see that an earlier review also mentioned non-functioning sleep-number beds, I would recommend checking the bed as soon as you arrive. The front desk staff was friendly, if not overly effective.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ffeb1ebe6f2242994f251577c98aa13e" url=""><![CDATA[Terrible hotel, great location Stayed at the Stanford Court earlier this year through a priceline purchase. Paid $110/night, which was great for that area. First the good - location is amazing. Great fun to walk down to Union Square, then take the cable car back. Close to everything, and great views (from some of the rooms). Now the bad - the hotel obviously has not been renovated in more than 15 years - totally unacceptable for a supposed 4 star property. The walls in between guest rooms were paper thin - had to spend two nights listening to our neighbor's conversation. I refused to walk barefoot on the carpet, it was so disgusting. The entire room (and most public areas) felt like I was staying at my grandmother's musty, old, dated house. If I had paid anything near normal price, I would have taken one look and left. There are much, much nicer hotels in the area - spend your money somewhere else!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>