<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="9e4254c2def321a4e07d16f6884c7d81" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful hotel My wife and I stayed here for two nights on the 7th 8th of September and absolutely loved it. We had a canal view room which I would highly recommend. The room was very nice and good sized as was the bath. There was a mini bar and nice toiletries for the bathroom, also houseslippers. The staff was excellent with very good English skills. The breakfast was not outstanding but was good by European standards. The hotel is right across the canal from the railroad station with a gondola station right in front of the hotel for 100 euros which was cheaper than the main tourist areas. An easy and delightful walk to the sights but be prepared to get lost, thats half the fun. We plan on staying here again on our next trip.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ef4803e5fbc8bd0df60364c26db87fd8" url=""><![CDATA[Very nice hotel Stayed here in early September and liked it very much. Only steps from the Ponte Vecchio bridge. The room was very nice as was the bath. The staff was excellent and spoke very good English. The restaurant/bar was very nice with great views. There was also an outside terrace adjoining the restaurant with awesome views of the city. Breakfast was very good. We would definitley stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0f9fd7b056475ec8c2b16c70ff0ee602" url=""><![CDATA[great location My wife and I stayed at the Chancellor Feb 11 to Feb 15 and loved it. We had a corner room, which I think may be a little larger, and found it to be very nice with a view toward Union Square. We were able to watch the Chinese New Years parade from our window. The hotel is very convenient to all the tourist locations and the cable car runs right outside the hotel. We walked to Chinatown easily and there are lots of restaurants and shopping within a few blocks of the hotel. The staff was very pleasant and helpful. All in all, a very good value for the price.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>