<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="4ad597eab496e9324199d68052377a7f" url=""><![CDATA[Great place, great people, great weather, great holiday Went there on a whim, and it was absolutely perfect. I laugh at the people who complain about American chips costing too much in a store of a place that has a cournucopia of food and drink in every direction, all the time; or people who are too whimpy to carry their own luggage to the bus, and almost missing the bus for lack of a bellboy. It's a different country, and you're in it. Our experience was awesome. The front desk staff were not only very helpful but also very efficient. I saw a few snively people try and mess with their heads, at which occasions they reacted with nothing but tact and professionalism. We were checked in immediately upon arrival (even though it was 9am), we didn't have to use a bellman because we can carry our luggage, so there was no delay there.The food was great. The buffet had a theme every night, we had everything from Mediteranean, to Japanese, to Mexican, to German... need I go on? Lunch had a vast variety of food for every taste, a good experiment to have is pay attention to various body types various food choices. It's quite telling. Oh where are those chips now?The staff were awesome. They work hours that would make us spoiled North Americans cry after a week, and still maintain an inspiring disposition. As far as the time share dudes, they appreciate you being honest with them, and telling them you really aren't interested. They all respected that. The Fun Club are heroes. I saw them taking care of people's kids, getting the sloths on the beach moving, and entertaining till all hours of the night. All with a genuine smile (if a little tired sometimes). They are rock stars.The Guest Services desk was so helpful the one time we had a dillema, and the gentleman went way out of his way to help out which he did (help that is), while having angry vultures hoovering over him.My only disappointment of the whole trip was witnessing how some of the tourists treated the staff. I was embarassed for them. And the staff and locals were truly beautiful people.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>