<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="465c5a7738bde1f1c73bd793f2f12cad" url=""><![CDATA[Raffles - The Best Hotel in the World ! During January February we stayed at the Chedi in Muscat, The Observatory in Sydney, Palazzo Versace on Brisbane's Gold Coast, Hamilton Island's beach club, and finally Raffles. Raffles was simply head and shoulders above the others, word's cannot do justice to this great place, I think you have to experience Raffles for yourself, even if it's for one night.... We stayed 4 nights in a Courtyard suite per night including breakfast in the Tiffin room. Everything about this hotel is first class, you are absolutely treated like royalty from the moment you arrive to the moment you leave. The period suite was a gem, seperate 'parlour' with dining area, comfy chairs and writing desk. Forget sending postcards, send letters using the Raffles retro stationary. The butlers call button in the parlour (I kid you not) was answered within 5 minutes and the delightful staff attentively dealt with any request.The Long bar and customary Singapore Sling is a bit touristy but it's better when it's on the house (nice surprise) and as a guest you are made to feel special. Got the obligatory Tiffany bracelet and ring for my wife Shaney as it was Valentines day and had a lovely Valentines dinner in the Grill. The absolutely superb piano playing and occasional gospel singing by 'Jimmy' which echoed around the restauraunt was an absolute delight. On our last morning we had breakfast by the rooftop pool (available 1 hour after Tiffin room stops serving) which was served by none other than 'Joe Louis', a very affable fellow ! We did venture out to Long Beach for some tasty Black Pepper Crab but apart from that and a visit to the excellent Mall across from Raffles, we hardly left the hotel. Had a couples exfoliation/steam/jacuzzi massage in the Spa which was a very romantic affair and was similarly priced to the Chedi. To say that our suite was around per night more than the other hotels we stayed on this trip and the Raffles suite was much larger than the others, I thought it was great value. A memorable experience which we'll be looking forward to repeating in the future - we'll be back !!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>