<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="e52bbfccf8cef53be9ea758c06c59b9e" url=""><![CDATA[Be Fine Prompted by a Red Sox ticket offer from some friends and a day at the Science Museum thrown into the mix we decided an overnight in town would make the adventure easier. To be honest the Westin was not our first pick, nor was it the second, or third even the top 10, but with a week left to reserve a room before the game date it quickly became our only choice. I was surprised at not just the room prices on Boston, but also the availability or lack there of. not sure if it was a busy weekend, but we tried everywhere online and via telephone for a booking. I can say that there were no conventions that I was aware of during our stay. From the experience of our stay that may have changed our overall experience. After reading reviews I was a bit apprehensive as to what to expect from the place that had now become our weekend default. We are low key, no fuss family of four.The Weston is easy to find and easy to drive to. There are 4 levels of underground parking. You do not have to use valet parking. You can drive directly into the garage and self-park within steps to the elevators to the lobby. The garage was a bit of a tight fit with a full size truck. There would have been a problem if I did not have a couple of spaces to pick from. We checked in late on a Saturday and there were approximately by my count 15 spaces left. There is other your parking lots nearby and possibly some on street. There should be no parking fears here. The cost of parking for our one overnight stay was $30 and we were able to remain parked until 6pm the day of checkout. We were advised to keep our room key, swipe it and deposit it on our way out the gate. That came in handy as the game was to end sometime late in the afternoon. BTW a cab to Fenway Park from the Westin cost $15.00Check-in process was done in reasonable time. There was a good size line when we checked in. It took about 15 minutes. The lobby however, is a great space. Plenty of seating, tastefully decorated, with a bar and a much needed albeit a more expensive Starbucks than at home. On the converse, check-out was a snap. I say that having not seen a all the charges applied, hidden or otherwise. We did not require any additional services.We called the hotel directly for reservations. The room was a Double/Double 14th floor facing the Cruise terminal and the end of the Logan runways. Plenty to look at if you wish to sit and catch your breath for a few. I do wish a Queen/Queen was available for our stay. The room was well furnished in a contemporary styling, great bedding, nice carpet and window treatment. I will say the addition of flat screen televisions have made any room seem bigger and more stylish. There were plenty of channels that kept us well entertained and informed. The AC worked well although it seemed a bit loud. A steady woosh of air out of the vent was much like that of a large fan. This did cancel out most of the hallway noise that tends to be prevalent on a busy weekend, but it did not cover up the door closings or slammings as mentioned by other reviewers. Noise wise, it was far from what could be considered dead quiet. The bathroom was great. Full lighting, Kohler fixtures, double shower heads, very easy to use. As mentioned in a previous review there is no bath fan only a vent that provides natural draft venting. Skeptical I was, but it does work for odors and steam, it just may take a bit longer. There was one bathrobe in this room that was available for use. The iron in this room was broken and would not heat. The family raved about the pool and hot tub. Both were used on two separate days. Use room key to enter the pool area, towels provided there, kid friendly (parental supervision) and if not mistaken accessible 24hrs. We decided not to eat at the restaurant in the lobby. This decision was gauged on our energy level and the appearance that it may have been too expensive for its value. Based on a few recommendations we walked (10min) to Salvatores, who but the way, serve colossal portions. Good food, well worth it and the foot traffic in the area seemed livelier than everyone has mentioned. It felt like a generally safe area. The next morning we opted for a quick bite and a latte at Starbucks instead of a sit down or eat-in breakfast. Overall I would now consider the Westin our without fault, default. Not at the airport, not near Fenway or Quincy Market BUT, we got great a value that suited our need. Based on the savings we saw compared to the other hotel offerings, of the less of a hindrance when balanced with its cost. Quite clean, still new looking, well kept common areas and I thought the room was very well cleaned. What ever notions or hesitations you may have about staying here all we can say is, Be We would not hesitate to stay again in the future.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>