<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="2b32bb44f449580221e0f0678024f1fd" url=""><![CDATA[Really Disappointed I use Trip Advisor for ALL my hotel stays and recommend it to friends. In this case it was well off the mark and I am surprised because in all other cases it has been spot on.I can't believe this is in the Leading Hotels of the World book alongside other Australian hotels such as Versace - no comparison and the Versace is cheaper!The hotel is at best 3-4 Star. Staff seem scarce, no-one to help with bags on arrival and a little bit snobby when they do finally appear - except for the porter an older gentleman - nice guy (who admitted they gave us a smaller not as nice room previously when bringing new keys). Someone mentioned the location as not being as good as the Four Seasons, I agree but does anyone mention how rough the area around the Observatory is?To say we felt intimidated is mild when walking just next door and down the street to see piles of rubbish, people hanging out of windows shouting abuse at each other, urine stench, the rubbish consisting of a computer screen, beer crates, general household effects at the base of the trees lining the road. This isn't happening up the 'other end' of the road this is opposite (view from our room) and next door to the hotel and all down the road.Knowing the area is so poor more could be done re: security - the balcony door on our room was loose and gaping and easily accessible from outside.Rooms are tired, the furniture is in poor condition, decor and drapes need an overhaul too. Public areas are scruffy and dirty in places. Given free strawberries covered in sugar very pretty the flies like them too! Also given free champagne in each room.What also bugs me is the way a lot of hotels and in particular this one, give you a 'dud' room first and expect you to be happy and you have to approach them again to get what you paid for.Given this was the most expensive time of year (for New Year's) we were obviously paying a lot to stay and it wasn't worth the money. When we did complain the attitude was very poor and inflexible and immediately they referred to it as a 'legal' issue and therefore they would not refund us a penny. It is on their booking form it is non-refundable but what can you do when you and your children don't feel safe somewhere? Why would anyone pay to feel unsafe when all they have to do is provide somewhere clean, comfortable and safe?We left and very luckily - given it was the day before New Year's eve got a cancellation at the lovely Shangri-la - a much better hotel and should be much higher in the ratings in my opinion.For information we did go back again two days later to take some more photos to make sure it wasn't just an 'off' day - it wasn't!! Drunks again shouting outside the hotel and across the road by the tennis courts and even more rubbish. This was in the daytime and whilst you could use the New Year's jubilations (extended!) as an excuse I doubt it was the reason. Ver dodgy area.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>