<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="ab5975c0cea2e6619d4920e018273d18" url=""><![CDATA[Nice location, decent hotel I used booking.com for this hotel. It had great reviews on TripAdvisor so I decided to go along with it, the price was good. The location is excellent. This is the main consideration for my visit to Amsterdam. It is right down the street from the main museums and right next to a major tram line. The stay went pretty smoothly, but when we checked in, there were 3 of us and we had asked for a double room and were taken to a room with a single bed. Then, the room was not clean - there were drinks, unmade bed, etc. from someone else's stay. We were immediately placed in another room with the double beds we asked for. The room was really clean and it was a nice looking set up. The bathroom was pretty and spacious. There is no shower curtain, only a small clear partition. For the price, it was an excellent hotel. The woman at the front desk was really nice. They say breakfast is included, but the breakfast is not much, really, but bread, fruit, coffee and juice. But the front desk person is really attentive and helpful. It felt very safe and the neighborhood is very cute. The TV in the room is tiny but hopefully in Amsterdam that won't matter at all! The room could have been a bit larger, so keep that in mind if you are traveling with more than 1 person there. Overall a great value, I would stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="334ecfd9a400adfdeab68288f6b51e0e" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel The hotel had a great special for the Christmas season. The front desk staff let us check in early which was nice. The beds were so soft and it was helpful to have the computer in the room to check attractions and look up locations. There really wasn't much of a view from the room, but the location was nice, in a small neighborhood. The metro stop is about a 10 minute walk in the quiet area and the front desk staff is helpful about giving directions and answering questions. The bathroom wasn't that great, it was sort of small but still it was nice. The rooms are a great size and you have plenty of space in the room. You could walk to the hotel from the center of town, about a nice 20 or 30 minute walk. The room service was well priced and prompt. If you get back to the hotel and are tired or just spend the evening in, they have a nice choice of DVDs which my friends and I enjoyed when things slowed down there during the holiday. The pillows on the bed were super soft. I have heard horror stories about London hotels being too small or cramped, but this one wasn't and the price was not outrageous, either. A great stay! I would go back, definitely.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c7e28f57d7c1e642ddf972e4cded214f" url=""><![CDATA[Great! This was a great hotel. I used booking.com, they had really good rates. The price was very reasonable. The front desk staff were extremely helpful and patient about every question and request. They give you free lemonade, beer, and water in the minibar which is cool. The room was beautiful and the view was excellent. The shower was great, there were 6 different water spouts. The only problem is the water comes out on the floor, but this was a minor problem. The glass wall for the bathroom was an interesting, pretty touch. The room was very nice, it was great to wake up and go to sleep to that view of the city. You can take the metro to the hotel very easily, and you can take the tram to many different places. Just be careful, the area seems very safe and far apart from the main mix of things, but I had my purse stolen not too far from the hotel. There is a great mall right next door for shopping and also to grab food and snacks at the last minute. I loved this hotel; it's great for family or friends, and especially a romantic trip. I would stay here again definitely. They also give free robes and slippers, which they continually refresh! Also, they clean the room whenever you leave, even if it's in the afternoon (most rooms are only cleaned in the morning!).
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>