<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="1bd277c8efc754f1e1b3e0ed8b9b5f6b" url=""><![CDATA[Great base for looking around San Francisco Like many of the reviewers we found ourselves in the Beach Road property - does anyone actually get to stay in the main building and if so who are you?The walk from the main building wasn't too bad, although we had just been traveling for about 12 hours and had loads of luggage. The smell from Denny's in the lobby is not great, but you kind of get used to it (not enough to go and eat there). Our room was on the third floor at the end of the corridor facing onto the street, though this rarely caused a problem during our stay.The room was reasonably spacious and importantly clean. The shower was good and the bed comfortable. The internet access was wireless and free and that was important for us. We were just minutes away from the whole fisherman's wharf area and had good access to transport systems if we wanted it. The hotel was just what we needed as a base for looking around San Francisco.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="da568ee865883f2beb1e623de286d051" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel Just returned from our second trip to the Barcelona Princess and had a great time. Our room was on the 14th floor, overlooking the city from where we could see a number of the major sights of Barcelona. We loved the large bed, the mini bar, excellent shower / wet room and the bath robes. Although the hotel is out of the city, the hop on hop off bus stops just outside. Also the Metro is just around the corner, and taxis are in good supply. We ate breakfast at a cafe over the road, as in the hotel it would have cost us 16 euros, this was despite an internet offer for complimentary breakfast which wasn't available to us because I didn't book direct with the hotel. We also enjoyed drinks in the corner bar, particularly the Cava which was just great. I would highly recommend this hotel, but book direct!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>