<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a721c3c7e3b6f94d35e697b5d8adf98f" url=""><![CDATA[Great Designer Hotel This is a great designer hotel. Having read some of the previous reviews I was a bit worried about noise etc but it was not a problem. This was a special treat so I booked a duplex room, which has a bedroom upstairs with shower room and wc and a living room downstairs with bath, shower, wc. Off the bedroom there was outside steps leading up to a sectioned off roof terrace with a long narrow pool. So, two wardrobes, 2 showers, 4 bathrobes, endless fluffy towels plus two pool towels and 2 minibars and LCD Tvs!On our first night we came back from a restaurant to find that we had been given a complimentary bottle of Cava. Even the glasses (by Schott) were designer. A nice touch.PlusesAs mentioned by other reviewers, the staff at the Grenados are really nice and genuinely interested in people having a good time. They were very helpful answering my questions and recommending hotels. They were professional, unobstrusive and a real asset.The Housekeeping was outstanding. Our room was checked 3x a day and any used towels replaced. They were also very generious with the toileteries.The bedroom had a comfortable bed and the blackout blinds were really effective. It was very quiet. The lighting and lit antiquities in the corners all added to the atmosphere. We had the fried eggs on the pillow bit too which was a bit strange........ The rather funky music and music system took a bit of getting used too, imagine trance and club chill music and this should give you some idea! By the 3rd night I was looking forward to some of the tracks however!The pool terrace bar upstairs and the atmosphere both at 7:30 in the evening and when we came back after going to a restaurant, was chilled. Other guests seemed to meet up there too and the cocktails, particularly the mojitos were lovely if very strong! We were there until 1am on two nights (the official closing time is 2am).The semi-private pool was nice but is really a strip of water that runs along the terrace and you can't really swim in it. It was also cold but we are used to this! Having our own sunloungers, table and umbrella on the terrace was a plus.We had breakfast at the hotel once on the day we checked out and it was good.We ate in the restaurant the first night and the food was modern Mediterranean My husband had a tuna tartare with wasabi sorbet which was exceptional. Again the lighting and design of the restaurant and outside eating area all added to the experience.MinusesThe cocktails were on the pricey side as was the restaurant but the quality was good.The downstairs shower flooded the floor, the bath has a channel running around it which fills up with water when the shower is on and floods the floor. The view from the semi-private terrace was uninspiring, and, if you book the duplex rooms leading from the ground floor( we had 206) you are a bit overlooked from the balconies above. I understand that there are duplex rooms on the 5th/6th floor but you may get more noise from the bar there.Finally, the steps in the connecting rooms are all in orange marble and the floors are wood, with the low lighting it would have been easy to miss one. There is a railing going down from the bedroom to the hall area but not to the sitting room. Because of the above I give the hotel 4/5 but I would definitely stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>