<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="baf280031905a7511d1cce19c0e44257" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful! Close to MRT, Very happy with Swissotel. Beautiful and clean. Breakfast buffet was expensive, but good. Attached to Raffles shopping mall.convenient to MRT. Within walking distance to Boat Quay where there are lots of choices for dinner along the river.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e9640f0b6939c98dee975c1a594f106d" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful New York Trip! Spent 2 nights, 3 days at Marriott Marquis in New York and had a wonderful trip! We were there from March 25-27 for a girlfriend's birthday. I read over 50 reviews of this hotel and it seemed over half gave a terrible rating about the elevators. We had no problems, but I could see where it might be a lot slower with prime times. We plan to stay there again on our next annual NY trip. We even had 4 women in one room and didn't feel too cramped! The beds were extremely comfortable. The fitness room was excellent and we also enjoyed dinner in The View restaurant. The breakfast bar was excellent as well.Concierge was very helpful. We arrived in the hotel around 9:00am on Sat.morning and we were given early check-in immediately!(I did call request it, but it was not guaranteed) The location just can't be beat.Walking distance to theaters, restaurants, shopping, tours,etc. Very convenient. All the staff seemed extra friendly and helpful! Great Hotel!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="13403ec7f1c706e950a6704bc5742c86" url=""><![CDATA[Room/Casino not much We have just had a very relaxing short trip, 4 nights, 5 days, at Breezes Superclub Hotel Casino in Punta Cana(Feb.9-13) When we arrived, after an hour ride from the airport, stopping at 3-4 hotels along the way to drop off other vacationers, check-in went very smoothly. (I would recommend getting a taxi unless your transfers are paid in advance.)The pool was fabulous, large and winding with a swim-up bar and lots of lounge chairs to pick your favorite lounging area. Food was available anytime, but I would rate it average. We tried all but the Japanese. Our room smelled very musty, probably from the leaks in the bathroom above our commode, sink and shower/tub. We reported the leaks, but they were never attended to. Every evening when I wanted to use the hair dryer, I never knew if it was going to work or not. They did send someone after the first complaint, but I still had wet hair for dinner. After that, I found the fuse box on our wall and sometimes resetting it, would help, sometimes not. It was a beautiful view of the pool and ocean, though. We love to gamble at the casinos when available, but were disappointed in the Breeze's casino. I played roulette and the spinner/dealer, was so fast, I couldn't get my chips down half the time. There were 2 roulette tables, but usually only one was operating when we were there, and there were 2 black jack tables, and not very many slots to pick from. I think there may have been one carribbean stud table as well. Just not very busy, and the staff didn't seem too friendly or accomodating. I would definitely recommend Punta Cana for the beautiful beach and ocean, but I would try the newer hotels next time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>