<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="d0a3a0018b3c512da3f91517e12257bf" url=""><![CDATA[Watch Out to Paradise! Awesome!!!! Hello:My family (5 of us) spent 7 nights at this wonderful resort. This has been the best vacation of my life, and to be honest I am a little dificult to impress. Everything was wonderful, there are so many pretty places and corners where to relax and to have fun that really make this place paradise.Food: Very good in general, In order of liking: Market Grill, Bana, Passion, Agave and Vento. Buffet is delicious for breakfast and it has everything you can think of to have for breakfast and then some.Facility: Gorgeous resort. Rooms are spacius, the finishing of the bathroom etc. is not as detailed as we are used to here in the US, and you will notice that as soon as you arrive. It is really a shame because this resort has so much luxury everywhere that I think they should have been more carefull inside the rooms, but again... I am picky with that stuff. Overall... great rooms, believe me.Activities: A different one every night, you won't be bored. I made some friends there, I am really happy with our trip.Service: GREAT! They will do whatever it takes to make you happy. A tip always helps, this is a very poor country and some of them have to stay at the hotel and don't see their families for days, others arrive at 5 in the morning, so these are very hard working people and a little tip goes a long ways.Beach and Pool: One of the best pools in the Caribbean (per Tripadvisor) and the Beach is much more nicer than I thought. Some seaweed but is not the kind that bothers you. Trust me, I was born in the Caribbean and I know about beaches :-).Premium Drinks are included. So.. feel free to ask for Heineken or whatever, if they don't have them at the pool bar, ask for them, they are supposed to offer them so... push for it if not find at first. This happened to my father who is a Heineken drinker, it turned out to be that there was a lack of the premium beverages in some of the bars, not sure if they are trying to save a little on cost during the slow season (now).Check out, chek in was quick, room was ready.No one got sick, always drink bottle water there is plenty of it everywhere.I strongly recommend this hotel, the difference in price compared to the rest of the hotels in the area is WORTH IT!!!!. Great people that should be mentioned:Pool Bar: Damian, Lenin, Venecia, FranciscoBuffet: Gregorio Vidal (great guy, I got emotional when he gave each of us a little local craft gift). Julio, Pablo, Jose, Margarito, Carlos.Ciel Bar: LuisBana: ObispoMarket grill: RicardoI am sure I am missing a lot of names here because most of them are just great.Dislike: The presure from the Vacation Club members, and I stated this in my ckeckout - interview. And I didn't care for the Disco bartender either, kind of arrogant guy, I believe his name is: Alberto or Adalberto Castillo.All in all.. great stay, wonderful resort, magical people, fantastic!!!! You won't regret making this your choice.Please contact me with any questions you may have via this website.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>