<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="2c3a1c8ac66b19d12ec301d88f95bfac" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic Resort My husband and I travelled to the Occidental Grand Flamenco in Punta Cana for 2 weeks in the middle of May 2006. After reading some of the reviews on this site we felt slightly anxious that we had made the wrong decision but we had not!The hotel was beautiful, immaculate and friendly. All the staff worked really hard to make sure that the grounds, pools, restaurants and beach were immaculate.The rooms were average but comfortabe and cleaned daily. The fridge was always stocked with water, Pepsi and 7-Up and the maids did an excellent job.The buffet restaurant was lovely with a huge selection of fish, meat, paste, pizza, salads and desserts.....the choice was huge and there was something for everyone at breakfast, lunch and dinner. The other restaurants were also great, the only one we didn't care for was the Mexican but our favourites were the Italian and the Oriental.The pools were enormous and very clean. There were plenty of sun loungers available and we didn't have to put our towels down early at all during our stay.The beach was amazing with white sand and turquoise water. There were plenty of sun loungers again and we didn't struggle to get a shady spot at all.We did a couple of trips out of the hotel, the helicopter trip i would recommend!The weather was perfect, sunny all day every day without a drop of rain or cloud. I would recommend sun tan lotion of factor 25 or more as the sun is extremely strong. Make sure you take plenty with you too as the shops out there charge about per small bottle!We stayed in block 11 which was close to everything although all blocks were well situated so it didn't really matter.The spa is worth a visit, we had massages which were very relaxing and all the staff there are fully trained.We tipped well, not because it was expected but because the staff deserved it and it was a pleasure. I don't think you would receive any less service if you chose not to tip but they all work so hard and are so well presented that we felt they deserved it.We had a wonderful 2 weeks at the Grand Flamenco and would recommend it in a flash!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0d699410ab9757678c6c4bfb55072730" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel view from the window
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>