<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="dd303ba14165c80c8dfb7367c2d54856" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel I was provided a corner room with a view of Boston from one window and a view of the Delta terminal from the other window.The room was clean and comfortable with typical Hilton Le Source bath products. My only disappointment was that there was no bottled water in the room. Not a bad problem to have if that is the only one.The fitness center was upgraded to all Precor equipment. I got to spend an hour on one of the ellipticals while I was there.The meeting rooms were comfortable and the food was very good.Transportation to/from the airport was quick and painless.I will definitely stay at this hotel again if I'm in the Boston area.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="feed5bae9a1a67a572d1dc9286e56c74" url=""><![CDATA[Nothing But the Best! This was our second trip to Punta Cana in as many years. Last year, we stayed at the Majestic Colonial. That was touted as a 5-star, but I'd probably rank it more as a 3-star. So, with higher expectations, based on more than doubling our travel costs, we headed to the Paradisus Palma Real from August 3rd through the 9th. My sister and BIL had stayed here when it first opened and highly recommended it to us.When we arrived, there was one person in front of us checking in. This was a fast procedure and we were provided with cocktails as we waited. I was worried when the concierge came over with vacation club magnets for my kids and had to show us a map of the facility. My husband said he wanted to find the room, so he took his key and left me with them. I rushed them through their speech and walked away with their forced appointment for the next day. When they called in the morning, I told them I wasn't interested and hung up on them. They never bothered us again whether in the lobby or around the pool.The bali beds around the pool were a wonderful respite from the daily grind of life and from the sun. My husband was up at 6:00 every morning and was able to secure a bali bed for us each day.The food was excellent. We talked to a few people who were not happy with it, but we really could not understand why they were not happy. The buffet was vast with many options. My husband had steaks made to order on our first night. We had good meals at the Market Grill, Vento and Passion. Bana, the Japanese restaurant was ok, but tons of food.The wine list had good selections. I wish that they had enough wine buckets to leave white and sparkling wines at your table like they did the reds, though, instead of making you wait for them to pour again.Our kids loved the game room that was open periodically through the day and from 9-11 each night. They had x-box and PS, etc., and our kids made friends with many others each night. They even got to go to dinner with some of their new friends while we had dinner alone.My son and I did the segway tour around the golf course and the villas surrounding the course. That was a lot of fun. He and I were the only participants that afternoon. It was worth the $30 for the hour and a half of fun.The bartenders were so friendly and a lot of fun both at the pool bar and in the lobby bar. There was a nice martini menu in Bana.We didn't spend much time on the beach. Only for walks during the day and at night. We didn't care for the seaweed, and the pool was so nice and relaxing.The fitness center was good, too. It overlooks the pool/beach area and has a lot of equipment. They were kind enough to let me use an elliptical in Crocs because my sneakers were in a bag that the airline hadn't delivered to us yet. We didn't get our bag back until a day and a half before we were leaving. I can attest to the gift shop having deoderant and a hair brush for purchase. The hotel supplied dental kits and shaving kits. This was important since our toiletries were in that bag. Not even this could get us down. We were on vacation at a perfect destination... What more could we want?If we go back to Punta Cana again, we will definitely stay again at the Paradisus Palma Real.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>