<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="e8d28f3bc3ba591070125e6fc2975e32" url=""><![CDATA[Just An Awful Stay We stayed at the Radisson before an early morning flight. I chose it because of location and location to a decent parking lot for our car, MasterPark. But it was one of the worst hotel experiences we have ever experienced. Mind you this is just my opinion and I'm sure many people have stayed here and been quite happy.The main problem for us was the bed situation. We are larger people and the 2 double beds just didn't cut it. It was us and our 2 kids and there just wasn't enough room. Plus I have to say, the adjustable beds are not much of o selling point. The MOST uncomfortable bed I have EVER stayed on in my life, hands down. All they are, are air mattresses. If you want a firmer bed it pumps more air in and if you want a softer bed, you take air out. Well, if you take too much air out you can actually feel the wooden bed frame. We were off to Disneyland the next day, and I woke up with a stitch in my back that just wouldn't go away. Not good if you are planning on walking 8-10 hours a day.We ordered room service, and it wasn't bad. We had the steak sandwich, and it was quite tasty. And the service was good all around, from the front desk to the room service.The hotel itself it a little run down, but I have seen much worse.But if you can't get a good night's sleep, especially before an early morning flight, then everything else just doesn't matter.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="32d5b86b52f97ea1925e3e6442cb3eed" url=""><![CDATA[Silver Cloud Inn - Never Disappoints We stayed here after a long flight home from LA.Before the flight we stayed near the airport and just had an awful experience. So we decided to just go with what we know for the trip home. Yes, it was about a 20 minute drive from the airport, but at least we know what we are getting when we stay at any of the Silver Cloud Inn's. A clean comfortable room. With beds you can just sink right into. I love that the parking is gated, not that it's going to stop someone who is really bent on breaking into your car, but it was nice.The 24 hour pool was great to come to, since our kids were just wired from the flight, and it was a great time to just go down there and let them relax.We got up too late to enjoy the breakfast, but if it's anything like the other ones we have experienced at other Silver Cloud Inn's, I'm sure it is wonderful.If you are looking a clean comfortable room with great customer service this is the place to go.We will definitely stay here for our next trip to downtown Seattle.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>