<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="32923c2ac1545c28559bbe14644e4dd4" url=""><![CDATA[ok The Ifa Villas is made up of 3 hotels, all in one 'complex' using the same facilities. what it doesnt tell you in the brochures is that it is in the middle of a private residential area, so when you enter the main gates dont be suprised to see lots of houses all multi coloured. Check-in was slow as the people at reception hardly spoke english. When we did get our key, we were taken to our room which was 4133 near to the beach. It was a lovely room with a king size bed and nice view. we were lucky as others had a view of some buliding work going on- not major, just building a wall round the complex. we had not 1 bug or lizard in our room, nor any problems with the air con. The only thing was that the patio door did not lock, which is a bit worrying as you could climb from the main staircase onto our balcony. We were a 2 minute walk from the beach, which was absolutly fantastic. The waters were warm and fish swam right up the shore all multi-coloured and different shapes. Brilliant for snorkelling. The walk to the beach is not bad as some people make out. Yes you walk down a path, but its nice and you can find all the cocunuts on the floor. The food- Well the buffet was suprisingly really good. There were different things nearly every night, and the was a pasta dish chef, kebab/mussels/burgers chef. On a morning there was on omlet chef and a girl that made fresh milkshakes, like pineapple and melon. The waiters were VERY slow, if you asked them for a drink, you would not get it unless you kept on asking. There was a young man who was very quick so we gave him a tip and he looked after us from then on.The mexican restaurnat was fantastic. NOT spicy unless you choose spicy things.The japonise was nice- the teriaki chicken was gorgeous.The caribbean was the best. The steak was to die for. The room was air-conditioned and really nice. Well worth waiting for as you have to book theses restauants in advance and they do book up quick. There was not a lot of entertainment unless you like everything in foreign.no-one spoke good english, and so on a night we were drawn to the ping pong table in the old gym. But someone smashed the ball, and when we kept on asking for a new one, we kept getting the reply- on vancation!Not many english there at all, we were a bit shocked and dissapointed at first. Not a lot to do for kids, other than swim in the pools and use the internet.We did 2 trips, quad biking and catalina island. Quad BIking was good. They took us to a gorgeous beach with green and blue waters, but the Catalina Island was absolutly fantastic and definetly worth visiting. You book it on the beach were you get the banana boat etc, and its 85 dollars pp. leave at 7, 2hr bus journey to the boat, then 20mins to the island. They let you snorkell in the sea off the island, and it was fantastic, the reefs were amazing. Then you go onto the isalnd and can sunbathe, snorkell again, or shop at the shops.they provide a buffet luch and you are on the island for about 3hrs. The island is a protected nature reserve and so no-one lives on the island.Overall we are glad we went to the ifa villas but we were very bored by the end of the 2 weeks. we would go back to the dominican but not this hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>