<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="04a307b6667d78fe0293aa42c8b64bc3" url=""><![CDATA[One of the best hotels we have stayed at... We stayed in an Emerald Suite that was on the corner of the hotel on the 30th floor, with incredible views. On one side was the Space Needle and the other view was the Market and the ocean. We went out of the front door turned left and two blocks to the Monorail station that went to the Space Needle.The staff was exceptional from the moment we arrived till we departed.One other note, we got a discounted rate since we have AAA. We booked directly with the hotel online as soon as we booked our Alaskan cruise.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5dc9046e4fdcfb2bae30f015609be0f5" url=""><![CDATA[A nice Party hotel, but the Montecarlo was much better for the same price... We decided to stay for 2 nights after a cruise after reading the reviews and was disappointed. The reception staff was wonderful, we had arrived early and they allowed us to check in and spoke great English. The room had a great king size bed, but the small table and two plastic chairs we outside on a small patio in a tower that was on the outside of the doors and became very hot and loud. So we moved the table inside to have a flat surface to put our stuff on. There was on small bookshelf, but no tables or night stands...the bathroom was the same also...no counter space.We went upstairs to the pool andd whirlpool area and they had a party the night before and bottles we in the pool and the decking sticky for spilled drinks. It was all cleaned up and chairs put back out for the afternoon. We went on a tour and when we got back tried the bathtub whirlpool but it was broken and they offered to move us to another room, but since we had unpacked decided it was not worth it. The next day we tried to use the pay for view movie feature, since we were tired from the cruise and it too was broken, they did give us a discount on the room at this point, but for the same price we had stayed at the Hotel Montecarlo before our cruise and it was exceptional and was more to what we were looking for...the Axel seemed more like a Party hotel...a good choice if that is what you are looking for...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6bb9810f7f1033e9e3f9307d089f5a8c" url=""><![CDATA[one of the best hotels we have stayed in... We decided to stay before our cruise to adjust to the new time zone and was very impressed. Our room overlooked Las Ramblas, very comfortable and quiet, there were two glass sliding doors to block out the noise and the beds were adjustable for a great nights rest. The bathroom we took pictures of, a two person whirlpool and was divine after a long flight. The staff was great, free internet to send our emails, the morning breakfast was not to be missed, the location was great and we even found a restaurant called the Attic, a couple of doors down on the same side of the hotel that had early supper times...for us Americans...the menu was in English.The hotel is owned by a family for 60 years as we were told and you could really tell the pride they have in this great jewel of a hotel...the staff made us feel very welcomed...will be there again if we are ever in Barcelona...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="05fd95836a2e2a48e2cb6dbd40a3826c" url=""><![CDATA[One of the most beautiful hotels we stayed... We had two rooms before our cruise on the Serenade of the Seas after Thanksgiving, the view was beautiful of Old San Juan and the ocean. The rooms are small, but very comfortable and we felt we were staying in a beautiful museum. Our room had an inside glass door to keep out sounds from the hallway, since there is an inside courtyard. We ate breakfast in the courtyard and really enjoyed our stay. They also arranged a walking tour of Old San Juan that was amazing, he meet us in the lobby and then off we went for a very personal and pleasant day before boarding the ship.For an extra treat, since our friends were on their honeymoon, we went to the Dragon Fly restaurant, since we had heard great reviews and easy to walk to from the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>