<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="bc559d065a977e3f99fa8878c90b2230" url=""><![CDATA[A very nice resort for the price Just back from the RIU Bambu. First off, I must say tripadvisor.com was very helpful for the planning and deciding of our final destination and other travelers opinions were great to read.So, where do I begin......our room was basic, nothing fancy, but it was cleaned very well daily and our fridge was freshly stocked with water, 7up, pepsi and beer throughout our stay. Some previous reviews spoke of thin walls and the ability to hear your neighbors real easily, but this was rarely the case. Now, most mornings people were out and about between 7-8am, so you would hear doors slam and people walking past the room and sound carried in the hallways. No big deal, why sleep in when the beach/pool are waiting!As for the food, my wife and I played it safe and didn't gamble on stuff we normally wouldn't eat. We ended up doing morning breakfast buffets daily (which resulted in eating little if anything for lunches other than a snack). For dinner of our six nights, we did the buffet 3 times and did a la carte 3 times.The breakfast buffet had a huge variety of items, we loved the pastries and especially the homemade donuts (made right on the spot). The pancakes and french toast were also good (and made on the spot as well).Lunches like I said, consisted of a quick snack at one of two possible lunch locations.As for dinner, the buffet nights were fine, nothing special or elaborate, but definetely something for everyone. As for the overall quality of the buffet food..........well its buffet food, so I don't know how high a standard should be applied to it. It was fine overall.....nothing to write home about, but nothing to complain about either.As for the overall cleanliness of the restraunts we did not once see any rodents or bugs crawling around, it was quite surprising given the fact that they were all open-air restraunts.As for our 3 a la carte nights, we did the Caribe Grille twice (twice because we really liked it) and the Steakhouse once (ok overall, but more than anything, a break from the buffet routine). The Caribe Grille was very nice and the food quality was the best of anything we had at the resort. This restaurant is actually bordering the RIU BAMBU and RIU Macao. One important thing to know....if you want to reserve a table for any of the 3 a la carte restaurants, plan to be up at 6:30am and be waiting on a line around 7am to reserve your spot! They are usually booked by 8am, and the Caribe Grille is usually booked within 15-30 minutes!The bars to get drinks were adequate, one at the pool and one closer to the lobby. There was an evening bar near the entertainment stage as well. It would have been nice to have a bar right on the beach, but no big deal, just a bit of a walk.A couple of %'s I'll throw around from previous reviews.I'm an American and as the reviews earlier stated, we were theminority there....I'd say about 10% at most. It didn't bother us at all, we pretty much keep to ourselves anyway and other than overhearing a few anti-American comments by guests from other countries, we weren't looked down upon or degraded by anyone.As for the number of topless females, I'd also put it at about 10% at most. Not a big deal at all.The beach was beautiful with plenty of space and chairs to lounge in.One nuisance for those spending the day on the beach, were the lack of bathrooms, you pretty much have to walk back to the lobby of the resort. Which is twice the hike of getting to the bar. Other than that, not much to complain about. I don't think its worth getting caught up in this 5-star vs. 4-star hype. Resort price (not stars) tell the story and for more money you can stay at a more upscale RIU resort. I think overall, for the price we payed for 6 nights, we were rewarded with a great stay.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>