<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a3d8cebc47b3e517a53f30dbe5e81a32" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect! Returned back from RIU Bambu on Tuesday from a weeks holiday, and I wish I was still there! The place was perfect for what we wanted and for the amount we paid it was a bargain and a half.We booked our holiday with Thomsons and I can say that they were 'OK'. There were no problems and they did nothing exceptional.The hotel is lovely and well deserves it 4+t rating from Thomsons. If you are expecting the Hilton then you'll be disappointed, but if you've stayed in a Thomsons 3t hotel before then this will feel like luxury.The pool area isn't that big and perhaps a little noisy at times but the beach is only a few footsteps away and it's nice and peaceful there, with the warm sea. If you want things to do during the day, there are plenty from dance lessons on the beach to darts. We were occasionally asked to join in, but we weren't pested, which was nice.The bar behind the pool is lovely and quiet in the evening (where they do the best margaritas!) and if you didn't know better you may think the bar was closed. Or there is the main area where the entertainment is on, if you want something more lively.The food in the main hall was OK, we always found something we liked. We ate in the al la Carte restaurants 3 of the evenings. The food at the steak house is lovely, but for a more romantic setting the caribbean grill is the place to go (we liked it so much we went there twice!)We were so impressed, that for our next holiday we will be going to a RIU hotel again, and maybe in a few years we will return to the Bambu.If you are planning to stay at the RIU Bambu then I have one piece of advice for you: Stop reading all the reviews and just go and enjoy yourself, I hope you have a fantastic time!! I read some bad reviews and worried a little... when there really was nothing to worry about.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>