<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="d91d264f39684d580e0a4589b739ff63" url=""><![CDATA[Definitely substandard We booked two nights at Novotel Benoa, under advice by the travel agent, but were mostly unhappy about our stay.Problems were largely attributable to peak season, the resort was fully booked. Yet this kind of service is not acceptable. Check-in was very slow, with more than one service assistant holding papers to the next. In spite of our request (made at booking time) of two adjacent rooms (not a strange request after all...we are a family with two kids...), we found out with disappointment that we were given distant rooms on the same floor. Lodging a formal complaint to the hotel manager was impossibile: nobody could find him. The deputy manager greeted the complaints with a Balinese smile, but no action and not even sincere apologies. We were promised a change for the second night, but this was forgotten soon the next day. When we got in our room at 8 pm there were no towels. In one of the two rooms one the two tables with the light next to the bed was missing (only one can read at Novotel Benoa...).The following day we asked to swap our dinner vouchers contemplated in the 1/2 board with lunch vouchers. The first time we were told in an unpolite way this was not possible, at the second attempt we were told it was possible but only for 1 day in the whole stay. The logic of this? Nobody could tell us...The hotel standard rooms are large but quite old and need restyling. The Balinese wooden style is ok, but many items in the furniture were damaged. The bathroom is quite simple and poor. Towels are far from being large and soft.The view from one of the two rooms was hopeless: a messy backyard. Many rooms in the 3-storey wing have same view but they have same price than those overlooking the swimming pool. It's a matter of luck Mr.Customer!The resort is split in two parts by the main road in Benoa, with one Novotel employee facilitating street crossing thanks to a noisy whistle to stop cars and mopeds. The rooms on the sea side are certainly better and less noisy than those on the other side. Do travel agencies know that when they advise customers? Cheaper rooms are obviously lower quality, but why go there when all neighbouring resorts in Benoa do not have this inconvenience? Common areas in the resort are on the contrary quite nice, huge lobby, nice swimming pools. The overall style is cute and typical of Bali. Nice beach with umbrellas an sunbeds.Breakfast is very rich. We tried the beach restaurant twice and were happy. Timely service and good food.Novotel Benoa is surey a 'budget' solution, but at least our experience (bad luck only?) was negative even on the quality to price ratio.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>