<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="cdd03ff8dd81f82eaca879c8ca88658e" url=""><![CDATA[Fine hotel, good location, service so-so We stayed at the Metropark Causeway Bay for 3 nights at the end of our honeymoon in May 2008 (the rest of the honeymoon was spent in Australia). We booked on the hotel website mainly based on the high marks the hotel got on Tripadvisor. It seemed to be the best value available on a decent room in a good location with a good view.We had booked a nonsmoking harbour view room - when we checked in at about 5PM, they said they did not have a room on a nonsmoking floor available. We had to wait in the lobby for about 15 minutes for the room to be serviced, and then when we got to the room we found it had 2 double beds despite asking for a queen bed (and mentioning it was our honeymoon). So we went back to the lobby and had to wait another 15 - 20 minutes for a nonsmoking harborview room with a queen bed to be made available to us. They apologized for the delay, but didn't offer any additional perks to make it up to us or do anything to recognize our honeymoon.Once we finally got settled into our room, our stay was fine. The room was small and the bed fairly hard, but I gather that is standard for HK. The furnishings were high quality and made the most of the limited space. The room was serviced daily and kept very clean. The location is nice - adjacent to an MTR (subway) station and streetcar line (makes it a convenient base of operations), and there are a number of fine restaurants in the blocks right around the MTR station. The room had a nice view overlooking Victoria Park and the harbour, and the view from the rooftop pool area is especially spectacular.Overall we were pretty happy with the hotel, and despite the problems on check-in we'd consider staying here again next time we are in HK. We were not as impressed as a lot of the other reviewers on Tripadvisor, though.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cca5a6a8791b3ff006f345103b3d7afe" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel - a standard Marriott experience This was the first stop on our honeymoon - we stayed at the Sydney Marriott on Hyde Park for 4 nights in May 2008. We booked the room through Priceline so the price was quite reasonable by Sydney standards. We mentioned it was our honeymoon on check-in and they gave us a room on one of the upper floors overlooking Hyde Park.The location was nice and central for exploring Sydney - we walked from there to the botanic gardens, the opera house, circular quay, Paddington market, etc. The hotel was clean and nice. The furnishings in our room were somewhat dated but looked fine. Staff was very friendly. We didn't spend too much time in the hotel but enjoyed it when we were there.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8e42bb15ccc69bddd3ec45e5a13e1121" url=""><![CDATA[Decent hotel, kind of strange location We stayed at the Holiday Inn Darling Harbour for one night, the last night of our honeymoon in Australia. We got to the hotel at about 11:30PM after an evening flight from Cairns and checked out about 5AM to catch our flight home, so we were not at the hotel very long at all.The hotel seemed fine - our room was clean and comfortable. We had a room on the first floor, which had a strange layout - bathroom and closet just inside the door, then about 4 steps town to a sunken bedroom area just big enough for the queen size bed. But furnishings were decent and everything worked OK.The area around the hotel is really Chinatown more than Darling Harbour. There are mostly chinese restaurants in the area adjacent to the hotel, but we found a diner-style place that was still open at midnight to get some food before bed.The hotel suggested we take the airport shuttle instead of a taxi - the shuttle picks up from the hotel every half-hour starting at 5AM. This was a fairly quick way to the airport and it was cheaper than a taxi, only about $10 AUD per person.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>