<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="cec7ccece6007f1fff0c103dceda3374" url=""><![CDATA[My Favorite Hotel in Europe My wife and I stayed at the Sofitel St. James in August 2005 on the first leg of our European honeymoon. We found the staff to be courteous and responsive, hotel to be clean, and the room (their most basic with a single queen bed) to be the most comfortable we would end up having on our entire trip. This Sofitel, like the others I have stayed in, also has a fantastic scent to it as well. We enjoyed the breakfast buffet, which was fresh and had good variety, but was very expensive. I returned again in October, 2006, needing the hotel for a single night before relocating to a friend's flat (they were away from town the first night). I made the mistake of taking the regular subway from Heathrow to Picadilly Circus (took a crowded and hot hour, with dozens of stops), and walking the two blocks to the Sofitel (easy down hill, but the last straw after 7 hours in an airplane and the subway experience -- take Heathrow Express into the City and then a cab!!). By the time I got to the Sofitel, bags in tow, I was sweaty and exhausted. The welcome I received as a returning guest was like none I've received in Europe. They took my bags from me, upgraded me to an executive room, escorted me to the bar, and gave me a cold drink on the house. They then came and found me after my bags were ready for me in my room. The upgraded room was lightyears better than the room we loved so much on our honeymoon. It was a corner room with two floor to ceiling windows with privacy shades that let some light in. It had a huge soaking tub, separate shower, and the standard (which is to say fabulous) Sofitel bed. I took a long hot bath, showered off, and went to bed. I woke up the next morning for a massage I was able to schedule on arrival the night before (they have a small massage room next to their fitness center). They contract out the massage services. The woman who arrived was in her early 20's, and gave me the best deep tissue massage I've ever had. My only complaint about the entire stay was that gratuity was apparently included, but the form I was given to sign after the massage had another blank for gratuity, and I gave her a full tip twice. I'd have been more upset if the massage hadn't been so good. (My only other complaint about the hotel is the lack of a pool or a hottub; if you can get a room with the soaking tub you should be able to make due without).On checkout, the bellman promptly hailed me a cab, and loaded all my things for me. I see no reason to ever stay at a different hotel in London, and will make the Sofitel my foreign home on every future trip.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a07a1e94802e8247025056e79b13004c" url=""><![CDATA[Always my first choice I work at a firm down the street from the Sofitel, and use it as a home away from home during busy periods. I've spent the better part of 30 nights there in the past 18 months. Short summary: I love the place, and always look foward to staying there (even if I'm there because it means I'm too busy at the office to go home at the end of the day).The rooms consistently have the best beds I have encountered anywhere, with heavy down duvets and many down pillows (I will admit the Heavenly brand beds found at high-end Westin properties come in a very close second). Built-in individual halogen reading lamps in the headboard over each side of the bed are a nice touch.Standard rooms are a bit on the small side by U.S. standards, but should be very comfortable for European travellers and those used to hotels in older buildings in big cities. Even a one tier upgrade, to their deluxe rooms, can make a tremendous difference in size, particularly in rooms that face H street (great soundproofing in all rooms, btw. Never hear road noise, even during rushhour on low floors). The rooms are uniformly clean, both upon arrival and at the end of each day. Adequate storage space for clothes for stays up to about a week; much more than that and you may end up keeping some things in your suitcases. Cleaning staff is good about straightening up personal items left in the room, without leaving you with a feeling that someone has gone through your things.The bathrooms make the place, with everything you would need already provided, and great water pressure. They also scent the rooms with something. It is a smell that to this day I cannot identify, but that I associate with soothing feelings even in times of great stress. High speed internet access is good, but expensive - as are the contents of the Minibar. Rooms always seem to have a good work desk and lots of lighting. Staff is excellent, and very responsive, even if there are too many French accents about for my taste.Food in the restaraunt is uniformly good, but uniformly expensive - I rarely ate there when I could not expense it. This is not a problem, as there are a number of good options close by: directly across the street is world-class steak at Bobby Van's (Not cheap either, but i'd put the porterhouse for 2 against Peter Lugar's in NYC). As another user mentioned, Georgia Brown's is 2 blocks away, and a D.C. favorite (Not cheap either, but less than the hotel). The deli at the end of the block (15th and I) is also a great lunch option, as is the Corner Bakery one block further up 15th. If you can get reservations (or are willing to wait for a table / eat at the bar), the Old Ebbitt Grill at the corner of 15th and G is slightly less expensive and not to be missed. For breakfast, there are literally five Starbucks locations within three blocks of the hotel.All told, there are better hotels in the world that this Sofitel, but they are few, far between, and generally much more expensive. No there is not a pool, and no, you don't have a view of the White House (2 blocks away), but for what you actually use a hotel for - the bed, the bath, and a central location, you simply can't go wrong with this one if it is within your price range.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>