<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="eb319a827f31f9386eef5adcb000094c" url=""><![CDATA[Great Resort, Great in Size The grounds at Gran Bahia Principe are beautiful. The upkeep of the resort is impeccable, and the service was also outstanding. I suggest trying to use a little spanish (as bad as you might be), because most of the staff speaks very little english and they are much more accomadating if you try using their language. The beach has calm water, plenty of chairs and umbrellas, and is private. You can rent a variety of non-motorized boats at the beach free as well (reservations required).The hotel has about 6 pools, all of which are vast, shallow, and have swim up bars. Chairs at the pools are in abundance because each is so huge. Each pool has unique activities from aerobics, vollyball, dancing, ping pong, water polo, however most activities take place in the main pool by the beach. The hotel has a large variety of a la carte restaurants and buffets style ones. WIth the all inclusive you can go to 3 a la carte meals a week (reservations required), and as many buffets as you like. The buffet food was decent at best, the a la carte was very good. One night as an a la carte meal they had a BBQ of jumbo shirmp, strip steaks, lamb, filet mignon, chicken, and flank steak, and it was all you can eat. This meal was outstanding. The drinks keep flowing, but most are served in small cups. They have all liquors and only a few premium ones and only presidente beer. The room are very large and clean, all have balcony/terrace, all have a whirlpool tub, and the minibar is restocked daily free of charge. The nighttime entertainment is pretty weak, and the shows did not keep my interest. The hotel has a mix of people from Europe, Canada, and the U.S.The only major NEGATIVE of the resort is it's IMMENSE SIZE!!! Most of the rooms will require you to get on a trolly to get to the beach because the place is vast, however the trolly runs often. You can walk from end to end of the resort in about 20 minutes, but all the dining facilities can range from 5 to 15 minute walk. The complex is very spread out, so be prepared to do some walking, even with the trolly.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>