<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="2b1ee8551afaadee7d326b9e8174fec3" url=""><![CDATA[Before you stay here, think twice if you think you get what you pay for!!!! OK, so this place has some bright spots, but the bad really outshines the good and it really sinks in and cannot be overlooked; especially when you are paying over $600 a night, this basically amounts to a 'Less than Ritz Carlton experience. Having stayed at other RC locations in the past few years, I have to say I was not at all impressed.Starting with our arrival, my wife and I and good friends of ours arrived at the hotel at 11:30am from Newark Liberty. The flight was only 3.5 hours, which is what makes Puerto Rico so attractive to so many in our area. The hotel is a 10 minute drive from the airport, which was great, and the taxi drivers we had during our four day visit were very nice...no shuttle to and from the hotel, but no big deal as it is very easy to catch a cab. So, are we ready for the problems??? We get to the hotel, we are greeted by a bell hop, he takes our bags, puts them on the baggage cart and leads us to the lobby; very nicely maintained, not huge but nice, open and airy, a good feeling of being away...and then I see there is a line of about 15 people infront of me and my wife and our friends, waiting to check in, not thinking it was a big deal as there were four girls at the front desk. 25 minutes later, I finally get to the front desk, offered a bottle of water while waiting and was told that my room was not ready. I was told that if I gave my cell phone number, someone would contact me when it was ready. I booked my trip with American Express Platinum Travel Services, and received a nice welcome from the front desk, warm smiles and lots of yes', to make me feel like this was just a minor set back and things would get better....After being told that the eligible upgrade was not available (fine, not a problem, this is the Ritz, how bad can it be) I would be given $100.00 credit during my stay and was told that an effort would be made in waiting for my room since I was a member. Great, that made me feel good...now, I ask where can I go and change, while I wait near the pool, as I was told I could do, while my room was prepared? Well, sir, you can go to the men's room, with your suitcase and change into a bathing suit. I am easy going, as is my wife and our friends, so we drag our suitcases into the mens and ladies room, change and go to the pool. Nice grounds, nice pool, and the first thing I noticed was that there is no kids pool and lots of families with kids. My wife and I, and our friends are in our mid 30's, we have a two year old, who we left home so we could relax, and low and behold, the pool is loaded with screaming, jumping, splashing children with parents who cannot control them. Fine, we are all easy going we say, nothing that an ipod can't tune out, right? We lay out for a bit, and get hungry, we head to the bar/ cafe at the pool. We ordered some hamburgers, a turkey wrap, salads. I would say that isnt to hard to make, well, I was wrong. After waiting 45 minutes, at a cafe where there werent to many people, for the burgers, salads and the wrap, I took a few bites, and my wife didnt even want to eat hers, our friends werent happy and we all felt that the food was not that great!!! We all looked at each other, and were hoping this was just a fluke, but we had no clue what we were in for. This was at 1:30pm and we figured hopefully we would get our phone call any minute and we would soon be in our room, unpacking and getting back out to the excellent sunshine, the only thing we wanted to do here in the first place; sun and relaxation at The Ritz!!! 2pm, 3pm, 4pm, 4:30pm, still no phone call, still no room, for either of us. I decided to go to the front desk, and there was still a line of people. I get in line again and after 10 minutes, I call out to our bell hop who was pretty cool and rembered me. I pleaded to him to see if there was something he could do as I did not want to wait another 1/2 hour to reach the front desk,just to find out if my room was ready. 10 minutes later he emerges, he lets me know that the room is ready and would take my bags to the room right away...relief is on its way. Oh, I had to ask for my friends as well, that took another 10 minutes. We get to the room, nothing spectacular, not much of a view but clean, nicely decorated, satisfying, but not up to other Ritz Carlton's that I have been to. We decided to shower; a clean bathroom, plenty of towels, plenty of Bulgari amenities and we got ready for dinner. We were really looking foward to dinner, as we were going to BLT Steak in the hotel, as there is one in NYC and every raves about the food...here come the let downs again...I dont know if the kitchens are as understaffed as the hotel, but again, the food iand service is terrible. I ordered a caesar salad, wasn't great, my wife, she had a salad, have had better at a NJ diner, and they werent cheap either...my skirt steak was good, my wifes king crab legs, mediorce, dinner costs us $200 for the two of us, same for our friends, and was worth 1/2 that at the most; I have had better dinner at The Cheesecake Factory. We headed to bed after a brief walk around the grounds of the hotel and a stop in the lounge. We got into a comfortable bed, and had a good night sleep. The next moring, we have breakfast at Mares in the hotel, it was complimentary with our stay each moring, and was good but not worth the $26.00 per person one would normally pay, I wouldn't recommend it if you are paying for it. After breakfast, I headed to the gym, like I did every morning of my stay, and it could have been larger compared to other hotels I have been to. I waited for a treadmill as they have limited cardio equipment, 5 to 6 treadmills and 4 EFX machines, two bikes...the weight training equipment is limited as well, older equipment, and just not up to par. The streching, abs, spin room was better equiped and had much more of a lively feeling...the main room is cramped, tight, hot and not to gym standards. After my workout, I showered in the mens locker room, again, just ok, I have been in nicer equipped locker rooms in lesser hotels, and headed to the pool, once again, greeted by kids and families, and there was no way you could relax here. We met other couples from our area with similar disappointing aspects of the hotel and were wondering why there wasnt a kids pool, why was the service so lacking we all felt the same way; is this really a Ritz Carlton? My favorite part of the pool had to be the couple who had their pack and play at the steps of the pool, their chairs at the steps of the pool and their rafts, with them on them in the pool, holding on to the railing leading into the pool, and had the nerve to say, you know what I hate about laying by the stair, the traffic... My wife and friends were jaw dropped, as we would never ever sit our childs play pen right in the middle of where people enter and leave the pool, let alone even have her there below a year old in the first place!!! Seriously, am I being overly dramatic here, because I am trying like crazy not be at all negative towards this place, just telling it like it is, as I was paying so much and getting so little. This is just not what I expected from a Ritz Carlton. My wife and my friends wife wanted a drink, anything, so I looked around, and one, I counted one waitress at the pool and this poor thing was running around trying to make everyone happy, but waiting guests makes for unhappy guest. I figured after 15 minutes of trying to flag her down from the other end of the pool, I decided to go get the drinks myself...when she finally got over to our side of the pool, she apologized ever so nicely and asked us if we needed anything, no nothing right now, but thanks for the apology was all I could say. I felt really bad for her, because you could see she was working her rear off, and there was no one to help here, and the understaffing was clearly seen here. There had to be 5 to 6 guys standing around handing out towels and fixing chairs for guest, and I was thinking, why wouldnt the manager have one of these guys take drink orders and help this poor girl??? This day ended the same as the last, going to the room, showering, and heading out to a mediocre dinner, but this time at Il Mulino, which is also in the hotel, and another huge let down...isnt this supposed to be one of the best Italian restaurants in NYC??? Again, I think it has to do with staffing and the kitchen, but the food and teh service was just not good...I am 100% Italian, I grew up in the NYC area and I think I have an understanding of good food and this is just not good food. I have been to quite a few restaurants in NYC, northern NJ and around the world at numerous hotels, and in their own ways, they all blow these restaurants away, and some for half the price. Day three went pretty much the same way, sub par food, screaming kids, lines, long waits for drinks, but nice weather for tanning and nice greetings from a staff that you can see knows they are in way over their heads, and try to my pleasure you into getting over it...it doesnt work...I smile, but it doesnt work. To this point, I haven't talked to a manager, first, because I don't like to be a complainer looked at as some snooty New Yorker with an attitude. I am just an average guy who is on vacation with his wife and friends trying to have a good time at a nice place, and believe me, like many, we do not mind paying a little extra for something good and something that is worth its price...secondly, I was seriously hoping this stay would have a miracle cast upon it. But I know this isn't the case and I am starting to feel like I am being robbed here folks. This nice guy is starting to realize he is being taken for granted by the Ritz Carlton San Juan, which at this point is looking more like the Marriott San Juan with nice grounds and a nice lobby!!! So, our last day comes, and we got up and went to the beach today to get away from the rants of the pool. We were nicely greeted at the beach entrance, and were led to chairs, towels and umbrellas at the place of our choice; nice beach, very fine sand and a nice warm ocean, great...we should have done this from the beginning I started to think, but who would know that we would wait once again for any type of service on the beach...not seeing a single service person on the beach until we were getting ready to leave didnt make for a happy beach day. I just dont understand how a place like this could be so understaffed and so inexperienced. When it was time to check out, I became a little smarter (too late though) so I sat down at lunch, ordered my food, then went to the front desk line, knowing it would be a wait of at least a half hour or so to get to the front desk once again, and guess what...when I finally checked out and went back to my table where my wife and friends were waiting, I only had to wait an additional 15 minutes for the food to get there, LOL!!!...I would have complained to a manager, but was told that she (Jackie) was not available and someone would call her if I wished to wait...No thanks, but I have to catch a plane in an hour to make it back to reality and I don't want to miss it. For the price, go someplace else, I recommend the One Only Resort locations, much better staff, much better food, much better EVERYTHING!!!! Puerto Rico, my apologies, but I won't be coming back as the only thing you have going for you at this point is the sun, and you can get that just about anywhere for free!!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>