<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="0e56d85e3b0c5c2ac75c5ca8a1eb37ad" url=""><![CDATA[Mixed feelings A group of us (14 total) just came back from Punta Cana 1/29/05 - 2/5/05. We booked with a Travel Agent for Apple Vacations. The hotel is very Romantic (should be noted couples only) in our group we had a couple singles and they had a good time but.....I enjoyed the food/drinks but yes a few had some dates with the toilet most of the week.Some of us had been to the Bavaro last January and LOVED it so that is why we came back. That hotel mentioned the guys to wear slacks, but when we got there - others were in shorts. So this year's hotel we checked several locations (Internet, web sites, etc.) so some of our guys didn't pack slacks but very nice Docker shorts. Well our first night there we were turned away from the restaurants. After speaking with the Manager the hotel did accomodate us very well. So yes, they want you HAPPY. So no compaints about the Hotel.Now the charter company Allegiant Air (who we traveled with last year) our return flights are the worst. Last year the flight crew (only way to say it) STUNK. This years at least they were up front with us. Both times the pilot hat to beg for more fuel. They only wanted to give us enough to fly to Florida or the states. Last year in the middle of the day (very hot) we sat in the plane with the doors open but still melting and a few almost passed out, for a hour or two. Yesterday we were suppose to leave Punta Cana at 515pm they had Technical problems so was delayed for 2 hours, then was told 3 more hours. Luckily Apple kept us at our hotel this whole time. So instead of leaving at 515pm we left at 1130pm - which put us in St. Louis at 145am. You have to check-out of your room at noon. So we had some very unhappy campers to say the least. Again I want to mentions Apple Vacations and Secrets were very accomodating. Our group will never fly Allegient Air again. This flight crew did bend over backwards to help us feel better but burned once ok the second time--- no more.Sorry so long winded just had to vent.I had a wonderful time but glad to be back home. Thanks for listening
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>