<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="4bf8fc504f91a6b1ad011741258e400e" url=""><![CDATA[Waikiki Wave - Great Location and Value My wife and I stayed at Waikiki Wave for 8 nights, 8/28-9/5 2008 for our first visit to Hawaii. I made the selection due to the high rating on TripAdvisor as well as the central location. We arrived around 10pm after a 12+ hour flight from Florida via Atlanta...and check-in was quick. I had booked a Deluxe Room...and noticed that the day before we left that although the rate for the first 3 days of our stay had gone up, the last 5 days the cost had gone down...I emailed and asked if we could take advantage of the new rates, and got an immediate email response that canceled our first reservation and a new reservation made that saved us over $100 for the 8 nights. MUCH APPRECIATED!Although we came back many afternoons to find that our room had not been refreshed yet, having previously had part ownership in a Sleep Inn, I can understand the need to make over the rooms of those that check-out before doing the rooms of the continuing guests. Our room was on the 12th floor (1213) which allowed great views to the east -- and even the top most point of Diamond Head, a couple wide views of the Pacific to the south, and view of the north with great rainbows after the short afternoon rain over the mountain. The balcony overlooked the entertainment area of the International Market Place... which always ended by 10pm, so was not an interference at all for sleep.The Expedia staff at the Concierge staff were very helpful in making suggestions for tours, and we did a last minute choice to fly to the Big Island for the Volcano Night tour. We did not rent a car -- but walked almost everywhere due to the central location to Waikiki. We did get the 4-day Visitor Bus Pass for $20 and used it for such trips to Diamond Head and even to the North Shore to get one of the famous snow cones. We had gone past it on our Grand Island Tour a few days earlier ... and Honolulu has an amazing public bus transit system.We usually ate breakfast in our room (did not opt for the continental breakfast plan) since we had a microwave and refrigerator. We found that most all the nicer eating places had lunch prices or early birds until 5 or 6pm. We saved a great deal by eating earlier. This included Cheesecake Factory, Atlantis, etc. The gift shop at the front entrance had deals as good as the International Market Place and Dukes Lane, and went in there about everyday to pick up shirts, hats, even snacks. The clerk was tireless there from open to close and very helpful. (The Food Pantry just a couple blocks away across the street to the east is a full grocery store, and a better option to the ABC Stores for food items - has deli areas as well.)Aqua Resorts seem to have their act together and have done almost a phenomenal job at remodeling this older hotel (a few cracked tiles in the shower, but all plumbing worked fine). The bed was one of the most comfortable we have had in a hotel ... the decor was exactly like their website photos - no bait switch and tactics with the photos. The lobby was smaller than the larger hotels but more than adequate with a seating area, the concierge desks, and a few small shops, plus a couple restaurants, business center, etc. The free Wi-Fi seemed slow although I had a very good to excellent signal ... so opted for my Sprint Broadband Wireless modem most of the time. All the staff from the front desk to maintenance to housekeeping always greeted us with an Aloha and/or Mahalo which shows they really care about their guests.This is certainly a location to consider as an option to the higher priced rooms in the area...and very centrally located.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>