<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="f1964fa21b178997c315401e2700287e" url=""><![CDATA[Would definitely stay again We enjoyed our stay at this hotel very much. They were very professional and I think it's a very nice hotel. They were helpful and accomodating. We stayed in a double double room, which was larger than a standard 2 double bed room and it was very adequate in size. The room was clean. It also had a big closet to store our luggage but they didn't have much shelf space to put clothes. There was a dresser with 3 drawers and that was it. The bathroom was large, except there wasn't much space for toiletries, so we had to be creative. The shower was good; It didn't change water temperature while using it and the spray was strong. Thanks to suggestions of other reviewers, we requested a room that was not on the main street and was much quieter. However, you do have to give up any kind of view and some natural light. It was a tradeoff we were glad we made though. They were nice enough to clear out the mini bar so that we could use it as a refrigerator. The pillows and comforter were made of down. The TV was a Sony flat screen and there was a DVD player and CD clock radio. The lobby area was also very nice. The concierge was helpful. The hotel is very well located. I would definitely stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="40ccf357d00df9edf6199f154997f3f6" url=""><![CDATA[Very Satisfied We stayed for a week and I would defintitely stay at this hotel again. I thought that the staff was very helpful and the rooms are good sized and clean. We used the concierge quit a bit and they were very helpful. On the 12th floor there is always free coffee and tea available as well as 3 computers with internet access. However, I should mention that whenever I tried to use the computer they were all taken. I did not use the restaurant at all so I cannot comment on that. We requested a refrigerator, which they provided free of charge, and we chose to eat cereal in our room. There are safes inside the room which is nice to have. The one thing that bothered me about the room was that the bathroom door did not stay open. It always closed and that might be because it was very close to the door of the room so they have it purposely set to close. I found myself propping it open with the waste basket for the times where I didn't need the door closed. The location of the hotel is great. There is a big drugstore (Duane Reed) right next to the hotel and a CVS a block away. Also a block away was a McDonalds and a deli/store. The hotel is a about a mile from Times Square. Times Square are is so loud and crowded that I was glad to stay at a hotel away from that area. We sometimes walked there and back and other times we took the subway. THere is a subway station right next to the hotel and another one a couple blocks away. The area seems very safe and there are lots of people walking around at night. They have a Lincoln towncar that takes you to LaGuardia for $35 so that was nicer than taking a cab.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>