<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="3f07eea2eea155bff2815bf3dc5b251c" url=""><![CDATA[Overall Good, missed details Just returned from a stay a ppc with friends. Overall the resort was very nice. The food was good, not great, just good. The staff was good for the most part. The rooms were nice. The resort just has some work to do to smooth out the details to become really first class.Arrived late at punta cana by about 8 hours due to the ice storm on the east coast and the total incompetentcy of whomever runs Philadelphia Airport. (Easily the WORST airport in the nation)We were immediatly jumped on by the baggage handlers at punta cana airport. They are very aggressive. When we asked for a cab we were hussled to a cab that in hindsight was probably working with the baggage handler. The ride to PPC was done without the usage of headlights (very exciting) since the cab had some sort of mechanical problem. I suggest you call your resort and have them send a cab instead of using one of the cabs hanging around the airport.When we arrived at the resort there was some confusion because of the expedia booking system when you split one resevation for 4 people between two credit cards. Expedia puts all the tickets and rooms under the name of the first credit card. There we met a Bellman named Eddie Wilson ( a true shining bright spot of our trip) We were taken to our room and found it was not the jetted tub upgrade we had paid for. Eddie Wilson ( who speaks english, a rareity at PPC) got on the phone to the front desk and told them that we had to have an upgraded room. From what I could catch with my VERY LIMITED spanish the front desk wanted to put us in a room for the night and fix it tommorrow. Eddie insisted they fix the problem NOW. He stayed with us and 30 minutes and several phone calls later we had our upgraded room. Then while we unpacked Eddie Wilson went back to the front desk and got our keys changed. My wife tipped him $10 and from that point on he looked out for us and tried his best to take care of us.Here is where they started to miss the details necessary to become a true 5 star resort. We were unable to make golf starting times even though greens fees were included in our package because the guest relations desk had closed. We were unable to get a lock for our in room safe because they were out of them at the front desk. The next day my friend and I attempted to get a golf starting time at guest relations and we were told just to go out to the golf course because they always have cancelations. The course the resort includes in the golf package is a 15 minute ride from the resort. When we got there we were told the starting times were full. We tried to make starting times for the rest of the week and we had 2 choices 7:20 AM or 11:45 am. nothing in betweenso we scheduled some of each. We then returned to the resort and found that our wives had been unable to get beach towels because they ran out of them (another detail missed)The remainder of our stay was typical resort, eat too much, drink too much and play a lot of golf. You have to walk a lot from the residential area to the Lobby area, about 1/4 mile because they do not have enough shuttles running (anohter detail missed) so be prepared. The target groups for PPC is Euorpeans and Families not American Couples.We extended our room to 2 pm on get away day and had our fried Eddie Wilson pick us up get our cab to the airport. All smooth on the way out.If you go to PPC DO:Ask for Eddie WilsonGet up early to get a beach towelMake all your starting times for your stay ASAP with the golf courseEat lunch at the beach buffet at least onceLearn some Spanish before you go.DO NOTRely on guest relations, she (there is only one) is overwhelmedExpect the staff or the waitstaff to speak englishExpect to get a snack between 4 and 6 all food service shuts downGo near the casino, just burn your money its faster
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>