<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="8565bd673a62af303c11210f408e124b" url=""><![CDATA[5 Stars and thumbs up! Stayed here as the first stop of my in Bali, and all I can say is Ellie's is a damn good deal. From just USD40, you get a spacious (really HUGE!) and fully equiped modern room (with or without balcony), with a splendid bathroom stocked with home-made toiletries. Included is a decent breakfast, return transfers, dvd library that comes with Extras and Little Britain, and last but not least, Sam's excellent hospitality.One thing that impressed me most: On the day of our departure, Jean the contracted driver who was supposed to send us to Kuta was working, so Sam arranged and paid for a taxi transfer. I don't usually expect this level of service from an inn, but Sam remains committed to his guests so that's brilliant.Although the location of the inn may not be beach front, or right smack in a 'hip' area, but its a short journey to everywhere. With Sam's recommendation, we went on a 5 hour trip to Gerger beach (damn gorgeous beach with minimal sunbathers), Uluwatu for sunset, and Jimbaran beach for dinner, all for just Rp270,000 in Jean's super comfortable leather upholstered land rover. Fyi, Jean is Ellie's contracted driver, a down-to-earth honest guide, and he stays next door.I'm glad I chose Ellie's over Westin and Conrad, as it was a good opportunity to experience balinese hospitality minus the absurb touristy expenses. Although we only stayed for a night, it was certainly memorable and I can't wait to be back. Sam and Lucy: Congratulations on your upcoming wedding! Best wishes from Singapore!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="469102997ee72e2737be5687d7ceda0e" url=""><![CDATA[Understated luxury More photos
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f0a6dbd39db4b69b33ee21e1ec7fe64b" url=""><![CDATA[Quaint Location - Must Try! Was given a very good rate hence decided to give the hotel a try. Initially concerned about the location as there's no MTR station within sight, but alas my fears were unfounded! Hotel Jen is located in a smashing neighbourhood full of local eateries and McD and KFC and even a wet market nearby! Best of all, its only 10 mins by bus to Central for everything posh and luxurious! Hotel has everything I need without being OTT. Luxurious bedding, free wifi (which is EXTREMELY IMPT IMO), dvd player, decent restaurant, fantastic seaview (ok not the pretty harbour who cares), pool and a gym, which is extremely rare for mid-range HK hotels. The hotel also has in place plenty of green features such as electricity auto switch off once key card is removed from slot.My only gripe is the Jen Lounge which although is pretty, lacks in service. During both times I was there, the only staff on duty felt sloppy, and breakfast was simply not inviting. Croissants and other breads were cold and hard, so I suggest its wiser to eat at the cafe. The hotel also offers a hourly shuttle bus service (mornings and evenings only) to 6 locations, so you can conveniently use it for macau ferry transfer, mtr connection or even pick-up/drop off to HK station for mtr to the airport. Brilliant!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="475c428b41303d9cce5e2df3aae29e49" url=""><![CDATA[Stay Away thin mattress camoflaged by duvet
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7f4188916f89766240e8545722fd857a" url=""><![CDATA[Fireworks fiesta! Threw a party over the weekend (5/8) to catch the fireworks festival, and the view from 1802 (Marina) was superb. Loved the humongous Sharp Aquos LCD tv, a DVD player is also provided so remember to bring your own movies.Other than the delicious bak kut teh and very fresh orange juice, Breakfast spread was just so so. IMO, Oriental wins hands-down.Late check-out was not accomodated, rollaways fully taken despite request made more a month ago, but otherwise requests were met within a short period of time.Worth staying only with a good rate.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>