<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="cb2a37b8fc87f83479a921b6fe191e79" url=""><![CDATA[Lovely hotel We had a wonderful stay in this hotel. We arrived off the Eurostar quite early and took a taxi to the hotel, hoping that we could drop off our luggage and then check in later. Even though we were early, the hotel found us a room which was lovely. In addition to the some of the traveller photos, we had a separate walk-in shower.The only downside of the hotel was the restaurant. We came back having walked all over Paris during the day, and just wanted an easy meal without having to set out again. The hotel's restaurant is Japanese style and seemed very stylised, rather than offering the sort of food we wanted. In the end we headed over to Carr's and had a meal there, which was nice, but quite expensive.The other recommendation that we'd make is to bring your fitness and swimming gear. We didn't - but checked out the pool and gym and they looked great. We would definitely bring our stuff with us the next time we visit.The best thing about the hotel is it's location - it's so central and yet very quiet. We loved it and would definitely stay here again.I would reiterate some of the comments about the prices charged by the hotel. We were waiting for a taxi to go back to Gare du Nord and ordered two coffees in the lobby - this came to about 25 euro, which I thought was excessive.There's so much to see and do in Paris that we didn't spend enough time in the hotel, but it's a great base to have for your stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1511845f92d60ab37685dfb2c1b6079e" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent hotel and location We stayed in the Covent Garden hotel for a long weekend over the May Bank Holiday, arriving on Friday and departing on Sunday. We booked a deluxe double for our stay and were in Room 6. Initially I was a bit disappointed with the room as it's on the ground floor and faces out onto Shaftesbury Avenue so you can see people on the buses going by! However, the quality of the room and the bathroom (plus the blinds, curtains and sound proofing in the room) is such that you soon forget exactly where you are as it's so quiet there!The check-in was very efficiency and the staff were very friendly and helpful. The location is fabulous as you're in the heart of Seven Dials and so it's no distance to go shopping in Covent Garden, or go down to Soho or to any of the theatres. Excellent location, but so bad for the wallet!We met some friends on the Saturday evening and it was no problem for them to meet us in the residents lounge for cocktails. The hotel was very accommodating in this regard.We had breakfast included in our room rate, and the breakfast is also great. Couple of niggles - it seems to take a long time for food to come out to you and so it's not too hot when it arrives. The buffet for the continental breakfast it great - there's lots of choice, but the honey pot that's out on display is full of honey so old that it's gone granular and it's impossible to get it out of the dish. But, small things in comparison to everything else.The shower in our room was to die for! I was drying my hair and I heard my partner getting into the shower. Then I heard the shower go off ... then two minutes later I heard it go back on again - yes, he'd got back in to the shower to have another go - it was that good!!We would definitely return to this hotel for another long weekend - just have to save up first!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>