<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="661129ce1bbc265ea8cb0827756016df" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location - wonderful time We stayed at the Edenh 3/10/08 - 3/17/08. After reading many negative comments here we decided to go in very open-minded to their problem areas. First, the positive. The location is fantastic, beach is gorgeous, property was clean and neat (no glass seen around beach). the staff was very corteous, from the moment we arrived from the aiport. Check in was very smooth, room was ready about 3:30 pm and was on the 4th floor as we requested. We stayed in 2421 so we had a pool/ocean view and that was wonderful. The bar in the lobby area had Great bartenders, especially Luis and Julio (thanks guys) who made the drinks we requested perfectly, even though they had never made a long beach before. We got great service from them every day. we had green wrist bands and so no difference in treatment to us vs pink bands. If you are ok without 'brand' name liquor, I would not upgrade.The food was decent, plenty to choose from, but I would not say it was gourmet. We were able to get in to all 4 ala carte restaurants. The Italian and the Asian were our favorites. The spa and casino were open and we enjoyed both.Now on some of the negative areas. Yes, they do need more beach chairs. We tried to get chairs one day at 6:45 AM and they were all already reserved. We decided to just lay our towels on the sand and enjoy a few hours on the beach anyway. Pool chairs were available for us all week, even as late as 10 AM, which was better than prior reviews told us. Hopefully they will add more to the beach soon.the reservation system for the restaurants is still as noted with long lines. Again, went in without expecting to get in to all. We would get there at 6:30 - 7 pm (party of 2) and were able to get into all but steak house on first try. took 3 nights to get into steak house, but Italian and French both had openings 2 of those nights we were turned down. If you have a larger party, you probably need to get there earlier, but honestly, the dinner buffet had steak, chicken, pasta, fish, etc that the cooks were grilling for you and they all tasted good.The bathroom scenario - it is very contemporary. Since it was only hubby and I, worked out fine, but I can see issues if sharing room with others. Not sure if the hotel will ever close up' that opening, so larger groups may need to try to put up some kind of divider for privacy.Overall we enjoyed our trip and would definitely go back again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>