<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="3d9f03462941b1a297628a70fe46ff20" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderfull hotel A really fabulous hotel. Amazing entrance lobby with huge fresh flower displays, plenty of glass, gold, mirrors chandeliers. To get the best out of this hotel use the Executive floor which has a comfortable private lounge with free refreshments and light snacks all day. It's great to use this hotel as a base, go out for a few hours, come back to the nice lounge and recharge with a snack and drink before going out again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bc64ad1955ad2c8aacbe5700913224c7" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel Typical balcony
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="906c8a477ee68146198dcc2d685102ed" url=""><![CDATA[Renaissance Parc 55 A well located hotel near all the action. Particularly good for Union Square, shopping and the cable car terminus.A medium quality hotel which does everthing correctly and efficiently. High level rooms are better than lower level which, as previous reviewers noted, are tired and in need of a makeover. The Club Lounge on 31st floor is unusually open 7 days a week and provides a good continental breakfast buffet, all day coffee and a small evening finger buffet and a limited selection of deserts. Good views from the lounge due it being several floors higher than neighbouring buildings. The only problem with the club lounge is the lack of tables for breakfast, as it is laid out as a lounge with sofas and low level glass topped coffee tables. It gets busy in the mornings as it caters for 3 executive floors as well as overspill from lower level rooms when the exec floors are overbooked. Check-in was a bit slow due to lack of staff at the front desk, (only one check-in attendant) but checking out was fast using the express checkout facility. 6 express lifts, ground to 31st floor in about 30 seconds and very little waiting in lobbies after calling for a lift.If you have booked a high level room with club access make sure you get it, don't be fobbed off with a lower level room with card access to the lounge as they try to get away with if you let them. The lower level rooms are not in very good condition and don't have the superb views that the high level rooms have.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>