<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="8015e71cd0632b93e2e65b8e833d8771" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Play To Stay We stayed at the Bali Hyatt Sanur Beach for 3 nights in early March. It was a rather last minute decision to book at this hotel so I know I did not get the best rate for our ocean view standard room, but still, it wasn't totally over the top ($140 for the Sunday night, then $175/nt for Mon and Tues night). Our rate included a breakfast buffet which was plentiful and very tasty. The hotel grounds are quite lovely with two pools and access to the beach. If you are looking for a swimming beach however, I don't think the beach in the back of the hotel is ideal. I would describe it more as a beach to sunbathe on or to splash around in. That was a bit disappointing to my boyfriend who enjoys swimming in the ocean. Our room, though a little old in appearance, was comfy. I liked the location of the hotel because we were able to walk to many shops and very good restaurants (we highly recommend Massimo's if you need a break from Indonesian food and want some delicious Italian at cheap prices). As with most Balinese hotels, the service was excellent at the Hyatt. I don't know if we'd book here again in the future but we did enjoy our stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1baf9f7ac7c8c6427729a74a8b4dff5e" url=""><![CDATA[Too Beautiful For Words! We just returned from our vacation in Bali and part of our trip was spent at the Alam Shanti in Ubud. If you would like to experience a little bit of Heaven on Earth, then my advice is to book a room at this hotel. Actually, the rooms are more like little bungalows set amidst the exquisite landscape of Ubud. You are literally swept away in a nature wonderland of sorts where the sounds of birds, frogs, gecko's, chickens, and all types of insects will lull you to sleep and literally be nature's alarm clock for you in the morning when it's time to wake up.Due to availability, we had the chance to stay in three different bungalows during our stay at Alam Shanti (Saraswati, Dewi, and Laksmi rooms). All I can say is, WOW! the rooms are all gorgeous with marble bathrooms, beautiful and comfortable beds, and views that are simply amazing. I'd recommend getting a 2nd floor room if possible because like I said, the views are amazing. The 2nd floors all have a terrace or balcony of some sort, usually with a nice big daybed and table and chairs where you can enjoy your morning breakfast which is served in your room. Of the 3 rooms we stayed in, Laksmi was the only one on the first floor but it too was pretty gorgeous (the first floors have a very huge porch area--also quite lovely). Not only were the rooms quite impressive, but I have to say that the staff at Alam Shanti were quite exceptional. Saying that they were friendly is only half of it. The staff, from reception to housekeeping, to the drivers, went above and beyond their call of duty, in my opinion. They were always ready and eager to assist with anything we needed, from helping with transportation, to ordering room service from the local restaurant, to just being so warm and wonderful to all their customers.We LOVED this place and hope to return in the future.Thank-you Alam Shanti for helping to make our vacation so fantastic!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>