<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="a80c0d52877b6d6699c50e786de40ecf" url=""><![CDATA[Secluded yet central, with top-notch hospitality Bed
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="69322cd5cfeda4f2491fc3240da1dc6b" url=""><![CDATA[Brilliant views of the Empire State Building! I stayed here for eight nights and can't recommend it enough. I asked for a room with a view and I got it - the Empire State Building. The king size, comfortable bed had seven soft pillows on it, flatscreen TV, wonderful light streaming in, and plenty of room for your purchases.There's no room service, but with New York at your doorstep who needs it? There's a coffee maker and empty fridge in each room. Downstairs, there's free coffee, a small shop selling junk food and drinks, a vending machine and ice. You can also order a breakfast in the morning, which was delicious and affordable for hotel standards (but you're better off going to the deli next door for a $3 breakfast).The internet terminal downstairs is free, too, but understandably this was often busy.Staff were so friendly - I had no problems cashing travellers' cheques or asking advice about things such as airport transfers.The basement gym was small but modern, with TVs attached to virtually every piece of equipment.Location is great - just five mins walk from Herald Square and Times Square is just around the corner (but not too close as to cause headaches!). Bryant Park is also good for a laze.This place is one of my favourites in New York - it's not the most glamorous but it's comfortable, it's clean, there are brilliant views and it's central. What more could you want?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c441a24cfb966663684f6de91dae3d33" url=""><![CDATA[Why all the fuss? I'm not sure why this hotel generates all the overwhelmingly positive reviews it does.I arrived late at night (11pm), only to be told they couldn't find my booking - when I had the reservation and confirmation number in front of me, clear as day. Their revenue manager who would be able to dig around to find the booking was not there until the morning so until then, they made me sign a guarantee to pay their full rates just in case -- and asked me to see her the next morning. As the full rates were more than double the rate I was paying, I was a little worried and didn't sleep well.Next morning, the person I spoke to said it was all sorted out; it had been a computer problem. This was a relief, and I was told it had happened to several other people -- but I didn't appreciate having to sign that piece of paper the night before, even if it was policy.In addition, a four-minute call to upstate NY cost me almost $30. I know hotels add a surcharge, but I couldn't believe it.As for the room, it had a view of a construction site (at 11pm I was too tired to ask for another room, and I would be out all next day). The room was well sized but very dark - not much light came in at all, and the indoor lights were weak. I was squeezed in a corner next to the amenities room which was constantly opening and closing. If I were you, I would make sure I got a suitable room with a view and light. The bed was comfortable.The airy gym was very good, with free fruit, drinks, towels and shower facilities.Midtown location was excellent - just minutes away from MoMa, Rockefeller Center and major subway stops.So all in all, service wasn't very good, location was excellent, and the hotel, for what I was paying, was underwhelming.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d859df0957be5a8ccecb8c2918d36db4" url=""><![CDATA[Quiet, comfy, free Wi-Fi I've been staying at this hotel for several nights and am writing this review from their room while on my laptop just before I check out! There is 100% free wireless internet (ask at reception for the code) which you can access in your room - so it's perfect if you want to combine business with sightseeing.The staff are friendly and speak English. I chose a double room with a shared toilet and shower, never had to wait to use either and both were clean. The room I chose was actually quite large by Parisian standards (maybe because it hasn't got a bathroom) - there is room for a desk, open wardrobe, comfy double bed, two bedside tables, phone, a washing basin, luggage rack and safe, and still room to do sit-ups! The safe was deep enough to fit my 15-inch laptop. The room overall was very clean, fresh and tidy.Cons are few. The lift is rickety and gives an almighty jolt as it hits your floor which was disconcerting, and the breakfast is, in my opinion, overpriced so I didn't choose it (there are many restaurants and creperies outside and it's very close to the Blvd Haussmann and several Metro/bus stops). Also, the TV doesn't have English cable channels, but this is no big deal when there's so much to see outside (and free internet). But if you're with kids, don't channel surf at night as you may get a surprise - it appears some of the more adult channels are not censored.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>