<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="33f2873fc640bf2649d9425347f24ff2" url=""><![CDATA[Best in Toronto We have stayed in numerous top hotels in Toronto but this place beats them all .. 4 Season, The Savoy, St Germain etc do not truly compare with the level of service, comfort of rooms and amenities.Each of the other hotels has its distinct pluses but none compare with Soho .. 4 Seasons location for restaurants and interestng shops of Yorkville and committment to service .. Savoy's ambience .. St Germain rooms but it is snooty and cold feeling .. the only down side is the Sohos's location .. a stiff walk to main attractions and better restaurants BUT close to night life of King Street and the funky shops on Queen St.We will be back!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d9ad3f294bd9c4968a03cced8f5d96be" url=""><![CDATA[amendment I posted an earlier review about a disappointing stay for a small group at Royal Palms .. I also wrote to the GM, Greg Miller. He has gone over board trying to 'make it right'. I do believe their interest is to be 'guest-centric'. He even refered to my posting here. So if you do book into the property you can rest assured that they will do their all to correct any errors. It IS a romantic setting and while expensive when they do get it right it can be worth it. Certainly better than the hundreds of rooms behemouths they compete with in Scottsdale.don.brown@brownchild.com
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f817192c13fd4429b1b3cda31a8e11a2" url=""><![CDATA[Best Value on The Rocks Not sure what hotel some of the reviewers stayed in but after three stays we think this is best value in Sydney. Location could not be better. A bright sparkling clean room with a kitchenette and a small balcony with a view that includes the bridge AND the Opera House! For many multiples more money you could stay at Four Seasons or Westin and have comparable views and an equal location but why spend the money! Our only disappointment was that during our first 2 stays breakfast was included .. now it is a high priced add on. Try the small bakery a short walk down the stairs to the next lower street.don.brown@brownchild.com
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>