<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="fb46947dc3c0ea9a0031808795f0f204" url=""><![CDATA[5 Stars!! I've stayed at Iberostar Bavaro during August of 2006 and I must say... Excellent hotel. The complex is filled with exotic plants and pools. The rooms are very nice, ours had a view to Bavaro beach and to the pool. We had All-Inclusive which is great because it allow us to enjoy not only the buffet but also the different restaurants (to which you need to reserve a table in advance) - I recommend te Mexican Restaurant (and the Margeritas). In adition to the hotel, Bavaro beach (right in front of the hotel) is also a paradise come true, crystal blue (and warm) water and white sand... Everything that one could ask for a Caribbean beach. Overall, an excellent hotel that I recommend to everyone who wishes to enjoy the best of Punta Cana.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6fc6e37851c42bf9acdfd2bf90b80ebe" url=""><![CDATA[I have to say... ish... Miami Beach (hotel's beach)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="42357f75c0b835ab8ed2bb77296d50a7" url=""><![CDATA[An average hotel Back in 2004, I went to Punta Cana and stayed at Barcelo Dominican Beach (it used to be called H10 Bavaro Resort). After staying at other hotels (like Iberostar Bavaro) I must rate this hotel as average. It's a tipical 4 star caribbean hotel. A nice lobby, a few good restaurants with a good (but not as good as other hotels) food selection and an okay pool. The rooms weren't nothing special... Small bathroom and the bed was scratched... And the AC was at when I first entered the room (great if you want to catch a cold). The beach is good... What one could expect from Punta Cana... white sand and warm clear blue water. Regarding the animation of the hotel it was good but the staff was kind of pushy to get the people that where lying in the beach/pool to participate at their games. Overall, although is a nice hotel, I recommend that you stay elsewhere because there are definitely best choices for you to enjoy all that Punta Cana has to offer.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>