<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="8bcf2639d8b96e36f56362711afb2c17" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel, in the heart of the Latin Quarter's tourist area My wife and I stayed at the for six nights in mid-July 2006, during the Paris leg of our honeymoon. We were looking for a nice, clean midrange hotel with air conditioning, located in an interesting part of the city. The Albe delivered nicely on all counts were both very satisfied with our choice.At first we were overwhelmed by the incredible choice of lodging in Paris, but we soon narrowed our focus to the Latin Quarter. We could find little agreement among our guidebooks on the best places to stay, so we decided to rely on TripAdvisor.We started by looking at hotels under and were attracted to the Carofftel Gobelins and the Comfort Inn Mouffetard Internet rate on the hotel web site). But since this was our honeymoon and my wife's first trip to Europe, we decided to pay more for air conditioning and upscale decor. We found a deal on a double room on the Paris Charming Hotels web site, which gave us one free night and breakfast for two for the length of our stay. Average price per night worked out to found the service to be quite friendly, albeit than Our guest room and adjoining washroom were both small (by North American standards), but very nicely finished. The bed was comfortable, the shower excellent, the air conditioning efficient, and the common areas modern and immaculate. We also liked the fact that the hotel had a minibar fridge that could be used to refrigerate grocery items, and an in-room safe. Be aware, however, that the elevator is typical of many older retrofitted European buildings, which is to say quite small will often find yourself waiting, or taking the stairs.Unlike some other posters, we were very pleased with the breakfast. True, the selection was a bit limited and the pastries merely adequate, but for a continental breakfast the offerings were perfectly reasonable: boiled eggs, toast, jams, pastries, cereal, yogurt, cheese, and meats. The best part was that, since it was a buffet, we could eat as much as we wanted, which often freed us to eat a snack rather than a full lunch later in the day.Access from CDG airport could not have been better. Even with two large suitcases, and two carry-ons, we had no problem getting to the hotel by RER B. Once above ground (use the Blvd. St. Michel exit), the is a mere throw away. The St. Michel station lies on line 4 of the which also happens to be one of the most useful lines in the city in terms of destinations and connections.The only caution we would offer is that the location in the heart of the Latin tourist restaurant area bustling with street performers and crowds well into the night. Reports from others about early-morning garbage truck noise are also spot-on. We loved the easy access to Notre Dame and the Seine, and the excellent hotel windows kept out 95% of the noise, but those who prefer a quiet neighbourhood should look elsewhere.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>