<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="b760f77cb649c96b8db65bdcd1b37072" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful Resort - Super time was had by all! Just got back from a weeks stay at the Bahia. We were travelling in a group of eight; four adults with a 13 year old boy, and three girls aged 10. Best way to review this place is to start at the lobby and make your way to the beach.However, first the airport. Have a pen with you in your carry on. You have to fill in immigration forms, one for each in group. Luggage out very quickly. Many people intimidated by luggage porters. A few firm no's are all that is needed. Give them the chance and they'll be off to your bus with your luggage. Important note on return to airport at end of trip. While one in you party gets bags, someone should be off the bus and in line as soon as possible. I felt the check-in process was very long and inefficient, even for the caribbean. Check in was a breeze. Greeted off the bus with women in traditional constume sporting refreshing drinks for the weary travellers. Always like this little touch. Lobby is absolutely breathtaking. A few things. They charge you for the safe in your room, we paid 26 US and I felt that this was really cheap on the hotel's part. Should have been included. Also, WATCH your step in the main lobby. Floors are beautiful marble, buffed each day, and you can't see the stairs. Seriously, this situation was just nuts and would not be tolerated in many places. Man I talked to took out half his face taking a tumble onto the marble floor. You'll see what I mean when you get there. RESORT IS HUGE, but trollies always running up and down middle of resort from beach to lobby. Pueblo Principe, shopping village, was a nice touch and offered a place to go at night. You can bargain with these guys. Tienda for gifts etc next to lobby. Keep for emergencies, you will find better prices. Food: In a nutshell loved it. Main buffet was absolutely awesome. Could not have asked for more. We breakfasted there everyday and all were impressed. Omellettes excellent, juices, fruit, great selection, and the kids loved the crepes. We suppered there 3 times as we had four a la cartes. Same story at dinner, even with group of eight, the longest we waited was about 5 minutes one night and we were there during peak weeks. Not much to add. You'll love it. We lunched most days at Olas 1 right near beach. More limited fare but was adequate for our group. Nice to just throw on sandles, not necessary and lunch near the surf. Again limited. Suggestion would be to go to El Charro Mexican which is about a 2 minute walk. Better selection and some in our group liked it. Note that you will need to put on at least a t-shirt,shorts, sandles, etc. as beach ware not permitted. As stated we had four a la cartes. My only comment on all the a la cartes is that they are geared towards adults with adult tastes. Menus are sophisticated and adults enjoyed while the kids needed to be adventurous. CHECK menus before you book. If you have the chance, try the Beach BBQ at Olas I. It is only held three times a week. Great BBQ, actually had a nice rib steak along with shrimp brochettes, chicken, pork, etc... Was nice touch being outdoors near the beach at night for supper. Mexican a la carte was also superb. Service was AWESOME. Felt like royalty. Food authentic and decor was stunning. Italian was so-so as far as I was concerned, alright but feel you may do better somewhere else. French had good reviews. Our fourth was the mediterannean. First class, food interesting and varied. Adults enjoyed, kids well.... All in all, food very good throughout the resort. Could not find a reason to complain. BUT others will I'm sure.Rooms: Beautiful. Bathrooms stunning. Heard lotsa complaints about mosquitos on first floor and can report that exagerated. Tried to switch, but stayed on first and was not disappointed. Saves on stumbling up stairs after a few Cuba Libres. Just use common sense and keep your doors, front and balcony closed as much as possible. We did have a few in room but not a problem. More at the cottage so you get my drift. Beds too soft, but day bed a little better for slab sleepers. Had quiet neighbours so can't report on noise (My main pet peeve). Party central next door would be a problem. Make sure mini bar stocked. Maids great and will stock bar with water, beer, softdrinks daily. We left a couple of dollars and a few knicks each day and left her twenty on departure. Other family had problems with card key for room. If this happens, get after them at once at front desk and keep after till problem fixed. Squeeky wheel gets....Pools: Must confess beach so nice didn't use pools too often. Middle pools in resort very quiet, good place to read book etc. Topless bathing not limited to beach, so be prepared for your 13 year old to get the odd eyefull!! hehe. Wasn't like that at the beach when I was a kid. Not as many as back in the day in DR, but again the odd one. (two I mean) Beach or main pool enormous. Kids loved it, nice touch with fountain in middle. Kinda resort that has stuff going on but you need to get up and find out. Note to rresort, get rid of the wooden planks that stop you from slipping crossing the bridges at pool and replace with plactic mats or something. Absolutely absurd and coupled with the lobby steps and invisible walls in pool, a lawyers dream of a resort. Take advantage of the free scuba lesson at pool. Show up at about 10:45. My son and I both enjoyed it.Beach: Gorgeous. Seems you need to get up at three am to reserve a chair under cover, but we managed on most days. Recommend getting up for sunrise if you can. Free and great for the kids. Also recommend getting water taxi to take you out to scuttled ship on reef. You can't miss this thing and the kids absolutely found it thrilling. We paid 30 US for seven of us to make the trip. I'd do it again if I could. If you are going to walk on beach, seems going south is the better way to go, market about 30 minute walk from resort. Swimming really nice, sandy bottom and no need for water shoes. I felt didn't offer as much snokeling as I like or am used to in Cuba, but reef is there if you wnat to risk life and limb. DON'T pass the swimming lines at beach even if you're tempted. Boats come by all the time and will take you out. We went to reef with excursion. Cost us 29 US per. Thrill for some if never done, but I felt it was a disappointment as far as reefs go. Was there 19 years ago and seemed better. Maybe was the day, who knows. We had 13 and 10 year old with us and they managed. Banana boat may be better use of funds for the kids. Reserve boats as early as possible.Shows: I felt them a tad above average, Cuba anyways, and actually watched a few. Great dancers and they are always practicing. Well attended mainly because there are so many guests.Bars: Service great at all bars and will fill whatever you want with whatever you want. Bar in lobby very nice. Felt all bars closing at 11 was too early. You need to go to Pueblo to get drink after that. Felt lobby bar should have been open till 12 at least. No hassles, nice crowd looking for a nice drink. Again, watch your step!!!Excursions: Only one I can comment on was my 13 year old and I did the Monster truck Safari. Highly recommend, nice blend between learning and seeing DR culture and rural lifestyle with bombing around in these huge Army personnel carriers from the 60's. Seems you go out farther afield on the monster trucks vs. the Outback and Bavaro runners but trade off with each. Go and you can be sure you will enjoy it. If you go bring lotsa dollar store stuff , school supplies, hats for the countless kids at the schools you stop at. SAVE some for what I understand were the Haitian kids at the sugar plantation we visited at the end of the trip. They seem to be in the most need. Great time and a real eye opener.A free trip that my buddy, my son and I took was a trip to the Don Lucas cigar factory. Free transport and since we planned on buying cigars, really enjoyed it. They give you a tour how they make their cigars, give you a sample of your preference to try, and a nice glass of DR or Haitian rum to wash it down. Ended up buying their House blend medium strength cigars which I felt were above average and a good buy at 75 US for 25 cigars. Just make sure you pester your ride back, we ended up waiting about an extra hour for him to return. Enjoyed it and fun if you need a small break from beach.All in all, really enjoyed our stay and would recommend resort to others. Beautiful, clean, a real joy at night as lighting is very beautiful. Beach is awesome. Food was above average for sure. Wine (Tinto) was plentiful. Kids loved it. No interest in kids club so can't comment. Rooms great. Will send additonal commnets if I think of any.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>