<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="766fcf648c9d24bc49408559731e910f" url=""><![CDATA[please take away a few stars! I arrived at the Savoy hotel with an open mind. After reading the reviews on this website I wasn't quite sure what to expect. It is very central there is no doubt about that. Check in was average and the reception area is nice. Corridors to the bedrooms are in need of a lick of paint and the carpet is quiet worn. Bedrooms are v small the handle was missing off the wardrobe. The door into the bathroom is a sliding one which looks v strange, kind of reminded me of a mobile home/caravan! The Sink and Bath are v worn and yellow looking, bath is quite high so you do have to almost jump up into it...would hate to see what an elderly person would have to do in this situation! Once I got into the bath I was literally too tall for the shower which is not securley attached so therefore water sprays everywhere unless you hold it with your hand.. After recovering from the bathroom experience my partner discovered that the bed was actually two single ones pushed together with the oddest lightest looking mattresses I have ever seen. With much annoyance I made my way to reception and enquired if there was a possibility of changing rooms. I was met with a cool forced smile that told me All the rooms are the same . that night the traffic was horrific and the room was so hot that a window had to be left open.. The worst though was the visible springs that were nearly up through the material of the so called mattress. I had the worst nights sleep so on my way to breakfast I made my way to reception and asked for the manager on duty who I have to say was v nice and efficient. After hearing my story he informed me that there was no problem in changing us to a newly renovated room on the 7th floor and explained that they were going through major renovations at the moment. It was a pity that the girl that checked us in didn't inform us of this!The new room was much more pleasant, new and modern. If we had gotten this room the first night we would have really enjoyed our stay as the breakfast room was excellent and had a nice enviroment.I work in a 4 star hotel myself and I really feel that the hotel savoy is nowhere near the required standards here in Ireland. So if you are going to stay there don't go with very high expectations and if your not too fussy and just going for a bit if shopping then stay here but by all means ask for a room on the 7th floor!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>