<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="756aaba10e0702e3b672654afa4cb8a2" url=""><![CDATA[Tiny Room - Fantastic Location - Immaculately Clean At the Royal Magda for 8 nights in April. The hotel was very accommodating -- we checked in at 10:00 AM wth no problem. The room was no larger than a closet. We booked a club room with 2 beds, thinking it would be a bit larger. The bathroom was adequately sized and almost brand new. The hotel was immaculate -- every inch of it. Yes the lift is good for 2 people but it's a lift and it works. Flor and Yohan were delightful and had excellent command of English which was most helpful when asking for directions.Everything good to say about this hotel except for the size of the room.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e682b00ebb05c62a521d3b5610a5644b" url=""><![CDATA[fantastic What a treat! The Estherea is a jewel. From the reception desk to the size of the room, the decor, the beautiful amenities and cleanliness of this establishment we were welcomed and thrilled. We booked a room overlooking the canal. The sun flooded the room through the 3 floor to ceiling windows. Eventhough you don't spend all that much time in the room, coming back to this comfortable room was a joy. Everything was immaculate. The bathroom was huge with 2 sinks and lots of room. Loved the towel warmer!The location couldn't be better. There were lots of restaurants around the hotel and pubs and cafes too. The bakery right around the corner made the most delicious pastries and croissants and we had them for breakfast every day with fresh squeezed orange juice. Transportation is fantastic. Hotel 3 blocks from Dam Square, a 5 minute walk from every tram and only 3 stops from Central Station. Our room was over $300/night but well worth it for the comfort this hotel offers. Hot tea, coffee and hot chocolate available all day with a lovely lounge, library and lobby in which to enjoy a rest.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>