<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="525dee79b322a80fe05ad3861b90b67f" url=""><![CDATA[Good facilities and location, poor service This hotel is built above a department store and could not be more central. That gives it the usual problem of a tiny street front presence and eight floors to travel before reception. I left my bag with the porter - 35 minds and four phone calls later it was delivered to my room with a surly nod. But I can't credit the phone calls for its receipt, as the phone didn't work either. The room facilities were excellent, and the location could not be bettered if you are in Sydney to shop. Its OK for business too although a little south of the main office area. Hard beds? Not what I found, but the bed is firm and I suspect those who like the soft American style might call that hard. At the discount rate I paid, this was very good value for the facilities, but I never sighted service in the hotel. Curiously the J P Bastiani restaurant had excellent service but very ordinary food.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="73824c6fe75ab615974cd80758653670" url=""><![CDATA[OK airport hotel close to airport This is a standard 3-star Holiday Inn close to Seattle-Tacoma International Airport. Good free transfer service to and from the airport. Comfortable soundproof rooms. Basic restaurant - you won't starve but unmemorable. Hopeless night manager at 2am - we finally sorted our intended room after two mistakes on his part and treks to the room and back on ours. Well furnished clean rooms. You can actually walk to the airport (we did for a stroll) and if you had the directions right and little luggage could do it on foot if you knew where you were going. With a good transfer service why bother. There are quite a number of other hotels along the same strip. We had a good light brunch at the Hilton, but in terms of independent restaurants there are only appalling American chain restaurants offering oversize fried meals within walking distance. So if you want a good meal, choose one of the nearby hotels. Day time desk service was excellent - we dealt with several different desk clerks and all were excellent, it was only the night manager who did not have a clue. A useful feature is a 24-hour accessible business centre where you can check in on line and print boarding passes. Good value at the price (discounted) which we paid.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b2f66606b98ca8f1b7177ccce90a309e" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent location to base a visit The Hyatt at Embarcadero is an older hotel which has been maintained to a good but not exceptional standard. Its real strength is the location - away from the shambles of Fisherman's Wharf or the night-risky areas near Union Square (the latter is not my view but a statement by authorities as to risk spots while we were there). It has one cable car at its front door, the major bus and tram routes next to that, and an easy walk across to the Ferry Terminal (worth a visit anyway for food stalls and cafes). We upgraded to a Club room which entitled us to (amongst other things) light breakfast on the top floor each day looking out across the Bay - a great spot. Over 3 days we found that this is a perfect base for local touring. Good value at the discounted price we paid.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>