<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="1052d8345b35295c111b28dcb0a3fc5c" url=""><![CDATA[Very Nice, would recommend Stayed at the hotel for 8 days in September 2006 with my boyfriend, we're 29 36. Found it to be exactly as others describle. I thought the room was great, rm 403. Big bathroom, lots of closet/drawer space, excellent a/c and 2 french doors to the balcony with view of Arc. The hotel never seemed crowded, the staff was helpful and spoke excellent English. I like that you never had to carry your key around they hold it at the front desk. We did return every night after the doors were locked and never waited more than a few minutes for them to open it for us.The hotel was very centralized, the Metro across the street is on the popular line that goes down the Champs Elysees -Louvre, very convenient. We also went to Versailles ourselves and it was about an hour total between taking 2 trains. Taxi stand was right in front of the hotel and it was never hard to get a taxi. Also we got the AirFrance shuttle navette (it's more like a bus) to and from the airport, 12E each way. Slightly confusing taking to the hotel, very easy taking it back. Make sure you have the hotel confirm your terminal before leaving since we got off on the wrong one and had to take another bus to the right one!We ate at the cafe La Flame around the corner for dinner/drinks on 2 occaisons, reasonable prices, great atmosphere. We also ate a fast breakfast one morning at the Quick fast food place 2 blocks away. We also at a few places along the Champs, Madigral and L'Alsace.... service was ok, food was mediocre, very pricey. Laduree was excellent!! We loved Barrio Latino in the Bastile area, great food and great music, dance floor was packed and fun to watch. We also liked the food court in the Lourve for a quick lunch. Le Petit Pont was a nice place to eat right across from Notre Dame, we also liked the live jazz at Le Caveau de la Hauchette. Lots of bars/cafes/nightlife on that street.We saw the Lido show and the Crazy Horse cabaret, Farooq the concierge, booked our tickets, he charged us 32E as a fee, the seats were great and we did get free champagne at the Lido, but just be aware he has a booking fee. Both shows were great I would recommend both. We did the entire city in 8 days, there is so much to see, we walked a million miles and the weather was hot for September, 85F. Always took a nap before heading out around 9pm for dinner. It was a great trip, I did a lot of research on the hotel and was glad that the Spendid Etoile was exactly what we expected!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>