<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="89bbb84fadbf989586cc17c515134a4b" url=""><![CDATA[A bit dissappointed We booked a two night break in the Shangri La on our way from Australia to the Maldives. On arrival we were very pleased and impressed by the atrium/lobby and reception; it was all very opulent and check in was quick. It was 2.00am in the morning so perhaps this wasn't surprising. We had booked a Tower, Club room which overlooked the garden and swimming pool. This was very luxurious but very, very small and we were disappointed. We had had 4 weeks of travelling and many club rooms, sometimes we even had been upgraded to a suite, this room was less half the size most of the other rooms and about a third of the size of the Sheraton at Noosa which we had just left. By this time it was about 2.30am so all we wanted was sleep and as we only had two nights there we decided not to complain. The bathroom was also very small but like the room was luxurious.We had breakfast at the Blu restaurant (Club room breakfast area). The view was fabulous and the choice and quality of the food excellent so we decided to book evening dinner here and a waitress made a note of our booking and request for a window table but as she couldn't make the reservation herself told us it would be confirmed later and we gave her our mobile number for this. No-one contacted us! At about 5.30pm we returned to Blu restaurant to check on the booking; although they had the note which clearly stated our request for a window table and time etc. they had done nothing about it. So at this late time we had to make the booking needless to say all the window tables had now been reserved! We said OK we didn't mind a table a little back from the window as we could still see the view. We went back to our room to shower and change and then to the Club lounge for pre dinner drinks and It was about 6.45pm and we were stunned to be told there was no seating available so we would have to wait in the nearby Blu bar where our drinks would be brought to us. We went in here and with great difficulty (I am only 5ft we climbed onto the very high chairs. We perched uncomfortably here waiting for our drinks - they didn't arrive!! . This bar is extremely cold, so much so that condensation had formed on the outside of all the windows and you couldn't see the fabulous view so this was not a good experience. Eventually my husband went to find the drinks only to be greeted by 'Oh, there is a seat for you now, didn't anyone tell you?' Well we finally got to the comfort of the Club lounge but only for a short time as we were now due to go for dinner. When we got to the Blu restaurant we were shown to table in an alcove (the only one without a view!). We protested to no avail! We should have left then but decided to stay and to be fair had a very excellent meal. I must say though don't go to this restaurant if you have a big appetite or a small wallet. Most of the next day we spent at the Botanic gardens, and then came back to the hotel for a welcome hour or two around the pool. This is lovely but, for the size of the hotel, too small and consequently it was very crowded with children everywhere and it was difficult to find two sun-beds. There is plenty of space for another pool in the grounds and I think the hotel would do well to do away with the tiny four hole par 3 golf and put in a second pool.Prior to our holiday I checked the website and was pleased to see that club rooms had a complimentary late check-out as we were flying at 1.30am (this influenced our booking). When we asked for this late check out we were told check out was at 12.00md. It took a lot of persuasion to get a change on this but finally they did relent and it was granted. I think the rules must have changed between booking and our stay. So, if you have stuck with me this far you may we wondering if we would stay here again. I am afraid the answer is that despite the obvious luxury and reputation of the hotel we would not. We were not made to feel special or a valued guest in any way, and next time would return to the Mandarin Oriental where we have stayed previously. This was wonderful and, although it too is a large hotel, the staff made us feel like royalty!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>