<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="c6a3c4e2073fbb42d1d76951f7c65683" url=""><![CDATA[Loved it here! Book this little gem of a hotel and you won't be disappointed!! On arrival into Venice as you come through customs look left and you will find the ACTV desk which is were you need to purchase your 12/24/48 hours travel pass for the bus/vaporetti you will need for your stay in Venice. Leave the desk and walk outside and take the number 5 bus which is from the second row. The number five bus takes you to Pizzale Bus station which link you up with the popular number 1 Vaporetti which will take you into Venice. The stop you will need for Al Ponte Mocenigo is San Stea which is the fourth stop on the number one. From the airport to the hotel it takes about 40 mins. If money is no object then take the water taxi but it's as the Vaporetti is so easy I would take it everytime. We arrived at the Al Ponte Mocenigo and found it easily after you get off at the stop walk to the left and you will see a little bridge this is the entance. The rooms were lovely and the staff are so friendly. We arrived and I had already asked Sandro to book us a table at a restaurant called the Vini Da Gigio which I heard some great things about on Tripadvisor, he had made the reservation and directed us there easily. What we hadn't known before we went is that Venice is so small and getting about is so easy, The restaurant was excellent and again the followig night Sandro had booked us into another restaurant close by called La Zucca another lovely choice. Breakfast is lovely warm coisants and cereal with gorgeous coffee. Nothing it seems is too much for the staff here and they welcome you to leave your bags with them on the last day after you have checked out which is 11am. Everything is close by even though on the map it isn't it really is only 10 minutes to St Marc square and the Rialto Bridge. I wouldn't stay anywhere else and I am already booking for September. Have a great time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>