<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="462d04999fd2bb97b5957af7e3c8a70c" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, nice hotel There is no denying that this hotel is in a great location. It's on Dam Square, a short walk from the main train station and canal boat terminus. A number of trams stop just opposite the hotel meaning that you are just steps away from a connection to all parts of the city.Damrak, the street on which the hotel is located, is home to lots of shops of varying quality. Just opposite the hotel is a large, high quality store and there are lots of souvenir shops a few doors away. The very impressive Magna Plaza shopping centre is just around the corner - it's worth a look just for the amazing interior.The hotel is not very impressive looking from the outside - it's quite unassuming - and the reception area is small and unremarkable. We were given a free upgrade from 'standard' rooms to 'superior' rooms. It seems there can be a great difference between the quality of superior rooms. My companion's room was lovely and big, with a large bathroom containing bath and separate shower, seating area for 2 people, and all in all it was a spacious room. My room was a lot smaller, no separate shower and the finish in the room was really poor - dents in the door and wardrobe door, 2 cigarette burns in the bed covers and net curtains. I wasn't very impressed - and probably less so because I'd already seen my companion's room!I was appalled to find that the bin in the room hadn't been emptied and peeping out at me was a porno DVD cover. When I checked the sink in the bathroom, there was a stain so I called reception to complain about the housekeeping service. One of the receptionists came up to see what was wrong, offered me a free drink for the oversight and sent housekeeping to empty the bin. It turned out the stain in the sink was a permanent fixture. I was convinced that this must be a standard rather than superior room, but on checking was assured this was of superior standard ... could have fooled me!I was suprirsed to read negative comments on this website about the soundproofing of the hotel because I found it to be excellent. I'm a very light sleeper and absolutely hate hearing noise from other hotel rooms. This is one of the few times that I can honestly say I didn't hear a sound from any other room. My companion who had the nice room, also had some kind of huge fan - presumably something to do with the air conditioning - just under her window and she had enormous problems getting to sleep, but in my lesser room, I had a great rest! I have to say the beds are very comfortable, there is a great range of channels on the TV - including BBC1 and 2 - and I LOVED the coffee machine in the room. It felt very decadent.The rooms also include a safe, ironing board and iron, mini-bar, 3 telephones (including one in the bathroom), a desk and nice leather chair. Another great feature was the guest office on the first floor which has 2 computers for guests' use and free internet access.As this was to be a relaxing break we decided to take breakfast in bed every morning at a cost of per time. This was only more than the restaurant price for breakfast so seemed worth it. We were very impressed with the lovely range of pastries and bread provided, along with eggs, bacon, coffee, juice and fresh fruit. I'd recommend it!We tried the restaurant for dinner on our first night and it was fine but nothing spectacular. The menu is unremarkable and doesn't change. I wouldn't really recommend it for dinner - you'd be better off finding somewhere out in the city.All in all, I enjoyed my stay at the Swissotel but there definitely are some problems there for the management to address. Staff at the hotel are helpful and courteous. The hotel has been rated 4* and I would say it deserves no more than 3*. However, you can't fault the location or the comfort of the beds and that's the main thing really!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>