<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="423d0352f97a969258453364ce4eadcb" url=""><![CDATA[Great Service and consistent with other properties I live in NY but will stay at NYC hotels when celebrating certain occasions with my wife. We celebrated Valentine's Day and spent a night at this hotel. I selected one of the packages they were offering for that weekend. I almost selected the helicopter ride package but felt the couples massage would be a better value. I'm glad I did.Overall appearance: The property is very clean and there were a lot of business people around. It's a few blocks away from Wall Street, so it seemed that this is one of the places to meet for a off site meeting or an after-work place to meet for drinks. The hotel is a bit difficult to find unless you (or your cab driver) is familar with Battery Park.Room: Very surprised with the size. I was quite happy with it. It wasn't as small as I anticipated and had a very nice sized bathroom. The shower had a good flow for being on a higher floor and very powerful. (I know a few people that would find that point helpful..) Rooms were clean and a comfortable bed. I had a harborview room and it also came with a telescope to check out the Statue of Liberty. You can save up to $100 bucks to get a city view room which I would have done had it not been part of the package. Besides, do you spend most of your stay looking out your window?Massage:The massages that were part of the package were EXTREMELY relaxing. The two women who gave us massages were very professional and knew what they were doing. My wife and I agreed that it was well worth it. The spa is located on the harbor side, so unless a firetruck comes blaring down the West Side Highway, you really can't hear the city noise that much. Plus, they had music playing at a comfortable level. In a few short minutes, you end up relaxing and ready for the massage.Before we went out to dinner, we grabbed a few drinks at the top floor bar. Great views and the clientel were young professionals. You'll pay premium prices since it's the Ritz, but the bartender made great martini's and gimlets. We returned that evening for our Valentine's Day Chocolate Bar dessert. The staff was nice enough to accomodate us an hour earlier than our original reservation time. The Chocolate Bar was in a private room with about 10 other couples. Think Salad Bar but with desserts. Not monstrous slices of cake or mousse, but small dishes that really wet your appetite. There were a ton of selections to choose from and capped off the evening wonderfully. Overall, I was very pleased with this hotel. Consistent with other Ritz Carlton's and would recommend it to others. If you are on a business trip to Lower Manhattan (and your per diem allows it) I would select this hotel. Normal rooms go for $300 and up. So, if you are a stickler like I am when it comes to rooms, you can't go wrong here.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>