<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="7daccb90cae059d36584412978cb6af1" url=""><![CDATA[Great stay, My family and I (Spouse and 2 daughters aged 14 and 12) spent 4 nights in San Francisco at the Argent Hotel from March 17-21st, 2007. We got to the hotel very early (noon) and was just expecting to leave our bags with the bellboy but the hotel was able to give us our room early. They upgraded us to a room on the 22nd floor and the room was spotless. There was a slight paint odour on the 22nd floor and that was because (I found out later ) that we were the first guests to stay in the room after the renovations on that floor. New carpets, heavenly bed, floor to ceiling windows, great view of Market Street and city and even Starbucks coffee in the room. Front desk staff were very efficient and professional. The room rate will certainly go up once the hotel is fully renovated and the Westin name is official- so the opprotunity is now. The only negatives are: you can hear the street cars going down Market Street, and the street people along Market and also on 3rd Street on the way to the hotel,
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="49a67651e91d68cbdc01d6ec3c2c0f7f" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel but location is questionable We stayed at the Sheraton Centro Historico Hotel for 5 nights at the end of August 2007. We were travelling with another family and had rooms next to each other on the 24th floor. The hotel is primarily a business hotel because during the week the hotel is very busy with the majority of the guests there to attend conventions but during the weekends, the hotel is much quieter. The hotel is new and modern with all the services you would expect from a upper end hotel- including an onsite spa, bank in the lobby, concierge, security, etc... The rooms were very comfortable and roomy. My wife and I shared a room with my 2 teenage daughters and even with the 2 double beds, we still had lots of room. The floor to ceiling windows make the room seem even larger and the air conditioning unit was very efficient. The hotel employees were very efficient and friendly. Most of the employees we dealt with spoke English. Hotel swimming pool was closed for repairs the entire time we stayed at the hotel. The hotel is located less than a 5 minutes walk away from 2 subway stop (Juarez and Hildago) and this makes exploring the city very easy and cheap. The Zocalo is 2 subways stops away (or a 30 minute walk) and the Zona Rosa can be easily reached by the buses that run along Reforma (or walked in 30-40 minutes). This is my 3rd visit to Mexico City (previously staying at the Hotel Cathedral and Hotel Nikko) and I really enjoyed the location and service of the Sheraton. There is a Starbucks next door to the Hotel in the mall (the food court is actually quite good). However, the location is not the safest - especially late at night/early morning - when there are not many people about. On the last day of our visit, one of our travel companions was in the Alameda Park, across the street from the hotel, when he was approached and asked for his digital camera and back pack by a young man. The robber did not show a weapon, and my companion just pushed him away and during this struggle, the police in front of the hotel noticed and started to chase the robber. I've alway wondered why there are sometimes up to 20 police officers in front of the hotel, and now I know why. This all happened at 3:30 in the afternoon.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>