<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="95246efeeed6de669dfc2cc0928351eb" url=""><![CDATA[Happy at the Hilton We stayed at the Hilton for a long weekend in Feb 2008. We stayed in an executive room and had access to the executive lounge. We finally got our luggage after a room mixup. We were a little miffed at the short wait but it did not matter that much. The room itself was comfortable but the bed was a little soft. The mini fridge did decide to gurgle at random times and the bathroom fan took an age to stop which was annoying when you wanted to go to sleep. Otherwise we had a nice room with a view on the internal courtyard which was not terribly exciting.The executive lounge though pleasant was far too small. Hilton have obviously been very tight here and could easily expand the lounge at the cost of say one bedroom. We had to wait for a seat sometimes but did not wait long. You do get a good view from the lounge.The food was very nice, especially breakfast. Pre dinner snacks did vary and the hotel have for some reason a passion for horseradish. They put it on almost everything, which was not necessary. I hate becks beer and that was it on the beer front. The decent scotch whiskey disappeared after our first night and never came back. The staff were very friendly and did their utmost to make you feel comfortable.The swimming pool was very nice but a little cold. The jacuzzi was a rather feeble effort and joined on the side of the swimming pool. Build them separately please! There are plenty of restaurants to choose from in the hotel or not too far away. You may have to walk a bit!The hotel is located next to Stadtmitte U-Bahn station. Do not get off at Mohrenstrasse as you will have to walk! We took the airport bus from Tegel Airport and this takes you to Unter den Linden which is not too far to walk from the hotel. Also buy a Berlincard and for 48/72 hours you will have all transport included (+ airport bus) and discounted entrance to lots of attractions. You can buy the Berlin card at the airport. At Tegel airport look for the information signs. Costs for 72 hours.The hotel is not far from Checkpoint Charlie and the Brandenberg gate which makes it a good base for sightseeing. We had a great time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>