<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="bc3afbc1b1f3df4234710b62f331ea81" url=""><![CDATA[What a great place! After reading so many negative reviews prior to going to this resort, we went with much anxiety. I was such a pleasant surprise. This is going to be a long review because I would like to cover everything possible. Arrival-Punta Cana Airport, whisked through and onto a bus, comfortable, ac, great guide. Arrived at hotel in 20 minutes, Bags were taken care of, no lline for check-in. Told the clerk what we preferred (8 of us) and we had rooms on 1st floor half way betwen the beach and the buffet and plaza. The room was very large (standard) and beautiful. Marble floors throughout (entire resort) Jacuzzi in bath, also large shower and lavatory. The toilet and shower had frost ed glass doors which gave privacy. There was a large approx 5x6 foot opening over the jacuzzi looking into the bedroom. If this is a problem bring something to hang over it. One family brought a sheet and duct tape. We are an older couple and didn't mind. The fridge is kept restocked every day with soda, beer and water. If you prefer more or a different kind they will happily oblige. If you are ready to have the room serviced p;ut the sign on the door handle. Put the do not disturb sign on the door any time you do not want to be disturbed. They do frequent checks on the rooms to be sure they are being serviced properly. The Beach-georgeous! Plenty to do-windsurfing, sunfish, Hobie cats, being towed on a tube or banana boat.Parasailing and ultralite raft rides. An army of people are out early every morning raking the beach to remove seaweed and any debris. I never saw a piece of trash the entire 7 days. They bring out a canoe and cut pineapples, melons, etc and put them on skewers for everyone to enjoy, There is also a grill down by thewater. The pools are large and clean. They are surrounded by chairs on the edge as well as chairs on the multiple pavilions that surround them. Yes,at times there are not enough chairs-more are still coming. Our way of dealing with this was the guys got to the beach at 7 and set up our chairs under two tiki huts with towels and other personal items on them.Then they went to the buffet for a boys coffee klatch. We were all out there by 8-8:30, and never had a problem. Food at the beach was great-a large grill and buffet under a large tiki roof. Terraced so you had a great view of the beach while eating. There was always grilled chicken, hot dogs and hamburgers plus an additional item. (fish, skewers). The staff is very attentive, always asking if you want another drink, etc. The bartender at the swim up bar is a real showman, must see to appreciate. Always stuff for the kids-ice cream etc. Main bufet-in the style of Vegas. Many, many selections. Some are navtive dishes, and they are worth a try. There is always a carving station which included on different nights, beef, lamb, pork, ham, turkey, salmon and local fish. One night was lobster, shrimp and various other seafood. The selections are always varied. Other restaurants-forget it! Ate at the American, great service, half a lobster, and a piece of steak. It was ok, but not what we are used to. We Americans are very spoiled when it comes to steak. Don't expect what you are used to. But, The meat is very tender and flavorfull, especially the beef on the grill. They also grill a variety of other meats for lunch and dinner. There is an omelet maker in the morning (Felix) he is amazing! We walked out of the Italian restaurant because we had waited 45 minutes and had not even gotten our salads. Menu was mostly pizzza, and a selection of pasta and sauces. Two waiters for a full restaurant and the hostess was not pleasant. The restaurant that most people were trying to get into was the Asian hibac hi because it had good reviews. Line for beepers started at 5 for 6:30 opening.Unless you have a team to take turns it is hard. Of course we are older and no one felt it was worth it, since we enjoyed the bufet so much. Entertainment-In addition to the staff,who were often very entertaining themselves, the shows were good! They were held in the plaza (outfdoor) and there was a variety.One night it was non-stop carribean music and dances who were amazing. Men walking on stilts seemed to glide. Lots of picture opportuinities. Kids loved it.Had face painting and made balloom hats for the kids. Got exhausted just watching. One night was Jazz, Sinatra,Ella fitzgralds, etc, anothe night, Circus with trapeze artist,another,vegas lounge act singer and impersonator. Was it Broadway?No, but it was entertaining and pleasant after a day at the beach a great dinner,and wonderful tropical drinks.- Don 't miss The Dirty Monkey, Domincan Sunrise, Mango Martini just to name a few. The power and air conditioner in your room is controlled by a card in a slot inside the door. The staff always left one in our slot so the air was running as much as you wanted. We often turned it off for a while at the thermostat, usually at night. Any credit card shaped card works in the slot. If the power goes out, it happened twice for a few minutes y ou must removed the card and replace it to turn the electric back on in your room. Mosquitoes-saw a few, swatted them. We live in South Jersey and ours are the State Bird. These were minis. If you need your room sprayed they will come and spray for y ou. We were on the first floor and they were no problem. Don t leave the sliding doors open! THE STAFF-I cannot find enough complimentary adjectives to describe them. The Dominican people are beautiful in both looks and manner. I cannot even imagine the ratio of staff to guests but it was more than ample. There is also a great deal of supervision. There was always a manager in sight, and they usually spoke the most fluent English. The housekeepinhg staff is is least fluent, but we could usually sign language our way to understanding. The staff truly makes your enjoyment their mission. It made us feel good just to be around them. They are proud of their country, and rightly so. They were always spotless and professional. We shared many laughs as they attempted to teach us their language and we ours. If your can't find a bar there you are blind! Would we go back? Definitely! Will we be able to afford it? Don't know, it is certainly a 41/2 star resort now and certainly will be a 5 star by next year. Upgrades-didn't find it necessary. Little larger room(maybe)robes in room, and top shelf liquor. (which you can get for an addition charge per drink:) One of our party did it once to get Absolut and after that didn't bother. The tropical drinks and thebeer were so good it didn't seem worth nearly $500 per couple. That's all I can think of. If you are going there you are lucky, have a dirty monkey for me! Marilyn, Cape May, NJ
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>