<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="f3025bef0c86a7e27fd607dd7cc3022b" url=""><![CDATA[great place Date: March 7, 8 10We had a lovely time at the Hotel Plaza Mayor. We stayed in room 503, a wonderful room at the front of the building on the 5th floor. A big room (for Madrid standards) with two big windows that opened and we could look out on the little square (Plaza Santa Cruz, I think it was?) to see everything going on. While there was no airconditioning, the room cooled off very nicely with just opening the windows.This hotel is not on Plaza Mayor actually but 1 block away, which meant that things quieted down quite nicely after 11 p.m., and also being up high meant we had less street noise. It is a small intimate hotel, and we really liked that.The staff could not have been more helpful with directions, suggestions for dinner, and help with the luggage. We actually left some luggage at the hotel when we went to Toledo one day. We stayed overnight in Toledo. When we came back to the hotel, they had us in the same room that we liked and our luggage all ready.The only reason I did not give this a 5 spot ranking is that we would have liked to have a drink when we got back after sightseeing, and relax a bit. But their little bar was closed, and the foyer of the hotel was underconstruction. The breakfast room was pleasant, and the breakfast while adequate was too expensive for what we got. We learned to have breakfast at a little cafeteria just around the corner. The carpet of our room was never vacuumed which I though odd and mentioned it at the front desk. They said they had plans to replace it. But everything was great apart from that. We felt very safe there day and night. This was helped by the fact that there was a big police presence in the square at all hours. We found out when we watched TV that an International Conference on Terrorism was being held in Madrid and one of the venues was a conference building about 300 ft. away on our little square! Political leaders from all over the world were attending! Then we understood why there were so many police directing traffic, standing around, and moving cars on the little square!We took the metro at Puerta del Sol and went everywhere. It was so easy to use. We loved the Prado - spent all day there and didn't see it all. We could have spent a second day at the Prado, but went to the Reina Sofia which was also wonderful.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e200b2e611ad2c23c80cd8ca935aab95" url=""><![CDATA[very good We stayed at the Hotel Continental Palacete on March 4 5, 2005.The location is ideal and very close to the Ramblas but in the better section of town just north of the Ramblas, and we felt absolutely safe there day or night. The Block of Discord was just around the corner and Casa Mila only 10 minutes walk away. The standard room we had was curiously shaped, squeezed in behind the reception desk and one of the public rooms, and and looked out on the street. There was no airconditioning, probably because the locals think that March is winter and aircon is not needed. Opening windows was not an option because of street noise. The hotel was beautiful and since I love old buildings I was delighted with the ambiance and decor. The little elevator is nice because I have artificial knees and could not manage the grand staircase although I admired it very much.The all day and night buffet was wonderful, and we made good use of it. The practise in Spain of late dinners was different for us, but we comfortably went sightseeing and had something at the buffet before freshening up and going out to dinner.If we go to Barcelona again I would stay here absolutely, but I would ask for one of their standard rooms in the back which do not have the street noise and have private small courtyards, and are the same price. The location and wonderful decor of this hotel make it a very good choice.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>