<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="7264666e1b0c24dd59cfb7db63ecc351" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel, a few problems The check-in was very smooth and pleasant, the room was large with quaint windows opening to the streets, the bath was large and comfortable. We had 2 issues with this hotel, the first that we could hear the people next to us whisper and talk, we could hear their t.v. shows, we called the front desk and were told that the person in that room (which didn't have a number, it was the connecting room to ours) was a regular and that is where he wanted to stay. They offered for us to move, even though we were there a day before this person. We chose to stay and made our own noise in hopes they would move!Our other MAJOR issue was that we wanted to order a pizza from a local restaurant and have it delivered. They were helpful in our selections; however, when the pizza arrived, they didn't call our room as instructed. After about 1 hour of searching for this pizza that was supposedly delivered over 30 minutes prior, we had to go search for the pizza as it was never delivered to our room.The location was quite a distance from most attractions and shopping so we did have quite a walk or required a cab.There was nothing special this hotel offered to justify the high price and/or high rating.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fad2d3ecbb56af74668c82a58bc9f399" url=""><![CDATA[Not Impressed I was very disappointed in the quality of the room they gave us. Not only was there water stains in several locations of the carpeting, the a/c unit leaked profusely thru the room, the television had to be replaced, and the complimentary fruit they left in our room had rotten items. The decor was old and not just in the historic sense, and my companion and I both experienced extreme itching on our legs both days at this hotel. We had to either assume we were both allergic to their detergent or possible bed bugs. We never had this issue at any other hotel prior nor any after. We stopped into the bar after dinner and although there were at least 6 others sitting, there was not a bar tender present until someone finally complained to the concierge upon which the hotel manager stepped in. My next experience was while I was frantically trying to use the internet to change my flights after the London bombings. There was a lady using the internet for hours to check her email. After discussing how much longer she would be, I found she wasn't even a guest at the hotel! She walked in off the street and needed to use a computer.On a postive note, the concierge went above and beyond to help in any way possible during our trip.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>