<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="44715878f14e101756ce9d616320c69d" url=""><![CDATA[Askanischer Hof. What a hotel!!! My family and I stayed in the Askanischer Hof for 5 nights. In summary, we found it excellent value, friendly service, well positioned, and had a relaxing environment.The hotel was centrally located on the Ku'Damn, one of Berlin's main shopping streets. A Louis Vuitton outlet was next store for example, and 100's more either side. The nearest bus stop was 100m away. M19 and M29 were the most popular routes, running every 5/10 minutes, taking one right along the Ku'Damn. The nearest underground stop was the on the U1 line (5/10 mins. away), following by the Adenauerplatz stop on the U7 line (10/15 mins.)There were four of us in total, including our 11 and 14 year old children. We had a large suite, number 30. This looked down into a quite courtyard. It was beautifully decorated in a classical style. The entire hotel was full of antique furniture and had high ceilings through out. There was a large selection of books too, in English and German.The staff were most friendly and helpful. For example, one of them actually volunteered to post some postcards, when we asked her where was the nearest postbox. In addition, they all had excellent English. The breakfast was a large and a typically German affair. It was served between 06.30 and 11.00am, or in one's room afterwards. Everything was fresh, tasty and well presented. Would definitely stay again!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4cca9994946bdea3507d87319cc1e026" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, good quality for the price in New York I stayed in this Hampton Inn for 5 nights with my family. Location on Eighth Ave., 51st. St., intersection was the main benefit. Time Sq., was only 9 blocks away on 42nd. St., the Ambassador Theatre was on 49th. Street (Chicago - The Musical, GREAT!!!) and the subway was on 50th. St..There were four of us in total (2 adults and 2 teenagers), so we took a room with 2 double beds. The room was large and clean. We asked for and got a quiet room facing onto the back of the hotel on the 8th floor.As expected given the other reviews on this hotel, the breakfast room always busy, when we arrived each morning at 8.45am. However, we were eventually able to get a table for four. In addition the lifts were busy at the same time period. So one just needs to be patient at the busy times.The food quality and range was good. The staff kept it well stocked for breakfasts. We had more than enough.The staff were efficient and business like. For example, one of my teenagers managed to block the WC in the bathroom at 2am one night. Once we notified reception, a man came within 5 mins., and had it fixed immediately.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0f91b49b44fe8dd24747e07d32cff853" url=""><![CDATA[Great location. We had based our selection of this hotel, for our family visit to Paris, on all the very positive reviews that we had seen on Tripadvisor website. As a result, we had high expectations prior to arriving. We got to the hotel from CDG Airport, by train/metro in about one hour, after getting a Carte Orange travel pass in the RAPD/RER sales desk in Terminal 2. The nearest stop is La Motte Picquet-Grenelle, about 200m from the hotel. The hotel is located on a quiet side street, off the busy Boulevard de Grenelle. The location is excellent, eg. only a 15mins. walk from the Eiffel Tower. There are many restaurants and shops nearby, including all the usual department chain stores located on Rue de Commerce, such as HM, Monoprix, Promod, Sara, Pimkie, Celio, Gap, Etam, etc.. In addition there is a supermarket, Le Franprix on Avenue de Motte-Picquet.We arrived at 6pm. Our check-in went smoothly. The boutique hotel theme hits one immediately. We stayed in room 32 for the four nights. There were four of us, i.e. my wife, two teenage children and myself. The room felt small for the four of us. The bathroom too was small. The decor was nice however, and very up to date. Versace tiling etc..One strange thing was that there were some flies in the room. Both my wife and son, woke up after the first night's sleep with multiple insect bites. I swatted all the flies subsequently. The flies may have come in via the air-conditioning system, or the window, which was a little loose and not double glased.We didn't have breakfast in the hotel, as we suspected that it was too expensive at per person. We found an excellent boulangerie chain outlet at 10 Rue de Commerce, called Brioche Doree - Le Fournil de Pierre, opposite the HM and Sara stores, only 250m from the hotel. Its breakfast was only and included an orange juice, a croissant with jam, and a coffee. Before we found this, we also tried Le Bouquet de Grenelle across from the Metro stop on the corner of Boulevard de Grenelle and Avenue de Motte-Picquet. It worked out at per person minimum.There were many restaurants in the area, eg. French, Indian, and Italian. There was also a MacDonalds and a Pizza Hut. We tried only one, Le Suffren (about 250m in the Eiffel Tour direction, at 84 Avenue de Suffren), as we were on the move each night. It was okay. All in all, we found it a nice hotel, well centered, and nicely decorated, but expensive.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="510534275e4b10230734a444998967b3" url=""><![CDATA[Good value, clean, relatively new, good food, but remote location. I stayed with my wife and two teenagers for 4 nights. We had a room with 2 double beds on the ninth floor across from the pool.The hotel is relatively new, located on the south west side of the city. Somewhat remote, but the hotel does provide local and airport courtesy buses, running every 1-2 hours. This more than offset the remote location. Note that the nearest subway station(Mass. Ave.) was six blocks or a 15mins. walk away. The breakfast area was always busy, and some days we had difficulty finding a table for four. However the food was excellent, particularly the fruit cocktail bowl.The bedroom was large enough for us and clean. It faced onto the back of the hotel. Note that the front faces onto to some major roads.The pool was small but open from 7am or so until 11pm, with an adjoining fitness room.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>