<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="1922e0bd2423fa52c4e4fd1cffd25ad4" url=""><![CDATA[Top class service and great views. My husband and I had both lived and travelled in Australia as backpackers and wanted our return to Sydney on our honeymoon to be special.Our travel agent got us a great deal in the Four Seasons and we couldnot refuse. (altho we later discovered that there had been a mix up and the booking agent got the price wrong and it should have been dblwhat we paid put they picked up the excess!)We arrived into Sydney and got the express train down to Circular Quay and strolled over to the hotel (probably the only ones ever to do so). We were very early to arrive but there was not a mention of this and we were checked in immediately. We were told we had a city view room, we enquired about upgrading as given the location you justhad to have a room overlooking the harbour. We were told it would be $25 to upgrade (not made clear if this was p/n or pppn we were too embarrassed to ask) but decided to go for it. We got the full talk about the hotel and all the facilities from the check in staff and really felt like vip's.The room was beautiful and definitely luxury but very very small, but when you opened the window to take in the view it didn't matter about the size of the room. With the Opera House on one side and the Bridge on the other we were taken away by the beauty, having spent many a day at the harbour dreaming as a backpacker we never thought we would be returning in style!The service was exceptional everywhere especially at the pool. The pool boy was extremely attentive and altho i agree with another reviewer they could do with more chairs you never felt awkward as you waited for one to arrive.We loved Sydney before we arrived at the Four Seasons and now like it even more.ps the upgrade was per room per night - bargin
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c9492d978cd0576171e08dc892bf01fd" url=""><![CDATA[A bit dated. We had a stop off here on our round the world ticket. We decided to stay 2 nights as most likely it would not be a place we would choose to travel too again.Outrigger was recommended to us and we heard that Duke's was the place to hang out so we decided to stay here.We had a partial sea view room which was nice and big and clean but in need of some modernisation. The bar was a nice place to hang out in the evening watching the sea. Altho there are a lot of other places to hang out too. We did not manage to use the pool either day and it was very noisy and full of children.We found it to be Very American - yes i know it is part of, but it is the place were even Americans go on holiday, we didn't meet any other nationalities. There were alot of groups of teenagers and then you also had your very over friendly college student waiting on your table being over nice to get a bigger tip.....we found it all abit too much and in your face.Hawaii over all was a nice beach resort, the hotel was fine, nothing special. They did give us early check in which was great but i can't see us returning to Hawaii anytime soon.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="80d26f9814b3c9574ec035202823226e" url=""><![CDATA[Clean, affordable and good location - would stay again! Getting a decent hotel in Barcelona within walking distance to the city is difficult but i would totally recommend this one.We flew direct into BCN and there is a bus transfer to the metro and then a change to get you to Arc De Triumph (sp?) Station.look for directions when you get off the train you want the Naples exit toward the bus station, from there it is a 4 mins walk.On arrival the receptionist was very pleasant and check in was very quick. I had requested a floor on the higher level but upon arrival we discovered we had been given a disabled room with a very small/low shower - (my husband is 6'2').we rang reception and they swapped us to a room on the 2nd floor instead.The free mini bar is a great bonus and plenty of toiletries and a hair dryer as standard.It was about a 15mins pleasant walk into town, leaving you at the top of La Ramba. Or 2/3 metro stops.We partied hard so did not use any of the facilities, eat or drink in the hotel but it did look all very welcoming and clean.i would definitely stay here again and recommend it to friends.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="03c3449bc70b91806be35bf8a82afb7e" url=""><![CDATA[Pure Luxury - Highly Recommended great idea
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>