<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="ac2fcc380f908c276dc192f7df3b158e" url=""><![CDATA[Good new hotel at fantastic price Myself and my husband have just returned from Hong Kong, and checked into this hotel 3 times,as we had a couple of side trips staying over in Macau and Tokyo. Can only repeat what the previous reviewers have said about this hotel. The first room we checked into was a great surprise as we hadn't expected much at this price range - it was their cheapest room as we were arriving late at night and leaving early next morning. Good clean room, nice furnishings, fluffy white towels and bathrobes, and a great comfy bed. Checked in again 2 nights later, again for just one night, to a room with a view of the harbour, much bigger, with a small sofa as well. The manager came across to speak to us while checking in, and was very welcoming, giving us his card in case we had any problems so that we could speak to him personally. Happy to say that there was nothing the staff could have done to make our stay any better. Third time we stayed for 4 nights,corner room, great view of the harbour, smaller than the first 2 rooms, but still not a bad size.Lounge access well worth the extra money, chef asked us every morning if he could cook anything special for us the next morning, he seemed concerned that we didn't eat much for breakfast thinking we didn't like the food on offer! We have never been asked this before in HK, not even in the Hyatt or the Langham!The area is not smart or upmarket by any means, but we did not feel uncomfortable at any time walking around. Buses and trams are nearby and leave every couple of minutes into Central. Taxis take about 5 mins into Central District for approx HKD20, or SoHo and Staunton Street for approx HKD25. This hotel and it's staff are obviously trying very hard to make a success of this business, and if they keep up this level of service, they deserve to succeed.We go to HK on a regular basis as our son lives over there, and usually stay at one the large 5 star hotels, great hotels,with great facilities,fantasic if you spend much time in the hotel- but if you are out all day and all you need is a good room with good service, give it a try - there are plenty of places in Hong Kong to spend the money on that you will save by staying here.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>