<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="028a4a1a0aec33f0c8d4f249f473c7d2" url=""><![CDATA[Almost all Americans and touristy location, but nice rooms and pool. 1) About 80% of the people there at least were Americans, most in their 50's. In my opinion that's an ambiance-reducer when you're in Paris, but may not be a big deal to you.2) Breakfast is 29Euros per person, find a rate with breakfast included or be prepared to walk somewhere else. Free wifi in the lobby.3) Nice relaxing pool, not a lap pool, but good for big kids. Nice lounges next to the pool.4) Workout room is pretty small but has a good amount of TVs.5) Location is near pricey boutiques and the touristy Rue de Rivoli. Also nicely close to the Louvre (5 min walk) and the Tuilleries which I love. So a push in this regard in my opinion.6) Room was small but nice, great comfortable bed, fantastic bathroom with separate shower and tub (I had a Superior room, 1 level above the base Deluxe room). Frankly I can't imagine how small a Deluxe room would be so I'd at least spring for the Superior.7) Room had a DVD player, so bring your movies if you like (no PPV). About 6 English TV stations including CNBC, CNN, BBC12, Eurosport, and France 24 of course.8) Lobby has a very nice, intimate wood-buring fireplace.9) Takes them about 10-15 minutes to get you a taxi.If you like seafood I went to Gaya in the Left Bank (across the street from L'Atelier Joel Rubechon for those who know). Fantastic seafood, but not cheap. If you're a sea-foodie then you should try it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8abf52dec904c9536991f52325b108b8" url=""><![CDATA[Terrible hotel, stay away Location is quite poor, this hotel is not right on Times Square but on 8th avenue instead, across the street from a bunch of [--] shops.Room quality was average, nothing special, and the hotel's ambiance was terrible, reflecting the neighborhood that it really is in.Frankly I felt very unsafe walking around the neighborhood, I definitely wouldn't come here with a family for sure.Also the poor location means that taxis are almost impossible to come by; you're quite isolated.Stay away, there are a million better hotels in NYC at the same price level.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>