<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="bd6b7b201346b7843e34db227bb68970" url=""><![CDATA[Good location, nice hotel, helpful staff...pity about the pool My wife and I stayed 12 days in Room 901. It was a very large studio, overlooking the Ala Wai Canal and Golf Course, with the Mountains in the distance. There is a good sized Lanai which gets morning sun.The well equipped room comes with a full kitchen including full sized modern frig, microwave, and stove/oven. Lots of storage for suitcases and as many hangers in the closet as we wanted. There is daily maid service.The free phone (local and 1-800 calls) and access to phone books was handy, as was the free daily newspaper.Although we were right alongside the elevator, the room is well soundproofed, so we heard little noise from the elevator or its lobby.The air conditioning worked well and quietly. We kept it running on low, 24 hours. It was not a bother at night, and we heard no street noise... only the odd ambulance siren.Good Tip... use small pieces of duct tape to seal the heavy lightproof curtains together each night. The sun rises before 6am, and the tape keeps out the narrow, bright sunbeams that can otherwise shine in through the gaps and wake a sleeper too early!The hotel has a sundeck on the roof (16th floor) and on the 10th. These provide for sunbathing anytime you like. There are lounger chairs.The pool was our big disappointment. It is small, and located behind the hotel on the ground floor. It has little deck around it, and is in shade much of the day. The high buildings around it create a wind-tunnel effect, so without sun it is quite cold and unpleasant.There are lots of good eating places close by, and of these we most enjoyed the newish Legend Chinese Restaurant just up the street on Kuhio. Reasonable price and very good food.The beach is only about three blocks away but when we were there that part (in front of Royal Hawaiian etc) was very crowded. We went instead a short bus ride to the beach alongside the Army Museum, near the Hale Koa Hotel. This was really nice!We recommend the Ilima Hotel as an excellent value, pleasant place for a vacation!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>