<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="abf42f24e4871f5c65ed50702cc107d8" url=""><![CDATA[A wonderful resort I had us booked at another resort, but after reading reviews on TripAdvisor about that resort (i.e. smoking EVERYWHERE) I contacted our travel agent and got us booked at the Majestic. I have been to almost a dozen all-inclusives in the Caribbean now and this one was one of the very best. We arrived by way of Miami. This is fine going, but I highly advise against it for the return flight, as I will discuss later in the review. Our flight was out of Baltimore and it is a very easy trip to DR. Thanks to TripAdvisor reviews, we weren't surprised by the thatch huts that make up the airport, and we also knew to avoid/ignore the throngs of taxi drivers. We simply looked for the sign of our tour company and got our transfer to the resort. The transfer was effortless and in about 1/2 hour, we were at our resort for check-in. There were no rum punch drinks offered to us like I read about in other reviews, but we didn't care. There was a line, but it moved at a decent pace. When we checked in, there were 3 of us and 3 rooms. 2 of us had our rooms ready and it was very quick, but one of us they could not find. Not a problem as they got the manager in a few Dominican minutes and he got a room for the third person. Be warned - of all the places I've been, the ability of the locals to speak English here is the worst. I highly suggest a phrase book or some translation software for your PDA if you want to have any real hope of communicating with the vast majority of the staff. We always got by and we all laughed as we tried to understand eachother, but I can imagine that if you ever had a real issue or problem in this country, the language barrier would be a significant hurdle. The grounds and the resort are exactly as pictured. The rooms are amazing and just like the pictures. We requested upgrades, but as the resort was booked, we didn't get them. No worries. The standard rooms were great. And even though it says on their website that room service is only included with the upgraded rooms, we had room service each morning for our meetings and there was no charge. No problems with electricity (the outlets look wierd, but are fine for our gadgets) plenty of hot water, toilets worked great. The rooms are entirely marble and wood. Very beautiful. We could not get the cable internet in the rooms to work for us, but the wireless in the lobby worked great and was very fast. There is an internet cafe up past the casino and it charges $5 per 1/2 hour and you get a code so what you don't use one day, you can use another. 2 of us were in building 3 looking out into the gardens and a third was in building 1 looking out at the neighboring resort. All of us were happy. I could see where building 4 might not have been great as there is much construction along that side of the resort. The pool is just spectacular and really is the crown jewel of this resort. It spans the entire length of the resort. There is an area for activities and then areas of quiet. Although the activities on the beach in the morning disturb the quiet of the one end of the pool, it is over in about 1 hour and after that, it's pretty quiet. The resort itself is a nice size. Not too big, not too small. I hope that doesn't change after the completion of the construction. I've been to monster resorts where you had to get golf carts to get from one part to another, but this one isn't like that. I saw quite a few handicapped persons at this resort and I wonder if this might be due to the size and the plentiful elevators. It is very well suited to wheelchairs and crutches. The food was the best all-inclusive food I've ever had. Understand that all-inclusive resort food is RARELY 5-star cuisine. The sheer volume of the food that has to be prepared each day just makes it impossible that the food is gourmet. But this resort had a great amount of diversity at all restaurants so even picky children would find something. Try the chocolate cake. I've rarely ever found deserts in the Caribbean to be good, but the chocolate cake was fabulous. The main buffet is a huge dining hall. A bit noisy. The beach resaurant was very good and had a great variety to choose from. Very few bugs anywhere. Did get bit a couple times sitting out on the balcony after sunset, but not sure by what because I never felt them or heard them. We didn't do the nightlife. We were on a corporate retreat so after working all morning and then enjoying the sun all afternoon, we were pretty tired at the end of the day. The specialty restaurants are good. We had no problem with reservations. The people are very friendly, but I noticed that in this country, you generally must make the first move. And I also noticed that they seem to mirror the attitude that you have when you make the first move. I made a conscious effort to be very happy and upbeat to everyone of the staff and that was exactly the attitude that I got in return. Consequently, I also took a lot of time and watched people and saw that those who were grouch in the morning, or who spoke to them with disrespect, got the same in return. Dominicans are a hard working and proud people, so be sure to appreciate that and show that appreciation and you will be rewarded. I was appalled by how some of the customers spoke to the staff and found it hard on several occassions not to say something. And I found it to be across the nationalities and not just the Ugly American. The nice thing about this resort is that there did seem to be little riff-raff. I've been to some resorts where it seemed like every freak in a trailer park who could scrape together $599 was there. This isn't one of those places (yet). At the prices in the Dominican, I'm surprised there isn't more of a Greyhound bus feel, but so far, so good. Another nice thing is that smoking is not allowed in certain areas, so if you are like me and get headaches or upset stomach from second hand smoke, you won't be bothered by it. The beach is beautiful but the surf when we were there was quite rough. Don't know if that is a regular thing, but I prefer the more shallow and placid Caribbean waters. There was even a strong undertow, so be careful if you are traveling with little ones. We went scuba diving one day. Somewhat disappointing. The visability wasn't great, but even if it was, there wasn't much to see. It was brown and dead as far as coral went. The fish were beautiful, but nothing spectacular. The dive boat is basically just a dinghy. Getting back into the boat, especially with big swells and rought seas was very difficult. One of us has bad shoulders so getting back into the boat was almost impossible. We did see a HUGE eel and that was a great experience. But we only went on one dive since we just weren't impressed with the first experience. We didn't do any of the organized excursions off the resort, but I did speak to a gentleman and his 12 year old son. They had done the dune buggy trip. They really enjoyed it and the 12 year-old especially enjoyed the 4 layers of mud he had encrusted on himself when he got back!! One of us got a killer massage in the spa. He just raved about Juana and how good her massage was. He said it was the best of his life. Based on his recommendation, I would suggest asking for Juana by name if you want a great massage. Be sure to take some 1's or 2's for tips. The staff at this resort are very hard working and certainly deserve it. The minibar has a 2 beer per day limit, but I just left a note that said 4 mas cervasas, por favor and a couple dollars and I always got what I wanted. The beds are very firm. If you are used to a soft pillow top mattress, you are probably going to end the week with a stiff back. We drank the water, ate salads, fruit, etc. One of us got an upset stomach one night, but we don't really think that had anything to do with the food since we all ate and drank the same stuff and he was the only one who got an upset stomach. I had an upset stomach one night too, but I think that was because I had a few too many pina coladas in the pool! Victor at the swimup bar is great and he keeps the drinks coming. Be sure to take a floaty if you like them since they are $13 in the gift shop. And be sure to take an insulated mug since the drinks (alcoholic and non) come in little 6/8 oz cups and the mugs in the gift shop are $12. We have Verizon cell phones and had no problems receiving or making calls. You don't have to dial a country code, just dial normally with the 1 and then the area code. And we even were able to send and receive email on our cell phones too. We did have a problem with reception in certain places. In our rooms, the reception was terrible (maybe because of all the marble and concrete) but out in the open or on our balcony there was no problem. Oh, one last thing; try NOT to have a layover in Miami!!!! I don't know if it is this way everywhere, but we had to go through customs and immigration (which was fine) but once you do that, you then have to go through security ALL OVER AGAIN!!!! When you are tired and hungry, this isn't exactly a welcome surprise. I have no idea why we had to do that since we had already been through security in the Dominican and the customs and immigration areas were highly secure. From now on, it's direct flights for me!!! Well, I think that is everything. Our trip was exactly what we expected thanks to the advice we got on TripAdvisor so I hope that this review helps someone else.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>