<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="19960ab6cbe4f5d34cb1a7b97a6f994b" url=""><![CDATA[Ideal base for discovering Berlin I ventured out to Berlin alone for the 2nd time this Easter. Having stayed over in Charlottenburg before Christmas and undergoing a long, long walk back to the hotel from sightseeing, I decided to stay in a hotel in the Mitte district where a lot of Berlin's attractions can be found. Trawling through a few websites, I came across a brilliant deal for 4 nights at this hotel. Arriving from Tempelhof, this hotel couldn't be easier to get to, take the U8 towards Alt-Tegel then change at Stadtmitte onto the U2 towards Pankow and alight at Alexanderplatz. It's even easier from Tegel (catch the TXL bus) and from (simply jump on the S9). The hotel entrance is literally 10 metres from the U-Bahn exit. Checking in was fairly easy, even if I was nearly mistaken as part of a tour group from Hamburg! The room was on the 9th floor, minimalist in nature (rather funky IMO), being made of dark wood, white materials and glass, and it was near enough perfect. Despite the building works going on at the adjacent Galeria Kaufhof, I still managed a couple of lie-ins! The hotel has a casino and bar on the 37th floor and I think there were limited fitness facilities too, though I never got to use them as I was out most of the day (and night) sightseeing and sampling the nocturnal habits of Berlin. Breakfast was excellent on the day I had it, as much as you wanted, vast selection of breads, meats, cheeses, fruits and they even did (a full English)! Couldn't really complain about the service either, the two meals I had in the Zille-Stube restaurant were spanking! Veal schnitzel, apple strudel, German smoked meats platter, the works! If you wanted to eat out, there were numerous restaurants in the vicinity, from Chinese to Italian to Vietnamese to Hungarian! I truly recommend this place!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>