<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="545714691831b6e8f9d0b3b5116f1230" url=""><![CDATA[Neat hotel, but we had some issues I am a corporate travel agent and I love good hotels. I was very excited to stay at the W Dallas Victory. Unfortunately, it did not live up to my expectations.We arrived and entered the lobby. The girl that checked us in was great! She was very friendly and not snobby at all. (We didn't exactly look like the cream of society, having been bird watching all day) When she was taking information from me the music was so loud she kept having to have me repeat myself. She said she always had problems with it and the later it got the louder it got. She did give me some recommendations on food and told me about the bars.We went up to our room, which was a very odd set up. As others have said, you walk through the bathroom to get into the main part of the room. I found that a bit off putting. The bathroom is very nice, but.... The bath is also open onto the room, though there are drapes you can draw. That didn't appeal to me at all. The sleeping part of the room was really nice. The bed was great, with wonderful pillows. There was a really nice chaise lounge and a plasma screen tv. I did notice that the duvet looked like a cat had walked across it, picking some of the threads with its claws. We had trouble with a lot of noisy partyers on our floor. Also,we are early to bedders, and at about 11PM there was a knock on our door. My husband answered it and someone said they had the pillow we had asked for. We didnt ask for a pillow. The final blow was when we went to check out. We had valet parked the car and they couldnt find my key! It took about 20 minutes to get the car. Over all the location is good. I like the chic modern style and the staff was very nice. I think that we were just there on a bad night, but I will have a hard time recommending this hotel to my clients.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>