<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="7">
		<document id="74b2d6af69c243c0a227d4ffcafba489" url=""><![CDATA[Terrific Value in the middle of Waikiki My wife and I stayed at Celebrity Resorts for two days in July because it appeared to be the best value in the area near Lane and the International Marketplace. We wanted to book a double room, but only a suite was available. The suite was worth the extra $20 a day, and it still cost less than a standard room at the Ilima Hotel next door. The hotel is served by a wireless Internet service called Wanderport that charges guests of this and other hotels $10 for 24 hours. It would have been a good deal if the service didn't get oversubscribed starting at about 9:30 a.m. The Internet unclogs again at night. Fortunately there is a good Internet cafe with reliable Internet access on Nahua Street, accessible through the back gate (room key can open the gate). We loved the round-the-clock availability of various kinds of coffee near the pool and the $3 all-you-can eat pancake and orange juice breakfast served every Thursday. Rooms were clean, and everything worked. The reception and cleaning staff were helpful, happy and friendly. We plan to stay there the next time we return to Waikiki.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="378039edf6f47181fbf3d186f20c2f34" url=""><![CDATA[What a great way to see Florence Room 411 was large
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8a65bfb2aa76b39564fc476c9210ef43" url=""><![CDATA[How long will they continue to offer this great price? Lobby looking toward entrance
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="89aaa58fb5a8859466563f10d0319eb0" url=""><![CDATA[Delightful Hotel Room 504 with porch on the right
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bd90488b2eb80d04bd336ffe29d766c6" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location for good price My wife, daughter, and I stayed at the Hard Rock Hotel, Kuta, on a Saturday night in February. It is located right in the center of activity with the beach across the street and Kuta Square only a short block away. We found Kuta's narrow streets too jammed with cars to be able to drive anywhere on a Saturday night, and when we returned, the hotel parking lot was full. The staff kindly gave us free valet parking. The free buffet breakfast was very good, and all of the staff were very polite and helpful. The price was extremely reasonable considering the location and facilities.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a25b20e6b114cb5b480ffcf4a6a87320" url=""><![CDATA[As Good as a Transit Hotel Will Get This hotel has changed names and operating procedures more than once, and I think it finally has found a good service formula. In July, United Airlines paid for my wife and myself to stay at Changi Village on the way to the US and on the way back to Jakarta. We have stayed there on several other occasions, and we were quite impressed because the hotel does an excellent job considering most of its guests stay less than 24 hours. The nuisance endemic to such hotels is noise from short-stay neighbor guests, and Changi Village always has arranged for us to move to another room whether our neighbors are screaming/running children or guitar-singers. You can hear planes taking off and landing at the front of the hotel (but not the back), but we were so sleepy that we didn't mind, even when we were booked in a front room facing the street. We always look forward to eating at the row of reasonably-priced open-air food courts by the hotel and buying durian from an itinerant vendor. We especially enjoyed the food at Tomomura (means village), the Japanese Restaurant. The best way to get into town is by taxi, so we tend to stay in the Changi Village area, partly because it has so many good places to eat and Changi airport has so many shops and restaurants. The buses to the airport really run on time, which one would expect in Singapore.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6cd62085fba817f3610d9c132aabbeb8" url=""><![CDATA[Not bad considering the price View of Clarke Quay from Rm 1009
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>