<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="df312d59e0c7cf9204b3074333dbdbe8" url=""><![CDATA[Great family stay My family (wife, son - 10, daughter - 8) along with 2 other families had a wonderful 7 night stay at this resort. We stayed in the Royal Service section and enjoyed this upgraded part of the complex. We enjoyed the food and ate at several of the reservation restaurants...the Japanese, Italian and Seafood were our favorites. We very much enjoyed the Gabi Restaurant as part of the Royal Service area. We ate all of our breakfasts and many lunches there. And dinner at the Gabi might have featured the most varied menu and best service.Accomodations were outstanding and truly 5 star. We had a one bedroom master suite connecting to a one bedroom suite in building 51.Service was adequate overall, if not a bit uneven. Sometimes it was outstanding, while other times you weren't sure the staff knew you were there. I did see many pushy guests and it was clear that they were not going to get anything extra from the staff by giving off attitude. My recommendation is to carry a pocketful of $1 bills and distribute them liberally...it will help...be a bit patient and smile alot. I'm certain that if I spoke Spanish, just a bit, it would also improve things dramatically. Much of the staff does not speak English at all, so do not expect communication to always go perfectly.While never leaving the resort complex, we found many activities to enjoy. This included: parasailing, snorkling, zipline and bungy jumping (for the kids), golf, and of course, laying by the ocean or a pool for some much needed relaxation.Again, for the price it was a simply wonderful experience and one we may very well do again in the future.A few other observations/tidbits:1. Big resort, but nothing ever longer than a 10 minute walk. I recommend upon arrival that you do a little exploring to get a feel for the place and determine the best routes to certain places. There are shortcuts that make it easier to get around.2. Dominican Airport Transfers was great and $80 round trip got all 4 of us to the resort and back to the airport.3. Beach features great sand and the water is quite nice. Security keeps the local vendors to a minimum, but the resort's own can be a little pushy at times (timeshare and water sports).4. Never had a problems getting chairs at the beach or pool. We like full sun though. If you want shade, an umbrella or a palapa it may prove to be more difficult.5. Gym facilities okay, nothing to write home about. Steam rooms appeared to be permanently out of service.6. I would not come here if I was on a singles trip or couples only type of vacation. Place seemed much better suited for families and they were abundant.If you go, relax and have fun. Its really hard not to like this place
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>