<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="d7973fac4449c11f92881185be7ac859" url=""><![CDATA[the walmart of all inclusives Stayed at this resort December 20-27, 2007. We are from Toronto, family of 3 with a 9 year old boy. Have mostly stayed at Paradisus Resorts in Cuba and Mexico. Let me start by saying that for the majority of Americans and Canadians this resort would be fine. For our family it was too big and impersonal for our liking. We also had a bad start as flight delayed 4 hrs got into the hotel at 2 or 3 in the a.m. Preferred Paradisus Resorts which are closer to 5 star in quality of food and amenities. We were in building 37, third floor, about two buildings away from the lobby. Ate at four restos: French/Gourmet, Seafood, Italian and Japanese.Pros: Short ride from airport (30mins), fantastic beach (soft sand turquoise water, clean good size rooms, good air conditioning and block out drapes, baked goods such as sugared donuts and corn bread, some fish, pizza hamburgers ok at beach grill, roast turkey at xmas, scrambled eggs if cooked fresh, some desserts, no probs with fridge not being stocked and when I phoned down for more pillows, beer and water it came in about 20 mins. (left small tip for maid most days), no prob finding a beach chair at any time but might have to drag one to where you want to beCons: resort is so huge you need to take a shuttle do go from one end of the resort to the other, runs frequently but who needs the hassle. no coffee at the dinner buffet and no coke at the morning buffet, no hair conditioner, no clock in the room, most food is fried in palm oil, grilled does not mean grilled its fried on a flat grill, have to ask the waiter if you like your coffee hot as their carafes they run around with do not hold the heat, the food is good if you like Applebees or Kelseys at the best (which for about 80% of North Americans is fine), first of all it is a virtual porkfest (slim pickings if you are jewish) and gross if you don't like pork e.g. one selection was called pig pizza, the a la cartes are mediocore at best (like most of the all inclusives they try hard but they could do better), lobster is plentiful but the small carribbean ones which are mostly over cooked and dry, the filet was ok for Applebees, Japanese set up is better at other resorts we've been to (miso soup was vegetable soup), omelets are all ingredients mixed together and not folded over, lack of flora and fauna (not so many trees and the odd lizard running around, no coral nearby for snorkeling, no outside jacuzzi's hot pools, occasional whiff of sewage in the air when standing on balconyto upgrade or not to upgrade?we originally were going to upgrade and backed off when we felt it really wasn't worth it for us. if you want to be nearby the beach (no guarantee of view and it is not oceanfront, only side view )then you should upgrade, you may also get into a two story unit (most of the complex has 3 story units), but remember if you are by the beach you have to take a shuttle all the time to access the main area (buffett, lobby, nightly entertainment and shopping square) and the beach area is noisy, the rooms are all the same size so no benefit there, private pool area is a joke as it it right beside the quieter resort pool and had the same number of people, extra a la carte (no big deal you can usually negotiate extra a la cartes without upgrading), if you like to have your own private lounge and internet cafe so you feel like a special person go for it, oh and you also get room service (which is the only thing we regretted as other 5 stars such as the paradisus chain, room service is standard)tips: stay away from Manati Park, its like a third world zoo with more vendors and peddlars than animals. variety of animals was sparse and boringtry and use a little spanish (polite and useful)bring small bills for tips, conditioner, moisturizer and bug spraycan buy all of this stuff and more at the lobby store so no big deal if you forgetbox of pringles (4$ and change), pack of Marlboro lights (5$ and change)when at guest services ask for extra a la cartes (get them to check cancellations)drinks better if ask for better brands and throw in the odd tip,hang out at the quieter resort pool instead of the main over crowded and noisy onedon't ask for third floor if you don't like climbing stairs or elderlywhen negotiating late check out be firm and creative (we got free checkout till 3p.m. and paid $60.00 to stay until 6:00 p.m. (well worth it)no smoking in restaurants except outdoor beach grillsprobably want rooms closer to main area if elderly or kids otherwise shuttling all the timetry to get rooms away from the main shuttle lines (they go by every 5 mins and emit exhaust fumes)resort is divided into two mirror images (Bavaro a Punta Cana) separated by main shuttle line with their own separate lobbys and restaurantsso paris and gourmet restaurants both japanese restos are mirror images that share the same kitchens and offer the same foodits hard to say which a la carte is best due to personal preference(you may like seafood better than filet but may find both at both the Seafood and French/Gourmet)brasilian resto is outside and prone to bugs
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>