<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="b652e9276d19801dc1a51306e9e31b87" url=""><![CDATA[Does exactly what it say on the tin........... Dam Square
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6ba25c006c75e32b82d8cd5d5fb6c454" url=""><![CDATA[Room with a view! Stayed at the Affinia Dumont for 5 days at the end of April 2008. I haunted the forums of trip advisor for months trying to choose the right hotel and I wasn't disappointed! It was hard decision choosing a hotel as we had a decent budget and we found that there wasn't allot in it price wise for the top rated hotels-except the Affinia it was the only one that offered a significant saving on the others which swayed us! We booked direct and they also offer non-refundable rates which offer even greater savings. We'd requested a room on a high floor with a view of the Chrysler building which we got. Wow what a view! Walking into the room and seeing that view is just something I'll never forget. The rooms are large and very comfortable. The bed was large and comfy and the kitchen was an added bonus having coffee making facilities. Although we never cooked in there the fridge was handy and the ability to have a quick slice of toast with your coffee first thing was also great! As others have said this hotel isn't opulent but it doesn't charge rates which reflect this either. To be honest it was as nice as the rooms in which we stayed at in 5* hotels in Las Vegas later in our trip. We have very little interaction with staff in general on our holidays unless we have a problem which we never did however all the staff from the doormen to the cleaners were friendly. the location of the hotel is quite residential with the barking dog next door which do breakfast lunch and dinner all at a good price and I found the quality good/expectable for what you paid. There is a little market next door too where you can get milk, wine, etc if you like. There are a couple of dinners close by too and bars and restaurants close by if you don't want to stray far. There is a subway stop about 5 mins from the hotel and this was our preferred method of getting around the city. The ESB is about 10 minutes walk away and Flatiron another 5 mins away. To me the location wouldn't be important to me if I returned as everywhere is accessible and you're never going to be close to everything. The Times Square area would be the only area that I wouldn't be interested in staying in and around just not my scene. This is a great hotel, my favourite thing was the view and if I were to return to NY I'd certainly check the rates for the Affinia and stay again!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9e07b15af67a7c41669f81f615cfb9a3" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel in a great city! After much deliberation and going through the reviews on TA we decided upon the Chancellor and glad to say we disappointed. We decided that the Union square area was more suited to us as there was only myself and girlfriend travelling. The Chancellor exceeded our expectations within 10 seconds of check in as we were upgraded for free to a suite, which had two full separate bathrooms, separate living room, fridge, and the all important tea and coffee making facilities. We had requested a room on a high floor with a nice view if possible our suite have a view so perhaps they we unable to give us a normal room with a view so they bumped us up to the suite? This was just my thinking anyhow and have taken the suite over a view anyhow!! We have very little interaction with hotel staff in general unless we have a problem-we had no problems in the Chancellor so our interactions were limited although all the staff were warm and friendly from the cleaners to the front desk staff. We booked our wine country tour via the tour desk in the lobby and our return transport to the airport she was very helpful. With our upgrade I offer insight into the normal rooms but the suite was probably decorated as the un-refurbished rooms from the website my girlfriend preferred the look of the older rooms anyhow. There really allot I can add from previous reviews-the location is excellent with plenty of dinning options and everything need in and about Union Square. To me the only problems people seem to have with the Chancellor are caused by them not doing their research! The Chancellor is a charming well presented Boutique hotel with great service, it pretend to be luxurious or fancy and their rates reflect this! a shame that the Chancellor and San Francisco are on the other side of the world from us otherwise return sooner rather than later! Great hotel that I hesitate recommending to anyone.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>