<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="745ca9ca42ba785c5fd44da768f69b97" url=""><![CDATA[Dissapointed with the Radisson - 3* at best Having secured a good deal on Ebay, which resulted in paying less than 96 Euros a night including breakfast, my expectations were not huge, as I counted anything at this price in Paris as a bonus!However, having stayed in many Radissons before, coupled with its 4 star rating, it is fair to say, that we were not expecting something basic - which is sadly what we got.To begin with, check in was not smooth, and the problems already started through the repeated requests on the telephone and via email in receiving a written confirmation of our room. Upon check in, the room that was allocated to us was filled with stale smoke, despite asking repeatedly for a non-smoking room. This was quickly and professionally dealt with by the front desk, but then, to our dismay, we were moved to a pokey little room at the end of a corridor, about half the size of the first room! We did not bother complaining again, and stayed put. Note to self: New Year's resolution: Take up smoking.The next dissapointment was the breakfast, which was a pretty basic affair, even for Paris, and cooked incredibly poorly. The baked beans were boiled so much each day, that all flavour had been methodically extracted from each bean leaving them bland and indedible, and the scrambled eggs were a cheap floury cheap mess - not even the orange juice could escape the quest for improving the bottom line, as this was severely watered down.Again, not what I would expect from a Raddisson or a 4* hotel.The last point that was slightly annoying was that no internet connection had been arranged for our room, and every day, I was forced to use a temporary account linked to another guest and his room. It solved the problem of course, but left me with the impression that I wasn't a valued visitor of the hotel as they couldn't be bothered finding a long term solution.Lastly, in relation to the location, it's not bad (a metro station is available two minutes away, over the bridge), but as one reviewer points out, it is a little too far to go if using it as a base to explore Paris. All in all, I would say that this Radisson falls behind the standards of many of the others in the chain. I could go on about its many other annoyances: Charged 20 Euros for alledged mini bar usage (didn't open the fridge once) - Charged 16 Euros for three two minute calls made internally in Paris - Felt the rumbling of the Metro at night underneath us, which could wake light sleepers etcBut not having paid top dollar, these things didn't annoy us as much as they would have done ordinarily.In conclusion then, I would not recommend staying here if you are looking for luxury, 4* star standard or convenience, but only if you can secure an absolute bargain!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>