<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="cce70c5d7632c8475ac0ded37cc31fda" url=""><![CDATA[Meh (ok for cuising) This hotel is pretty mid-level. Although our stay included some hotel related injuries, the location is prime. We picked the hotel because of its close proximity to the pier (as we were taking a cruise). The location is perfect if you plan to take a cruise sailing out of old San Juan, as it is literally steps away from the pier. This was highly convenient.The bar and gill attached to the hotel and casino is great. They have great drinks, but the service is slow. Its a nice place to read a book or lounge around and people watch (when you aren't in a hurry). We actually ended up spending about 3 or 4 hours there after we checked out of our room (and we didn't want to wait in line to get on our cruise). While the wait staff is on the slow side, they make up for it with unexpected attentiveness- i.e. going out of their way to light your cigarette for you. The casino was sub-par. Not very interesting and I was nearly accosted by an over-zealous security guard who wanted to check my ID. He kept saying ID! ID! and then when I said I was staying in the hotel and started to look through my handbag for my ID and room key, he Puh!-ed me away and shoo-ed me. The gaming is just not worth it at this casino.The picture of the roof top pool are pretty deceptive. Its TINY, but has a good view. As always, with a hotel, watch out for the hot tub. My party and I went up all geared up for a soak, only to find a nasty couple making out in there and god knows what else yuk- so we didn't go in.BEWARE OF DOOR STOPS OUTSIDE THE BATHROOMS! Two people in my party were injured (one VERY badly). The door stops outside of the bathrooms were placed WAY too far out from the wall. We had to put the ice bucket over it since everyone kept tripping over the stupid thing.The rooms were just Meh. We had a wonderful view of a parking garage from our window. The room was clean, but nothing special at all, just your run of the mill bland, exactly what you expect from an airport hotel.The front desk staff was very friendly and helpful. Also we enjoyed the bell boys, they were very friendly and gave lots of good advice.... Also if you stay in this hotel, you MUST MUST MUST eat dinner at Aquaviva (a few blocks behind the hotel). One of the best meals of my life!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d1fe55568412bb58cb3b7e9ef67f6bbd" url=""><![CDATA[Loud and way passed it's prime While the photos look great and I can appreciate what this hotel was once trying to do, it is no longer the amazing Conde Nast praised destination it once was. The design of this hotel is great. The roof top bar and lounge area is great during the day. It has an amazing view and I was able to spend a good chunk of time in the sun there.Beware of the LOUD experience... on many levels. When entering the hotel you'll be greeted with the sound of rushing water... not only are there many fountains all over the building, they pump in (loudly) the sound of running water and crashing waves. While I appreciate what they're trying to do, the water sounds pumped into every level, on every floor in every nook and cranny, are way too loud and way over done. The upsetting part of the stay was the horiffic sounds at NIGHT. And I'm not talking 10 p.m. 11 p.m. or even 12 p.m... A roof top DJ party raged well it 6 a.m. While I was staying on the 8th floor (and the roof top is the 11th), I was kept awake by blaring techo music and crazy people screaming drunk in the hall ways all night long. I am a very heavy sleeper, and it was the first time I can remember being kept awake. I was not notified that this party was taking place (by expedia, or the hotel). Upon calling the front desk at 4 a.m. 5 a.m. etc, no one even answered so that I could complain about the rediculous noise and bed base shaking boom boom techo going on. (Please note that I am 22 and not a 60 year old... I like to party as much as the next guy... and I didn't even get to bed until 1 a.m. that night anyway) In the morning the manager of the hotel promised to comp money for the horrible time, however this never happened and I've been sent on a wild goose chase to try and get some type of compensation for my almost 300$ night laying awake listening to screaming drunks and techno. The only up-side to the loud techo late-night/early-morning techo party was that it music was beyond loud enough to drown out the annoyingly loud water crashing waves music that may have otherwise kept me awake as well. The area surrounding the hotel is unsafe. Speaking with the bell boys, I was able to find out the area was previously very over-run with drugs etc, and that police were constantly patroling the area to try and keep an eye on the safety of the tourists. While this might appear to be comforting, be aware too that you can take a short walk around the corner to one of the worlds biggest cock-fighting arrenas. Its a stange area to stay in. While its a pretty location and the decor in the hotel is great... beware of the LOUD music and water noises. Ask in advance if there will be an all night techo party before booking a stay at the San Juan Water and Beach Club Hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>