<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="b3514a538ca45283f5f6cea096d517ba" url=""><![CDATA[Marvellous Hotel! Four Seasons Hotel - Sydney AU My wife and I stayed at the Four Seasons Sydney for two weeks in April prior to sailing on SAPPHIRE PRINCESS to Los Angeles. The hotel is wonderful and we had a marvellous time. We had a full harbor view junior suite (rooms ending in 15 have the most spectacular views of the harbor - Opera House, Bridge and Circular Quay) and it was large and elegantly furnished! (Note: regular rooms appear to be beautiful but on the small side). We paid the extra fee for membership in the Executive Club which was pricey but worth it with wonderful breakfasts, cocktail hours and desserts daily plus a fabulous concierge, Jane, just for Exec Club members. She was very helpful in all ways and invaluable in finding my wife a doctor when necessary. The regular hotel concierge, Jorge, was also great - booking restaurants, etc. The Hotel's restaurant, Kable's was excellent - great food and service (not fancy or fussy!) and we enjoyed eating several dinners there (much better food than we had at some of the top and most expensive restaurants in the Rocks/ Circular Quay area). We did not use the Spa but the outdoor pool was lovely and the poolside lunches were great. In summary, this was a lengthy stay at any hotel and we will remember it as one of the best hotels we have ever stayed at anywhere! Wish Australia was not so far away so we could return often to the Four Seasons Sydney!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0b95f27d7f3813c81ed1bc5f6092185f" url=""><![CDATA[Very, Very Tired! We have just returned home after 5 nights at the Grand Hyatt in San Francisco, stopping there to get over jet lag after flying back from two months in Asia. We had a Regency Club room which really offered nothing more than a not impressive continental breakfast in the over crowded lounge on the 31st floor. The room was not large, the decor was drab and the furnishings were very, very tired. In fact, we had last stayed at this hotel 32 years ago and I am sure the furnishings, with the exception of the very comfortable bed, are exactly the same as they were then when the hotel was new. This is the only hotel I can ever recall having absolutely NO BATHMAT or RUG of any sort for the bathroom floor and the very low tub/shower combo has no grab bars for safety when using the shower. The Grand Hyatt up the road in Seattle is one of our most favorite hotels in the world and the Grand Hyatt San Francisco could certainly take some lessons from her Seattle cousin!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="262b6a0734a67adde157d7f8369ac954" url=""><![CDATA[Conrad Hotels in Asia are Wonderful! We recently spent a week at The Conrad, Hong Kong at the end of a two month trip to Asia and this stay really finished off our Asian sojourn in style! We were on the 59th floor facing the harbor and just down the hall from the Executive Lounge. Our room included breakfast, either in the Lounge or downstairs in the Garden Cafe which opened onto an outside terrace by the gorgeous pool. Our room, tho not particularly large was extremely comfortable and very nicely decorated in an oriental motif. The only negatives about the room were the fact you could not adjust the airconditioning temperature or air flow and the commode was in a very tiny separate cubicle off the main bath which was awkward and uncomfortable. Overall this is an elegant hotel which offers great convenience and outstanding warm yet professional service! We will certainly stay at the Conrad Hotels in Hong Kong and Singapore when we return to Asia!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0a3d110d2fcb05de87604e7d7d6f61b7" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Experience! We just returned from a month in Asia and stayed a week at the Conrad Centennial in Singapore. I am Hilton Gold HHonors and have stayed at all the Hilton brands all over the US and Europe but this was the first fime we have stayed at a Conrad Hotel. What a terrific hotel! The room was lovely, the bathroom fantastic and the service throughout was exemplary. We were particularly impressed with the Executive Lounge on the top floor. It took up the entire floor (as I remember) and had great views in all directions. The food and service were wonderful - full breakfast, elegant tea, and other food/beverage service all day long. Did not use the gym, but the pool was beautiful and there was very attentive poolside service. The only thing about the hotel we were not crazy about was the only restaurant - Oscar's. It had a 24 hour a day buffet which looked good if you like buffets (we don't) and was very noisy. We ordered several meals from the VERY LIMITED menu which were OK but it really would have been nice to have had a more conventional restaurant available in the hotel. But we loved the Conrad and would rate this brand as equal to or superior to Ritz Carltons we have stayed at in other cities.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>