<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="88f9e00e0ad47a13f9e986d4bad36ebf" url=""><![CDATA[very nice hotel in a great location I stayed 2 nights at the ESJ last month. I was there for a friends weeding, so I took advantage of a special rate, which was very good.The hotel is located about 10 minutes drive from SJU airport, which means the cost of taxi was very affordable. I was greeted by a bellman who promptly took my bag and ushered me to the front desk. Check in and out was smoothe. The front desk staff was very efficient. The lobby looked beautiful and was very busy after dark. I walked through the casino, but I was hoping they would have a sports book. They didn't. It was small. Not my scene. Lots of slot machines.The room was very nice. Spacious, clean and very cool. The ac works very well. The bed was extremely comfortable. You could sit outside and smoke on the patio.The beach is on site and gorgeous. I didn't stay near the pool, so I don't know what its condition was. The housekeeper who took care of my room was very sweet. She was very helpful in offering suggestions on places to go and things to see in the area.On the first floor, right past the front desk there is a starbucks. Further down the corridor is a variety of fine shops. I like to smoke cigars and they have a fine selection in one shop. I ate at the palm steak house restaurant on site, which was very good. My steak was delicious and the service was excellent. There is a trattoria which was good for a light lunch. There was also a very nice looking northern Italian restaurant and a night club, neither of which did I experience. There was plenty to do right in the hotel itself.The facility for the wedding was really very nice and the banquet food was good. It was a beautiful wedding and I think that the staff at the hotel did a fine job. My only regret was that I didn't have more time to spend. I would definitely recommend this hotel to friends and family members who were looking to stay in San Juan.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>