<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="204c9042a3bbbaa22bfab2a39d874728" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location - Ok Hotel... Usually stay in the what was the Ramada but is now the Tulip Inn and compared to that this was not as nice. Reception area is lovely. Hotel is in middle of a re-furb at the moment so there were lots of workmen pots of paint all over the place so was a little hectic during the day. Thankfully this did not disturb us too much! Sadly was unable to smoke in any of the 3 rooms we had booked within our party. Did manage to change one of them to smoking in the end. However the no-smoking rule is being rolled out 1 July 08 so not sure how that is going to change all hotels let alone the city! Biggest plus was the location - literally a 3 min walk from Central Station. Also if you are anything like me the Shower is important and I can confirm that they have good ones at the Sint Nicolaas! Would I return - no. Would I return to what was the Ramada - yes! Also be sure on what you rate you are paying at time of booking as they tried to charge us an additional 50Euro which we swiftly got knocked off.Breakfast in reception in the mornings between 7-10 was nice and I found the hotel staff to be helpful.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6574dfe180bd08e6ad4b493422096b67" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel My mum I stayed here back in Feb 07 (standard room at back of hotel). We really had a pleasant stay. Rooms were clean and the shower was really hot and powerful! I can't comment on the b'fast as we ate every meal out! There are some fab restaurants all within walking distance of the Ramada. Particularly the chinese which name escapes me for obvious reasons!!!! opp side of street from Ramada about 100metres on the left going in direction away from Central Station. I must really compliement the staff on reception - I was most impressed that they never once said our room number out aloud. If only all receptionists were as professional with female travellers. ..Location of hotel is great - about a 4-5min walk from Central Station with good links to trams etc. Returning to Amsterdam in July with my boyf - hopefully it is just as nice. I will do another review as have booked a 'Star Room' for my next visit! Oh and if you have room at back of hotel be prepared to see a few ladies in windows - as liberal minded as my mum is I must say her face at the window saying Blimey - there is a woman dancing in the street in just a bikini will always make me laugh! Happy Travelling .................
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>