<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="1ca7b232b99c2b11c609b8c2d4577cfe" url=""><![CDATA[Loved It!!! I just can't say enough good things about this property. My two older sisters, my 19 yr old granddaughter and her Mom spent 3 short nights here. Oh how I wish it could have been more. Once I called the condo/hotel and made reservations, I had several emails with the reservations manager. I had several requests to make this trip special for my sisters, mainly, because of their age, it will probably be the last trip to Hawaii together, so I really wanted something nice. I asked that our 2 BR, 2 BA Ocean Front Deluxe unit be between the 15th and 18th floors, that we have an 02 or an 03 style unit and that we get one of the newly remodeled units. Every request was met! 16th floor, 03 unit and very nicely remodeled with granite countertops in the kitchen and bathrooms and stainless steel appliances! So nice and so spacious!!! We never got in each others way.We were greeted at at the FREE valet parking garage with a warm aloha and welcome to the tower. We were directed to check inwhich went quickly and we had only been in our room a couple of minutes when our luggage arrived. The bellman put our suitcases in our respective rooms for us and explained some of the features of our unit before he left. Ech and every time we left or returned, we were greeted with Aloha, did yu have a good time, etc! We were totally taken with the staff. So nice and so friendly.Housekeping surprised us each night with bed turndown and candy on te pillow!!!When it came time to leave, our luggage was collected on time and stowed in our rental car.Back to the condo, our view of Kuhio Beach Park was outstanding. We were a few blocks from the International Marketplace in one direction and a few blocks from Kapiolani Park, the aquarium and the zoo in the other. So lovely to enter through a walkway that had beautiful flowers along each side and trailing orchids overhead. I hope to be able to return here one days! I can't wait in fact. I can't recommend it enough.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f0748ff4110dfd547e1e65d1e80653cb" url=""><![CDATA[Will only EVER stay at the Aston Waikiki Circle! We have stayed at the Aston Waikiki Circle a total of nine times between 1978 (before Aston)and 2001 and cannot even imagine staying anywhere else in Waikiki. The staff has never changed in all those years and we have become friendly over the years. Going back each time is like re-visiting old friends! They are wonderful to us and we have no complaints at all. The rooms ARE small but have all you would need as a place to sleep and the view CANNOT be beat! If you look, you can find a great rate too. I would only book into an ocean view or oceanfront room though for the best location. Going back in 2005 and cannot wait!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>