<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f4fe2ea85ac7fc0ad1959fe31e7b5359" url=""><![CDATA[Bahia Principe is Excellent! BACKGROUND: We have traveled to various Caribbean destinations: Mexico, Mayan Riviera, Cuba, Jamaica and the Dominican, always going to 4-5 star resorts, booking all inclusive, and relying on Trip Advisor before we book. Our primary concerns when doing research on a location are as follows: (1) Trip Advisor reports and ratings (2) the beach (3) pools and amenities (4) brochure ratings. We spend hardly any time in our rooms, apart from changing/cleaning up/sleeping. Basically, if the sun is up, we are outside. TRANSFERS FROM AIRPORT:This is a nice part relatively quick 30 minute transfer to the resort, with a glimpse of the local scenery along the way. While on route, we received our check-in package, wrist bands, etc. so that when we arrived all we had to do is bring our luggage to the resort transfer trams (waiting for our arrival) and we were off to our rooms. This avoids the lineups at check-in; a nice touch. If you want a room safe, though, you will have to go to the lobby desk to book this, which we did right away.RESORT/GROUNDS:This has to be the nicest resort in terms of lush tropical vegetation, constantly being maintained and groomed. We have been to some very nice resorts over the years, but this location is stunning in terms of the landscaping.Yes, this place is HUGE, but we knew that and loved it. Always something or someplace to go. The trams run constantly, and we used them when we were tired, but also enjoyed many nice strolls through the grounds. This is an excellent resort to take advantage of the walkways and exercise off some of that extra all-inclusive consumption we all tend to enjoy!The resort is divided up into the following sections: Punta Cana (708 suites), Bavaro (540 suites), Club Premiere (288 suites), and the Ambar (adults only) sections. Inside these sections are the various exclusive clubs: the Royal Golden, Club Diamond and Club Hacienda. Your booking will determine which section, and sub-section if applicable, you are staying in. FOOD/RESTAURANTS:I tend to not give our personal reviews on the various a la carte restaurants, as opinions vary so greatly in this area, even at home. I might like one type of locale, you will like advice is to book whatever you can, enjoy, and if you want something else head back to the buffet. As for the buffets, typical for your all inclusive resort. They need to feed hundreds of people with various tastes and preferences; some people will be thrilled, some will not. Personally, I enjoy the varied selection and appreciate the choices. As for service, we were treated very well and promptly at all meals. Our attitude is that these people work very long hours, for little pay or gratitude. We make a point of greeting EVERY waiter/waitress with a genuine smile and engage in our best broken Spanish/English conversation, and they would always light up and smile in return. We always tipped, but this made no difference in the level of service received. In fact, being kind and appreciative would get the best service, rather than being miserable, complaining, and then leaving a tip. We observed both behaviours, and I feel sorry for the wait staff when they have to deal with these rude people. ROOMS:All the rooms are junior suites, and well appointed. Lovely marble tile, etc. - we were in some brand new buildings which were not even on the Resort's maps yet! Book your in-room safe as soon as you arrive (we paid $31 US for the week); no sense in risking losing anything. The resort is not responsible for any valuables not locked up in the safe, simple as that.BEACH: Stunning, amazing, goes on forever with adjoining resorts along both directions. There is a nice set back from the edge to the start of the resort, allowing for ample room for sun and shade choices. Loungers were in abundance, and the shade choices for those with sunburns or young children were excellent. The sand is a very light tan/brown colour, and extremely silky soft underfoot. Absolutely no stones, shells, coral, or other hazards for your feet (which we have experienced at some other resorts, unfortunately). Again, excellent for wonderful walks that go on forever in either direction. The water is incredibly warm, quite a pleasant surprise for the ocean have experienced cooler waters further south! BEACH FOOD DRINK:A nice touch are the two restaurants close to the beach, which you can use without having to cover up. You can go in barefoot, with your bathing suit on, and enjoy the beachside buffets, self serve non-alcoholic beverages, and the bar. This might sound lame, but when you are hot and sweaty from lying out in the sun, putting on clothes to get something to eat can be such a hassle; I really enjoyed being able to just walk over and get some food/drink along with all the other people doing the same thing. POOLS:A nice selection to chose from, and large. This is a nice option for those who like the pools; they are big, and provide plenty of room for singles, couples, and families with children. We personally prefer the ocean, as we have pools up here, but we do use them on occasion. The pools/pool bars close around 5:30 pm for maintenance and cleaning; typical for down south. EXCURSIONS:As we have been to the Dominican before, we have done the excursions we wanted to do, and decided to stay the entire vacation right at the resort. However, in the past we have done the Saona Island and Swim With the Sharks/Catamaran trips, enjoying both. Saona Island has the most incredible white sugar sand! The only downside of this excursion is that it makes for a very long day, with a long bus trip each way. EVENING ENTERTAINMENT:Again, typical for the all-inclusive resort; they work hard, and do their best to keep you entertained. We enjoyed a few shows; every resort seems to have their Michael Jackson look-alike to amaze you (we enjoyed that show as well). ONLY DOWNSIDE:We were astonished at the high percentage of people who smoked, everywhere! If you have any sensitivity to second hand cigarette/cigar smoke, take care to position yourself upwind. I normally get put off by things at any resort, but this was a surprise, even when at the huge beach. You are not allowed to smoke inside any enclosed restaurant, but in the open lobby bar, theatre, and beach restaurants its okay. We found that our enjoyment at the beach, lobby bar and at the theatre was compromised by the volume of second hand smoke; more than once we had to move our beach loungers to avoid cigarette smoke. This situation is a non-issue if you smoke. not complaining, just astonished. RECOMMENDATIONS:This is a very nice 5-star resort, and comes highly recommended. Do your homework before you go, so that there are no surprises. If you prefer individual, royalty treatment, consider upgrading to the Ambar adults-only section, but remember you are still part of a very large group of vacationers. Leave negative attitudes at home; they will not get you very far when travelling (ever wonder why the complainers, who keep it up all week, always have such a lousy time?). We did hear of some couples having problems with their rooms/air conditioners/etc. but the had these issues rectified to their satisfaction. There will invariably be issues when you travel, but being prepared is a big part of enjoying your vacation. Book your room safe for valuables.Enjoy!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>