<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="ab79f56c102dad6639b240e1ebdb7066" url=""><![CDATA[Just as Great Second Time Around We just returned from our second visit to the Dominican Beach. We were there in Jan 2006 when it was the Ocean Bavaro. We really like this resort for the fantastic beach, great pool, beautiful grounds, the general convenient layout of the buildings, the friendly staff, and, of course, the price. Apparently some of the rooms need repair, but we have had fine rooms both times. This time we requested and got a room in Block 100, which is the newest. We enjoy the activities during the day and the entertainment at night. The food this time was acceptable, but not quite as good as the first time. The guests were generally young and not American. There were large contingents from Quebec (French), Italy, and Germany. We are 65-year-old Americans, but we enjoy the excitement of the young people and the cultural diversity. If you need older English-speaking people around, you should probably go somewhere else. We will be keeping our eyes open for a good deal to return next January.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="79f20d854fa0ddaa2ef69448af57e1e2" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic Time at the Ocean Bavaro We just got back from an absolutey fantastic 6 nights at Ocean Bavaro. I do not understand the negative reviews that had us very worried. If you need an American 5-star hotel, then stay home or pay three times as much. We loved the mix of languages and cultures. It was like a beach vacation and a trip to Europe combined. There were very few Americans, but a significant number of Canadians so there was English spoken in addition to Spanish, French, Italian, German, and Dutch. We got lucky and got a good room first time around in Building 96. The room was freshly painted and similar in quality to an older Holiday Inn. Building 96 is as far from the beach as you can get, but this was not a problem. It is a short 5 minute walk through the beautiful grounds to the pool or beach. We enjoyed finding our way through the maze of trails with new picture opportunities at every turn. I kept taking pictures of the beautiful flamingos and cranes in the lake. The grounds are immaculate. Every morning, every stray leaf and twig is swept up. We also did not get a single mosquito bite and saw only a few flies. Beach: The beach is awesome. The powdery white sand makes the water a ittle too milky for snorkeling, but it could not be better for everything else. Pools: We loved the main pool with its palm shaded nooks and islands. We made good use of the swim-up bar. All the bars were well staffed with no more than a 0 to 5 minute wait. The pool was comfortably warm because it is sheltered from the wind. In some other hotels cold water is a problem. Food: The food in the buffet was quite acceptable. It ranged from average to excellent. There was much variety, so you could only eat the things you liked. The beach grill was a favorite for lunch. On different days, they had grilled lamb, pork, beef, or fish, as well as the usual buffet. We went to all of the ala carte restaurants, but found them generally no better than the buffet. We ate everything including the salads and the fish, and the goat, and did not get sick or hear of anyone else getting sick. We also liked the almost 24-hour pizzzeria. Staff: We found the staff to be friendly and helpful in every way. They sometimes know little English, but, hey, I don't know any Spanish. I did, however, learn enough to order my pina coladas and Bahama mamas con mucho ron. Summary: We loved it and would absolutely go back.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>