<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="c0667e1bf37c2eb79418df7c2fdae05c" url=""><![CDATA[5 Nights at the New York Helmsley We arrived on 22nd Feb (we were there for our 25th Wed Anniversary on the 24th, ...a treat to ourselves) After a very long day we arrived at the Helmsley only to be told they were expecting us on the 27th, the receptionist made a phone call and told us it wasn't a problem etc etc and that they'd give us a nice room. The room was on the 14th floor, king sized bed, which was the best bed I've EVER slept in! The room was clean spacious enough for the two of us. We had a view of the chrylser building. My only disappointment was that they don't have any tea making facilities, although we later found out we could ask for them (and have it added to our bill) anyway... please take a credit card as you need it to check in with, not a debit card, one of ours wouldnt work but thank god my hubby has his american express which was accepted everywhere we used it. His goldfish card wasn't, nor was my personal bank card (which had plenty funds in it).. also beware of the cash machine in the lobby, it accepted my bankers card but never gave me any cash.. sorry to harp on about cash etc but if you're new to the states like we were, we didnt have a clue what would or wouldnt be accepted.Breakfast in Mindys (downstairs) was great, we founed we didnt need to eat again until about 4pm as the breakfast were buffet style so we ate as much as we wanted/needed.The staff in Minday and Harry's bar were very attentive, and being British we weren't used to it, but to be fair I could get used to it, the service was great, fast and efficient.The hotel is in a great situation for Grand Central, but to be honest we walked most of the time, we did buy a 7day metro ticket for $23 each which was so handy and if you're tired it's so easy just to jump on a train, having said that, cabs are cheap enough if you want to use them.Overall we had a fab time, and the hotel was as I expected, it was clean and comfy, and believe me, Im a clean freak and I was very happy to stay there.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>