<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f4d1398225462cea4b33d03153286866" url=""><![CDATA[Very good, but not great We have just returned from a trip to Bali including four nights at the Karma Jimbaran (see review) and three nights at Uma Ubud. Our stay here did not get off to a good start. We had booked a car to pick us up from Jimbaran, but the car didn't arrive. I phoned the Uma and they sent a car immediately, but due to the distance between the resorts, we ended up waiting over two hours in total. We also had to switch rooms after the first night due to some plumbing problems, which wasn't such a big problem, but certainly not ideal. We received a free late check-out at the end of our stay, which may have been intended as compensation, although no-one said this explicitly.As for the resort, the reception and pool areas are beautiful, and the restaurant is set lower down in the valley with nice views and a lovely open-air feel. However, the resort is situated on a relatively small piece of land, and therefore the villas are packed tightly together with no sense of space. This was a huge contrast to the wondeful Maya Ubud, where we stayed last year.We stayed in a garden villa, which was not the cheapest category of room but probably the worst. The room itself is nice, if very simple, and the bathroom is beautiful, but the garden consists of a small sitting area with a table and two upright chairs, and a tiny lawn. Both areas are completely surrounded by 3-meter high walls - meaning that your view is a small square of sky - and both are too small to fit loungers. The cheaper terrace rooms had beautiful views of the valley, so if a view is important to you, go for the cheaper option!We ate at the restaurant for breakfast every day, and for lunch and dinner on other occasions. The food was good, but nothing amazing. We also tried Mozaic, where the food was fantastic, but we found the whole experience to be exhaustingly fancy and formal - not the kind of thing we're looking for in a holiday in Bali.One of the great things about the Uma Ubud is its location just steps away from Sanggingan Road, where you can find lots of nice shops and galleries, a few restaurants (including Mozaic), and the fabulous Bintang supermarket for beer, juice and snacks ten times cheaper than the mini bar at the resort. We also had a superb lunch at the Kafe Batan Waru in Ubud town center - my beef rendang was the best meal of the whole trip. Definitely worth a visit.Another mention should go to the reception staff, who were incredibly helpful and polite.I've listed quite a few negatives here, but I still enjoyed my stay at the Uma Ubud. Nevertheless, I would probably go back to the Maya Ubud or splash out on the Four Seasons Sayan if I went back to Ubud for another visit.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>