<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="fc70515ec7edfa0d1859feacf9728028" url=""><![CDATA[Would go back there again anytime... I have posted this on the other - also popular site - so you may read it twice. First of all, this wouldn't be as much review of the place - which is excellent - but our rather humble comment - to some of contributors.It wasn't my intention to enter this good-bad exchanges (reviews),but after reading several very contrastings reviews, I have made a decision,to supply my 2 cents worth and contribute myself... And I can say: I'm doing this for the first time ever. (Of course this will be second time, first time was the other site.)Unfortunately, it won't be as much about this resort (or place),but rather about those people pretending to be a world wise travellerswho know everything best...To start with: I will not mention places I have travel to - or tohave an experience with, because it doesn't make sense at all.Instead, I will say only that this resort, by all means, deserves those four-and halfto five stars ratings you can see. And for you, those people complaining about small, petty,and excuse me - quite stupid - problems, I can say only this:go to the real world. But please, don't pretendto be a know-all everything person. Because you are not!If you were, you wouldn't mentioned those silly problems youmay - or may not - have encountered.Remember this: they can happen everywhere!In Paris Ritz Carleton or Waldorf Astoria in New York...It is your privilege to whine, complain (or -----) about everything,but remember: in the real world you can always - and everywhere, find something that p/o you, or that you don't like. However, there is a big difference between your subjectivityand objectivity as a whole...Now briefly to the facts - objectivity or subjectivity:We returned from Bavaro Princess in Punta Cana 11th of June, and by all means - and truthfully - we can say this: it was a perfectexperience and we had very enjoyable vacation. Again, we will not brag - ormention places we have been or we seen before, but regardingthis resort- it is thumps up, and its 4.5 to 5.0 stars rating well deserved!With an exception of a poor orientation in such a big complex, everythingwas, and worked just OK. (And we didn't have to buy VIP' suite...)As an example: there was a problem with lights when we arrived,and we had reported thisbefore lunch time. On our return - about two hours later, it was fixed!Would you get this in Sheratons or Hiltons?... I guess you will. But same we got here.And those complains about language - what a crap...You people think that staff there will learn all those languages theymay encounter: English, German, French, Italian, Japanese and so on...?Don't be naive. With an exception of Holla we didn't know much more.But we communicated with everyone we had to...And the last thing: please, don't be el-cheapo - as we have seen this several times.It means even if you are all inclusive, it is a courtesy - and I would say a normal thing - to give some token of appreciation in a form of gratitudeto a waiter/waitress that served you in a reservation only restaurant...I frankly can say that I was ashamed to see people leaving without leaving even thosepathetic 25 cents as a gratitude! Can you imagine to do this any place you live in: USA, Canada, Australia,Germany or Great Britain...? There you would be mark for ever!!! (And we are not talking about some huge tips, just a dollar or so would do thatand go a long way...)So it is all, and for your info - I'm from Canada - but originally from Europe.To close all this: Bavaro Princess is 5*PS: Try not to fly - if in Canada - with Skyservice. It is no good.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>