<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="b0f97b1fbc4a5331dc5ad364c80f655c" url=""><![CDATA[Over-priced but Efficient My wife and I have just returned from a week's stay at the Caribe Hilton in San Juan PR , paying a convention rate which still was quite expensive. Every additional item was charged and the restaurants' meals drinks were extortionate - so thanks to previous travellers who suggested the convenient Subway on the corner nearby. It is often worthwhile getting a cab into Old San Juan ($10 to $11 each way) to sample the numerous restaurants there and the vibrant street scene (a festival on the Sunday celebrating San Sebastian and noisy Birthday celebrations).The room was comfortable and the front desk did move us at our request due to the dull view across a cigarette butt strewn roof we had from the third floor room initially allocated. One bright spot was the pride in his job shown by Augustus who took care of the pool area near the tropical gardens. It was kept absolutely pristine and it was clear how much he cared for the area and the hotel guests who used it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c4a1da76ea6bf02ba81844306e21c142" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful place to stay After 7 days at the Caribe Hilton, where every little item is charged for as an addition to the room rate, it was such a refreshing change to stay here for three days.The old convent was tastefully restored 10 years ago and although in need of some minor renovation this did not diminish our enjoyment. Close to the shops and restaurants - it was simple and safe to walk around the Old Town. (NB away from the no-go areas of La Perla its nearby graveyard).Impeccably and frequently cleaned, the service from all staff was beyond expectation, (UK-USA electrical transformer loaned at no cost), the daily wine cheese reception (comlimentary) was superb and the restaurants dished up very tasty food. If dusk is between 6 7 pm, the bat aerobatic display is an interesting entertainment during the wine cheese reception.There is a 350 year old tree in the courtyard - a roost for these bats birds.A most enjoyable experience.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>