<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="812a35c6aa6841c600172705661ffb4e" url=""><![CDATA[Tucked away My wife and I were very satisfied with our stay. We arrived jet lagged and found the staff helpful and responsive. Breakfast had a nice spread of hot and cold foods. We had a French Tour group staying with us so the dinning area was packed. We did the European thing, asked if we could join someones table. (This is appalling to Americans) The Hotel is very safe inside as outside walking home at Midnight. We didn't bother with the Metro even though we had a stop close by. You can walk to most places of interst without fanfare. I use crutches by the way...... We did take a cab on suggestion of the Hotel to a Bus station and it was reasonable 5 Euro cross town. Within 8 city blocks we had a Tony Roma's, Hard Rock Cafe, Sub Way and Burger King. For some this can be handy since the Spanards eat late. Tony Roma's for example closes at 2 PM and opens back up at 8:30PM. We ate the local food which is excellent. I would stay in this Hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="187e2c720577d764f49bea0bfd321428" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent stay We had a excellent stay on our Boston vacation. The staff were always available when we had a question. Check in was fast despite a convention registering just before us. This hotel is not located in the city center. However we had no problem navigating with our car or on mass transportation. A good GPS. is a must for Boston. I realize from some of the reviews, we are more adventurous than most people. The view of the waterfront and Logan Airport across the harbor was relaxing. Our room was very quiet. We never heard anyone in the next room or hallway. My son loved the pool and the soft beds. We always felt safe venturing out at night walking to a restaurant. One night we found a Italian Restaurant that had great to go pizza. There is a Micro Brewery around a ten minute walk away. It's closed on Sunday and Mondays. We used the free WiFi in the lobby area. I didn't see the need to pay for it up in the room just to check email. The compliant we had was with having to Valet park our car. If you want fast food and shopping out the door this Hotel is not for you.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>