<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="8404960a8013ff79ef8a979e6495d34d" url=""><![CDATA[Nice views, but more business-like rather than resort-like View from the Ala Moana suite 20th floor
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="daa973d64093a3f52ca254a6640c2f48" url=""><![CDATA[Will Never Stay at this Holiday Inn - Cheaters and Liars We didn't even get to stay here! ...And we never will. They are very insulting of my intelligence and regards for quality customer service. Trying to check in by parking in the portico was terrible to start. But the worst was when 3 different ways of booking the room came out to very different results. Let me first mention that I am aware that hotels have internet only rates. WIth that in mind, when booking the room on the internet, I was able to get a room for $107 with the Entertainment Card rate, AAA rate $134, standard rate $179. I didn't book the room in advance because I needed the room at noon for my family to check in, and I wanted to do it at noontime so that they could tell me if it were possible to check in right away. So, I called at noon and was told over the phone that the room type I wanted was not available anymore, but a lower room was available, but for the same price as the better room. For some reason, I didn't trust this person, so I drove over there since I was only a few blocks away. When I got there, the front desk person had a different story. He said the room type I wanted was available, at $179, but there were no discounts since the hotel was busy. No AAA rate, nor Entertainment, nor anything. He suggested I go back to the internet and book the rate I was getting and then come back. I told him that AAA and Entertainment are not Internet rates and I am almost always able to get at least a AAA discount at the front desk. He didn't care. He was cocky. I have never been turned away at the front desk before trying to book a room. Usually the hotels I go to will do anything to keep you there - find some sort of rate other than the rack rate! I couldn't believe it. It was insulting. I have never stayed there, and I don't know why I was making such an effort to stay there. I am a hotel junkie and like to try different hotels, especially in SF. Plus, this hoteI had a pool, which is rare in SF. I have stayed at the best and at 3 star hotels, but I know I will not try this hotel ever. For a comparable price, try the Miyako Hotel - excellent service, room decor, views and location. Also, the Comfort Inn on Lombard. My feeling is if I can get even one person who reads this to not stay at the Holiday Inn, I will feel satisfaction that they didn't really make any extra money by not booking the room to me at the discount price and by lying about availability and rates. Stay somewhere else.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="09bd5596199d64bfc41358dba7abd43c" url=""><![CDATA[Chic but overpriced I have stayed at many hotels in San Francisco, and the room we got at the W seemed the most cramped. The Chic, trendy theme and the window seat made it bearable. The decor and fixtures were great. We used our Starwood points to stay at the hotel to try it out. For the weekend we stayed, it was a busy weekend in SF, so the rate for our standard room would have been $389/night if we had paid for it. Unfortunately, it was not worth it. We enjoyed the service, views, location, and the XYZ restaurant, but we feel there are better hotels in the city for even better price. We asked for a corner room, but they claimed there were none available. Perhaps that corner room would have changed our view of the room since it would have been more spacious. In all fairness, most of the large hotels in SF have small rooms, of which the corner rooms change the entire mood of the stay. We liked the pool and hot tub. Small, but a treat since many hotels in SF don't have a pool at all. I liked the glass ceiling. The Bliss Spa (operated independently of the W, but inside the hotel on its 4th floor) seemed unnecessarily snooty. Overall nice stay, but due to small standard room size for the price, we won't be staying at this W again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7cad1487b3a66bbdf2d9429e9adf5f6f" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent quiet location, but overpriced View from the Dolphin Lanai
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>