<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="c2a9e1f501b6f8bca00767508c7796e2" url=""><![CDATA[Glad we got a good deal We found a great deal for the Westin Palace through expedia, and having heard that this was one of the grande dame 5* hotels in Madrid we decided to go for it for our mini-honeymoon weekend break. On first glance the hotel appears to be exactly what it claims: a 5* elegant, grand hotel in an excellent location. However, our impression was that this grandeur is becoming increasingly faded, especially in the public areas and corridors: faded, worn out carpets and peeling wallpaper. Aside from the bedroom (very clean, wonderful shower and very comfy bed) and service (great generally but see below) this is more of a 4* establishment. We came directly from a stay at The Dorchester Hotel in London, and the Westin Palace was notably inferior.My husband had emailed the concierge ahead, unbeknown to me, asking for flowers and champagne in our room on arrival. Nothing was there when we checked in. He spoke to the concierge simply to make it clear that he didn't want to be charged and the concierge apologised profusely. Later that afternoon champagne and flowers duly appeared (along with a cake that declared Happy Anniversary...it was our honeymoon!) for which we were not charged. We felt that although this was a little glitch they more than made up for it.Oh, and we asked for a recommendation for somewhere to see flamenco and were directed to Cafe de Chinitas. It was geared completely towards tourists and a total rip off (200 euros and we weren't drinking!) and not really the genuine, gritty flamenco that we were looking for. They also recommended Thai Gardens, which was a wonderful Thai restaurant - the best I have ever eaten!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1f3e3b45e8f7d226ac8da7b9eab5cc4a" url=""><![CDATA[Quintessentially English We stayed at this hotel for only one night, and it was definitely too short an experience! We would have asked to stay another night but unfortunately we had to leave that day.The service and the smiles that you get with it are the characteristics that set this hotel apart. You get the feeling that the staff are really looking out for you, and genuinely want to to make your stay exceptional. There is no austerity nor pretentiousness about the place.We stayed in an executive double, which was small but perfectly formed. The room reflected on the hotel as a whole: quintessentially english but with all modern conveniences and luxuries too. I particularly liked the fact that nothing was stingy - there were more than ample toiletries (Penhaligon's), complimentary snacks etc. We went out after a light tea and returned at midnight starving so plunder the pantry was fantastic for us; the breakfast was also delicious.All in all, this hotel is onto a winner: 5 star facilities and service, in a great location, with a distinctly personal touch!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>