<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="d50a9be113d5415d1bf22724e0f96df9" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic authentic hotel Our bedroom
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="489c743e6b239078f308d3b735fa10ef" url=""><![CDATA[Good location Stayed here for four nights in mid December 2007 with my husband as part of a three month trip around the world. We had booked the hotel solely based on its rating and the reviews on this website. Firstly, the hotel is excellent value for money. We had a bed and breakfast deal and found the inclusion of breakfast a great bonus. We had a huge choice from the menu and the food was plentiful and excellent. It was also served until 11am which was great. The hotel is in a central location right behind the Zucolo. The rooms are clean and spacious. If you are on a budget or just want great value for money this is a perfect place to stay. However it is fairly basic so if you are looking for luxury, consider an alternative. The only criticism really, as other reviewers have said, is noise. We too were kept awake from all night construction on a site behind us. Also, the hotel plays piped music throughout the corridors from early in the morning which can be heard in the rooms. We are not early risers, preferring to enjoy the nocturnal sights of a city, and found this quite annoying and completely unnecessary. Another bonus with this hotel is the rooftop terrace which offers beautiful views and a great place to catch some sun during the day. Also at night we saw plenty of residents on the terrace drinking a bottle of wine and enjoying the lights of the city. Again another great facility if you are on a budget or just fancy a night in.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f148ce4566a0fd2b1970db0814292256" url=""><![CDATA[LOVED this hotel View from reception
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f6a50a0cf561572c6f650a524994217e" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel Stayed here for two nights in October and have to agree with most of what has already been written. The hotel is excellent, part of a big shopping mall and also right beside the buzzing and fascinating Mongkok. If you want to be down near Hong Kong itself with views of the bay then this is not the place to stay but we went down that part of the city several times quite easily by MTR or taxi and did not feel we were missing out by staying in Mongkok. In fact it was quite refreshing to be staying somewhere a little different. We were in a standard room but found it well above average, though small. The glass walled bathroom was quirky and the bathroom itself well stocked. Bed was comfortable. The only small criticisms were that there was some very obvious damp in the bathroom and the internet in the room was very expensive. Staff overall were friendly and efficient and we used the concierge service for restaurant recommendations and other information. Finally a word has to go to the fabulous rooftop pool and the magnificent spa. Prices for the treatments might seem a little off putting but are well worth it. We stayed here as part of a three month trip around the world and this was the best spa we came across.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>