<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f1b1775fae25b8b76301d0881d1aa20c" url=""><![CDATA[If you have young children, read this With the deal we got on Expedia, we couldn't resist taking a chance on the Copamarina resort. It seemed to good to be true that we could get such a deal, so I called the hotel to ensure that the resort wasn't under construction or had a recent outbreak of something or other. The friendly and patient person I spoke with at the 1-800 number for the hotel kindly answered all my questions, so we made the leap. And I'm glad we did! My wife and I have two young girls under the age of 5 so we wanted a relatively quick flight and a resort that we could entertain the kids in. Copamarina fit the bill and provided us with a very relaxing experience. We arranged for transportation from the airport through the hotel. We met the courteous driver, John, just outside the luggage pickup when we arrived at 10PM. He loaded us up into the comfortable minivan that already included 2 car seats installed for the kids, put on some soothing music and then drove us the two hours across the island to the resort. The rooms were comfortable and certainly adequate. The room was not spectacular in terms of furnishings or amenities, but it was clean and roomy enough for the four of us. The best part is that our room, like almost all rooms on the ground floor, had a porch that was about 50 yards from the beach and 50 feet from the kiddie pool. It was a great feature that allowed us to relax and enjoy the tropical paradise we came for. One of the only limitations of the resort was the food. Enjoy the buffet breakfast because the lunch selection is somewhat limited, especially for kids. Dinner at the main restaurant is excellent, but not for kids. The only option is to feed them before 6PM when the only other restaurant closes. And going to the nearby town didn't really seem like an option without a car. By squirreling away food from breakfast we did just fine. For the over prepared parent though, I can see how this might have a negative impact on the vacation. The resort itself was spacious, but not huge. With four pools and the beach, there was always plenty to do with the kids, as long as that is enough for you. We are usually very go-go people, but we wanted to just relax with the kids so this worked out perfect for us. There are other things to do like snorkeling, diving, kayaking, gym, spa, etc. so without kids any guest should be fine. We spent four days here and I'd say that it was just right. Any more time and I might have started to get antsy. We did employ the babysitting services for a grand total of 4 hours over two nights just so we could eat dinner at the restaurant. One of the hotel employees, Wanda, was our sitter and the kids loved her. Our kids are pretty good with sitters, but I was amazed at how they took to her. Even at $15 an hour, this was a true bargain! A few other quick items, do take the boat to Gilligans Island, or if it is closed go to the alternative deserted beach they suggest. It was a neat feeling to be all alone on a truly secluded beach where the snorkeling was easy and amazing. Do go to the town that is the jumping off point for Phosphoresent Bay, but DO NOT take the big boat. It is crowded, loud and generally not much fun. I've heard that there are smaller boats that will take you, but I didn't see where you can get them. Find a way to get the small boat, or skip the 1 hour trip entirely. Do eat at one of the fine reataurants in town suggested by the hotel - the chef and food are phenomenal! In summary, this was a great vacation and I would highly recommend Copamarina to anyone who is looking for a good, relaxing Carribean vacation.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>