<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="30925d97f111110bf00b43e686bec78e" url=""><![CDATA[Visited many of the top hotels in Tokyo I won't repeat what others have wrote so here's some new information: I visited (didnt stay) the 4 seasons maronouchi, mandarin oriental, park hyatt (stayed 1 night) and here's the deal: You cant beat the grand hyatt. I am not sure if the rooms are better at the other hotels since I didnt see them but the location and lobby of the hyatt can't be beat. It's so spacious and the MO and 4S seemed very small. It's as if the only thing on the ground floor is the front desk. The GH has many places to eat and is attached to the mall which means there are at least 30 different places to eat, amazing. I highly recommend the high end japanese restaurant on the 4th (or 6th) floor of the hotel connecting the mall (Shinbou may be the name). I had lobster sashimi which is nearly impossible to find in the US. The tail was filled with meat and was separated from the body but the lobster kept moving it's eyes and legs while on ice. Also had fugu (the real deal costs at least $200, mine US$300 for one person at kuromonto near this hotel (5 min taxi). This restaurant serves fugu 5-7 different ways so it's a good way to try different preparations (and yes, one is sashimi). It was very good but not excellent but it's the fish not the restaurant's issue. Cool front entrance, somewhat nice interior. The park hyatt has much fewer restaurants but an amazing bar that is worth visiting for a drink due to the view from the 41st floor with glass walls on 3 sides.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="45a189115f229a8846d2d13ae7fc62af" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent hotel in great location MY TRAVEL STYLE: I hate business hotels and strongly prefer resorts that resemble the Four Seasons, Aman, and Oberoi but try to find similar properties at lower cost. I seek out the and I encourage you to view hotels I have stayed at and their respective reviews (by clicking on my name).LOCATION: Perfect! 20 minutes walking distance from Forbidden City and Tiananmen Square. 5 minutes walking to a very high end mall. Restaurants surround the hotel. TYPE OF ROOM: Fashion SuiteBED/SHEETS/PILLOW: Bed is on the hard side with good quality linens that were brand new and should hopefully get softer with use. Pillows are medium thickness and fine.LIGHTING: Tons of lighting in both bedroom and bathroom. like that the light switch lights (so you can see where they are at night) light up too brightly when trying to sleep.BATHROOM/SHOWER: Incredible in the suite. Round tub is excellent and the shower has medium shower pressure with the hot water never running out. Towels are of excellent quality.TOILETRIES: Good, nothing too special, but fine.CLEANLINESS: The entire room and hotel is very cleanA/C: A/C and heat works quietly and quickly would get the room warm or cool.CLOSET SPACE: Walk in closet is one of the most impressive seen in any hotel. Huge!STYLE OF ROOM: Contemporary and beautiful. change much here. The room has floor to ceiling windows and runs for wall to wall, impressive!QUIET/MORNING LIGHT: The room was very quiet with the exception of music that would play during the daytime from across the street. Almost sounded like being next to a nightclub but not as loud. If you require complete silence, you may have better luck asking for a room away from the street that is in front of the hotel. Curtains would block out all morning sun light.FOOD: We only had room service which was mediocre (pizza soup). Would suggest ordering from kitchen one block away with free delivery.TV/INTERNET: TV is flat screen and of good size for the room. About 3-5 channels in English including a few movie channels. Internet is very fast and included at no charge (via wire only). There is a computer in our room if you have laptop with you. SERVICE: Staff are very helpful with good enough English to answer any of your travel questions. We were very disappointed with the housekeeping that replace towels, clean very well, and replace toiletries often enough.COMMON AREA: Exterior of building is not so nice but the lobby is good with a semi-hip feel to the environment. There is a bar in the lobby and places to hang out but I would rather spend my time in the beautiful fashion suite or some of the nicer bars in Beijing with better atmosphere. No pool. The gym equipment looked new, but the location is strange since it is out in the open in the dark basement below (but the gym is lighted well). ROOM CITY TIPS: There is a travel agent in the basement that can provide tours and airline/train tickets. Definitely splurge for the fashion suite as it is a very worthwhile upgrade. If you have breakfast included, kitchen is a 3 minute walk away and has western style breakfast (they deliver at n/c too). Also, there is a starbucks at the oriental plaza mall (basement of the mall on the right side once you cross the main pedestrian path). Booking through a source other than the hotel provided us with half price rooms.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5dc57457b32b9f34d74a5574614a580e" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic Roof Top Terrace Bar
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>