<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="1802c66b162f13de8aca78cd95c051b1" url=""><![CDATA[Dear god! HIGH CARB BUFFETS!!!!! This was a great hotel. Staff are helpful as long as you're not a complete snob (ie; from Victoria, want to be pamperred like you're at a W hotel, etc). Rooms were clean, well decoraded, and the mini-fridge was great to have. Buffet was good even though it, um, was not, Atkins Friendly (I'm a nutritionist, don't get me started on that diet ;) Housekeeping staff were friendly and attentive, and best of all, it's close to Qwest and Safeco Stadium. You'd be a fool to take a Cab from this hotel to the stadiums, simply jump on a Pierce Transit bus. Unless you're easily spooked by, *gasp* the homeless and racial minorities, it's a great way to actually see SEA and to get from place to place. Have fun!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a36053ece70d98715b6ec4c298dc3a3a" url=""><![CDATA[what is everyone complaining about? I am a former Starwood Junkie, recently converted to the ICHotels brand. As a Priority Club Platinum, I must say this was MY BEST Holiday Inn experience yet. The location is GREAT, but short of AMAZING, however. It's on the corner of Van Ness and California. It's quite a bit away from Union Square, but the Cali Cable car will get there, as will the 109 south to market with a transfer on the muni rail. That being said, there's plenty to do in the vicinity; there are lots of good sit down/take out places, and a BEVMO which is two blocks south. Google BevMo and you'll see why a boozing-enthusiast like me was so happy to see how close BevMo was to this property.My traveling companion and I took the BART/MUNI from SFO to get here. We arrived in under an hour and spent $6 each. We walked into the lobby and we were promptly helped. There was no priority lineup, but a airline crew lineup. Having airline crew stay at a hotel is definitely a GOOD sign. The clerk recognized my status and offered us both some bottled water. We were placed on to the top floor. Check in was swift and without incident.Our room was great with regular Holiday Inn amenities; tv, chair, fridge (8 beer capacity), comfortable bed. The room was clean but while we were in the room, we got crazy allergies; something we thought was a bit weird for SFO in the summer. We spent the last two nights in SFO at the Westin Union Square without any allergies in their room, and we guess it was because the air filter on the heater/ac had not been cleaned. Otherwise, we couldn't complain with the room. It was nicely decorated (about mid-90s look), and no issues with cleaners. Our room was cleaned every time we returned to our room from a day of touristing-around. Service at this property was impeccable and the front-liners at this property deserve the finest in recognition. For example, one night, we got a bottle of wine but didn't have any glasses or an opener. On our way out of the room for the evening, we passed a room service guy and asked him if he could get some glasses and an opener up. He said he would do that, and the fact that we were out of our room was not an issue. We returned to the room a few hours later and were delighted to see two wine glasses, an opener placed very elegantly onto a tray AND the guy put the wine we had on some ice. Amazing, I wish I left a tip and I further wish we got the guy's name. The pool was great but kind of weird to have in SFO; it's cold every day there. The warmest it gets there is 20c. But nonetheless, it was nice to dip into for a change. A hot tub would have been nicer, in my opinion.The lobby was busy all the time, especially with airline crew from Qantas, along with the Germans and Dutch. The gift shop lady (who also sells those weekly muni passes) gave us a really bad vibe. We never checked out the bar nor restaurant because there are so many other non-touristy places within the vicinity. Everyone (except gift shop lady) and everything at this property was great and left a positive impression of what a Holiday Inn can be. I will return and I insist that you book this property. You will not be disappointed, unless you're a snob and you want the W without paying the $250 internet prepaid rates.tips:-for a fun and cheap night of boozing; head out to the tenderloin, it's not THAT bad, and the characters you will meet FAR outweigh the grubbiness. just don't look like a bloody tourist complete with shorts, camera around neck, and lonely planet guide-there is a whole foods, located one block WEST down california and van ness; it's kinda hidden-any pizza place on van ness is good, there's a place on california a few blocks EAST that's good as well-breakfast at grubsteaks or the polk st diner is a sure bet-bev mo = amazing. if you thought you got a deal at duty-free, haha, well... go to bevmo. for example, canadian beer here is about half the price of canadian beer in canada. -get all your snacks at bevmo, NOT the rip off convenience stores on van ness that are near the hotel. -save on ATM fees; buy a piece of fruit and get $200 cash back from walgreens for no fee-the cleaners (forget the name) three blocks EAST down california is awesome. have them do your laundry; wash and fold for my entire wardrobe was something like $10 and it was done within 24 hours.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>