<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="3eeb9da1f4569cc74344a7a3bd169103" url=""><![CDATA[OK but can be noisy on weekends Between the price I paid for the room and the Hilton name I was expecting an outstanding property. It was nice but not anything special.The good:- Large room, with separate sitting area- Good housekeeping- Proximity to hiking trails.The bad:- Room was a bit shabby (scuffed furniture), had no view, and overlooked the parking lot- Not much close by. You really need a car, although there's a Safeway and some shops about a mile north.- 5 pools, none of which are big enough to do laps in- Exercise room (for which a resort fee is charged) is underwhelming, with a limited selection of equipment- Party destination, not a luxury resort, on weekends. I stayed there Thu-Fri-Sat. Thursday night was fine. Friday night the people next door dumped a whole bag of beer bottles off their balcony. Saturday night, the same room was occupied by a different group who were up doing shots and talking and laughing on the balcony. I called the front desk at 1:15 and 2:15 and it took 45 minutes each time before things quietened down. On checkout, front desk staff were relatively unsympathetic (and the ass't front desk manager was borderline rude), saying, we have no control over who stays in our hotel rooms. True, but you do have control over how you respond to complaints, especially if your guests are paying over $125 night for your rooms.Overall, it's OK. I guess I was expecting this beautiful luxury resort and it's kind of just an ordinary hotel with a few more swimming pools.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2b772b2771c4fa809ec1f6db583872ba" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, very nice hotel This new hotel is a 5 minute walk from the S-bahn line. Front desk staff were very friendly, spoke excellent English and responded to my request for an extra blanket very pleasantly. Rooms are a good size by European standards and very nicely appointed with windows that open. The free bottle of water in the fridge was a nice touch. Bathroom was large and, apart from the strange shower door, was nice, although the bathroom door didn't close as easily as it should have. Exercise room was a good size although there wasn't really much in the way of weight equipment. The sauna is excellent - very hot and a nice size. My only complaint is that we couldn't check in early and for security reasons they won't store luggage so we had to take the S-bahn to Alexanderplatz Bahnhof and store our luggage there for the day. Don't go to the Hauptbahnhof as the front desk recommends - it's farther away and costs a Euro more for the lockers.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>