<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="ed76ba6145eb3d9811c8403a8cd9c9ad" url=""><![CDATA[Five Star View We stayed at the Park Hyatt for 5 nights in March 2006 and here is what we observed:-There may be a nick or two in the furniture and it could use some exterior touch-up paint but make no mistake about it-this is truly a 5 star property.-The main reason you would stay here is the excellent location and the stunning knock-your-socks-off view of the harbour and Opera House. For this they get big bucks. But if you're not going to have a room with a view you would be better off staying somewhere else.-We stayed in balcony room 334 (top floor-level #4)and had a full straight-on view of the Opera House and a slightly-angled view of the downtown area. Most of the rooms to the left of room 333 (i.e. #332 down to about #300) have great city views but only a lateral view of the Opera House (everything over the hotel lobby is in this category) so if you want to sit on the balcony and take in the Opera House and the harbour views while having cocktails or pre-dinner snacks as we did every night you would have to lean over the railing and look sideways to see the Opera House. Rooms to the right of #335 down to around #354 have full Opera House views and partial bridge views but no city views. Rooms to the right of about #354 have only partial or no Opera House view. Rooms at the other end of the S-shaped hallway toward the bridge have Opera House views as well as bridge views. Then there are some rooms with just water views but without the Opera House or bridge or city. The rooms on floors 2 and 3 presumably would have the same setup but I didn't see them. The best thing to do is call the hotel directly on one of the dial around numbers like 1010987 and you can confirm for yourself the exact view of the rooms-it only costs about $2USD to talk for about 10 minutes. Don't waste your time calling the Hyatt toll-free central reservation number--they haven't the foggiest idea of the layout of the rooms or which way they face. The hotel's direct number from the US is 011-61-2-9256-1101.-Speaking of balconies, every third room facing the water has only a small semicircular balcony with no chairs or tables so if you plan on using the balcony on a regular basis you should consider the rooms with the larger balconies with furniture. Also, the top floor (level #4)balconies have a pergola-type overhang which lets rain and other things falling from the sky onto the balcony. If it's raining you couldn't use it and if it rains at night the chair cushions will be wet the next day. However, the balconies on the first and second floors (levels 2 and 3) have a fully-covered overhang from the balcony above.-The balcony rooms also have double sliding and locking glass doors which removes 100% of the noise of the harbour.-We arrived by cruise ship which docked at the overseas passenger terminal only a 3 minute walk away. I walked over to the hotel and got the bellman to come over in the hotel car to pick up our luggage and take it back to the hotel.-The hotel has a convenient location for many Sydney sights-10 minutes to the BridgeClimb office -5 minutes to the weekend market at The Rocks -20 minutes to the Opera House -10 minutes to Circular Quay -10 minutes to the Hero of Waterloo pubThe congierge staff is first class-they can arrange the BridgeClimb or set up private tours to Hunter Valley or the Blue Mountains using their recommended guides and drivers. They will also make a heavy-duty electrical converter/adapter available for your appliances.-The only negative we found was the exorbitant price of breakfast. Easily to overcome-there are several sidewalk cafes in the Rocks and along Circular Quay that are a 5-10 minute walk away. Additionally, there are several lunch and dinner restaurants right outside the harbourside hotel entrance.-When going to the airport the hotel can set you up with their limo for $90 or you can just have them get a street taxi for about $40.-When checking in I asked for and received a further 10% senior citizens discount off the room rate. At these prices that paid for our wine tour to Hunter Valley.-In summary, this is all about location and 5 star views. I thought it was worth it. You'll remember the view the rest of your life.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>