<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="64cba7138bdf2bc9285b93414eb74840" url=""><![CDATA[Biltmore has the Wright stuff! Attended an event in Phoenix that took place at Biltmore. I was initially apprehensive booking at this Hilton-Waldorf Astoria Collection Hotel. I usually prefer the Four Seaons option in Scottsdale. But I was pleasantly surprised!Checkin was personalized, efficient. Our room comfortable and spacious. Large screen HDTV was a surprise. Extra large closets were not expected. Our valley wing room 3425 was a value for the money- large balcony, spacious bath and amenities. The on site shops were friendly and well priced. The casual restaurant was fine- not exceptional dining, but great breakfast and lunch choices. The lobby bar was stylish and the place to be at night- although the lobby temp is frigid!!! This is a standard observation of all who have visited! Bellmen and car valets are top notch as are the spa attendants. The spa is top notch although the locker rooms/ communal areas could use some updating.We actually booked a return visit later this year!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b797b6e16cd83b544ffa4d7c2d179208" url=""><![CDATA[New Oleans Charm Just returned from a wonderful New year's visit to New orleans and the Windsor Court Hotel. Hotel was charming! Very accessible to french quarter and streetcar lines to the Garden District. Staff was gracious and appreciative of all patronizing the hotel. Rooms were quite spacious and comfortable. Our group booked junior suite and a one bedroom suite and were very pleased. The hotel has recently upgraded floors on Club levels that are more up to date. The rooms we had (911, 915, 917, 918) were all clean, luxurious, comfortable although were a bit dated. Huge marble bathrooms. Spacious dressing areas and small kitchenettes.The restaurants were great and staff quite accomodating. Special rates made this an amazing buy for this 5 star property.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>