<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="1f4ef778debc6b86bbb9e82c3d11afcf" url=""><![CDATA[It is very difficult to recommend this hotel UNLESS......................... you enjoy an excellent assortment of food, well appointed rooms, beautiful beaches, clean and attractive grounds, a well maintained pool area, and finally, friendly and helpful staff (everyone from the front desk to the cleaning ladies to the servers). Yes, there were a couple of minor glitches e.g. the phone didn't work in the room (it was fixed) and one day the maid forgot to place towels in the room. Having said that, I have stayed at a number of 45 star hotels (depending on who rates them) and rest assured there are always glitches.As far as the pool area goes, I will reiterate what others have said be prepared to get up early if you want to reserve a spot with shade. The unfortunate part of this is that a number of ignorant people will get up reserve these spots and only use them for an hour or less during the day. The security staff try to do their best but it is amazing how ignorant some people can be.If you have a problem going to another country and expecting everyone to speak perfect English and you are unwilling to use a little patience to try and communicate... DON'T GO as you will only be dissappointed. I saw a couple of people ranting and raving over very minor issues e.g. one man was asked to put a t-shirt on to go into a restaurant for breakfast and he became very belligerent, I don't believe this was an unreasonable request especially since there are notices everywhere about proper dress codes. The other was a person who expected to be able to use the facilities after checking out. It is not the hotels fault that the person and/or the travel agency did not make arrangements for a late checkout. Pretty much any hotel you stay at will not let you use their facility once you check out which is between 11:00am noon at most hotels.All of the Ambar rooms are within a 5 minute walk to either the main lobby or pool/beach areas. It is roughly 10-15 minutes to the rest of the Bahia property. There are trams operating on a regular basis throughout the entire Bahia property.I will not individually rate the restaurants as everyones tastes are different you will just have to try them. I can be a picky eater and enjoyed all of my meals. Overall a great vacation spot and would highly recommend it to others.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>