<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="c06a01329eac972a879aa30e73b5297b" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, better than expected room, good service, comfy beds! I took my mom to NYC for her Birthday. We planned to see 5 shows in 4 days, so wanted to stay in Times Square, near the theaters. The Marriott Marquis is my mom's sentimental favorite in NYC, so although I *really* didn't want to deal with the elevators and crowds there, we booked the Marquis, because after all, it was HER weekend. I have to say that Mom, as always, was right about this place! I was pleasantly surprised with the improvements they have made to this property. They fixed the elevators, which are now all electronically coordinated so that we never had to wait more than a minute or so for an elevator. We had a large (for NYC) room on the 36th floor and had a great view of Times Square (which we paid extra for, but we thought it was worth it for the small amount of time we actually spent in the room). Super comfy beds, newly updated decor, nice bathroom with marble counterops. See the Drowsy Chaperone which is playing at the Marquis theater. It is a throwback to old Broadway, where shows were just fun and meant to entertain us. No big social message...just happy and fun.Anyway, I'd stay at the Marquis again. Its not cheap, but conveniently located for the Theaters and easy to take the subway Times sq shuttle to Grand central station so you can catch the subway to many points in NY .
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fbd271061437579d87d357f23e7010f8" url=""><![CDATA[5 Stars?!?! You're kidding, right? I am currently staying at the Hotel Majestic. I had my business travel agent book this hotel based largely on the reviews on TripAdvisor. Upon checking in, I asked about the size of the room, as I had read some reviews complaining that some rooms were quite small. (Also, as I was checking in, I overheard 2 people trying to change rooms because they weren't happy with their first rooms). I must compliment the front desk clerk who helped me check in. She was extremely nice, but when I asked her about whether my room had a view or was a nice size, she frowned and said, that yes, indeed, I had been booked in one of the smaller rooms, but a nicer, larger room was available if I was willing to pay more. Since I have been traveling on business in Europe for more than a week and desperately needed sleep, I decided the extra charge was worth it for a better room, so I took it. While the room does have an extra sitting area, I have to say that this room is NOT of 5 star quality. There are marks on the walls, the furniture upholstery is worn, and the overall qualilty is more of a 3.5 star hotel, as far as rooms are concerned. There is also the annoying LOUD sound of water rushing through pipes on the other side of the wall of the room, approximately once an hour. The lobby area is nice, and the general location of the hotel is quite good, but as a business traveler, I really want the rooms and beds to be nice and comfortable. This marginally passes those criteria, particularly for the price for this room. Also, there is no ethernet connection so I am connected to a wireless connection that is not very reliable. Location (and some good online reviews) were the deciding factors in choosing the Majestic. However, having been here one day already, I am disappointed and wish I had gone with my first inclination to stay at the Hotel Arts. I would encourage the Hotel Majestic management to update the rooms and also encourage restaurant staff to make foreign visitors feel a bit more welcome.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>