<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="7ed46135ecce5a963d43b72390f640f9" url=""><![CDATA[Great, but not outstanding This is a prefect hotel for a trip to NY. Great location, good rooms, good staff, good value for money and all in all a very good 4 star choice.Only things that stop this being a 5 star rating, conceige who have a scam going with some private hire car firms who ripped us off and being placed in smoking room even when I tripled checked that it was a non smoking room.Otherwise would easily recommend this tip top 4 star NY hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a58f9a1b6de3421972b2bf55a2fd16af" url=""><![CDATA[Prefect city Break Hotel City breaks are all about location, and look no further than this cracking hotel.Located in the heart of the city - easy 50metre walk to Placa da Catalunya Metro station (direct trains to airport) and easy 2 mins walk from La Ramblas, main shops, and loads of restuarants and bars including Hard Rock Cafe (if thats your thing!).We just found the htel the ideal base to get around the city.Inside staff are warm and friendly, the atmosphere is relaxed, but being a new hotel all the rooms are well finished to a high standard e.g. flat screen TVs, huge showers and 1st class bathrooms. Breakfast was excellent (included in price)The only thing that stops this hotel getting 5 stars is the room size, which I felt was a little on the small size, but being a 6ft 4 chap - you may not have the same problems!All in all, the hotel made Barcelona a delight to visit
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6ff43afeaf61f21d7098e41275ec99b8" url=""><![CDATA[Top Business Hotel I stayed in this hotel for one night for business.I was upgraded to a junior suite without request and the room was fabulous (jacuzzi bath in the bedroom!) the hotel is finished to a very high standard and the breakfast was fantastic!The best hotel I have stayed in for a business trip ever! This place is worth every penny!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bd57348083b84711a6212069ff74bfff" url=""><![CDATA[Spot On This hotel is spot on!Value for money is very high, we booked over the internet on a rate of The rooms are very nice, and of high spec and finish. Similar spec to a 'Malmasion' hotel if you have stayed there.Should probably be a 4 star hotel. Very, very impressed.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>