<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="562a451a5925ebd18c554f0734e7d07d" url=""><![CDATA[Simply Perfect Everything about this hotel is perfect. The rooms, staff, room service, and location couldn't be faulted. This is an intimate hotel in a quiet part of Venice. St Mark's Square is just a few minutes away by Water Bus. There are only two reasons not to stay at Ca Maria Adele that I can think of: (1) It is expensive, (2) You like large impersonal hotels. Venice is a phenomenally expensive city but of all of our expenses the hotel was by far the best value for money. We stayed in the Fireside room for the first night and loved the lapping of the water just inches below our windows. It was light and airy with a fabulous walk-in shower. For the next two nights we stayed in the Doge's room. Opulent, luscious, deep red walls with a fabulous light and bright en-suite with two massive windows onto the street outside. When we arrived we were given two gigantic glasses of Prosecco and some Venetian biscuits while our room was prepared and the lighting adjusted just so for maximum impact. The hotel was an oasis of calm after hours of walking through the crowded streets of Venice.Of all our meals out the best by far was at the Linea D'Ombra restaurant, which the hotel recommends. We had a drink on the terrace overlooking the canal and then retired inside to the contemporary dining room for the meal. The staff were attentive, friendly, and knowledgeable. The food was very good and I would give it 8/10. It is however impossible to judge the restaurant on value for money because every meal and drink we had was exorbitantly priced. It was at least twice as much as we would normally pay for a meal of that quality for 2 with a single glass of wine each).Surprisingly one of the best cafe drinks we had was in St Mark's Square. for a hot chocolate for 1! But the second best hot chocolate I have ever had and it was worth it to watch the snakes of tourists get entangled as they tried to negotiate their way between tourist attractions.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>