<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="2e48b400d2b44bc827e658859e494a49" url=""><![CDATA[Great central NYC location! There's no better place to stay if you want to be right in the middle of it all! Smack in the middle of the wonderful chaos that is Times Square, mere feet away from the best of Broadway (including the half-price ticket line), and subway stations. Walking distance to Rockefeller center, Central Park, and other top NYC destinations! Of course this location means sirens and honking taxicabs at all hours, as well as hoards of pedestrians and tourists filling every inch of the sidewalk. Don't stay here if you're looking for peace and quiet, although I must say the windows are fairly successful at keeping out all the noise. The rotating restaurant on the roof is a must-see, even if just for drinks. It's too bad they took out the rotating cafe on the main lobby floor, but the new renovations and additional restaurants are wonderful! Weekend brunch is a pretty good value too, especially since the restaurants right outside your door are incredibly overpriced. Get out of Times Square if you're looking for a more authentic NYC experience. The Marriott Marquis can't be beat though if you want to stay right in Times Square/Broadway!! I've stayed here many times, with family and for business, and I keep coming back.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3aa275a37c961194d72b3188b0319c37" url=""><![CDATA[Great Boutique Hotel This is a great boutique hotel located in the financial district of Seattle, just a 10 minute walk from Pike Place Market. Maybe not the best place to stay if you want to be right in the middle of the action though. Vintage Park has a great restaurant and wine tastings right in the hotel. If you want to stay in a little quieter area, but still close enough to all the excitement of Seattle, I'd definitely recommend the Vintage Park. The rooms are awesome, with really comfortable beds, a large bathroom, and beautiful decor.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0f0df71658498b1c45d718cd5614303f" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel in a great location! The Astoria is a beautiful old hotel with lots of charm. The front desk staff was very helpful, although slightly limited with their English. The rooms were spacious with simple decor and artistic touches, the bathrooms were large and clean, and the building itself seemed well taken care of. I'm not sure where all these negative reviews come from! It's not the Ritz, but it's comfortable, clean, and well-situated, right down the street from the Medici chapels and the train station, and just a 5 minute walk to Il Duomo. Great restaurants right outside as well as a small supermarket. I wouldn't recommend eating in the hotel restaurant, especially with so many outstanding options just outside your door. Definitely check out the roof balcony if the weather's nice. Lounge/bar area a great place to meet with a group.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>