<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f8282b3e69359cb499f6448196909fb9" url=""><![CDATA[Riu...Really?? My husband and I just got in yesterday from a week at the Riu Taino and I couldn't wait to sit down to write this. We travel to the DR twice a year and couldn't wait to get there this year. Before driving up to the Riu Taino we drove through the Naibo first. The smell of sewage was soo strong that I honestly thought the driver took the wrong turn...The roads leading up were over flowing with sewage..The looks one the guest staying there said it all!! We were to originallly suppose to stay there but after reading the reviews I changed to the Taino 2 days before our depature. Upon arrival to the Taino check in was fast and easy...Finding our room..not so..We get to our room the door is open and the bed had been slept in...and the bathroom used..The Guys at the front desk didn't believe us and told us they had nothing else left!!After losing my cool we were finally assigned a new room which was much better. Yes beds are hard....Yes if you read this bring your own pillow!!!! You only get one per bed and they are flat as pancakes!! Grounds are beautiful...pool area always kept clean..beach gorgeous!! Buildings are very tired looking and are in desperate need of TLC. Staff....-Pool guys awesome!! -Servers at breakfast and dinner very attentive after being tipped -Housekeeping...hmmm ...I tipped extra one day and got 2 burnt out bulbs replaced! -Front Desk...Now these guys were the most upsetting. They couldnt be bothered with you what so ever!! Its very upsetting when one understands spanish...And these guys don't realize it. Some one at the Riu chain should teach these rude ignorant Boys some manners. I have never been so insulted in my life!! I am not from Germany nor am I from Italy...I am a Canadian who would appreciate the same respect that I give you!! I have stayed at many Riu's before and have never been treated in this manner. 1/2 of the people on our bus staying here all had the same experiences as us...the [--] fest one the bus I do have to say was one of the best highlights of this trip..Usually I am upset when the final day comes...as most of us get..This time around I couldn't wait to get back to the snow and the -10 weather..take that as you may..
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>