<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="ecc8906b0eca39f62946f225ec5e9ffb" url=""><![CDATA[Still the Classic Mansion Hotel Wife, 8 year old and I were in Dallas for the Cotton Bowl,, checked in Dec 31 for 2 nights. In Room 710 (next to Presidential Suite). I havent been to the Mansion in over 4 years, but still as I remember it. TALL ceilings in rooms, spacious setting in rooms (nice desk, chairs), giant closet. My room had a French walkout balcony (no view really, just some tree tops, and the hotel courtyard),, It's just a nice way to let in fresh air. King bed very commfy. 100% tiled bathrooms have nice double sinks, deep, deep tub, and a glass in shower. Very thick and large bath towels, and lots of bath amenities (tons of soaps/shampoos) along with fresh flowers in the bathroom too. Standard amenities include 2 times a day cleaning with evening turndown.We ordered room service, and it came up in quick fashion,, hot, and as ordered. Had drinks in --The Bar-- and breakfast in -The Restaurant-. Both places very nice and efficient, and suited to the Top Drawer fashion of the Mansion.Wife had a massage. She also did a AM work out in the gym,, all good she said.The room rate I paid for a -deluxe king- was 395/nt,, and since they did not have any 2 bedded/double rooms,,had to get a rollaway. The rollaway was a bit steep at 40.00/night. Thought they should eat the $40,, but I did not say anything,,just paid it.The only room negative was the TV. It was the --old-- standard 24 inch tube TV. In my home I got rid of the tubes a year ago and I'm spoiled to the HD/flat panel LCD sets. I've been to a ton of nice hotels (Ritz/ Four S. Penninsula, etc) and they all have gone now to flat panels. These tube sets are from the dark ages and should be replaced. They had a --tv volume-- control in the bathroom, but it didnot work. Not worth the hassle for me to call and -report- it. The check in/out smooth and efficient as the Rosewood Staff know the game. Car valet and unload/load of baggage very efficient. Keys given and baggage in room with in minutes of arrival. Complimentary coffee and tea all day long in the reception area. All the newspapers you would ever want to read are free in the morning. All in all, a great stay and I would go back for a repeat visit if business/vacation takes me to Dallas.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="586ab8eda3133e67181628ed3fe5b910" url=""><![CDATA[ultra hip Palomar I styayed here with wife on Dec 29, for 2 nights. Paid regular rate of aprox 325/night for a deluxe king. Staff very friendly and helpful. Car valet guy brought car up in quick time. Check in was quick. Luggage was brought to room right away. Wife needed a razor for legs, and it was brought with in 3 minutes of the phone request. Did breakfast room service,, quick and tasty.This was a Hilton back in the late 60's. It was closed and Kimpton totally redid it and it reopened in Sep 2006 as the Palomar. It reminds me of a -W- type of property.They had a nice 1 hour free wine/champagne happy hour in the lobby, along with free coffee in the morning. Small touches,, but those build a repeat visit.Small things but... in room desk area had a --4-- port electrical plug in for computers/phones. etc. Free internet, bioth wired and wirelss. 2 phones (1 handsfree), 2 line telephones. Great LG HDTV/flat panel LCD TV's... Nice radio, and cool reading lamps on bed so wife could sleep while I worked (sorry, we are married)... Another thing.... so many hotels now use compact flour. light bulbs. They put off a stange color, but at the Palomar, true incadesent bulbs, bright enough for reading/working. Lots of dimmers for lighting. Also, nice bathroom shampoo/soaps. Wife did yoga at the Exhale spa.. Free workout equipment access. Overall a great experience and highly recommended. PS The new Trader Vic's restaurant just steps around the corner from the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>