<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="d94fc3df15f4015d784cd3490d362420" url=""><![CDATA[Not Good This was our fourth trip to the Dom Rep, having previously stayed in Riu and Iberostar hotels which we consider to be much better. This hotel is vast, some might say too big and is still expanding. The apartments are set out in attractive gardens giving the impression of a town rather then a hotel. Our apartment was about a 10 to 15 minute walk to the reception/bar areas. Cars pulling tailers ferry people to and from the reception area from other parts of the complex. Beware, if it rains during the evening you will get very wet when going to eat or drink. We found the food to be below the standard you would expect and the choice very limited. It was often served up cold. The snack bars around the beach area had a very limited menu and did not change thoughout our two week stay. The main buffets were situated on the other side of the complex in the reception, if you were on the beach this involved a lot of hassle so people mainly eat in the snack bars during the day. The room was ok but not as clean as we would expect, often when we returned in the late afternoon we found the towels had not been replaced we would then phone and wait anything up to an hour for clean ones. During the evenings entertainment consided of a singer/pianist in the lobby bars, again the same music every night. Each night they had a show in the theatre which ran for an hour. These were put on by the entertaiment team and consisted mainly of dance routines. The big downside for us was the seating. Most of the chairs were set out like a cinema, very few tables, the drinks were served in small plastic throw away cups. Not conducive to a social evening out. The beach is great,, flat white sand and very long. The European habit of saving sun beds with towels has caught on and if you arrive on the beach later then 8am you may have problems finding one. Compared to other hotels we have been to in the Dominican Republic the overall consensus of our party of four was one of disapointment..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e5a3acc5c4d3f2104155c3e919da5ea9" url=""><![CDATA[Good Value We stayed here for four nights and found the hotel to be clean, modern and comfortable. As previously mentioned it is situated away from the centre of town and necessitated a 15 minute trip on the Metro to the Ramblas and port areas. We found the Breakfast to be fine and the room plenty big enough. The hotel is a five minute walk from Sants station which made it easy for connections to the airport and places further away such as Montserrat and Sitges. The staff were friendly and efficient which made a pleasent stay.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>