<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="124430af4db03cb3064cdf863ce91992" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location Stayed at The Radisson for 6 nights. Hotel is in great location close to Darling Harbour. We booked a 1 Bedroomed Suite which was spacious,clean and comfortable. Yes mono rail was a little noisy but we got use to it. Nice balcony facing towards Darling Harbour. We ate most evenings at Darling Harbour and I found prices reasonable.Didn't use leisure facilities in Hotel but pool was obviously back in use. My only complaint was the quality of the breakfast. The hot buffet didn't look appetizing and was always over cooked no matter what time we ate breakfast. Also I had advised Hotel that my wife has a Gluten free diet and they promised to get in some products for her. However when we arrived for breakfast on the first morning there was a blank look on everyones face. Eventually I went to see the duty Manager and in fairness they did get some products the next day for her.We loved Sydney, the ferry services were superb, the Bridge climb was stunning and The Opera House magnificent.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8dda8ebeb0de8b31d3fcaf074b948d9d" url=""><![CDATA[Great location... Stayed at the Hotel Laurus for 4 nights. The Hotel is well situated close to the Rail Termini and only a few minutes walk to the Hotel. As prevously mentioned the Hotel has recently been refurbished with nice bright decor. Rooms are quite spacious with a nice bathroom.The 6th floor Breakfast Room with it's balcony terrace was lovely. This room was also the bar for drinks during the day and evening. The Hotel is within walking distance off all the major attractions in Florence with the Dumo less than 5 mins walk and visible from the terrace. Streets are quite noisy outside Hotel but double glazed windows shut out the noise. Rooms are air conditioned.As expected Florence was very busy and hot but plenty of places to grab a cool beer. The Restaurants we dined at were superb, we particulalry liked the Trattoria Il Caminetto in via Dello Studio a little road just off the Dumo Square. Not cheap for sure but the food and service well worth the money.Prior to this stay we had just spent 4 nights in Rome and travelled to Florence by rail. We enjoyed Rome which of course is renowned for it's Historical interest whereas Florence was very much about it's culture but both very interesting places to visit.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>