<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="ed0fef046e6e384f0fc92189b5652ee2" url=""><![CDATA[Is this a boutique hotel or Hampton Inn wannabe? I have some mixed feelings about this place, though in the final balance of things I would recommend it. Here are my compliments and (not huge) gripes:on the plus side:--very comfortable bed, nice selection of high quality pillows, excellent small lights/sconces for restful evenings, handy fridge/microwave/coffemaker--WINDOWS THAT OPEN -- and large ones at that, with wonderful views. Nothing like sleeping with fresh instead of bottled air.--great that they filter the tap water--if your room is near the ice and soda machines, don't worry -- they automatically turn off at 7 p.m. so no white noise! (products still available thru the night)--very friendly staff, who try to help--TWO bathrobes in the room! (I always wonder about those many places that only have one in the room -- when so many people travel in pairs).on the minus:--online reservation system/auto. confirmation letter does not include promised room rate! you just have to trust them that the price will remain the same...--They are VERY kind in offering that you can come behind the front desk and use their computer/printer to print something out without charge. I realize this is very unusual. However, their software is VERY old so don't count on it being able to recognize your file!--The coffee in the room is a Starbucks pack and of wretched quality, and no cartons of 1/2 n 1/2 or milk offered -- only yucky unhealthy powdered creamer.--One of the outside key-entry doors along a side of the building doesn't work well, maybe not at all, and the staff seemed aware of the problem but it wasn't being addressed.--USA Today delivered to the door instead of the Seattle Times? It's a Seattle-themed place -- how about offering a local paper instead of the most low-brow of national rags?--Cramped looking workout room means you're working out virtually on top of others -- just a bunch of equipment piled in there -- my workout room at home is more spacious!--The breakfast buffet, while ample, is not worth the time and effectively wastes an opportunity to have a great meal in a great foodie-lover's town (HORRIBLE coffee, juice not fresh and some more like Sunny Delight, scary looking pastries definitely not freshly baked or high quality, scrambled eggs looked like they were reconstituted powdered variety). This is the thing that makes me think that it's more like a Hampton Inn or H-I Express. And then, once you start to see the affinity with a motel chain, other details emerge in the same vein -- the ice machine plop in the hallway, the low quality TV, the absence of staff/services that would normally be present in a boutique hotel.All that said, the price was great (we paid $159 for a standard room), the location is perfect if you know what you are doing (people who complain about this didn't do their research!), it has a positive and personal feel altogether. We would certainly be willing to stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d468578cde1faef11b632a6413da527c" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent all around I expected to get a leftover room since I booked through Priceline, yet not only did I receive the type of room I requested (with two beds), but I was given one on a high (11th) floor with a view of Puget Sound and the Pike Place Market without even requesting!The room was very spacious and had nice touches to make one feel comfortable: pillow top mattresses, four down pillows per bed (!), a pair of bathrobes in the closet, nice toiletries (basil/lemon scented), granite sink, additional sink outside the bathroom, TV discretely placed inside an armoire, and one wall a floor-to-ceiling window with several attractive layers of drapes. The climate control worked beautifully regulating the temperature in the room. Everything was perfectly clean. The beds were very comfortable. Newspapers delivered in the morning included two on Saturday morning (the Saturday Seattle Times and the Sunday edition).Attendants were polite in every encounter we had -- at the front desk and with housekeeping.The only flaw in the room that I noticed was that when people showered in adjacent rooms there was a sort of rumbling sound that came through the walls. Another negative: The Elephant Castle Pub downstairs may fancy itself to be an English pub, but it does not at all have the atmosphere of one -- way too sports bar-ish and dull.All together, an excellent hotel that can be booked at an extremely reasonable price.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fbaf2c995e9d9a2ca8b778677950b1c0" url=""><![CDATA[I really wanted to like it I love to stay in small-scale, modest inns and consider myself to be tolerant of a bit of grottiness, minimal service, noise, etc.... Being a Seattle native and UW alum, I've wanted to try the College Inn for years. I was thus so very inclined to like this place -- but came away with a combination of anger, disappointment, and the decision not to return. Here's why:--This place is not clean where it matters. The blanket on my bed STANK of some other person's perfume or deoderant -- very distinctive, not an aftersmell of detergent. If they wash the blankets at all, they don't do a very good job. --The shower drain was badly plugged up, so that within a few seconds I was standing in my own wastewater, which, of course, then sloshes together with the remains of other people's showers -- ugh, I don't want to go on thinking about that....--I was promised a double room and received a twin room (two twin beds). This was after having booked well ahead of time and getting both a phone and email confirmation of this. They were completely full and since we were staying for only one night, I have a strong suspicion that we were given whatever was left over. I also know that they had switched rooms on us at some late point b/c I had received a call from Chris, the manager, giving me the room number and telling me that since we were arriving late in the p.m. to get buzzed up and just go straight to that room which would be unlocked. On arrival I found that the door was locked (I probably disturbed whoever was there by trying the knob), and I had to buzz the staff who live upstairs to let me into the room that they had set aside for me -- a different one from what I was originally promised.--The next morning, when I mentioned the room switch, the manager did not at all appear surprised or concerned. He said that it should not have happened but his statement that it shouldn't happen again was not at all convincing.--Website is dishonest: under Parking it says, Saturday and Sunday free parking one-half block away on a space-available basis. When I called to get directions to this free parking area I was told that it is between 42nd and 43rd on Brooklyn -- which is more like 5 blocks away from the inn. We're walkers, so NBD, but this seems to me to be indicative of a tendency to paint a rosier picture than what actually exists.--Having had a difficult day of travel and getting only 5 hours of sleep, the next morning I made the error of leaving a clothing item in the room. Two days later, I realize that it is missing and I work hard to follow up with the staff there to locate it. I leave a message, call back when I don't get the courtesy of a return call, stop by in person to inquire, speak with Joe (I think that was his name) as well as Dean. I get a couple of assurances that I will receive a call back -- they say they have to check with housekeeping. Even with my repeated calls, including an angry final call that got me the assurance that Chris would call me back the next day, nobody ever bothered to phone me, even to tell me that the item went missing. My guess is that this has happened before, so no big deal from their perspective, and that in my case the housekeeping staff knew someone who could use my clothing item.The only positive comment I will make is a heartfelt one -- but it isn't about the Inn, it's about the College Inn Pub downstairs. The place is friendly and has an excellent choice of ales. Scruffy and real, if you are a beer enthusiast and are after authenticity instead of hype and polish, I would really recommend the Pub.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>