<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="8b9af51b3cac9e28efcfab302eafd80c" url=""><![CDATA[Great Resort! The Perfect Vacation! As a family of 5, after our stay at Caribe Club Princess from Dec 22-29, we have only good things to say about the place.First of all, don't let any of the bad reviews discourage you!A run down of everything... Check in: Smooth. The shuttle bus from our travel agent with TMR was ready when we were. In the airport, there's a little booth where they direct you to your bus. As well, porters offer to bring your luggage. You also have a rep from your travel agent whose available an hour a day at your resort to answer your questions, and who gives a welcome meeting to go over everything to new guests. Our room was ready when we arrived. We took the VIP package, so we got the coupons we needed right away (massage, motorized water sports, and Internet.)Food: Excellent. The food is prepared differently than in mainstream North America, but it definitely is good. Breakfast is, as other reviews say, pretty much the same thing daily. However, there is so much available, that you don't get bored of it. The fresh omelettes are delicious! You choose what you want inside (tomatoes, red/green peppers, ham, cheese) and the guy makes it for you on the spot. As well, you can have eggs easy over... There's also muffihs, bacon, potatoes, scrambled eggs, waffles, pancakes, rolls, and so much more. The fresh juices are also really good.Lunch is also really good. There's 2 snack bars at either ends of the Tropical/Caribe Club beach section, which are only about 3 minutes walking distance from each other. The food there is delicious, there's always pasta, hamburgers, hot dogs, nachos (with cheese or salsa), and more. As well, there's a bar at each lunch buffet spot. (The buffets are at the seafood restaurant, and the dominican food restaurant.) As well, there's always the lunch buffet at the place where the breakfast buffet is, which is just a wider selection. However, you need to have shoes and a shirt to go in there...You will not go hungry at Supper either. There's the buffet at El Higuera (the place where the breakfast is), and a choice of 5 restaurants that anybody can use, and 2 that cost $25/person. (Or if you have the VIP package, you can choose 1 of them once per week at no extra cost.)The supper buffet is always great. They have a different theme each night (like Italian, Brazillian, Dominican, etc), and the food there is always good. There's easily 100 things to choose from there. They seem to always have some things made on the spot too, like fried vegetables, or fresh pasta with the sauce of your choice. If you see something made on the spot, get it. It's usually a hint the food is good. There's also icecream at the supper buffet.... Once you bring your food to the table, a waiter will get you your drink.As well, the restaurants are also good. In some regard, some of the food you see at certain buffet themes you get at the restaurant. We ate at the mexican, italian, chinese, and steakhouse (VIP extra).Mexican (Sombrera)- Food was great. They come and sing you a song while you are eating. Nice variety.Italian (Mamma Mia)- Really good. Pasta with seafood sauce was great.Chinese (Shanghai)- Alright. Certain parts were great, certain parts were alright. They serve you sushi and beef on a stick when you sit down, which is really really good. However, the main meals are only alright. Nothing amazing. The fried icecream (vanilla icecream, with fried dough around it, with chocolate sauce on the side) is amazing!Steakhouse (La Cava)- This was included with our VIP package, and definitely was amazing! The food was delicious! The steak was cooked perfectly! The apetizers and main courses were humongous and delish! The shrimp surprises (apetizer) and the steak were amazing. Definitely recommend this place.The other VIP restaurant, or $25/person one, is the seafood restaurant which we didn't try. (El Pescador)Now onto other stuff...Staff- The staff were always very helpful, and wanted to help you. The waiters at the buffet were usually on the ball and got you your drink pretty quickly. As well, they kept the place clean for you when you arrive. The waiters at the restaurants were always on the ball, having a new drink ready for you basically as soon as you finish yours. The bartenders also were great. There were a few instances where the staff only spoke Spanish, so it was a bit difficult to communicate. But usually they would know some English or French (french was a bit more common).Housekeeping was usually on the ball. If you leave them gifts and a tip, they make up your room fast and sometimes leave towel designs (like a heart or a swan..). One day they forgot about our room though, and didn't make it up until we got them in there at 5 PM. Animation staff - Amazing. Always on the ball. Throughout the day, there'd be water aerobics, step up aerobics on land, merengue dance lessons, darts tournaments, pentaca tournaments, bowling down pineapples with coconuts tournaments, etc. If you win a tournament, they present you a diploma at their nightly show (more on this soon). They'd always try to get you to participate, and they definitely are fun to be with.Beach - Spotless. Therea are people there picking up garbage all throughout the day. The sand is so soft and clean, and the water is a beautiful blue. The water is always warm too. You can get a boogie board free for 1 hour a day. As well, there are some excursions that you can sign up for at the aquatics hut (at a cost), that we didn't bother with. Some were snorkeling with dolphins or whatever... The beach is also cleaned throughoughly at night. There was never ever an issue trying to find chairs or getting a hut. And this was during their high season...As well, with our VIP coupons for motorized water sports, we tried the banana boat ride. Its basically an inflatible long tube that everybody sits on with a handle per person. And one of the water staff on a motorboat pulls the tube fast throughout the water. Only try this if you like moving FAST, and getting wet. Definitely a lot of fun, and recommended....The pools were also always clean. We only used the main pool (the one with the swim-up pool bar) where all the action is, but there definitely was never any issues here. Only thing is the water is a bit cold because it's not heated. Bars: Tons of fresh drinks, fruit punch, soft drinks, slushy drinks available that don't have alcohol. Also tons of alcoholic drinks available for adults. If your VIP, you get access to all the liquors free of charge, whereas non-vip's only get national alcoholic drinks.Besides the beach, everywhere else is clean. There's a kid's club that we saw doing activities throughout the day, but never really looked into it. There's also teen club with foosball tables and pool tables. There's tennis, and mini golf available at no extra charge for those who are interested.For those who aren't sure, the VIP package is definitely worthwhile. First of all, all the VIP people stay in one hotel. In this hotel only, every room has a *private* balcony. Elsewhere, balconies are not completely private or sometimes even shared. There's a concierge in your hotel from 9-4 PM daily to answer questions or for you to reserve your restaurant. Much easier than having to wait in line with everyone else to reserve. And overall, you don't want to have to pay more for anything during your stay. The massages are so worthwhile, as well as the motorized watersports if you like that. Also, at the bars, you don't want to have to be charged for a drink if it costs extra. As well, your hotel is perfectly located. You're right at the beach and the main pool with all the action. There's no real walking distance.Nightly shows: Most of them are good. We were fortunate to be able to see the Lion King, and that was fantastic! They always have nice sets, lighting, costumes, etc. However, they mouth the words to any songs or dialogue in the show. Luckily for us, the Lion King was all in English! They also have many dance shows with different themes (Carnaval, Christmas, etc..). Their comedy show skits were cute, at most. They also give the tournament winners their diploma before the show. After the show, the animation staff (who perform in the show) invite the audience to come and dance with them for a bit before they send you off to Areito Disco which we never went to. Don't make our mistake. The theatre near El Higuera (the buffet place) is NOT the main theatre. That's for a little show guests put on that we never really figured out how it works...Everything is really close to each other. The only real distance is about 5 minutes to the lobby and the theatre with the nightly shows. And there's a shuttle that comes often anyways...The lobby is beautiful too. They clean it so often.Something else they have is a photographer who goes around during the day with a different animal or model to take your picture. There's a little monkey, iguana, parrots, beautiful white birds, or sometimes a male or female model. He takes your picture with whatever he has, and then the print is available in the lobby at night or the following day. The pictures always come out great because they use a great camera, and they add to it a nice border with Caribe club... dec07 or whatever)... but pictures are $15/each. If you buy more than 10, its something like $12/each. Although there's no committment to buy it...Also, after 4 days they throw out any pictures unpurchased.Tipping- No obligation, but if you do, people definitely make an effort to offer you better service. $1 goes a long way here. No need to tip more than $2-3 at at a time. These people work hard and don't get paid much as it is.Checkout- Also went smoothly. We purchased a late checkout (at 6 PM) because our bus left only at midnight. You can only get this though the day before or day of checkout. Otherwise checkout is at 12 PM. You' re still able to get access to all the resorts features until you leave. They can also lock your luggage in a safe room so you don't have to worry. With TMR, our shuttle bus was on time. After a few stops at other resorts, we reached the airport. 30 minutes to go through check-in and security. It's a bit different than other airports, as in, you get to see planes taking off because the airport is just one giant hut of sorts. Anyway, I think that's it! If you have any questions, feel free to contact me. Don't worry, relax, and have a great trip!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f87d799bb2e3895a00d8ccc9fe70f6a3" url=""><![CDATA[Amazing Resort! We just got back from Gran Bahia Principe Punta Cana a few days ago, and as a family of 5, everyone had an amazing time! Here's our run-down. If you have any questions, feel free to send me a message! You can't go wrong here!Went for a week (Dec 20-27) from Montreal, with Air Transat. Not great flight times, but everything was on time, bus left prompty, and we were the first stop. Only 25 minute busride. Chose the Royal Golden package.Check-in: Arrived at 3 AM, so the resort was pretty quiet then. Only one person at the front desk. Check-in was fairly quick, followed by a short wait since only 1 bellboy was working at this time. Had to get our safe activated the next day in the Royal Golden area. We were told to stop by the Royal Golden area the following day. When we got to our room, we found a letter from them. They made our restaurant reservations for us, but we were more than welcome to change them. (You get 4 dinners with the Royal Golden, 3 without).Royal Golden Reception:We went the following morning to the Royal Golden area by the lobby, made the dinner reservations that we wanted very quickly and easily. Got our safe activated here too. They have a safe door there to demonstrate exactly what you need to do. They have a very very small bar here, and 3 computers for your 15 minutes of internet. Officially it's 15 minutes of internet per day per room, but during slow periods you could get away with 15 minutes per person too.Rooms:We had 2 adjoining rooms, on the second floor in villa 2. Very spacious, clean, only saw 1 bug all week. The maid did a good job of keeping everything in order, at a decent time, with a gift and a dollar or two left daily. Although the rooms were always tidy, didn't see any decorations in the first half of the week. As teh week progressed, we saw a heart with flower pedals and some balloons. The a/c worked perfectly fine in both rooms. Just be aware it only works if your balcony door is firmly shut. As well, bathrooms were interesting... No fan or shower curtain. It gets very steamy in there after showering, but not a problem. Beautiful bathrooms none the less. Remember, the tap water is not drinkable. Shower towels were never a problem.As well, at night, we often found beach towels for us for the next day from the maid, along with candies, or chocolates. As well, any dirty towels from that afternoon were already gone.Grounds:Stunning grounds. All throughout the day, there is always someone picking up garbage, painting, cleaning, spraying insecticides, and more. The resort is big, and it is true, it takes a day or 2 to figure out your way around. However, it is manageable. We were in Villa 2, which is 5 seconds from the beach, and we barely used the trolley. It's about a 10 minute walk to the lobby only.Beach:Just like the grounds, it is constantly being cleaned. There are people picking up plastic cups on the ground throughout the day constantly. The beach is beautiful! Bavaro beach (the beach where the resort is next to), has such smooth and soft sand with crystal clear water. We did actually have some problems with beach chairs when we tried to do it the polite way, and not reserve chairs. We like having our chairs near the beach, to the extent that we had to sometimes go into the pool area and take chairs from there. Later on in the week, we reserved chairs around 9 AM and never had a problem. But by 11:30 AM, it's much harder. A towel or a sandle does the trick.There are vendors about 20 minutes along the shore to the right on the beach. Good stuff, just be prepared to haggle as always. Pools:We spotted 3 pools during our stay, but only used 1. There is a pool right near the beach which has the bulk of the animation and action, and halfway to the lobby there are 2 more pools. One of these pools is for everyone, the other is reserved for Diamond/Hacienda club members only. Every pool had a swim-up bar. Pools were kept clean, and we never had a problem swimming in any of them. As well, short wait at the swim-up bars (and this was during the high season!).If we were to be critical, we found the animation to be lacking a bit. It did exist, but there wasn't as much as another resort we were at. However, some may prefer this as they aren't in your face all day.Bars:To add a bit more about bars, there are many throughout the resort. One on the beach, one at every pool (both inside and outside the pool), at every location where food is served, and more. The drinks were good and served quickly. The beach;/pool bars had all the typical frozen drinks like Coco Locos, Banana Mamas, Pina Coladas, lemondade and so on. The bartenders were always willing to add alcohol as you may desire. Every bar also had water, which is 100% bottled water. At the pool and lobby, there are people who also bring drinks to you. No drinks inside coconuts. Punta Cana LOBBY and Lobby bar: Beautiful open-air area. Lots of areas to sit and relax. In my opinion, the lobby bar served the best drinks. They had the largest variety, and were always served the nicest. They just were classy. Had little pineapple and cherry's sticking out, sugar candy rim, and so on. In the evening, there would be usually someone playing piano and singing or just music playing which was nice. As well, there are staff who come around and offer to get you your drink. They also have the drinks here that cost money (international drinks). Very enjoyable area throughout the day. In the morning, they also have good muffins and croissants here.FOOD:Main buffet - Orquieda:Air-conditioned buffet.Huge variety of food, throughout the day. Be careful of the hours when meals are served. At any buffet, when they say it ends, it ends. They won't ask you to leave if your eating, but the food will be gone then. At breakfast, they have 2 omelette stations, which were really good. As well, the usual nice variety. Fresh juices, scrambled eggs, toast, waffles, pancakes, bagels, yogurts, cereals, bread (which was quite good!) and more. Nobody goes hungry.Lunch was good here as well, typical variety. Only ate here once, so don't really remember what it had.Dinner: Every night is a different theme. We ate there on international night, and I think spanish night. In any event, the food was great. It was served hot, fresh, and a nice variety. Every dinner has a pasta station that's served and made fresh with food for kids as well. Often had stuff like lambchops, and what not being served for u at different stations. For all meals at the buffet, never had to wait long for coffee/juice/soft drink/wine. The waiters come around often. Second Breakfast Buffet:Air-conditioned.There is also a breakfast buffet near the beach, at El Pescador restaurant. They have a much smaller amount of food, but it's fine none the less. Still have eggs (just not cooked in front of you), along with fresh juices.Beach lunch buffet:Open-air Great food served throughout the day. Had salads, sandwhiches, hamburgers, hot dogs, fries, pastas, and so on daily. They don't let you take food out of the buffet area officially, but if it's in a napkin or something, nobody will stop you. A la carte dinners:We ate at El Charro (Mexican), La Trattoria (Italian), Garden Grill (Steakhosue), Mikado (Japanese). All air-conditioned.All the restaurants we ate at, besides Mikado, have buffets for apetizers and dessert. We didn't mind this, since it allowed us to try all the food we want. Some restaurants served you a little appetizer none the less.El Charro: Good food. Everything was served hot, with a nice variety. No complaints. La Trattoria: Lambchops (meal) were cold, sent back, and weren't much better. Not a big deal, still edible. That aside, great variety of food.Garden Grill: No problems. Steak was cooked perfectly and was quite good.Mikado: Hit or miss with the chefs. Our chef wasn't all that entertaining, he just cooked the meal in front of us, and left. Other chefs (as we heard) really got the crowd applauding. Yummy food. The dessert is served just outside the showroom, and the fried icecream was delicious.Christmas Dinner:Ate at the buffet. Very nice variety of food. Had a cold seafood buffet, steaks, fillet mignons, salmon and more. Huge variety of very delicious food. Also, a few interesting carvings by the staff. Nice amount of christmas decorations, and music.NIGHTLIFE:Shows at Tropicana Theatre:We were there for Mr. Bahia Principe, ideal couple, Michael Jackson, Circus, Musical Legends, Lion King, and one other pop music show. The first 2 listed were cute, with the usual audience participation.The other shows were well done. Of course they lip synch the words to the songs, but it was well rehearsed none the less. Very enjoyable.As well, the circus show was quite impressive with quite a few interesting acrobatic stunts. There is a bar by the theatre as well.Shops and post-show entertainment:The Pueblo Principe area, where all the shops and vendors are, becomes the hub of the nightlife after the shows. During the day, this is where the vendors are. They can be quite pushy, but be prepared to bargain for at least 1/4 of their price. They all have the same stuff, and it isn't unique to them. Either way, got some nice souvenirs here from them and the stores. As well, at night, this is where the after-hours eating takes place (hamburger restaurant from 11 PM - 7 AM), the casino, nightly house band from 11 Pm - 12 AM (with chairs and servers offering you drinks), and the casino and bar. Didn't use the casino or bar really. We found the nightlife to be lacking somewhat, especially since the lobby bar closes at 11:30 PM. Would have liked for some more entertainment maybe, like dancing after the show. (Besides the disco.)ROYAL GOLDEN thoughts:We found this to be a very useful upgrade. The 15 minutes of internet was nice to have, along with a 4th a la carte restaurant. The location of the villas close to the beach is also very convenient. And finally, with towels, we usually got away without needing towel cards because of our bracelets at the towel shack.Check-out: We needed to leave our room by 12 PM, even though the bus only came for our flight at 11:20 PM since they were overbooked. (Otherwise, $12/hour extra for the room. You need to ask the day of if it's free.) Since it was daytime, and the Royal Golden area was open, that is where we had to checkout (unlike where we checked in). Took a while, because there's only 3 people there, and a lot of people had just arrived. (Like over an hour).We had to shower in the hospitality showers near the main-lobby. Make sure you bring beach towels, because there are none there. Somewhat inconvenient, but not a huge problem. Your luggage is stored in a locked room, just make sure you have your valuables.Our bus came on-time, and our flight left the airport on time too. Very easy.Note about Punta Cana/Bavaro/Ambar:Punta Cana and Bavaro are the same thing, just with different identical lobbies. Ambar is the same as well, just adult only. Royal Golden is in Punta Cana side, Diamond/Hacienda club is Bavaro. (Diamond/Hacienda perks are their own pool, and private breakfast/lunch lobby.)Trolley:Came very often in both directions. Very easy, and quick.Staff:The staff was always very friendly, and always greeted you with a friendly Hola. Most new some english as well, and we never found it a problem. FINAL THOUGHTS:Gran Bahia Principe is an amazing resort. It definitely merits its 5 stars, and it's very easy to be happy here. We all had an amazing time, got lots of sun, and nobody got sick. We would definitely recommend it. We thought the animation team was lacking a bit during the day, but the place is still very relaxing! That's all I can think of. Feel free to message me with any questions, and have an amazing vacation! You'll love it here!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>