<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="6dff97dfdb6c8fab78a9f110e6aaa3d2" url=""><![CDATA[Just OK We just got back from sunny Punta Cana, where we stayed at the Sirenis Tropical/Cocotal Resort Spa and Casino. TIP: DO NOT pay a cent extra to stay at the Tropical as the only difference is a slightly larger room.First of all -- we are truly pretty easy to please. We are on holidays - so we are relaxed and really are not complainers. Overall, we had a great time, great weather and such, but the Sirenis resort was OK at best.Basically, we have decided that if we return to Punta Cana, we will spend the extra $200-400 or so to stay in a quality resort. Small details are the things that make the difference. The grounds are nice, the food OK (you can usually find something) and the beach is pretty. Both pools are shallow in most areas, therefore there are children everywhere with no real designated child area. Most kids are great and well behaved-- but this can still take away from your element of relaxation. Ironically, the swim up bars are located right next to the kiddie shallow areas. My husband and I always laugh at people who write about language barriers BUT this time it WAS really obvious. It was nearly impossible to communicate, staff was honestly often unfriendly (not all ----but definitely front desk area) and they really just liked to pass the buck so to speak. Not even for anything major --- just simple things like trying to get a bottle of water. Often, you'd just accept that you wouldn't get anywhere and forget about what you were looking for and deal with it. The door to our room was ridiculously tight and hard to open. I actually got stuck IN the room one day -- and due the the language barrier we not only couldn't seem to get the door fixed, but I was stuck in the room for nearly an hour waiting for someone to come. I had to phone 4 times.Plan to wait in fairly long line ups if you want dinner reservations.New Years we had to book to eat at the buffet and waited in line for over an hour. It was the only place you could eat and you had to have a ressie. Goofy.Anyway ---- not to go on and on, but here is my BIGGEST complaint.CLEANLINESS!!! I like clean and tidy. This resort often has glasses, plates, garbage floating around everywhere - especially in the morning when you'd expect it to be clean and fresh. When they come around periodically to collect glasses, they dump them (right in front of you) into the plants STRAWS, LIMES and all. This is just left in the plants. There are hardly any garbage cans around, so lots of garbage just gets left all over. The garbage cans they do have do not have bags in them, and they don't get rinsed often. Therefore - there is often a rotten smell coming from them --- WHILE you're laying at the pool!! It's really yucky! Further more -- pool cleaning and such is done during the day while people are using the pool. Most resorts that I have been to do this at night while people aren't around to see. It is really kind of gross. It's just those small details that to my husband and I, make a difference in how you relax and enjoy your holiday. To us, it is definitely worth a bit of extra money to not see dirt falling from the hallway above you as the maid sweeps onto the roof outside your room. Just yucky. Also the resort is really starting to show signs of agin...exposed wiring, (we had live wires from our patio door air conditioner thingy), peeling paint, broken railings and such.If you like clean --- I'd skip this resort. Surface tidy it is --- but clean it isn't.Oh - and we saw cockroaches --- on the grounds, in our wing of building. There was also a dead tarantula lying on the sidewalk at the shops. Not a large deal --- but GOOD GOD!! Just sweep it away. TIPS: Everyone (including your tour guide) will tell you NOT to drink anything but bottled water. They put 4 in your room each day and that's all. You cannot get it anywhere else, no matter how much you ask. I was 6 months pregnant on this trip and they still wouldn't give us water. We tipped the maid lots extra though and she made sure we had plenty of water.There are no alarm clocks in your room. Bring one if that is a concern -- because wake up calls only came on some days, not on others. Almost missed an excursion.Towels - there are only two towels, one bathmat and two small handtowels in your room. No faceclothes. If you don't put your towels on the floor -- you aren't going to get a new one no matter how dirty they are. Again, not a large deal --- but took a couple of days to figure out.Restaruants -- if you're going soon, there are two new restaraunts that they don't tell you about. There is an Italian and a Japenese. Try both!! The Italian is listed on the map ---- but not where it is on the resort. They moved it.Saona Island Excursion ---- worth seeing as it is gorgeous!!!! Expensive though --- and a long drive through poor, poor country. The drive is not for the faint of heart, as you will honestly be terrified that your driver will kill someone. NOT KIDDING!!All in all, we had fun, we relaxed and that is exactly why we went. BUT, that being said -- we won't return to the Sirenis -- it's just not worth the money. I hear the Bahia Principe, the Majestic and the Iberostar are the way to go!!! Spend a little bit extra and I gaurantee you won't be as disappointed as we were.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>