<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="46a663ffbb9b8a94e8e84dc267833e79" url=""><![CDATA[The finest hotel in LA for it's price, just add self parking option We stayed three nights in the Palomar hotel in Westwood, mostly based on location, an attractive 50% off offer on Expedia and its #1 ranking on Tripadvisor. And this is sure the ranking this former Doubletree hotel, now stylish renovated by Kimpton, deserves. Not just for the big spotless rooms with countless amenities like a huge LCD TV and the best king I've slept on during my whole 4 week stay in the USA or the excellent location (just minutes away from Beverly Hills, Santa Monica and UCLA) in a safe neighboorhood. Most of all this hotel is my new LA favorite spot because of the most attentive and truly friendly staff. From front office, to bell and valet everybody gives you that warm welcome feeling like you are at home and will do almost everything to make your stay as pleasant as possible. I cannot remember any other hotel on the many trips I've made to the USA where I found a similar experience. They even offer a complimentary wine hour, but we were to busy exploring LA to join !Only thing missing was a balcony to enjoy the streetlife or hotel view and the WiFi reception was unfortunality rather bad. But nevertheless this hotel would be my choice again next time (hopefully again with a good Expedia offer 'cause their rack rates are kinda pricy for me, though worth the money). Final remark is that the hotel parking is also pricy (USD 30 overnight) and they only offer valet service. As an European I'd prefer to do the parking myself (although the valets are most attentive) but I simply find self parking more comfortable. So it would be perfect if the hotel would offer self parking too, their indoor parking lot is huge and the infrastructure surely allows possibility of self parking.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dc3193bdb8a4e97d5c5507985f90fd10" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent hotel near the beach ! We stayed at the Resort Quest Waikiki Beach Hotel for four nights on our first trip to Hawaii. This hotel is great value for money, most friendly staff and we had an excellent king size bed on which we slept really well. Our room had a nice partial ocean view, on which we were complimentary upgraded (we booked a saver room). Balcony was little small though (on the other side of the hotel you have bigger ones on which you can sit). Nice big screen LCD TV, free wireless internet in the pool area and this included lovely breakfast on the beach concept. You get a breakfast bag (which you may keep as a souvenir) and you can choose to have your bite either in the pool area or on the beach. Nice selection of breakfast items, fresh fruit, yoghurt, cereals, different juices and much more and constantly being replenished so if you arrive at the end of the breakfast hours still much to choose from, we just missed some simple bread or toast (for the healthy minded). They also have a very nice fitness room. If RQ Waikiki Beach keeps up its current price/quality ratio this will definitely be our choice again on our next trip to Hawaii ! Tip: if you arrive from airport the Airport shuttle takes you fast to the hotel for just USD 9 per person !
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>