<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="38c3a46fb28635376407b01c41ee0c7b" url=""><![CDATA[Good location, pretty hotel - rooms on the smaller side I recently returned from an enjoyable stay at the Harbor Court hotel in San Francisco. The hotel is about 3 blocks from the Embarcadero BART stop and very convienant to all of the activity along the piers and ferry terminal. Highlights:-free access to the YMCA next door. An amazing facility with lap pool, bball court, full sauna, etc. I never thought I would be on a treadmill with a view of the bay bridge!-free cocktail reception every night with quality wine and beer-free fresh cookies and milk every night-good coffee and tea available at all times-great customer service-flat screen TVs, ergonomic desk chairs, iPod docking stations-across the street from the ferry terminal farmer's market (thursday/saturday - probably the coolest farmer's market I have ever seen. I highly encourage a visit)Lowlights:-a very, very small room (maybe 12' x 12') that takes a little getting used to. And a $50 flat surcharge for a room with a view of the Bay Bridge.The room we stayed in was well appointed, and we got used to the size, but I would caution any families from staying at the Harbor Court. Even finding space for a crib would be a challenge.San Fran is an amazing city. Go visit!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d13c16e900e9fab5b1f9325e58f6bfdf" url=""><![CDATA[A nice stay at the Holiday Inn! I stayed at the Holiday Inn Amsterdam for 5 days in late December with my girlfriend. We had stayed in the Amsterdam city center on the first leg or our trip and I booked the Holiday Inn through P*riceline ($95 US) as a less expensive alternative on our last leg.The hotel is located on the outer ring of the city, but it is less than a 3 mile walk to the heart of Amsterdam and about 1.5 miles to the Van Gogh museum. It is located right next to the RAI station and the beginning of tram line directly into the city. The proximity to the RAI station proved to be a great benefit as it was only 1 stop from the airport and allowed us to avoid the obscenely expensive Dutch taxis. It also made a day trip to Haarlem very accessible.We stayed in a large room with a comfortable king bed and good bathroom. It was larger than most European rooms and much better than the Holiday Inns where I have stayed in the United States. Ultimately, I found staying at the Holiday Inn to be a great budget alternative to staying in the city center (which I also recommend if the price is right). It is located across the road from a nice city park (with a large hedge maze - recommended for kids and adults) with easy access to the city. My only regret is not being able to visit during the warmer months. Renting a bike (I think you can rent them under the RAI station) and exploring the city would have been awesome. Maybe next time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>