<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="9fa6a3829f1271cbaf7ad6be23743a70" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel in excellent location We, a family of 4 stayed in this hotes for 4 nights in February.I really would not say its in need of total renovation. Our suite was lovely, (Executive suite with sep. living room) and I did not see worn out things.When you travel with kids they only allow you to one small pool and not to the big lap pool near the spa. Location is superb, s short walk to Orchard and you are in the middle of it all!Breakfasts are good, only the room s really dark and with no daylight i did not like it. Maybe this is not important to some.Service was excellent, everyone had a smile and was helpful all the way.Massages in Spa were very good either.Just one really negative thing, if you use their internet its a real scam. About 7 Euros for a 15 minutes use is just a rip off. I did not see why a top hotel can not offer it for free, the prices for a room should justify it!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6caa59936f776497dc783627710714d8" url=""><![CDATA[Really expensive Hip Hotel We had a good 3 nights stay in The Bryant Park Hotel.However i can not understand the raving comments about this hotel.Pros:Good quality room, we had a Junior Suite with two double beds, they were really huge, also room really spacey, bathroom well equipped, nice big tub.Location is very good, one minute away from 5th avenue, but other hotels like Sofitel, Marriott Residence inn have an equal location.Cons:Not a single bottle of water provided in the room as a gratuity. We payed 625 Dollars for our room to find our that a small Evian would cost 12 bucks?! Thats really annoying.If you forget toothpaste: you have to buy it from them for a fortune! No breakfast incl in the priceThe view of Bryant Park is only available from a few rooms, ours was promised to have a view but then you really have to stick your head out to see the Park.Reception and Concierge staff were quite helpful but did not go the extra mile and i think they were acting quite a bit too cool for a hotel of that category.Dont expect a five star service. The hotel is for people that are mostly into fashion and hip and cool stuff.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>