<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="20d9ef318b094e11c956be67afe0389d" url=""><![CDATA[High-class experience at the luxury Langham Over the Easter holiday, my boyfriend and I decided on a weekend jaunt to Boston. We found a deal online, referring to our last minute choice as a Luxury Getaway. Flight and 3 hotel nights for $330pp seemed like a good deal.It turned out to be a GREAT deal. The Langham is a beautiful hotel. The room (I'm sure one of it's smallest) was a queen standard. Impeccably clean and quiet, with lovely furnishings and an extremely comfortable bed, it was a welcome sight after schlepping around as a tourist all day.The staff at the front desk was very pleasant and welcoming. Both members of the concierge staff with whom I spoke were also friendly and helpful, giving us a variety of dining options and succinct directions.Although I did not get to dip into the pool, we could see it from our hotel room (the roof of the pool center is made up of glass panels, visible from the rooms above). The area looked inviting, safe, and spotless (I regretted not having brought my suit).As for location, the Langham is spot-on. 3 to 5 blocks in any direction will bring you to a main attraction. 5 blocks from the Freedom Trail, including Faneuil Hall and Quincy market where there's food and shopping galore. 5 blocks to the Aquarium, where the center ocean tank and the jellyfish exhibit are must-sees. 4 blocks from downtown-crossing, a major shopping area including Macy's and Filene's, as well as a T stop. We were thrilled that so many things were within walking distance: tourist attractions, shopping, restaurants and nightlife.If you're there on a Saturday, try the Chocolate Buffet between 12 and 3PM. 50+ desserts! Also, try to catch Mystery Cafe at Elephant Castle 2 blocks from the hotel--a fun murder mystery dinner theater that had us cracking up.My ONLY complaint about this hotel was the pricing for brekky. $21 for juice and toast...literally! The pricing deterred us from having breakfast in the Cafe Fleuri(?), but the restaurant nonetheless LOOKED beautiful from afar!Overall, I would highly recommend this hotel. We were fortunate to get the best of service for such an affordable price!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>