<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="8">
		<document id="67d92c9eda1efe823ceb38e155549a20" url=""><![CDATA[Very comfortable central hotel Stayed here for 2 nights and really enjoyed it. The hotel was comfortable, central and very good value for money.The staff were very helpful of particular note was Scott the concierge.We were upgraded and the room was pleasantly decorated.Definitely would stay here again if in the area.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2c93053459a9d5154995619a47e927af" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel My husband and I stayed at this very comfortable hotel for 2 nights between christmas and new year and had a very pleasant stay. As Conrad is part of the hIlton group of hotels ( and we are Hilton Honour Diamond members) we were upgraded to a beautiful suite. The accomodation was spacious and of a very high standard - with great views over city. I note from a previous review that the lifts and layout of the hotel caused confusion and inconvenience to other guests. I would endorse this in one respect - there were an inadequate number of lifts serving the bedroom floors, so very often this led to a long wait.All the staff we encountered during our stay were very helpful and there was a great selection at breakfast. The pool was nice and the public area around it very well maintained.Overall, I would recommend this hotel and although it is in the business district the efficient transport network ensures that you are within easy reach of central Miami. We have previously stayed in the Conrad Chicago and would not return to that particular Conrad. The Miami Conrad was a complete contrast and we thoroughly enjoyed our stay which was further enhanced by our upgraded room.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="357612170a63aeaff133d1caa29748bd" url=""><![CDATA[Average Hilton with above average staff We stayed in this hotel for 2 nights (1 before and 1 after our cruise from Barcelona). As Hilton Diamond members we were upgraded to an executive room which was clean and modern.The executive lounge was good and the staff were incredibly helpful - nothing was too much trouble. We were checked in by a girl called Patricia who was exceptional, her English was excellent and she was extremely helpful. All the staff seemed good but she certainly stood out.We had booked 3 rooms as we were travelling with family but used points for one room. As identified by other reviewers this was an expensive hotel and certainly was amongst the most expensive Hilton hotels. Based on location and facilities I would say it was costly. This is probably a good business hotel and is accessible via good transport links to centre of Barcelona. Overall it is an average Hilton in terms of standard and value for money with well above average staff.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="38986aa1f7659a4fcdc7b3491a2e4c4c" url=""><![CDATA[Good, convenient hotel We stayed in this very convenient airport hotel for one night after a week in the Caribbean. We found it very good, friendly staff with extensive facilities for an airport hotel.Airport shuttle very efficient and regular. We were upgraded to a suite as Hilton Diamond members, it was a really lovely room. Curved in shape with living area and quite spacious(although bathroom was small). Yes there was some noise from the planes as pointed out from another review, but you expect this from an airport hotel and it wasn't really too troublesome.The executive floor was well stocked and staff all very helpful.We ate in the restaurant for dinner and thought the buffet was good value and pretty good quality food.Would definitely stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4e4b32cd99700c3ecdd03b556fa759ae" url=""><![CDATA[Fine, a bit dated but very welcoming staff We stayed at this hotel for 1 night and found the staff very friendly and helpful.The room was fine a good size, comfortable bed (though not sweet sleeper) but generally the hotel was maybe a bit tired. The building works next door didn't seem to generate noise during our short stay (as with other review) but then we were there at a weekend.Overall it was an above average hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="627ae3349b199d06c7efe8b47d2e2901" url=""><![CDATA[An excellent executive stay We stayed at this fantastic hotel for the last 3 nights of our stay in Singapore and the hotel was absolutely fantastic.As Hilton Honours Diamonds we were upgraded to the Executive floor and were personally escorted there for check in. The staff at check in were polite, efficient and extremely welcoming. They even provided a cooling welcome drink and moist hand towel whilst they were completing the paper work.The executive room as mentioned by a previous reviewer was large with little extra touches like fruit, chocolates, rubber duck and teddy bear. Fruit was replaced daily and the twice daily housekeeping service was good.The staff were incredible so attentive and nothing was ever too much trouble for them. The executive lounge was lovely with views over the city breakfast, afternoon tea and evening drinks provided - a very relaxing place.Overall we found this hotel excellent. We enjoyed not being in the mayhem and rush of Orchard Road, but still easily accessible to all of Singapores amenities and sights.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="089759b2077b21902ce4ef405c172f37" url=""><![CDATA[Fine but not the best We stayed for one night at this hotel over Easter weekend. It was not really the standard I have experienced in other Sheraton Hotels. The gentleman at check in was very irritated with the computer and as a result was far from pleasant with us - not a great first impression. We were lacated on the club floor and the room was fine - bed very comfortable. Concierge very helpful.Overall the hotel was nothing special and I don't think I would go back there again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="568143c01e9718eb00b8faa99ffccff6" url=""><![CDATA[Average I stayed at this hotel for 2 nights when in San Francisco. As a Hilton Diamond got upgraded to executive floor. Room was spacious and well decorated. Executive lounge was not the usual Hilton Standard and the continental breakfast was sparce compared to many Hilton Executive Lounges in USA. It is very much a business hotel and other hotels eg Westin are much more central and better value for money.Average nothing special.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>