<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="483a2363e32f4775891a32bbe7e7177e" url=""><![CDATA[Ok for short stay on budget My family of two adults and two children stayed in a one bedroom apartment at this property in March. I can see why reviews have been so positive - I don't think you can find any apartment type accommodation in the CBD for the prices they charge. We paid an average of AUD $184 per night for 4 nights, and this was for essentially 4 people.However, having said this, you do get what you pay for. While the apartment was very spacious, the standard of the room was about 3 star at best - furnishing was very basic and showing wear. Kitchenette was missing some items so that we ended up with only 3 sets of certain pieces of crockery instead of the usual 4 (eg. cups). While the apartment was cleaned well when we arrived, the carpet was actually quite dirty. Sure the carpets were vaccumed, but what it really needed was a good heavy duty steam or chemical clean - or even replacement. The balcony was also quite dirty and too small to be relaxing in. Having said this, the air-conditioning/ventilation was good though. The iron, ironing board and drying rack were all in good condition and proved very handy. Water pressure in the shower was good, as was the hot water system - always hot water when you needed it, and quickly too. Bathroom was great if you are not too fussed about a bit of staining in the grouting. Water pipes made noises after use of toilet and shower, but noise stopped after a minute or so. Note that this is NOT a serviced apartment. The apartment is serviced only with stays of 7 days or longer. OK for short stay, but maybe not so good for longer stays. On day 3 we were getting tired of having to organise for clean towels and having to walk over our own crumbs on the carpet. No restaurant or cafe on site or within short walking distance, but there a small Coles grocery is just round the corner next to Wynyard train station. Service was very always very smart, professional and efficient. Nothing to fault here at all.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a2e55cfc3247f4e7f14825984ab61f8a" url=""><![CDATA[Reasonably pleasant stay Stayed one night in July on business. The Good : As per previous post, good location - very close to Rocks area and leisurely stroll away from Darling Harbour/CBD. Cafes/restaurants and seven elevens all within short walking distance. Free on site car parking from check in till 12 pm on day of check out. After 12 pm on day of check out, you pay $15.50. Very reasonable when compared with other hotel parking options. Apartment spacious (booked into the 1 bedroom), very clean, tastefully furnished and with everything you need. Kitchen not as well equipped as it could be, but still handy for making simple meals. Pool/spa area small, but clean and outfitted well. Pool small but heated. Heated spa very nice. Gym small with a few pieces of equipment - looked a little cramped to me. Service very pleasant and accommodating. Staff always asking if everything is OK and if you need help. The Not So Good : Difficult to locate especially when driving. Hotel located at the intersection of York and Margaret and if you miss it, you need to go one big round in the midst of busy Sydney traffic with its many narrow one way streets and weird traffic flows. Car park entrance on Margaret street, but you wouldn't know unless you asked. A bit noisy inside apartment and out. Constant traffic noise - not so bad if all windows and sliding doors closed, and if located on a high floor. As per previous post, balcony area not relaxing at all given the busy street frontage and associated noise. Within apartment itself, older model fridge gave off a constant low hum. Could hear plumbing and water heater noises from next apartment. All in all, a pleasant stay and would go back again if we got a good rate.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>