<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="d62920a0873170d8c1cdb5f51ba4ec4a" url=""><![CDATA[Wasn't As Good As Expected Out of all the Four Seasons we have seen and stayed in, this definitely was not one of the best. We were in a room directly overlooking the public gardens, which were lovely. The rooms are nicely decorated but on the small size. Our bed was quite hard. However, upon request, housekeeping did put an egg crate on the mattress and that really helped. In the small bathroom, a glass door only covered 2/3 of the shower leaving the last third open. Between that and the gape between the glass where it opened, we had a flooded floor every time we took a shower. On the plus side, check in was smooth, the hotel was clean and the location is outstanding (on Boylston Ave. near the best shopping and restaurants in Boston) and overall the service was good. The t.v.s were plasmas with a great picture, the towels were nice and soft.The Bristol lounge was a bit slow but the food was better than in room dining. The cocktails were also quite good and potent.There were two incidents that made my husband and I think that there is a little lack of communication with their staff. Each morning, we would receive a call that was meant for another room, waking us early, followed one morning by a maid delivering a pair of pants to us at 6:00 a.m., only to be told they have the wrong room. We grew tired of them waking us for reasons that were not ours. Also, when the turn down maid came to deliver fresh towels, she put them on the toilet seat before she attempted to hang them up. I told her we didn't want any new towels. By now, I thought there were some things that management should know, so I made a call down to them to make them aware of some of their staff issues. After I spoke to the manager on duty, she told me that she would comp most of our room stay to make up for what happened. We were very thankful that she handled the problem with so much generosity. If she hadn't, I could not in good conscience, have given this hotel even four stars. As it was though, she redeemed their hotel, especially by talking to each department that had made the mistakes. We received apologetic follow up calls from each department involved. We sincerely hope that this will help their service to improve here.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>