<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="6588ea6f7cfb77a9f59eb9302474002b" url=""><![CDATA[good hotel but! Stayed for 5 nights, no idea of the cost as my company picked up the tab.The hotel is dated but had everything you need for this kind of break.Breakfast could of been better, best tip is eat elswhere.Staff were very good except for the bar staff who rarely smiled, expected tips, which I know is custom but surely you still need to give good freindly service ! the only one that showed good manners was Jerry. The bar waiting staff deserved the tips [which they did get] far more than the servers.The pool and gym area was a great place to relax and wind down in the sun.Rooms to Brit standards were good, roomy and great air con. Bathrooms were dated but did the job.All in all a good hotel in a good location but I do think you could do better.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f5221347d413fcbacc77435e5f2911d2" url=""><![CDATA[well worth the good reviews Myself, wife and 22 year old Daughter stayed here for 5 nights from April 30th in a 2x double bedded room. [1028] Very clean good size room, small useful kitchen area, great coffee maker, but no kettle for tea, good size fridge and microwave. Bathroom small but clean, good hot water, good shower, clean good towels every day.There are four lifts, two in the centre and one at each end of the corridors.Check in was easy we arrived at 12.30 pm and they had a room ready.We had breakfast on the first morning and wish we had,nt the 'hot' food was cold after complaining they only charged us for a continental about 13 dollars each, don't eat here instead, turn left out of the hotel, cross over 8th avenue and eat at the Pigalle,on 8th ave under the Days Hotel, far better food,service and price, we even eat there twice in the evening, great French type food at a good price.This hotel is in a great location, shops, bars, subway stations, restaurants all around, book it with confidence
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>