<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="d1fc28cad76bc77fedf1e63c54245818" url=""><![CDATA[Service standards need urgent attention!! My wife and I stayed here for 3 nights at the end of February as part of our 50th wedding anniversary celebrations. How fortunate that we were due to cruise on Queen Mary 2 for the next 10 nights; and what a contrast in the standards of service!! Only one clerk on duty at reception in a 667 room hotel! A request for a possible upgrade was met with a brusque negative. The hotel had been informed in advance of the occasion but we were given a very basic room about as far from an elevator as you could get. No account was taken of my wife's mobility problemsand a promised room change never materialised. The room keys we were given didn't work so we stood in the corridor waiting for assistance. Reception would send someone up straightaway but 15 minutes later no-one had arrived. A bell boy eventually arrived with our luggage and used his master key to let us in; but we still did not have any keys for the room.The information folder said that breakfast was available in the restaurant until 11.30 am. Going down at 10.15 we were told that the buffet would close at 10.30 and we had better hurry. Sure enough the shutters on the buffet were brought down prematurely at 10.27 and the waiting staff couldn't get us out of the place quickly enough in order to set the tables for lunch. A very bad impression and very misleading information in the room.On the next two mornings we breakfasted at a nearby diner where the food and service were superior and at about 1/3rd of the price.The rooms are larger than average for New York and the location is good with easy access to the lovely Brooklyn waterfront and good subway connections to Manhattan. It is also a short taxi ride to the Brooklyn Cruise Terminal. But the management of the hotel needs to get its act together.We have stayed in at least a dozen other Marriotts in USA from San Diego to Las Vegas and this was our worst experience by far.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>