<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="2684ec12e19710404ee67c25caa41174" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location We spent 4 nights last week at the Hotel Berchielli as I always check anywhere we are going with Tripadvisor before I book (quite obsessively) I felt I had to tell others what a great choice we made.We last visited 9 years ago stayed near San Lorenzo but I wanted to stay elsewhere after hours of searching cross checking with Tripadvisor I finally chose the Berchielli. Some of the reviews I read before we left gave me cause to worry but that all changed when we arrived. I am very fussy about hotels have been lucky enough to stay in lots of great hotels all over the world, but I'm sensible enough to know with a city break you don't spend much time in your room. STILL I do like it to be nice very clean hopefully with good service. Well we got more than that with the Berchielli. I requested a room at the front (despite other reviews saying how noisy it was) and we had room 503 which to my delight was lovely. It was large with 2 big windows overlooking the street / river below views to the Ponte Vecchio.We had ample wardrobe space a safe inside, writing desk chair, large comfy armchair flat screen tv, ample lamps to light the room the twin beds were quickly made into a king at our request. The bathroom had a normal size bath good shower overhead, 2 sinks,shaving mirror. hairdryer, bidet plenty of toiletries on offer. It was very clean there were no dreadful plumbing noises to be heard anywhere. The cleaners did a great job everyday we had clean sheets towels everyday. We found all the staff to be friendly helpful and the breakfast was much better than you normally find in European cities. There were cereals, fresh fruit, fruit salad, prunes, yoghurts, cold meats cheeses, croissants, jams, loads of different breads, jams, ryvitas, fruit juices, and a hot breakfast selection as well. The capuccinos were to die for (as you'd hope for in Italy really ).We thought the location was great as you could easily access both sides of the river nowhere is far to walk to in Florence anyway. (The views from Piazzale Michelangelo back across the city are well worth the walk on a clear day.) I will admit that the rooms at the front of the hotel can be a bit noisy during the night because of the traffic on the one way street below, but you should be that tired from your days of exploring the wonderful city that you won't notice. Alternatively you can request a back room, but I loved drawing back the curtains each morning admiring the wonderful sights and sounds of one of the best cities in the world.I would never do this lightly as Everyone has different opinions on places but I WOULD RECOMMEND the Hotel Berchielli. Book now have a great time!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>