<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="6bb1ce48f5ce9cebbf05e6bd3c4e24f8" url=""><![CDATA[Super friendly staff We stayed at the Courtyard downtown Miami for 1 night pre-cruise. I don't think I have ever encountered a friendlier staff at any hotel. Everyone you encounter not only says hello, they offer some conversation. The room was clean. We had a view of the pool, which was between highrises, so not much for sunning. The bed wasn't the best, wasn't the worst. Great pillows though! It was a little bit of a walk to the Bayside Marketplace, which I highly recommend for the evening. The breakfast buffet was pretty good, but a bit pricey. They did arrange for a $10 shuttle to the Port of Miami. Downside was we had to sit in the lobby with our bags for 1-1/2 hours between check out time time to leave for the port. I'm not sure if it was worth the price, but kudos to the staff! I think next time I will try the Holiday Inn for it's location.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e817f58b1f9ac4d361149cc453739744" url=""><![CDATA[Great Pre-cruise hotel My husband I stayed at the Holiday Inn for 1 night prior to our cruise. The hotel is located right across from the Bayside Marketplace has a wonderful view of the Port. We were given a 9th floor room with a lovely view of the port. It was cool to see our ship from our window in the morning! We arrived earlier than the posted check in time, but luckily our room was ready we were allowed to check in. The front desk staff was very friendly helpful. Our room was clean comfortable. We were right across from the elevator but I didn't hear anything like I was afraid I would. With the Bayside Marketplace across the way, there was plenty to do within walking distance. The hotel has a nice pool dining room and we were given a card for a discount on breakfast the next day. We could not get on our ship until 1:30 so we had a few hours between check out leaving for port. The hotel stored our luggage for us so we could kill time without hauling all our stuff with us! Overall our stay was very pleasant and we would stay here again before cruising.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>