<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="86abec6c13ebcc82b62e707f248a59da" url=""><![CDATA[An Exceptional Stay We arrived at the Omni after a 10.5 hour flight from the UK and I'm pleased to say the positive comments made by others on the hotel were accurate and we relaxed in comfort.Check in was hassle free, staff in general extremely courteous (especially the doormen). The two concierge we dealt with were very useful regarding transport and finding places to dine in the evening. The room aspect of the stay was very pleasant - a wide variety of channels (around thirty), a comfortable bed (although I found the pillows massive and prefer shallower ones rather than deeper ones) but got round this by sleeping on the very edge of them. View was of Disney Concert Hall and very interesting. Despite a large variety of business traffic on weekdays the room remained very quiet within. Bathroom nice, very clean with nice products. The rooms are furnished with desk, small coffee table and small sofa but are certainly not the most elaborate I have stayed in - but, very clean and functional. Lifts, hallways and lobby were all exceptionally clean and adequately decorated. Gym is good with a wide variety of equipment and pool is nice - a shame the towering skyscrapers around the property don't allow much sun to it - so is quite cool even on hotter days. We rented a car from concierge one day and it arrived on time and was a good rate. About $70 a day + fuel for a 22/23 year old with extra insurance coverage for younger drivers.If I was being very critical of this hotel I would say it's weakest point is the location. Although it is a five minute walk to the 720 bus to Santa Monica and the 16 To Beverly Centre, after dark there is the very little to do and what restaurants there are, are pretty expensive. The Daily Grill to name one was pricey with terrible service (I think it's on 6th St). Try the KooKooRoo opposite the hotel (out back door of Level Two, its very affordable and does a nice variety of chicken and sides for about $6 a person - we found it excellent. It was NBA off season but, during the season you could get the hotel car (Lexus) to take you to the Staples Centre (5 mins by car away) which would give you something exciting to do.Travel wise to Santa Monica it's about a 60 min journey + 20 in rush hour, to Beverly Centre/The Grove about 30-40 mins (bus journey).I would definately stay in this hotel again but, maybe tempted to locate to a hotel nearer B.Hills/The beaches if you don't want longer bus journeys to the stereotypical attractions. As a downtown business venue it is second to none. OVERALL I WOULD RATE THIS HOTEL EXCELLENT!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>