<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="551581a3c321f545e2276a124918085a" url=""><![CDATA[loved the hotel Can you say great location!!!! The hotel was located right in the middle of everything. The rooms were huge by Europe standards. The bathroom was even bigger. Nice amenities for the price. Hotel staff was terrific. They went out of their way to make sure we were happy and booked some extra tours for us no problem. Breakfastm was a little weak but everything else more than made up for it. I will reccomend this hotel to anyone going to Florence
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="892d8d92dd09e380b80147ee94b21c72" url=""><![CDATA[not nearly as bad as the reviews!!!!! Just came back from the resort. We were there February vacation week which could have been a disaster but it wasn't. I was very nervous going in having read the reviews:1)This is an all inclusive if it is marketed to you in a different way find a new travel agent!!!! An all inclusive is not going to have 5 star food and service. It was fine.I never met any one who worked there who was rude. I thought the bartenders tried very hard to accomodate you as well as the waiters especially the girl walking the pool.A few dollars every once in a while also goes a long way. I maybe spent 25.00 in a week in tips and never had a problem whether I tipped or not. I had to complain at first (which I shouldn't have to do) to get adinner reservation for one of the 1st 2 nights I was there. I spoke to the manager and he tried to be helpful and eventually came up with a reservation at Bamboo which was excellent. After that I waited online and took 3 9:00 reservations which were fairly prompt with their seating. (note to resort:when it is a holiday week hire extra staff to clear tables it will make a HUGE differnce in service)2)My 17 and 13 year old daughter traveled with us. If not for the Lacrosse team from Westchester it would have been very dull for them (Thanks for bringing them down)(note to the resort: Add a Disco or some sort of club for teens vacation week if they are happy so are their parents even if nothing else is good. Its a great resort for the little ones. We even watched the clown a couple of nights he was pretty funny!3)rooms were gorgous but can't seem to get rid of the mildew smell.All in all my husband and my thoughts were it can be a fantastic resort if they somehow fix the dinner reservations and put in some sort of club. I would go back in a few years.PS THERE WERE NO BUGS AT ALL AT THE RESORT (The general thought was that they must have sprayed it after there were so many complaints in December)All in all the reviews on this site have not been what the resort is really like.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>