<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="1cfaaf32d4a310adc495994fe4870f0a" url=""><![CDATA[Only place to stay on Oahu My family (ages 13,12,9) just returned from an outstanding 1 week stay at the Kahala. It was outstanding in all respects. We'll hopefully be coming back very soon.A bit of history - wanting to visit Pearl Harbor and other Oahu sights, I booked a room at the Hyatt on Wakiki. Even having lived on Kauai for 2 years, I didn't recalled my brief visits to Oahu that Wakiki was hawaiian for ZOO. The Hyatt itself was very nice, clean, very helpful staff. But everytime I walked out I wondered what was I thinking?. If I just had to be on Wakiki - the Moana Surf Rider across the street was beautiful and at least had some roped off beach area for guests only.So we drove out the Marriott (both the time-share and J.W.). This would be my 2nd choice, but it's a long way away and didn't seem to be much else around. But a beautiful facility, nothing like theKahala, but very family friendly and the lagoons are indeed unique.Back to the Kahala -- I went to the Kahala and from the moment I drove up I thought 'now this is more like it'. While only about a 15-20 minute drive from Wakiki, it was a 1000 miles away it seemed. It is an absolutely beautiful hotel at the end of the road. Very private. (while all beaches in Hawaii are 'public', the location of this beautiful beach that the hotel fronts had only hotel guests). The staff was outstanding, wonderful swimming beach with swim platform (the beach is sheltered by an offshore reef), especially the Plumeria Restaurant was outstanding (the other 'signature' restaurant was very nice but for the money I've had better -- try the original Roy's which is about 15mins. away). While we didn't do the Dolphin experience (Dolphin Quest is on site) - we certainly enjoyed watching the others interact.I have never been an Oahu fan. My family has lived in Kauai for 2 years and been many times to Maui (Grand Wailea, Kei Lani and Hyatt on Kannapali) and Big Island (Kona Village and Hilton Waikaloa) -- We all agreed that the Kahala was our favorite. No, it's doesn't have the large elaborate pools w/slides and water falls -- but the charm, location, staff attentiveness, beach, private feeling nature, etc.. was what to us a Hawaiian vacation was all about.By the way -- this was the end of a 3 week vacation where we stayed again at the Hilton Waikola on Big Island(too large and the cute little boats get really old after a while) and Grand Wailea on Maui (spectular loby, and a really beautiful hotel. But too big and just too many people lining up at 7am each morning to get shade chairs around the pools (which I admit my children loved -- but tired of after a while).p.s. the Kahala has speicials , and even their standard rooms, make it very competitive with Wakiki hotels. GO! You won't be disappointed. I've checked ok to contact if you want more discussion. /ap
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>