<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="3f7eee225ffd9a21cd5c25cb2a750ae5" url=""><![CDATA[Nightmare in Paradise !!!!!!!!!! Where do i begin??? Let's see when we first walked in the hotel we were told at the front desk that our room was ready. To make a long story short when we got to the room it was a mess as if someone had just checked out. Going back to the part of first walking in we were encountered by a concierge named Leonardo. He told us we were staying in the reserve section of the hotel. Which is suppossedly the newer and better part. He said we had access to the private pool and beach. The next day we had found out that was a lie. We asked the bartender at the reserve section for a drink and were denied. Going back to our lying concierge Leonardo we did not confront him because we were on vacation and didnt want to deal with headaches so we left it as is.Our second day Leonardo invited us for breakfast at the Gabi restaurant. He never prepared us for any of the following.... he told us we would get a free gift for walking through the property. OK.. so we agreed. To find out when we got there it would be a 90 minute time share presentation..which i need to say turned out to be 2 1/2 hours long. We had a pleasant young lady escort us and show us through but later encountered by a beast named Randolf. I don't know where they find these time share people. Randolf was rude and highly unprofessional. He was trying to belittle my wife and I. Constantly laughing at us and making nasty comments. To much to write. All i have to say is whoever decides to go to this hotel BEWARE!!!! We complained about this uneducated man immediately and nothing was done.!!!!!!Lets now go to the service of the hotel. Let's see WHAT SERVICE! This place sucks!!! To put it simple. If you need a spoon bring one from home. If you need a fork bring your own. If you need soda go get it yourself at the bar before you eat . As a matter of fact get 3 or 4 drinks so you don't have to keep getting up. These people don't ask their guests if they would like refills . They throw away your food and drinks if you get up at the buffet. There is no service for food or drinks on the beach area. So if your used to that like we are you are in for a huge dissapointment.One more heads up about this place. You must remind that appetizers come before the main course at those so called reservation only restaurants. Like Fuego at the Paradisus.I strongly urge my fellow vacationers to never, ever stay at this MELIA/PARADISUS PUNTA CANA property . If you must stay at a melia property I would say go to the PALMA REAL it may cost more but you will be treated accordingly. We have stayed at other properties in Punta Cana and the Carribean and this hotel is horrible. Food was limited because all the resatraunts were on different schedule which means you had to find out on the day ofto eat. Front desk had no clue what was open when. The food was outright bad not much options. Dont waste your time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>