<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="1242c78704da7da9ba2f4dc889a6c582" url=""><![CDATA[Club Room a Must! Our group had 3 rooms at this hotel - one standard room and 2 club rooms. We got a great deal at Travelzoo for the rooms which was why we decided to stay here. The club room was large and clean and had a balcony with chairs and a table overlooking the street. Street noise was not a problem when the balcony doors were closed. However, maintenance seemed to be a problem - the shoe polishing machine in our room did not work and the coffee machine took 45 minutes to brew. In my friend's club room, she stepped on a carpet nail that was poking up and hurt her foot. Our friend in the standard room hated it - her room was cramped and dark.To get to reception from the valet parking was a journey involving an elevator and multiple stairs. Be prepared for that if you've got luggage or mobility issues. And watch out for the hotel parking charges - $35 a night!!The service at the front desk was indifferent, but not rude. The location is great to access the theater district, the aquarium, union square shopping and China Town. Basically, it was an ok hotel for the price I paid (about $120/night). If I had paid more for it I would have been quite disappointed.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8b6123d7dd28a918bebe581b99e6c985" url=""><![CDATA[Good Value We decided to stay here because the reviews were pretty good, it was a Joie de Vivre property and because I found a rate of $88/night midweek on the Hotel Bijou website. Although the hotel is no longer a Joie de Vivire property, it was a perfectly adequate hotel in the Union Square area. The hotel was easy to find, it is near transportation and there are several parking garages in the vicinity. It is on the edge of a bad area and there is construction going on next door, but we weren't bothered by construction noise or the homeless. We did request a room on a higher floor because the noise from the street and the street people can be very loud. Also, like most homes and older commercial buildings in SF, there is no air conditioning. If you want a breeze, you open the window. On check-in, we were told we could have a larger room on the 2nd floor (apparently all rooms ending in -03 are corner rooms and larger than usual) or a regular room on the 6th floor. We went with the regular room and it was fine for two people. Everything was clean, if not fancy, and well maintained. One problem with the room was that the bed side lights were located on the wall above the headboard. My tall partner kept bumping his head into the lamp shades when he sat up in bed. One other odd thing was that although there was a terrycloth bath mat for our first day in the room, we were never given another one, so we just used a hand towel as a bath mat. We could have called housekeeping and gotten a bath mat. We didn't, so it was clearly not a big deal for us.The employees were friendly and helpful. We didn't try the free breakfast or the movies offered in the evening, so I can't speak to those services. Overall, this was a great hotel for the price. It is a budget hotel and I would have felt disappointed if I had paid over $120 a night. I also would have been disappointed if I was expecting a fancy or romantic ambiance. At $88 per night, for a clean room, I felt like I got a deal (hence 4 stars, rather than 3).
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>