<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="69f9e2ec72e524c15e5e5afcf1da03a5" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful, Relaxing and Enjoyable!! Wow! We booked this hotel as part of our travel package through our travel agent. When reading some of the reviews here (before traveling) I was VERY worried! However, the Caribe Hilton rooms, staff, facilities and offerings were all very accommodating for us! We arrived in SJ early (10 a.m.). We were allowed to register at the front desk, change our clothes in changing rooms, explore the hotel grounds, and have a very delicious lunch. When we checked back our room was ready. I must admit I was disappointed that our OceanVIEW room was not oceanFRONT!! It's hard to describe but from our balcony we could see the ocean but just below our balcony was the ROOF of a smaller hotel building so we had to try to block out that cement eyesore and look way over it to see the beach. I returned to the front desk to ask for a room with a better view and was told NONE of the rooms is truly oceanFRONT and that they were full and therefore unable to move us to another room. I was not happy about that but must admit the rest of the stay (ignoring the obstructed view) was great! For the reviewer who said they didn't change the towels... there was some notice that stated in an effort to conserve energy the hotel gives the guests the option to have their towels changed daily or not. If you wanted them changed you were to take the used towels off the racks. If I had not read that bit of info I too would have been upset to return to the room to the same old towels! But a quick call to housekeeping would have resolved that. We enjoyed the pool, the beach, the restaurants, the fitness room, AND had delicious pizza from ROOM Service (can u believe that?) We also took advantage of the tours available in the lobby ~ opting for a day at the rainforest. Our travel agent put together a pretty comprehensive package so we weren't hit with any surpise fees or taxes... Oh! and by the way, we took taxis from the hotel to Old San Juan a couple of times including the day we were leaving. So, once again, after checking out the bellhops held our luggage while we ran into Old SJ for a museum tour and some final shopping. All-in-all, the Caribe Hilton was beautiful and fun and the staff was wonderful!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>