<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="7978ed11d643cf0440f0cdba93034f67" url=""><![CDATA[Best Island vacation We just got back from Punta Cana Resort Club last night and as always its time to write a review. I am an Airline Pilot and use trip advisor for other peoples opinions on our winter vacations. We brought our 2 children and our Nanny. When we go on vacation with the Nanny she is there for vacation not work. The grounds where spectacular. The resort is very clean. We stayed in building 5 on the first floor. It was a good building to be in because it was close to everything. My wife raved about the beach. We typically take a winter vacation somewhere warm every year and almost always end up in the Carribbean. The beach is a long, never crowded stretch of sand that is easy to find shade. I will say this, bring your sunscreen!! My wife is a dermatologist and we had a hard time keeping from getting sunburned! The one negitive we had was if you forgot something from home get ready to pay..Prices where quite steep for sundries..I paid $28.00 for a 5 oz. tube of sunscreen. The beer (Presidante) is about $5.00 drinks are typical Island drinks and are also around $5.00. My kids are 5 and 3. All they need is a pool and playground, this place had both. There was a supervised kids program, but since a family vacation we did take part. Food was above average. We have been to the typical Club Med, Sandals thing and the food was better. Buffet style with good selection. They also have 4 other restaurants availible. we tried the seafood and italian above the lobby. These were very good! we mostly went to the buffet so we sould not bother other guests with the kids, but when we did go up there it was quiet and the kids did well. I am a golfer and got to play 3 rounds. The golf course is wonderful. Pete Dye designed it and he did a wonderful job It streches out to 7159 yards and the conditions were excellent! they broke ground this winter on another 18 designed by Tom Fazio. The club owns the international airport so all of the flight crews stay at the resort. For this to happen the airlines have to periodaclly check the resort for food and water contamination for safety sake..We did not drink the water in the rooms, but had it at the restaurants and ice in drinks and we all did fine. The staff did a great job. Reading some of the other reviews made me worry a little bit, but I could tell while we were at the resort some people are made to argue. We see them at the airport everyday. All in all a great family vacation and we will be back next year!! Any questions I can answer, email me at FRTDOG540@aol.com
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8ebf3959776e01239c6ed25fc8078bca" url=""><![CDATA[Great Vacation! I have written reviews on Punta Cana before, so I feel I have to do one on this property. One word, Perfect! I can give you a fair opinion on the overall property because we stayed in both the Reserve rooms and the regular Jr. Suites on the same trip. I have a 5 yr old and 7 year old and they both had a blast! There are tons of activities for both the kids and adults. We went back to Punta Cana because of the ease of getting there from the East Coast, and the properties. I am an Airline Pilot and we go to one of these all inclusive things each year for the kids spring break. This by far tops all the other AI's we have been to. The food was excellent! Not only the buffets, but the a la carte restaurants were awesome.What we really liked was the variety and the healthy choices you could make (or not!!) We ate at the steak house, Japanese, and the new Vento in the Reserve section of the hotel. The Jr. Suite room is where we stayed the first 3 nights. It was very nice, typical Caribbean room. It was a good size, clean, and the bathroom was fine. The air worked well and the TV had a lot of US channels. Our Nanny came down for 3 nights into our trip and we could not get rooms near each other on the property, so I elected to upgrade to the Reserve rooms (Reserve is the newest section of the property. It was opened Xmas '07) The rooms were spectacular! There were 2 flat screen TV's in it, a very good size Jacuzzi and well appointed bathroom. The upgrade was $50.00 a night and was well worth it! If I would have known earlier in our trip I would have done it! The property is HUGE! The kids club is up in the new section. We do not typically leave the kids in a kids club on family vacations, however they wanted to check it out and they loved it! It was fun for us, as we got to play tennis or workout when they were up there. The pools are great! The ones in the reserve section were quiet and it was easy to find a hut or chair. My wife is a dermatologist, so finding shade is a must! We love the beach, but we are the dumb looking ones all covered up!! We loved the fact that if we wanted to head down to the beach, it was a good 10 minute walk and we were getting lots of foot time,although they have golf carts that come by a lot and will take you any where you want to go...The people could not be nicer! I think like in anything else the nicer you are, the more out of the way folks will go for you..The property has a vacation club. The workers will ask you if you want to go to a 1 hour session and they will give you some kind of certificate for it. we declined and we were not asked again on our trip. I played golf on their course which is about 15 minutes away and was pleasantly surprised in the course. They don't charge you greens fees, just for the cart which I think was around $30.00 US. They bus you over there and pick you up. You have to make a reservation 24 hours in advance I wanted to play that afternoon and when I inquired at the PR desk and they told me to go get my clubs and I could get the bus in an hour. I also went over to Cap Cana to play and it was the nicest course I have played on worldwide. It was in perfect shape and the views are spectacular! Check it out on TV the week of March 31, The Champions Tour is there for the first time and I think they will love the course. It is about a 30 minute ride over there. Overall, a great experience, great family vacation, and we will be back!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>