<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="4f5f29896cc3ab9ea7dd2de3a05a1613" url=""><![CDATA[What amazing rooms What was good: -The spa!- The room service food.- The location for shopping/eating/drinking.- The bedrooms: large, fantastically appointed and the best bathrooms of any city hotel I've seen.- The service was faultless. We even recieved a call in our room one morning to let us know that someone had noticed our door was slightly ajar and was this intentional...WOW!What wasn't:-The view.- The hotel was small.- The lobby was small and the hotel although the rooms were amazing lacked the grandeur and sense of occasion of larger hotels.- You can't help wondering that if the Landmark is so fantastic, just quite how great the larger Mandarin Oriental in the city would be!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b199e9918cd4961ada0660505da79a12" url=""><![CDATA[Is this the best city hotel in the world? This has to be the best city hotel in the world.The rooms are fantastic.The location amazing (views on the harbour and linked to the IFC mall directly).The service is absolutely in every single way faultless, any requests arrive at your door within 5 minutes.I could list for hours how well this hotel serves you and still not do it justice. The staff are all efficient, knowledgable and pre-empt requests before they have even been made.The food is fantastic (breakfast and room service menu).The spa is one of the best I have ever seen, the treatment rooms overlooking the harbour complete it.The pool and gym are also aurplus to anyone's requirements.Even the most difficult and discerning traveller would not fail to be amazed at the standards this hotel offers. It trumps the George IV and the Four Seasons New York...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f28d6bdeca892922b682904f73c7bbb6" url=""><![CDATA[Finally! A Boutique Hotel to rival the classics I am based up North but find myself in London every two or three weeks and this has been the case for several years. I used to hotel hop like mad going through all of the classics including the Dorchester, Ritz and Mandarin Oriental as well as taking the odd flyer on the Sanderson, St Martins Lane, Malmaison and the Hemple (what was that place about?) Now again I found myself going back to the odd one a few times (The MO in particular) but recently I have been opting for hotels in the Firmdale Group noteably The Haymarket, Charlotte Street and The Soho Hotel and I am now a loyal customer. Having been unimpressed by the style over substance of the Schraeger hotels I was very surprised by the depth of quality in all of the Firmdale properties; the service from start to finish, the FB offerings, the appointments of the rooms and the quality of the beds were all top drawer. The Soho has to be my favourite as I think the location is spot on and the atmosphere in the public areas is always half decent - I will continue to take it over the oligarch-ridden hotels in Knightsbridge from now on.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c02f89543059f026118a62481f870e17" url=""><![CDATA[Great if you like being rodgered for no apparent reason Ok, so its the MO, the newest addition to the high class hotel scene in NY, one of the coolest cities on the planet - it's GOT to be good. Well yeah, its exactly that - good, it's not great. It's got a dramatic and original lobby (unless you've stayed at the Park Hyatt in Tokyo), it's got a spacious spa which looks impressive and well equipped (not compared with the one in the Four Seasons in Hong Kong) and it has the genuine pimp factor associated with staying in a hotel of this calibre (not on a par with rocking up to the George V in Paris). This is a good hotel with all of the artillery required to arm it for future greatness but ultimately it doesnt deliver if you are a truely discerning traveller. I didnt have a bad stay in this hotel but as other reader's have commented with all of the hype and the fanfare expectations are high. If you like being rodgered and want to tell your mates you stayed there, DO IT!! It's close proximity to Per Se and Masa is a good enough reason if you are a foodie.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>