<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="880170baa5eed7d565faf85ca365d099" url=""><![CDATA[Exceptional Hotel! We stayed at this hotel for three nights after having finished a cruise in Quebec and driven down through Vermont and New Hampshire for ten days, having stayed in several country inns.What a wonderful hotel! Great location in the Back Bay area of Boston. Right on the corner of Boylston and Exeter, very close to the subway and within walking distance of downtown. Very close to Newbury Street with lots of shopping and restaurants. One block from the Prudential Center.Our room (819) was spacious, impeccably clean with large bathroom and a walk-in cloakroom with safe and a large flatscreen TV which was welcome in the evenings to see the latest financial and election news!!The check-in and concierge staff could not have been more helpful as was the rest of the service. Every evening a maid came round with an optional turn-down service, complimentary water and cookies.The hotel also has complimentary internet facilities and Wi-fi and a state of the art gymnasium for those with the energy to spare.We use the hotel restaurant but we did use the adjoining Irish Pub which belongs to the hotel. Great food and atmosphere at very reasonable prices. We did eat one evening at the Atlantic Fish Co. opposite the hotel which was very good and well worth it for the experience but it was fairly pricey.All-in-all, a really nice finish to our month-long stay in the USA. Will most definitely book again, well worth the money
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="010e2a339418e5b3bd2db86ef8770f01" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Choice We stayed in this hotel for two nights pre-cruise on the strength of reviews on tripadvisor.Must say it was an excellent choice. We were travel weary when we arrived after a transatlantic flight and we requested a quiet room at the back. 'The staff at the check-in were most helpful and cheerful and gave us what we needed. The room was very comfortable and clean and had complimentary internet facillities in the room.It was an oasis from the buzz of the NY streets. Excellent location, within a stone's throw of Times square. Rick's cafe on the second floor welcomed us with complimentary wine and cheese.The staff at the front door were most helpful and really went out of their way to make our stay comfortable; they are to be complimented.Will certainly go back again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>