<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a7e0372f150cf501e59c71a9edccc0a7" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location, English Speaking, Great Value! We stayed at The Hotel Alsterhof between the 4th and 6th December, and spent the weekend in Berlin. It was fantastic. The Hotel was very good. Great great location, within walking distance of great shopping, xmas markets, the zoo, the main train station etc... and there is a U bahn station just outside the doorstep. When we checked in, there were candles all round the reception, they advised us that the hotel had no power between 1-6pm. We were out most of the afternoon anyway so it wasnt too much bother. When we returned however we were promised candles in our room by one receptionist and then it was not fulfilled. They didnt really know what to offer as light. They said we werent allowed candles. Im guessing because of fire or smoke risk however we were in a smoking room!? Anyway they eventually found us a flashlight that we had to use for an hour. The reception staff are fairly helpful, however do speak very good english. Our room was a lovely size, it was a double room, however two twin beds pushed together, however it didnt bother me. The bathroom was a nice size as well, with lovely bath and powerful shower. Everywhere was so clean and tidy. Just one tip for English people, the hotel does not have tea and coffee making facilities in the room and they also dont have english tea. closest you'll get is scented tea.As for breakfast, it was delightful. Lots of choice, we went down late both days so it was very busy so I would advise to go down earlier. On offer was Tea, coffee, fruit juices, Cereals, Bread and Rolls, Croissants, Pastries, Fruit Salad, Yoghurts, Dried Fruit, and Hot food including bacon, scrambled eggs, minced meat balls, boiled eggs, baked beans, and potatos. And to finish pancakes with maple syrup yum yum! You cant go far wrong with a breakfast like that to start the day.As for the evening the restaurant we found wasnt very popular with guests. It was very expensive in relation to some of the other eating places around but I guess it is a four star hotel. there was only 4 other people in the restaurant when we went in, so no atmosphere. If you want a great meal for next to nothing money, just turn out of the hotel and turn right. At the traffic lights turn right again and on the right hand side there is a restaurant called Toro Negro. Very busy, all candle lit, great atmosphere, great music. Its a spanish run place but they do all sorts of food. Pizza, pasta, mexican, tapas, Salads etc... We had Camebert, Large Rump Steak with Chips, Mozzerella and Herb pizza, 2 fantas, Crepes with icecream, 2 beers, and 1 wine and it came to 34 Euros! How cheap is that? The waitresses speak fairly good english as well. So overall the hotel was very good for what we paid for it, other than the electricity problem, we had a great time, and I would throughly recommend a stay in Berlin and a stay in this Hotel!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>