<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="ad424c82cc604ba4f05e5a8966846dcb" url=""><![CDATA[all-around excellent value We just returned from a 5 day stay at the Majestic and would love to go back someday. There were 5 of us (4 adults and a 7 year old) and there was truly something for every age and interest. After a long, 2 plane flight with layovers, we were greeted in the huge lobby with a cool towel and drink. As with many places in the Caribbean, the lobby is open air, so any bit of cooling was appreciated. Even in November the temperature hovered in the high 80's with humidity. Our rooms were next door to each other and exactly 1 minute from the beach. As requested, Emely gave us exactly what we had asked for. The rooms are spacious and kept very clean by the friendly housekeeping staff. A bottle of champagne and plate of fruit was waiting for us. Another day we found a bottle of wine and chocolates, along with flowers on the bed and strewn over the huge, open Jacuzzi tub. The bathroom set-up is more open than many Americans might be used to, but it didn't bother us. The door to the loo is frosted, but does not quite go to the ceiling, so it is not as private as most bathrooms. However, the shower is huge and we were really only in the room to sleep and change.The beach is spectacular with tons of lounges and palapas. The water is warmer than we are used to (thank goodness) but still refreshing with some minor waves. The sand is crystal clear white. Strangely, there are absolutely no shells, so walking is carefree.There are about 7 restaurants to choose from and only 2 require reservations. We loved the gigantic buffet breakfast where there was truly something for the pickiest eater. We remarked that the Europeans all selected healthy yogurt and a bran cereal while the Americans were loading up on bacon, sausage and made to order omelets, or waffles or pancakes. You get the idea!The guests reflect the world, with about 60% from North America (lots of Canadians having a great time!!) and the rest from Europe. There was a little topless on the beach, but our 7 year old got over it faster than the 2 adult men in our group.You had a choice of where to eat for every meal and I thought the food was above average for feeding so many. We particularly liked the Steak House chateaubriand and others told us the Gourmet Restaurant was lovely. We could not visit there because they do not allow children, which makes for a romantic adult evening. Drinks of all kinds really flow and they stock your in-room refrigerator with water bottles, soda and beer every day. My recommendation would be to drink some kind of liquid everyday as you do get dehydrated from the heat.The pool is the biggest I have ever seen....and beautiful as it meanders along one whole side of the resort, crossed by wooden bridges at various spots. Bring a floatie if you are a pool person!Finally, one of the nicest things here was the lovely Dominican people. Every person we encountered, from a gardener, to the maids, to bartenders, waiters and front office staff were charming and working so hard to ensure guests had a lovely time. Please...this is a poor country, so tip them often with a smile. They are working hard to improve their lives and the lives of their families and they responded so kindly to my poor Spanish and a smile.This resort gives you amazing value for the money and we would quickly return again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a6eec5efdbae131ac703f325ad9e6804" url=""><![CDATA[Best view for the price We stayed here for 4 nights in early May and found it just right for the two of us. Excellent price through the Entertainment Card with a 14th floor ocean front room which gave us spectacular views of Waikiki. (#1407 gives you a view of the Ala Moana Surfrider and the Pink Lady Hawaiian) This kitchy little hotel is directly across from a park so views of the ocean are fabulous. This part of Waikiki is where the surfers gather early every morning...what a sight. The rooms are small and it's kind of weird being in a circular hallway (!), but they are kept immaculately. The personnel on the desk are so helpful, even calling up maps on Google for us to take with us. Beach towels and chairs are free to use and, while they have no restaurant on site, there are loads of places within a few blocks. We loved the option to eat elegantly or quick and cheap. Parking was only $10 (a bargain in Honolulu) and you never had to wait to get your car or pay someone else to get it for you. Free paper and coffee every morning...Until I win the lottery, I would NEVER stay anywhere else.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>