<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="0028661ae5c43e640fd723f816da264b" url=""><![CDATA[A little bit of Polynesia in the Caribbean Sivory in summary is the ultimate escape from all that ails you in this fast paced world of ours. I came here with my wife and I can highly recommend this to be the place for couples and families looking to re-connect/re-energize themselves without the help of a therapist.We both work and travel quite often and the wife and I needed a vacation to be with each other, to rekindle that youthful vigour we once had when we were younger. We sure found it at Sivory.At check in were greated with champagne and the cool scented towels of the the carribbean. Great start, especially with ease at check in and the attention paid to us by the whole welcome staff. The hotel manager was a quite charming fellow. The staff always seemed to know ahead of time of our needs...really cool. Not intrusive at all.We proceeded to our room...WOW! Impeccable. I am a bit OCD and need things clean and new. I had no problems here.This place got us away from the computers/TVs/phones/parties that would normally distract a romantic getaway. We walked along the private beach for a picnic lunch the hotel packed for us and had total seclusion (about 1/2 mile up from the hotel). This place is so conduscive to romance. The staff were super attentive. We never had to compete with other guests for attention. All our needs were met. For a bunch of foodies, we were impressed (8/10) with the food. Excellent food for the carribbean. I would call it a semi-gourment menu. With that said, take the all inclusive meal plan, it is so worth the price with food and wine and the rest...The spa services were excellent. The hands and the environment were great as well...a must do when you are there. The spa is a great place to spend the day as well.This hotel is great for honeymooners who are not looking for wild antics and just look for the peaceful seclusion we need. I highly recommend this is a well bargained priced (Ritz like in Santo Domingo) escape.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>