<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="94baa747dfd471df3fbb8cd48bdf551d" url=""><![CDATA[has become a HK classic I'm in HK very often on business and stay in a mid-range hotel (Bishop Lei, see entry in TripAdvisor) but this time a client paid for a couple of nights in the Shang. I used to stay there many years ago when, after the Asian crisis, rooms were about the same price as the Bishop Lei is now! The Island Shang always used to feel very brash and arriviste compared with the grandes dames of the Oriental and the Peninsular, but it's matured well and has become a real classic. The service, in particular, is off-the-scale attentive, practical, polite, and effective, as only the Hongkies and the Swiss deluxe hotels can pull off.The decor is dress to impress chinoiserie, like it or hate it, but it has scale and grandeur. All rooms are high floors (the middle of the building is offices) so even the Peak view (=rooms at the back) have great views. Nice bathrooms, not as high-tech as some super-5 star hotels, but big baths and plentiful toiletries including bath salts, a great touch. The rooms are big and comfortable, with big desks, and a kettle (hooray!). The minuses are that the internet is very expensive and rather idiosyncratic (had to re-log in every time I opened a new browser window), and the minibar is predictably outrageously priced.The pool was closed for a party one day, and closed for emergency cleaning the next (must have been quite the party!) but the Conrad's 25m pool is one minute's walk away and offered reciprocal usage. Room service was fast and good, and breakfast in the cafe was comprehensive, pleasing the highly cosmopolitan clientele (contrast the almost club-like concentration of middle-aged white men you'd find at breakfast in the Mandarin's Grill Room).But the main take-away is that this has matured into a really classy high-end hotel, with its own character. Paris Hilton becomes Judy Dench... well, not quite, but give it another quarter-century and it'll be there!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="62791da193b18fa1b98c9feb5263d2c2" url=""><![CDATA[good value simple accommodation in central Sydney This is a basic, functional hotel in the city centre, well located for transportation and most business addresses. It's clean, well maintained, respectable, and has a very decent restaurant attached. There are no ancillary facilities that I'm aware of. The rooms are simple but with a kettle to make tea/coffee, and (expensive but quite good) internet connection. It's on a busy street but the window insulation seems to be fairly effective in keeping out the noise.It's good value for money - I've stayed in many different city centre hotels in Sydney in this price bracket, and this is one of the better ones.Part of the cost efficiency clearly comes from having a small staff headcount, so be prepared for delays if you're unlucky with the timing of your check in or check out.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e4b23060f502589066049cc21ea79a51" url=""><![CDATA[un-Japanese glitz! This is one of those jewel in the crown hotels. Part of the swank Roppongi Hills complex, it's wall-to-wall investment bankers, independent wealth, and their entourages. The cafe is the place for business breakfasts, the bars are the places to meet. The service is a perfect mix of Japanese courtesy and politeness, with international 5-star flexibility.The rooms are beautifully appointed, and the bathrooms wonderful.Of course you pay for all this, but if you can... you'll be pleased. The only negative I found was in the sports complex. While the gym entrance is free (or at least it was for my status with the Hyatt frequent-stay programme), use of the facilities within isn't. And when I used my training fins in the pool, the staff firmly told me not to, in case I hurt a small child. I was the only person in the pool at the time and this was clearly ridiculous. I was then doubly cheesed off to be charged separately to use the pool.But fundamentally this is a wonderful hotel, one of the world's best modern hotels.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="88e62c7e4a9e0f0ce8a532cbd472674a" url=""><![CDATA[your best bet for civilized budget accommodation in HK I'm in HK 6-7 times a year on business, and always stay at the BL (and have done for more than 4 years now, as have most of my work colleagues). The hotel is renovating their rooms which prompted this review. The rooms are small, Tokyo-sized, but clean and fairly well-maintained. The staff are professional and polite. The location is in the mid-levels, a residential neighbourhood, but only a 5 minute cab ride (or free shuttle) from the business area, or a 15 minute walk up or down the mid-levels escalator (a string of connected escalators that take you from office-land to sort-of-suburbia). The room rate is a fraction of the big-name hotels in town - not quite hostel-cheap, but very affordable. The internet is free and fast, and the beds are comfortable with good duvets. There's a kettle and cups in the room (a must-have as far as I'm concerned).If you get a harbour-view room (you'll have to pay a bit more, BL's not that generous on upgrades 'cos they're usually full) the view over Central towards Kowloon is stunning. The renovated rooms, apart from having a fresh makeover, have bigger showerheads, shaving mirrors, small flat-screen TVs, and bigger beds (not much of an advantage as the rooms are no bigger, obviously, so there's less space for your luggage!)What do you give up for the price? Breakfast is average and you're better off grabbing something on the go outside the hotel. The pool is a dipping pond, no point actually trying to swim, and the gym is token. There are no bathrooms, only shower rooms. And you occasionally find the modest-sized lobby crammed full of mainland Chinese tour groups.But given that, in HK, you're likely to be out and about 18 hours a day, and all you really need is a smile, a room, and a bed, BL scores very highly for value for money.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>