<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="569ba1337932d1ca5b08acd728385994" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location, great room but noisy neighbours We spent three nights at the Princess at the end of November/beginning of December for my husband's 50th Birthday treat.We caught the red eye from Luton so arrived at the hotel not expecting to check in but fully prepared to leave our bags and go out exploring, but the very nice chap checked us in and whispered that we would get a junior suite as the hotel was very full, which was a definite bonus. The room on the 10th Floor had a sitting room with sofa and desk, the main room and a bathroom with shower. We found the room to be clean, of a good size and with plenty of storage space (especially as the sitting room had a wardrobe as well). It is a very modern hotel but we like this style; it may not be for everyone. The views are great (although the bridge between the two halves of the building was a challenge for my husband!).We stayed from Thursday to Sunday and the hotel definitely emptied out at the weekend when all the corporates left.Earlier comments about the noisy neighbours are spot on. At the weekend the local rave venue is very noisy and does go on well in to the early hours. Fortunately we did so much walking we were too exhausted for it to keep us awake but it has to be said that it is extremely noisy and was on every night we were there. We walked to Port Olympic from the hotel which was lovely especially on Sunday morning when the place is buzzing with families, cyclists, roller bladers, etc., enjoying the sunshine.Port Olympic is definitely the place to eat. We would particularly recommend Sylvestre which was very lively with friendly staff and the sea food out of this world. All the restaurants in this complex looked great and were very popular with the locals.Getting around the city is a breeze with the Metro being very efficient, clean and safe. The two day unlimited pass was very good value and very convenient.We had a wonderful weekend at the Princess with the only downside being the noisy neighbours.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>