<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="0b85abb91e5d39f1acd0c8eed6dd9a28" url=""><![CDATA[Have stayed here and at Elysee (sister hotel) 6 times in 2 years-great We have stayed at the Casablanca 5 times in the last 2 years, finding it to be just the right spot from which to go to shows in the theatre district and wander up to the museum district or down to SOHO (albeit in a taxi). While the rooms are not grand in size and some air conditioners can be a bit half-hearted in very hot weather (i.e. August), they are quite adequate when one considers that the 2nd floor lounge is always available for sitting around with coffee and newspapers etc. This place is a haven for NYC (as is same at L'Elysee, which can provide somewhat larger rooms and an east-side location near museums). The continental breakfast is varied and abundant. The cheese, snacks and wine plus coffee, tea or hot chocolate are always welcome afternoons, with usually some left after the theatre. Some of the time there is a pianist in the lounge area just off the breakfast bar area.I find it difficult to imagine why anyone would say the staff are indifferent. We have always found them all to be quite pleasant . . . and folks with whom we've talked at breakfast or in the lounge have all been equally positive . . .of course, if one is unfriendly toward them, perhaps they would respond differently, I don't know. The manager, Joe, is most always around and stops to talk with guests to be sure things are going well. He's on top of everything and a friendly person.Last month, because of a request by friends we were meeting in Manhattan, we stayed at another, larger and well-rated hotel. Yes, the room was somewhat larger and it had two large chairs; but, the a/c was not operating as it would have made folks on the 15th floor and below too cold. The suggestion was that I should open the window of the 39th floor room . . . which was pretty much stuck. This kind of treatment would not happen at the Casablanca in our individual experience as a couple. Perhaps people who can't stand walking through the malay (meaning melee'?) of Times Square to get to the Theatre and restaurant areas might be happier in hotels that charge more like $600 - $800 or more per night and are in more prestigious areas. They do exist and they aren't bad at all . . . just a taxi ride or somewhat long walk to the theatre district.We're headed back to Manhattan again in September and November and definitely will be booking at the Casablanca. We find it more pleasant than the 4 Seasons where we recently spent 5 nights (though not in NYC). . . it's just a matter of atmosphere, I suppose. So, if you want location, a reasonable Manhattan tariff, (parking next door if you need it), an included continental breakfast spread plus cheese, wine etc. at other times along with what we, as constant travelers, found to be a friendly set of staff members, this is a good bet for you. Admittedly, they aren't like the staffs at an inclusive resort on a remote Fiji island, but this is New York City, many of them are/or recently were coming from an Eastern European country where English wasn't the language, and they've always been helpful and friendly to us and to others we know who've stayed there.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>