<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="01416691b63b6058b39755bdeb961dcb" url=""><![CDATA[Great value, awesome location. My family stayed at the Wave for four nights, 2 in June and 2 in July. We had to make our flight connections in Honolulu for our trip to the big island and Kauai so we added an extra night each way to enjoy Oahu. Overall it was a great deal and the location is fantastic, right next to the international marketplace, about one to two blocks from the beach depending on the route you take. We spent our time on Oahu exploring the shoreline from Diamond head to the north shore and spent very little time in Waikiki.Rooms are quite good. We stayed in a family suite with lots of room and three double beds (one in a room that can be seperated with sliding screens). The beds and bedding are excellent quality. There was a small fridge to keep your drinks cool. Each room had it's own flat screen tv. Yes, the lights in the bathroom are energy savers and take a minute to warm up to full brightness. Leave the lights on if it bothers you and you don't care about saving energy. The hotel is an older building but I think they've done a great job in upgrading the property. The washroom and showers are basic, no high end fixtures but plenty of water and water pressure. Please note if you open a balcony door the air conditioning turns off automatically. We didn't quite close the door all the way and the room warmed up very quickly.Wifi was free and much appreciated. The pool is small, difficult to get to through the parking lot, located in an alley, and your view is a fence. We didn't bother even trying to use it. Parking is tight but we always found a spot.Noise. We were on the 9th and 10th floors during our stay. I had read the reviews and was expecting it to be noisy. I only noticed the noise one night when someone was having a fight/screaming match in the alley below. I have to say it was so noisy that I thought the window had been left open, but it was closed and I could still hear them arguing from the 9th floor. I think it depends on where the noise is coming from and how it bounces off the buildings.Service was excellent with a few qualifiers. I had the same desk person as was noted in some previous reviews. He was attentive and pleasant but neglected to give us some very important information. We didn't know about the continental breakfast on the first floor until our second stay, and we found out about it from another visitor. When we tried to use it the last morning of our stay, we found out you also had to book the breakfast and get vouchers from the front desk, or you had to pay $5 each. For coffee, muffins and some fruit it didn't seem worth $5. It's a very basic continental breakfast but a good deal for free!. It would have been nice to be told about it at check in. We were not told where the pool was. If I hadn't read some reviews before we left I would not have known it was there. We were not told about the overflow parking area but it never came up because we always found a spot. They REALLY need to put a sign up to show the parking lot entrance. We found it on our second time around the block only because the alley seemed the only possible entrance.Brian (or the Big Brown Guy) at the front door was fantastic, really helpful, cheerful and full of Aloha spirit. I hope the management appreciates how much the guests enjoy him.Overall I'd reccomend this place for the price and location. I'd stay here again. Ask for the highest floor possible to reduce the noise.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5a6a4aafe33234cb408526309f219da8" url=""><![CDATA[best location for the price We stayed here for two nights on our way back home from the Big Island. The hotel location is fantastic for the price. Value-wise it's hard to beat this hotel. It is directly across from the main beach at Waikiki. An ABC store on one side of the main entrance for incidentals and a McDonalds on the other side for a fast breakfast on your way out!. Coffee down at the front desk in the morning is very good quality. The front desk staff were very knowlegable and I asked for their help several times for driving directions etc. The rooms are small but if you are two adults traveling together there is plenty of room. If you are two adults with two children you will be cramped. There is a small fridge in the room which we found very helpful. The views from the lanai, even the city view rooms, are still decent if you are on the upper floors. Staying up higher also gets you out of the noise from the street and traffic. My only real complaints are that it would be nice to have a pool for an evening cool-down, and they don't have nearly enough parking for hotel guests on site. The heat in July was a bit more than we expected and we didn't want to go to the beach in the late evening. We had a car because we wanted to get out of Waikiki and see the less populated areas and beaches. We had to park at another hotel a few blocks away for one night. The next day they made room for us outside the lobby area at no charge to help us out which was very nice of them. For the money? GREAT DEAL! I'd go back tomorrow.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4fc707462d63fcc94a986045a0ab91d1" url=""><![CDATA[not worth the money We stayed here for two nights on our way to the big island. The property has a great location, next door to the International Marketplace, just down the street from main area of Waikiki beach. My main complaint is that the cost of the room is far too high for the benefits. The room is what you'd expect at any family motel or hotel for under $80 a night, nothing special. For what I paid I should have been in the hotel across the street. The lobby and pool area are the only nice areas in the hotel. The foodservice at the hotel is average but the price is very high, as are the bar prices. The pool area is nice and we appreciated the live music and dancing while we were there. On the down side, the service from the two waitresses looking after the pool was incredibly bad. We waited to place an order, waited to get the order, waited to get the bill. It was laughable. The first time I tried to order from the bartender I was told I had to order from the waitress. It seemed to depend on the bar tender as later I was able to just pick up my drinks. No valet parking which wasn't a big problem but a bit time consuming. I wouldn't go back. There are better places to stay for the money.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>