<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="424c3cc7a455213efe95b570ac17c8c7" url=""><![CDATA[Two Words: Perfect Honeymoon After having gone to Secret's Excellence in PuntaCana, I have to say this.If you do not take time out of your life and go here,you are truly missing out on one of the best places onearth. The staff there go through a better trainingregiment than any Disney worker, or cult member forthat matter. (is there a difference?)When you say thank you, you will most likely here Itis a pleasure, and they mean it. Thanks Isiah, and other guy who's name I can't remember (water aerobics and dance lessons) Roberto at the front desk, Antonio with general info, and of course Pedro at the Swim up bar! They are so happy to help you. Their english isn't that great,but there were no problems with anything.Every day was 86-87, most days with nice breeze (77 atnight). No rain. Water in both pools and ocean wasperfect, expecially after visiting the swim up bar.They have activies from learning how to dance themerenge, racing RC cars for rum, free 30 minutebroadway-esqe shows, discotech, etc.... The views, walks,food, everything was perfect. The steakhouse had this green peppercorn sauce for the filet that I am stilldrooling about. It may not be 5 star gormet $200/plate meals, but piled on top of everything else it's great.OK, there are some things you may want to consider. First of all, if you are up tight and anal about something starting exactly ontime to the minute don't go. In fact stay where you are, vacation isn't for you, and I don't want you whining around me during my honeymoon. If you are looking for a hot night life and wildness, go somewhere else. We floated in the pool or walked in the ocean most of the time, and did the hotel provided activities. The ocean is no rougher than the Jersey shore. You want calm, go into one of the nicest pools out there. Some people that go are rude and take the floaties out of the pool and put them under their chairs even when they're not using them (sometimes when they leave the pool area for a while). Their regular room is very nice. We got the 4000 building near the cascade pool which was nice and quiet.Next time we want to go back and try the Saeuna Beach excursion. This time we did the helicopter transfer to the airport which takes you down the coast. Beautiful. OK, that's enough. You want more, feel free to email and ask questions. Thanks!Joe
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>