<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7f49528e6fbd6181b9ab525084738112" url=""><![CDATA[Very good!! I chose the Caribe for a pre cruise stay because of its proximity to the piers in old san juan. It was awsome.We arrived early (around 2 pm) and had to wait for our room to be ready. Check in time is 4pm, the bellstaff stored our luggage and we headed to enjoy the facilities, the front desk staff took our information to let us know when the room was ready. By 3pm they had already called us to give us our room. At the desk we noticed several other guests complaining about having to wait for their rooms since noon. As the bellman escorted us to the room I asked if it was frequent that guests have to wait so many hours like those other guests. He told me that this hotel runs full almost everyday, which makes it hard to have vacant/ clean rooms during the day for early arrivals. He also mentioned that the more of a hard time you give the front desk the worst of a room you will get. So beware.Thankfully our room was lovely, we stood in room 1865 at the tower building, it had the most awsome ocean view. The hotel layout is side ways so no room is ocean front but this side of the tower building is the only one where you wont see the roof of the next building in the hotel. Since it was the 18th floor we saw some of the front garden , a park , and the ocean, during the day you can even see the ships as the approach the pier. The room was spacious and had a great marble bathroom with a walk in shower instead of a tub. We always had fresh towls and sheets, although you have to request them, as a hilton standard the beds now have only a duvet instead of sheets.Since we are hilton honors members we have free access to the lounge in the executive level of the main building. It was nice because it offeres continental breakfast in the day and in the evening they have appetizers and cocktails, if you are not a gold or diamond member you might want to consider upgrading to the executive level to have this access because the food in the hotel is expensive and there are not much options outside the hotel unless you take a cab or rent a car. Walking distance there is a minimart, a small local coffeshop that makes great sandwiches and awsome eggs with bacon, and a subway restaurant. But thats about it. The options inside the hotel are good although expensive, they have a Morton's steakhouse, a pan- asian restaurant called Lemongrass, an Italian restaurant called Il Giardino and a Spanish restaurant called Madrid - San Juan. My favorite was Lemongrass, wonderful sushi. My least favorite was Madrid San Juan, the service was not so good and the food was just ok.The grounds are perfect, a nice big 3 tier pool,very kid frindly beach, plenty of hammoks to nap under the shade of the palm trees, we always were able to get umbrellas and towels, although the hotel was full we never felt crowded. They also have a nice quiet tropical garden with a pond with swans in it, also they have peacocks that stroll around the garden , this garden also has a small pool that you can enjoy if you pefer to be in a more quiet and private surrounding. Our check out was ok we did the express check out option to avoid the lines, we booked with travelocity so we had to pay the extra resort fee and occupancy tax that is not covered by these wholesalers ( Travelocity, orbitz, hotels.com, priceline,etc) the resort fee is about a 12% of the rate and the occupancy tax is 5 dollars per person per day. If you book with a travel agency ask if its included so you wont be surprised when you check out.Also, be carefull when you give your credit card, as in all hotels they put a hold on the card for an estimated amount of your total nights rate with taxes plus 75dollars per day per person for incidentals, if you use a debit card these funds will be automaticly deducted from your account and you will not be able to use your money . If you use a debit card I suggest you withdraw the money and pay in cash. In my case i was promised they would not make a hold but rather keep the credit card number to charge me at check out. I gave them my card and a few moments later I checked my balance, they had taken an approval for 800 dollars, when my total stay did not sum up to 400 dollars. I had to wait a week to get the money back in my account.I would surely return to the Caribe hilton , the staff was always friendly and had a can do attitude,I always felt welcome. I'm already planning my next trip!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>