<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="285a7b3f9381382a8a6e6c5cc4d4a216" url=""><![CDATA[Small, Efficient, GREAT PUB downstairs!! My husband and I travelled to San Francisco for the Nike Women's Marathon Oct 22-24 and stayed at the CQ for 2 nights. We had two rooms, and although I requested adjoining rooms when I made the reservation, when we checked in, we were unable to get them. Instead, we were given rooms that were sort of across the hall from each other. The hotel is located across from the embarcadero center, so we spent a lot of time walking through the shops and just enjoying the sights and sounds.The hotel is clean and nice. The front desk was friendly and check in/out was a breeze.The rooms were definitely small. They weren't as tiny as I'd feared, but the smaller of the two rooms we had was not something I would choose to stay in again. There are either two twin beds in the room or one queen- much smaller than most of us are used to.The door to the bathroom was odd- even fully shut, it had a noticeable gap that you could see through, or worse, smell through... sorry to be graphic, but this is a terrible feature of this hotel. This hotel is definitely geared toward the business crowd, with high speed internet free in the rooms, as well as internet on tv for a fee. I would think if a businessperson had a co-worker/client/etc to their room the bathroom door would be a real inconvenience. did i mention the bathroom doors need to be replaced?!I also was disappointed in the walls. They were very thin, and when the person in the next room didn't shut off his alarm clock for 30 seconds at 4:50am, I got the pleasure of lying awake listening to him get up, take his shower, and get ready for his day. I had my 18mo son in the room with me, and I can only imagine his crying in the night must've interrupted our neighbors' sleep as well. Also, the hotel is literally around the corner from the fire station, so although this is a nice safety feature, be prepared for sirens at all hours-- more sirens than normal, anyway.The bathrooms/bedrooms were very clean, and the showerheads were wonderful. Overall, I'd recommend this hotel if you're travelling on business. Otherwise, I'd suggest something a little more comfortable for a vacation.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>