<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="dd59f77a2cb3c083cd022b745644ce05" url=""><![CDATA[VIlla Real was OK We were there in September - 2 rooms. I agree with many of the comments - the hotel is VERY central which is it's biggest plus. Second is the nice bathroom (small...two sinks but one is behind the door so not very usable) with good amenities (they had hair-conditioner, a rarity, but don't use it because it was very hard on the hair!!). And, we got a bottle of wine in our room which was lovely and a few flowers and the chocolates at turn down service. The room was immaculate. The bedroom was the top level with a step down to the lower sitting level which is a nice feature....but the space would have been better as one nice larger bedroom since the bed corner was right by the step down - very dangerous if you're stumbling around in the dark (I managed not to fall till the last day when I was packing...and really got a terrible bruise froim hitting the bannister on the way down.) My friend's single room was extremely tiny with small twin beds.The hotel service is spotty...some people were very friendly/helpful, others totally ignored us or were outright rude. I felt there really wasn't any nice communal space - the lounge area was not well appointed, furnishings modern and the space uninviting. While we were there, no one actually seemed to use the part of the space that was a bit elevated (except at the computer) - it's very underutilzed and a waste. It's a shame they didn't expand the bar/tapas lounge instead - it was nice to have that in the hotel but no part of it was non-smoking so the smallish space could get pretty bad. And you never felt special as a guest in that area since there was a lot of walk in traffic to the bar.Our rooms had no information in them (e.g. about the restaurant, the area, hotel services, use of the Urban's facilities) or instructions on how to use the phone, (I had to make a call to France and the hotel operator gave me the wrong instructions twice...and my short call cost me 38Euros - - so make sure you have your own calling card) there wasn't even info on how to call another room, etc. There was no clock in the room (but that's pretty typical). My friend asked if she could have a clock and they said no clocks in this hotel.Last time in Madrid we stayed at the Palace which was fabulous but with the Euro/dollar rate it was just too much for us to spend on a room - rather spend that money on other things (we did go over there to sit in their lounge and have an evening drink). The Villa Real was a decent compromise and very functional but I think I might look for something a little more special next time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>