<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="05991db7f7a36560bfdaed31a74dc441" url=""><![CDATA[Special Hotel for a special occasion As previous visitors to Paris, we wanted something a little bit special to celebrate our 25th Wedding Anniversary, and with a little bit of help from Trip Advisor, we found it in this Wonderful little Hotel in a lovely part of the city.As our three night stay here was part of our ongoing holiday, we drove our car, and pre-booked a parking space with the Hotel. This worked very well, as one member of the hotel staff escorted our bags to our room, whilst another accompanied me to the Car Park. This was essential as, although the car park was a short stones throw from the hotel, a tricky 'one way system' needed to be navigated. Once there, the car was left, extremely secure behind locked doors, for the duration of our stay, although we were able to gain access to it if required. The excellent location of this hotel enabled us to walk to most of the places we wanted to visit, and the only transportation we used was the River Ferryboat, to explore further along the Seine.We booked the 'Romantic Package' and everything in the room was pretty much as, or more than we hoped for; with Champagne, cakes, fruit, candles, rose petals, music etc. for our welcome. The room was very spacious, with the biggest and most comfortable bed that I've ever slept in.One big surprise after reading the reviews here, was the excellent FREE Wi-Fi available in our room which was fantastic for communication with our two lads we left at home, and checking out places to visit. The only tiny imperfection of our stay was our Champagne etc was on our arrival and not our special day. This was soon rectified by a visit to the little off licence (liquor store) around the corner in the nearest side street, next to the Car Park. (For those not paranoid about mini bars, additional Champagne was also available in our room).Also in this side street were Patisseries, and a small supermarket, not to mention a friendly little informal restaurant, with lovely food (as recommended by the hotel desk staff). I know you have read this before, but...What makes this Hotel so special is its staff; from the guys and gals on reception, to the maids who turn your bed down and leave a little chocolate on your pillow at night, to the man who tops up your coffee at breakfast and the guys who take you to the Car Park. Everybody we met was always efficient, courteous, friendly, but never patronising. To any of staff who may be reading this, we wish to say a big thank you for making our special occasion so SPECIAL.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>