<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="e6a57e568f2fd3d9a564a4dac2d23973" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel, could have free wireless! Getting to the Westin is easy- take a cab, or take the Silver Line bus from Logan Airport ($2, pay in exact bills to the driver or get a ticket in the arrivals hall before going to the bus stop) to the World Trade Centre. There, follow the signs to the Westin walk is about 5 mins across a walkway, and worth it, as you get a great skyline view of Boston. The World Trade Centre is the first stop from Logan, and takes about 3-4 minutes to get to. much better value than a cab, and Silver Line buses are very frequent. With a hotel of this class and price though, have expected a shuttle bus to the airport.The Westin is a very well-appointed hotel, and I really enjoyed staying there. Check-in was fast and painless, and staff was friendly. The room was clean and of a good size, and the bathroom was great best part being the double power-shower, which was wonderful in the morning. The room came with a TV (annoyingly, the default setting was to go to pay-per-view), and a coffee machine. A good touch was the Starbucks coffee in the room choice of African roast or mixed blend. Having a decaf option would also have been welcome. The room service was, as noted by other reviewers here, generally ok but sporadic. I stayed six nights and some days the coffee replaced; some days the shampoo was not a rubber thing which was lying on the ground when I got to this Westin was not hovered up during my stay there. I think this probably had to do with low staff numbers rather than staff quality - throughout my stay I was surprised by how few service staff there was on the floors. Hotels already pay service staff very little - they could employ a few more and get standards up.Fast internet is available in the rooms. This is $9.95 for a 24-hr period, or around $5 for 30 minutes. Go figure. There is free wireless access in the lobby, although staff told me might not Again, for a hotel this price, providing free wireless would be a good thing.The hotel has 2 bars, both in the lobby. The main bar is in the Sauciety eatery. The food is expensive ($10 for a tasty but simple salad), as are the drinks ($5-6.50 for a beer, $14 and above for a cocktail if I remember correctly), but the barman was very good and friendly and the atmosphere chilled out. There is a Starbucks in the lobby, and the cakes there are fairly inexpensive ($2.26 on average), but the coffee is going towards $4.There are some restaurants on D Street near the hotel, but I try these. I was recommended a restaurant called on the street, a few from the hotel.Getting into Boston is easy, but takes a little bit of time. You can either take a cab, or the Silver Line from the World Trade Centre, or, as I did, walk 5-10 minutes to South Station and take the T or the commuter rail from there. The walk is scenic (skyline views) but may be cold in the winter. Again, this is where a hotel shuttle bus would be very useful! If you have time, you can walk straight into the financial district in about 20-25 minutes from the hotel.The swimming pool was ok, very chlorinated and to a good size. The fitness room was also good. A good touch were the changing rooms with lockers and stacks of available towels. If you have children, the swimming pool has no lifeguard, so it is not a place to let them swim on their own.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>