<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="d10f585d9040157d2f5ce6f5863d8b65" url=""><![CDATA[Great Experience at the Doubletree Market Center I've always been a fan of the Doubletree brand and the Market Center hotel was no exception.I was in town for A-kon and the Sheraton (once known as Adam's Mark) was completely booked, so I poked around and the various properties along the Market Center stretch seemed like a good value.One thing that pleasantly surprised me about this hotel was the complimentary internet service. I'm of the opinion that free internet should (and will eventually...) be the standard for hotels, but so many of the higher-end and even luxury properties seem to be stuck in this $10-per-day sinkhole of anti-productivity-doom. Not so at this Doubletree. I was prepared to pay for the internet, anyway and I was not surprised by the Wayport access screen; however, there was no other hoops. Just the screen asking if I wanted to connect to the complimentary internet.Shenanigans! I proclaimed, but my bill reflected no extra charges upon check-out. I was pleased.Also, I would like to lay down massive kudos to the gentlemen that operate the shuttle service. So long as I gave them a little notice and a little information, these fine drivers were willing to take you anywhere and bring you back afterwards. Shoot, they even took on a couple of extras I'd picked up in the West Village and dropped them off downtown on the way back to the hotel. That's dedication!I didn't have a chance to partake in the food (probably b/c it wasn't complimentary :-( ...Doubletree Brand, take note of the Embassy Suites!!!) so I can't offer any opinion on that aspect. However, the in-house restaurant looked very pleasing and inviting.My one and only gripe was with one very minute aspect of the room. I confirmed a reservation for a non-smoking double queen and was assigned a double room (not queens...that's NOT my issue though) but the room was a connecting room. Now, I didn't have any problem with this on principle, but the very first night, the room connecting to me must have been a family rushing to catch a red-eye b/c I could hear EVERYTHING they were saying and doing through the door at 3 AM. I have now resolved to request non-connecting rooms in the future.Other than that, it was a great time and I'd definitely do it again.Thanks again Doubletree!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>