<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="302517475611e48b94718eb52a8d8b56" url=""><![CDATA[A Paradise in Punta Cana While the road to get to this hotel was bumpy (and I'm not just reffering to the actual road, the airline we flew was repugnant), the trip was well worth it. The check in was a breeze, we were greeted with a glass of wine and a cool towel. The front desk staff was efficient and very friendly. The rooms were immaculate, beautifully decorated and very spacious. The dual headed shower was very nice as was the giant soaking tub. Our room was ocean front and the view was stunning! I especially loved the balcony with the chaise lounges perched on the very edge of the perimeter.The pool was just the right size with a great view of the ocean. Lounge chairs with comfy cushions and shaded by great big umbrellas lined the pool deck. The beach was covered in soft, golden sand and lounge chairs (some under shade, some not) were dotted along the edge of the resorts landscaping to the beach. It was very serene and peaceful.The restaurants (there are three) were good! Every morning we awoke to a tray of pasteries, coffee and fresh squeezed orange juice awaiting outside of our room. The service at all of the restaurants was absolutely first class. They are very accomodating, even creating a Dominican menu for us one day that was probably the best food we had there. One night they served us a completely impromptu dinner at the (closed) pool bar, complete with candlelight and tablecloth! We had been in the pool and then it started raining so we were stuck at the pool bar area and the servers grabbed umbrellas and walked from the nearby restaurant to serve us. The Spa is not to be missed! The unique pool with the different water therapy areas was a treat in itself! I tried the signature Rose Quartz treatment, it was heaven! The therapist was a magician! Overall the place is secluded, peaceful and completely luxurious. The staff was friendly and helpful. It is not your typical all inclusive fare that common in this area, but I didn't want that in a vacation. I don't know how kid friendly this would be, it's more a romantic place. It was our honeymoon and it was perfect!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>