<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="d72d33d015d0a1a9bf138d1a8eba9d02" url=""><![CDATA[Looked good but shame about the rest! Arriving after an 18 hour flight at 10pm with bookings not only made but paid for many months previous and then treated as if we had just walked in off the street! We were asked if we wanted smoking or non-smoking when all this was pre-booked. We were then told there was only a twin room available when we had booked a double. I got out my papers and pointed out that we had a Superior room booked and was immediately told that Superior meant their STANDARD room. I think it was more the attitude that she had and she was definitely in the wrong job! She then proceeded and in our tired state we presumed she had indeed given us a double room. We arrived at the room to find it was a twin room. So my husband immediately rang asked for the duty Manager and told them to get it sorted out and hung up. Within 5 minutes they were back with a keycard to a double room, I wonder where they found that seeing as they didn't have any! So our stay started off badly and continued like that for 4 nights. The hotel is built around the pool and all day there is noise from children in the pool and at night from the bar and restaurant out there. We were woken up 3 times one night by wrong number telephone calls put through up until 2.15am. Breakfast was a disaster as it's all so badly arranged it seems crowded and you bump into people even when it's not. Chairs are far too low (and we are tall) for the tables. Food is very ordinary, bacon burnt to a crisp, not much choice of cereals or fruit. Tables are laid with not complete cutlery or serviettes missing and clean cutlery not available unless you get it off another table. Wait staff more interested in talking to each other than serving anyone. Went to look at the buffet one night and it was terrible so we didn't bother. Our actual room was OK (but noisy) and clean and bathroom was reasonable too. Long corridors to lifts. When we left we had a late flight and found the hospitality room was also the laundry and nowhere comfortable to sit! So we sat in the lounge in the foyer and found staff using this all the time to sit in and 2 of them were actually asleep in there! Management seems very slack to let standards reach these levels. Although it was convenient to Clarke Quay the food places there were overpriced and I think Orchard Road would have been better. The only saving grace of the hotel was the Concierge Department they were without fail very efficient and helpful. The hotel had a shuttle bus to Orchard Road and also another to Suntec and Raffles City but taxis are cheap anyway.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>