<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f90145e6a91c49086b58dc962f146f7e" url=""><![CDATA[The reviews are right. Immaculate Hotel. I'm not sure what more I can add that the other 2000 reviews haven't covered, but I'll have a go.The hotel is immaculate huge. I saw repainting going on several times while there, everything was swept, ashtrays were emptied daily, no garbage or empty cups littered the pool and beach areas. That's an amazing feat given the 2000 rooms and 2400 staff work at the Bahia Principe and its subsections (Punta Cana, Ambar, Bavaro, etc.)Most of the staff don't speak English - but then again, I don't think many of the visitors do either. More than half of the resort was filled with European tourists from France, Germany, Italy, etc. It's important to put the resort in context:1.) Dominican Republic is a 3rd world country2.) Unemployment is 35%. Inflation is 28% annually thanks to influx of tourist dollars3.) Outside of the resort, you are lucky to have running water electricity is very unreliable. Take a tour and see the real DR. The resort is just a great illusion. 4.) Average wage is $300-$400 per MONTH if you are lucky enough to have a job.5.) The resort deals with visitors from all over the world - not just Canadians Americans. Each has their own needs and diverse expectations.Given the surroundings and circumstances, the resort staff do an outstanding job. I never saw any staff give attitude to customers, they always had a smile on their face. Unfortunately, I cannot say the same for visitors, several of whom I saw taking out their frustrations on employees at the resort. I never felled pressured for tips - can't say the same for most of Mexico. If I had to name a few downsides to the resort its:1.) Lack of chairs by the pool2.) Average food at dinnertime. I tried 4 of the restaurants. The best meal I had was at the Mediterranean (Prime Rib). I admit my food standards are pretty high though, and I regularly spend $200-$300 on a meal for two in Canada at a nice restaurant. 3.) Beach was quite crowded4.) Stall vendors in the Pueblo were annoying With regards to Internet access Wi-Fi at the resort. There is an Internet cafe ($12 USD or so for 1 hour. You can use the 60 minutes over a period of 5 days). You can also purchase Wifi access in the lobby for $15/day if you want to bring your own laptop on vacation. Don't expect Wifi in your room though. You can also rent laptops for $20/day. Overall, this is the best of the all-inclusive resorts I've stayed at.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>