<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="9e9347bc8b3fdf8573f29f4dd8f2ec67" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Alternative to Big American Hotels My husband and I stayed 5 days at this resort in early May 2006 after a three week tour of Thailand, Vietnam and Cambodia. We have traveled extensively (60 countries to date) and usually stay in 5 star hotels, often boutique hotels.The Bali Tropic differs from other deluxe or luxury resorts in Bali in that it is locally owned. As a result, it has less glitz and polish than a Marriott, Sheraton or Four Seasons, and also fewer amenities such as fancy workout rooms, full bar of call liquor, Wi-Fi in rooms, etc.We booked a Royal Room directly through the hotel with an all-inclusive package and paid under $200/day. The Royal Rooms were built at the back of the property 3 years ago and we found the rooms to be spotless, well-appointed with soaps, shampoo, complimentary water, and nicely fitted out with a four-poster bed with netting and high quaility local furniture. The decor was very nice--I would say rustic Balinese, with several niches in the walls with back-lit sculpture and a lovely balcony with a unique rattan lounger. The beach is a nice size with plenty of shade and palapas (though you need to get out early and throw a towel on one to reserve it), but is not pristine white powder. It is sand color and has seaweed that arrives regularly on the tides. There is a staff member who rakes it up and buries it...but it is also a problem in the water, though not enough to to keep us from an occasional dip.Our rate included pick-up from the airport, and staff member was waiting for us with a card with our name when we got through customs. We were at the resort in about 20 minutes and the reception staff escorted us to our room for check-in, as it was hot. The air conditioning had the room nicely chilled and worked very well during our stay. We did ask for additional towels and got them delivered within 5 minutes, nice towels of a bath-sheet size. We also were told that our rate included complimentary pressing for 8 items, a one-hour Balinese traditional massage, two and two glass-bottom boat rides.The pool is on the small side, but very nicely laid-out with a swim-up bar and plenty of shaded, padded loungers. The food was better than average all-inclusive fare. Breakfasts were varied and excellent, with an nice omelet station and the best croissants we have had since Paris. Lunches and dinners were fine, often themed with Balinese or Chinese food. Salads were fresh and available.Entertainment was so-so. One band called the Electric Duo was good and entertaining, the other was 4 Balinese men trying to to do country-western. It didn't really work well. One night they did a traditional Baliese dance, set on the terrace outside the main temple or shrine at the hotel. All the tables and chairs were moved onto the grass below the terrace. It was very well done--in fact better than a similar show we saw on tour the day before.The staff were extremely accommodating and professional, though most of them speak very limited English, if any. We didn't find it to be a problem.In all, we were very glad we chose the Bali Tropic. We wanted something informal and low-key, no pressure to be dressed a certain way. It worked well for us. We were the only Americans...met a couple from Montreal and a couple from the UK. There were many Germans. I have many photos. I will add some later or can send them to anyone with a special interest.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>