<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="a3e0e2946ccb97a9c032165c8ce0636c" url=""><![CDATA[Contemporary Modern Hotel Stayed there for 3 nights near the end of September 2007. Very modern contemporary rooms with a flat screen t.v. and open view of the bathroom from the bed via sliding doors. The room size was average, but the decor was nice. Great customer service. Doors were always opened for us as we entered or exited the hotel. The front desk were very warm and always inquired as to how our stay was going. The hotel is a little bit of a walk to downtown where all the shops were, but the weather was perfect for us to walk in. It was great that there was a Whole Foods Market downstairs, so we had a few meals there as it saved us a little bit of money and there was so much variety to choose from. Really enjoyed our stay at the Pan Pacific and would absolutely recommend it and would stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="67f25c4b68fc0ef9ad00732c9afacc7a" url=""><![CDATA[Loved It!!!! We recently got married and had flown to Maui to honeymoon and planned on staying at the PK for the night before we flew back to the main land. When we got to Maui, we hated the location of the cottage we rented and said Screw it so we flew back to Oahu and extended our stay at the PK from 1 night to 5 nights. In hindsight, that was the second best decision we made right after our first decision to get married in Oahu. We totally loved our time at PK. We really, really loved the band that played at night. We would sit on our lanai and just listen to the great music the band played which ranged from Hawaiian to contemporary songs. We so enjoyed the music that we spent out last night at the hotel downstairs by the bar to actually see the band play (we would have sat in the lounge chairs by the pool like we did the night before, but it sprinkled that night). Along with the music, we had a great view from our room of the pool and the street. Although we were not on the beach, I thought that our location was perfect because we could just walk across the street to the beach and there were so many places to shop and eat around us that we didn't miss the beach that much. The hotel is also next to the International Marketplace and we practically went there everyday to shop and eat. We totally loved the little sushi place in the food court at the Marketplace. It was cheap and the quality of the fish was awesome. Although we didn't eat at PK, we totally enjoyed our stay and the friendliness of the staff and the excellent location. Overall, we could not have asked for a better place to stay. On our next trip, we would definitely stay at PK!!! Plus it's a Starwood hotel so we got lots of points that we will definitely use when we stay the PK again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>