<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="c77b7fcbc19e3a30d80d94c627c2f8a7" url=""><![CDATA[A real 'pretty woman' hotel! Gorgeous! Queen Mary 2 coming into harbour
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bc2aace4a32c6b08fd88585170566a2f" url=""><![CDATA[Wow... When I was booking my 10 day 30th birthday treat in New York, I wanted something special and not too expensive. This hotel caught my eye and I was immediately seduced by the traveller photos on tripadvisor. However, although it was very cheap for what it seemed to be offering, it was a little more expensive than other hotels in the exact same area, and the money would only be justified if it really was as special as it looked (tripadvisor reviews vouched for the great amount of space, but as I was travelleing alone, charm and fantasy were much more important to me). I decided that it was too much of an expensive gamble and I went for the safe and cheaper bet of a well known chain hotel in the same area, which had raving reviews. Upon arriving in New York, even though I was satisfied with my hotel, I was curious to see 'The Kimberly' for myself (also since I'd fallen in love with New York, I wanted to check it out for future trips!) The staff were without exception immediately very welcoming, and I was shown around several different types of rooms! The lady that showed me around was obviously very proud of the hotel she worked in (that's always a good sign!). I just had to post this review on tripadvisor for all those who think this hotel is 'too good to be true' when they see the pics on the hotel website, and like me, opt for safer options and never discover the beauty of this rare place. The rooms are even more beautiful, spacious, and luxurious than they look on the website. From the gorgeous fluffy bedding to the luxrious carpet that your feet sink into as you enter the room. And so calm and sunny. I thought that being an appartment hotel it would be full of noisy kids, but actually it has more of a 'couples' feel to it than 'family' feel. It would certainly spoil the feel of the place if there were noisy kids running around, but it doesn't seem to have been designed with kids in mind. A word of advice - they have a mixture of dated and more renovated rooms. Personally, I prefer the dated ones (they're very well kept, and I prefer the charm and character of these), but I know some people would hate this decor, so don't forget to request a more modern renovated room if that's the case (I had a look at one of these too, and they are the same as the pics on the hotel website). As I say, I didn't stay here. But I fell in love with this hotel as soon as I saw it, and I thought that maybe there is someone out there reading these reviews, looking for something really unique and special for their trip to New York, and thinking like me, that it all looks too good to be true... I went for the safer option, and I was very lucky with my choice of hotel too, so I don't regret it, but I just thought this place deserved a special mention, since it really is a very special place in a wonderful location. And hopefully, someday soon, I'll be back here, and will be able to write another review...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b2a18f8c9c511b1915ca22fe5692b88c" url=""><![CDATA[Totally exceeded my expectations! View from room looking down 3rd avenue at night
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>