<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="b5ba26b3bfb02c21c101c4ca942644e8" url=""><![CDATA[Lovely Little Hotel, Centre of Everything! My mum I visted Paris from 23rd - 27th April. Our stay in this hotel was perfect. I had read all the reviews and they were all really good. I had my reservations about the fridge and small cooker etc, however it was fine. We didnt make use of the facilities apart from the fridge. There is no kettle so any water you need boiled is best done in the microwave. We tried the hob to boil some water but took forever. The location is perfect. It is around 400m from the Pantheon. Notre Dame is about 600m directly down the hill. There is a big street about 500 m away - some nice shops. The hotel is at the end of a very short cul-de-sac. The staff are just the most helpful you can imagine. All speak English perfectly! We had a room on the ground floor that was just beside the reception. I was concerned that we would be woken by people coming and going through the night - but didnt hear a peep! So if you get this room, it's not as bad as you might think.Places to eat nearby - we were recommended Le Coup Coup (or something similar). From the crowd in the place we expected it to be wonderful... However it was less than so. The Rack of Lamb, was definately not a lamb - more Mutton. And it smelled like mutton. The duck was ok, as was the soup. Generally we didnt get any good evening meals. Of 3 places recommended to us 2 were pretty average and the third was ok. So make your own mind up on hotels recommendations.Nice lunch can be got at a place on the boulevard down from the Pantheon - cant remember the name but it was packed solid even at 2.30! its on the left if Pantheon is at your back - think its about the third or fourth place. Otherwise we found the Lourve and Musee D'Orsey restuarants very decent!In all I would definately recommend this hotel to people. Only draw back is there is no bar or resturaunt in the place but theres loads within a stones throw!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>