<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="b1ed63a0ef1710a681eda97fcc5977b6" url=""><![CDATA[Wow - just a fantastic room and view - good food too! Upon arrival, due to my Starwood status, I got upgraded to a corner suite which was absolutely fantastic. The views of Waikiki from both balconies were stunning, and the room was immaculate with every amenity you could possibly need. It was far too much living space for one poor business traveler, but it had 2 big-screen TVs, and the bathroom fixtures were gorgeous Kohler. In peaking into the regular rooms while the cleaning crews were working, the quality seemed high throughout the hotel. But for the value I paid - it was just superb.The hotel restaurants, while a bit pricey as can be expected, have some very good food. RumFire has some great food - the fried rice in particular was top notch. Breakfast was also nicely done.For a business traveler like me, it was top notch, but I can see some potential drawbacks for a vacationing family - the pool is a bit small, and you aren't directly on Waikiki Beach. Also, the hotel next door is currently under construction, so some views on that side may be a bit obstructed.But overall - a great stay - would recommend it wholeheartedly.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="da1b258aaf973cf0cdc6392ea3ab1386" url=""><![CDATA[The most mediocre Westin I've experienced This was the third Westin I had stayed in within a week (please see my other reviews for the ones in Columbus, Ohio and San Francisco), and it was not up to the Westin standard. First impressions count - and the rugs in the lobby were fraying along the edges. Front desk staff was amenable, but nothing above and beyond, considering the price tag. My room was clean and everything in working order, but I think it was smaller than an average hotel room - this may have been an optical illusion, as the hotel tower is rounded, so the rooms are round, rather than rectangular along the outside. It could be a really neat effect, but I don't think the room was oriented to make that happen. Room service breakfast was good, but overpriced (even for a Westin).When reading previous reviews of this hotel, I noticed that one reviewer mentioned that the thread count on the sheets was not up to Heavenly Bed standards - I almost brushed it off, but then I got into bed - and the reviewer was absolutely right! Having just come from two nights at the Westin St. Francis in San Francisco, the sheet texture was totally different and not as smooth.Don't get me wrong - the hotel is still better than your average hotel, and has all the amenities of a Westin. I just think that there is room to improve, especially given the $200+ price tag for the average business traveler. But one odd compliment - for a hotel with nearly 40 stories, I never had to wait long for an elevator!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c83777250c0b038f47520f733e7ef096" url=""><![CDATA[Not worth the price or it's star rating Every time I book at Four Points, I assume it will be better than it ends up being. I know that Starwood has been trying to upgrade this brand to bring it more in line with its other brands, but it still falls short. This hotel in particular, while a great location in Sydney (especially for tourists visiting the Darling Harbour area) just isn't up to par given the price tag. I had a Harbour View room on the SPG floor (the view was good), but the room was incredibly damp, even allowing for the fact that we were three blocks from the water. The cielings were quite low, making the bathroom dark since it only had one light. It was rather ironic, in that I read the Starwood brochure provided in the room, and it said one thing that Four Points had was a good shower - and this shower was not very good. Even the furniture in the room needed updating. The prices for all services - room service, in-room telephone, and Internet, to name a few - were all more expensive than the Westin Melbourne where I had stayed previously.After I arrived and got settled in, I checked out rates for the 5-star Sheraton on the Park across town. For the subsequent nights I had in Sydney, the Sheraton was the same price - so I checked out early the next day (the front desk was very accomodating, so a thank you to them) and transferred.It's not that the hotel overall was bad - probably 3 stars overall, and definitely suitable for tourist groups - but given the higher perception that the hotel gives on its web site and the newer, more upscale look Sheraton is trying to put on this brand, I can't give it more than the 2 stars.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="58988b07e0275aaea313d3d72ac3950e" url=""><![CDATA[My go-to hotel in San Francisco As a business traveler, the St. Francis is in a perfect location right in the heart of downtown San Francisco. The front desk staff was very helpful to me on this particular trip, as I had left an item in my room upon check-out, returned five minutes later, and they quickly helped me retrieve the item. I love the size of the rooms, along with the big-screen television (HD for more channels would certainly be a plus). For a high rise hotel, I very rarely had to wait more than 15-30 seconds for an elevator - and the hotel was nearly at capacity.Only a couple things prevent this hotel from being five stars in my book - first, the closet doors in my room had obvious nicks in them that almost seemed calling out to be fixed. Also, the toilet fixtures don't seem to match the luxury image of the hotel. On the plus side, the Heavenly Bed is great, along with the views from the high-story rooms.Whenever I'm in San Francisco, I would stay here, especially since the price is typically the lowest of the Starwood properties in downtown San Francisco.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9e2c01191cdfc6afad87a55ed52ab870" url=""><![CDATA[Great stay, just shy of the 5-star mark Sheraton on the Park has a prime location (as the name would suggest) on Elizabeth St right next to Hyde Park, and a short walk from most major businesses and Sydney attractions. The rooms were very well furnished and comfortable, and the bathroom was gigantic and gorgeous (separate shower and tub). My only hesitance, and why it's not five stars in my book, was that there was slight evidence of wear in my guest room. The desk chair looked a bit used, and there were a couple chips in the bathroom vanity and toilet. It may sound very nit-picky to call those out, but when everything else is so superb, you do notice the little blemishes.I enjoyed the fact that turndown service was available but not mandatory - as I often find as a business traveler that it occurs at times when I'm actually in the room. The concierge staff was quite nice, and directed me well on all occasions. Staff members were always pleasant and helpful without being overbearing. If you do go in the summer - I would recommend the rooftop pool - the view overlooking Hyde Park is gorgeous (and it wasn't even a nice day when I went). Room service is a bit overpriced, but there is a Starbucks right around the corder, along with a Food Court in Sydney Tower down the block if you want to grab food instead. Overall, a great hotel that I would solidly recommend - based on their reputation, I am confident that if brought to their attention, the blemishes would be quickly fixed.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>