<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="f95af27c28b2b6858ecce540f20034cd" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Stay at the Radisson I stayed at the Radisson Boston from Oct 21-Oct 24 while attending a conference at the convention center. Check-in was very smooth efficient I was given a room on the 11th floor. The Radisson is billed as a non-smoking hotel, which was my primary reason for booking there, but on entering my room I was greeted with the odor of stale cigarette smoke. Why do smokers do this? I phoned the reception desk and they offered me a new room. After a trip down the elevator with my suitcase, I was reassigned to room 2121, which was virtually identical minus the cigarette smell and with a fantastic view of downtown. The room was comfortable and nicely furnished. The bathroom had a nice showerhead and decent water pressure. Best of all was the sleep number bed, which was very comfy. Though my room was located near the elevators, it was very quiet--one of the most quiet rooms I've experienced in any city I've visited. I really didn't spend much time in the room except for sleeping and didn't use the fitness center, restaurants, pool, etc. Other than the cigarette smoke, my only complaint is that the hotel is a little far from the convention center, requiring use of shuttle buses or taxis. Traffic is snarly so it took awhile either way to get to meetings. Fortunately there is shopping, restaurants and sightseeing within walking distance.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="afac10893c0c1c025a9bc71250a0ca90" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful Resort Our stay at the Iberostar Bavaro was from Aug 30 to Sept 6, traveling with our grown son daughter and their spouses. stayed at a number of other Iberostar properties, but this was our first time at the Bavaro. A week or so before our trip, I emailed the resort to request rooms in the same block. Though I receive a response, everything was in order when we arrived. The front desk staff was very pleasant and we were greeted with a slushy drink. We immediately booked reservations at three a la carte restaurants. The lobby area is nicely decorated, though the bar is pretty plain. Our flight down was only about 25% occupied and the resort seem very crowded.Rooms Housekeeping: Rooms were nicely decorated, but musty smelling. We were in room 2546, which was a great location and just a short walk to the pool, beach, and lobby. My son daughter-in-law were disappointed to find two double beds, but called the front desk and housekeeping came later and pushed the beds together to make a super large king bed. As repeat IB customers, we found a bottle of rum and plates of pastries and fruit on arrival. Our rooms have flat screen televisions, but TV is pretty limited and not what we were there for! The rooms were kept spotlessly clean and decorated daily with flowers. The maid was very pleasant and always greeted us enthusiastically when we saw her. We tipped $3-5 dollars every day. Rooms were cleaned early in the day. The only slip-up was on the last day we get any bath towels. I called the front desk, but towels never arrived. The towel art bird on the coffee table saved the day and my husband used his beach towel. I was able to get towels from the maid first thing in the morning so we could shower before heading to the airport. Our only complaint about the room was the moldy smell and the weak air-conditioning. . The temp stayed around 80F the whole time and was really humid, which explains the moldy smell. Definitely bring air freshener for your room and dryer sheets to stash in the closet and suitcases. The odor in our clothes washed out, so not that big a deal.Grounds Public Areas: The grounds are gorgeous! The Bavaro is a tropical paradise with natural ponds, lush landscaping, and a variety of ducks, egrets, and flamingos. Someone is always working on pruning, painting, repairing, cleaning, etc. The public restrooms are immaculate. Just about every time I used the restroom at the beach, someone was cleaning it.Beach: The beach is one of the most beautiful anywhere in the Caribbean--wide with a gradual slope. Someone was constantly grooming the beach, sweeping up cigarette buts and trash. We had no problems getting our favorite palapas everyday. I was usually on the beach before 9, but there were still palapas available later in the day. We hung out near the beach bar, so it a far walk to get a drink. There is no wait service at the beach or pool at the Bavaro. Restrooms are located nearby. miss the French fries at the beach bar. even better than The pool was nice enough but not huge or opulent like at other resorts and the water was surprisingly cool and refreshing. The pool bar was nice, but would be nicer if it was adults only. I like sharing the bar with infants and toddlers in floaties.Food: I would rate the food at the Bavaro at the top of the all-inclusives visited. Chefs took pride in their elaborate food and veggie carvings that decorated the buffets. Service was a little iffy. Most waiters were extremely friendly and talkative, some seemed aloof, but maybe a result of the language barrier. None in our party got sick from the food except from over-indulging. We ate at four of the restaurants: Le Couple (Gourmet) was fantastic. The fillet was one of the best had ever and the lobster excellent. The Cajun was good, but the wait staff had a bit of an attitude. My blackened grouper was delicious. The jambalaya was not what been used to, but my husband liked it. The Star Rock was a major disappointment. Food was menu for an We expected I enjoy the cigarette smoke. The Mediterranean was good with mainly seafood on the menu. We enjoyed the appetizer buffet more than the entrees. The main buffet was very good, with lots to choose from. Breakfast was excellent with just about any standard breakfast item you could think of plus the European favorites like meats and cheeses as well. Pastries breads were to die for. The fresh fruit was excellent, especially the mango. Foods were labeled and kept at the appropriate temperature. Dinner also had lots of choices. Even the pickiest eater could find something to eat. The fish was delicious and there was always a carving station with pork, beef, etc. On Friday they had lobster, which was a little disappointing. We enjoyed the beach buffet for lunch. Twice during the week they had beach parties, one day with barbecue steak and chicken, another with paella. Other days they alternated Chinese, Dominican, Mexican. There were always hamburgers, hot dogs, chicken and pasta dishes. Again, even picky eaters could find something and the variety was nice, so you feel like you had to eat the same thing every day.Activities: There was plenty to do, but we participate much. Star Friends were friendly but not pushy in getting people to take part. My daughter, daughter-in-law and I had massages one rainy day. My massage was the best had at a resort and the prices ($50/hr) were reasonable. Weather: We had two days of rain thanks to TS Hanna, but we still went to the beach and had a great time. The resort provided nice golf umbrellas for us to use on the rainy days. The rest of our week was beautiful with temps in the and not as humid as Mexico during the same time of year.Once again, Iberostar has proven to be a good value with consistent ambiance, service and food. I hesitate to stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="29f64dfa24354774d7f46c04a3fed65b" url=""><![CDATA[Please Fix the Food! My husband I stayed at the Majestic from Feb. 23 to Feb 29 and chose the resort based on Trip Advisor reviews. Our goal was a relaxing vacation at a nice beach, and that wish was fulfilled. There were many things we liked, but some things need attention to make this resort deserving of its ranking.Things that were great: Check in was smooth. Richard greeted us, showed us to our room and helped with our restaurant reservations. Such a nice man! He was very helpful before our stay and really showed personal We had booked a swim up room (2129) and we were not disappointed. It was worth the extra money and we loved the location, about halfway between the lobby beach. The room smelled just a little musty, but I brought a room freshener, which took care of the problem. The bed was very comfortable and bedding looked fairly new. The room was very quiet and we slept well. Air conditioning was adequate, and easy to control. The room was clean with only two mosquitoes sighted and no bites during our stay. The robes and treats (champagne, fruit platter, sushi, and grapes wine) delivered on four nights were a nice touch. The beach and pool were beautiful and it was wonderful to be able to get chairs and palapas without playing the towel game. The beach is great for walking and is so beautiful with all the palm trees. The pool was always clean and has many quiet nooks to hang out. The swim up bar was a lot of fun at happy Drinks were good. The signature Majestic drink is delicious. They make a great cosmo at the downstairs The staff were very friendly for the most part and were always smiling and happy. It helps to smile and try to speak a little Spanish. The animation team was friendly, but not overbearing. They tried to get guests involved, but took no for an answer if you interested. Evening entertainment on the plaza, the sax player and combo, were very good. It was nice to be able to go to restaurants without making reservations. The resort is a nice size. You can walk from the beach to lobby in about 5 minutes. Needs improvement: chef Gordon Ramsey when you need him? have a field day here. The food in itself will probably keep us from returning. The buffets are reminiscent of college cafeteria food. Soups and hot foods were cold, cold foods were warm. Beef was tough. Things displayed to even attempt to make them look appetizing. There enough tongs for all the dishes. (This sounds picky, but when you think of how many people touch the tongs, it really spreads illness.) We did have a few good restaurant meals, but service was often rushed. You finish one course before the next arrived. Some of the restaurant meals were awful. (I can give you more details if you like.) Breakfast at the main buffet is probably the best meal of the day. Lunch is not good anywhere. At lunch there are too many logjams at the buffets. People pile up waiting for pasta, grilled items, and panini sandwiches. They need to come up with a way to serve simple, tasty, appetizing food quickly for lunch. And what is that tacky hut doing in the middle of the palapa restaurant? Maintenance is an issue. I can see this place going down hill fast from lack of maintenance. Things stayed broken all week. The ice machine near our room work. One of the shower heads at the beach shower broke off was never fixed. A halogen light kept blinking off on at the plaza stage where the sax player band play. Walkways around the pool have potholes. a path at the bottom of one of the bridges at the pool that is pieces of stones just sitting in some shale. People kept tripping on the stones all week. This really needs fixed before someone gets hurt. On the other hand, we saw a maintenance worker polishing the floor in the lobby at 9 PM while people were trying to walk through or sit and relax. This seemed like bad timing to Sickly landscaping. Trees and shrubs look healthy. Grass is lumpy. No birds or animals. Not enough public restrooms by the pool beach. Please put up some paper towel holders and more soap dispensers! There is just one soap dispenser per restroom and very inconveniently placed! Paper towels got wet setting on the sink counter. I saw so many people go to the bathroom, rinse their hands without using soap then proceed to the palapa restaurant where they touch those tongs that are in such short supply. No wonder people get On our third day, I was sick and confined to my room with diarrhea, vomiting and severe headache. I was unable to eat or drink much the following day, but was ok for a few days, then the sickness returned just in time to get on the plane. My husband never got sick, but we ate different Tiny plastic drink cups. Make sure you bring your own cup. Iberostar used larger plastic cups that they rewashed. It bothered me to think about how much plastic was going into the garbage between the bottled water and the drink cups. The animation team could use some new tapes. You could set your watch by the end of the week. Same music everyday for stretching, aerobics, etc.If booked the Majestic, despair! There is a lot to like. We had a nice time, but there is definitely room for improvement. This place has the potential to be a first class place, but I can see signs that management may be letting things going downhill. Maybe a cash crunch due to the building of the new resort next door? I would give the food a 2 and the rest of the resort a 4. I would probably not come back unless the price were right. We paid a premium price for this place, but have had better food at resorts that were less expensive.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>