<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="8111da973977223f99abafdfe56538c8" url=""><![CDATA[Very nice, but not quite there yet.... My wife and I just returned from our stay at the Melia from June 20-27, 2008. We were located in Royal Service bldg #51. Overall, we found this property to be very well maintained and as many have said before .... very large. Understanding English is sometimes a problem but you can easily get by and everyone is very friendly and willing to help.Our comments/advise are as follows:Airport in Punta Cana - open air and somewhat humid depending on the outside weather. $10/person required to be paid before entering the terminal and baggage claim. Taxi and shuttle providers each have a counter after you exit baggage claim to the right. Ride is about 20 minutes.Hotel - checked-in at 1:30pm and was told that we were upgraded but that the room would not be ready until 3:00pm. Luggage did not arrive until after 4:00pm. Had to make 3 calls to VIP Lounge before receiving it. Butler showed up once and offered an extension number to call if we needed anything. Called to have luggage picked up when we were checking out, but no one showed up. Beach - less than 10 minute walk from room with shuttle service available whenever requested. Beach is groomed each morning to remove seaweed but there is always some in the areas closest to the shore no matter where you go. Beautifully white and never hot. No issues for availability of covered huts or chairs. Vendors kept at the shoreline to limit the amount of selling.Food/Wine - our favorites were the French, Hibachi, and Gabi. Beef was very good in all restaurants. Most meals were unseasoned and average for an all-inclusive. Service is slow and not very well trained in all venues. Had to ask for knives, forks, and napkins. If you are a wine drinker beware: both red and white offered are horrible....but you can purchase others for 2-3x retail price. We bought a bottle at the Palma Real mall across the street, however, we were charged a $10 corkage fee by the resort. Bottled water is available everywhere.Recreation - for-fee motorized watersports offered by hotel. (Non-motorized are free). We went parasailing (2 for 20 mins for $99). Nice people and great service but took almost 2 hrs from the time that we were loaded onto a small boat to be transferred to the main one. Later in the week, we took a full day Santo Domingo tour (6:30am-8:30pm) that was an eye-opener. Much poverty outside the resort areas.One last comment. As these people do not make much money, please be kind and tip whenever possible. (One waiter told us that his wife and 2 children live 3 hours away and that he works 14 days at a time with 3 days off between 14 day shifts. )
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>