<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="5fe39ce27eb0aa94a949313423603bfa" url=""><![CDATA[Overpriced Hotel This is one of the newest hotel and also the biggest boutique hotel (280 rooms) in Singapore. However, one of the wing of the hotel is not ready yet, hence there are probably only 100+ rooms at the moment.You are able to choose from rooms of four ethnic themes. However, there is not much difference in the rooms except in the basic decor. The rooms had been renovated so it is completely different from the public housing blocks it is using.Had some problems with the check-in but was sorted out promptly. The manager was a bit snobbish too. The staff at the reception needs to improve on their service.Was not told there was a promotion for foot massage at the hotel. Had to ask a male staff at the reception for it in the evening. He was pretty rude and was only willing to give me one voucher despite I was staying with someone. Was able to get the vouchers from another lady.The staff for check-out was also not friendly too. Command of English was not good. The staff asked if I took anything from the fridge but the funny thing was that the fridge was not stocked and there is nothing for me to take.Found it strange that the reception had four-five staff at times and on other occasions there was only one staff.Overall, a number of staff (especially those at the reception) at the hotel was aloof. Only the chambermaids and a male staff (wore spectacles) was friendly. The male staff greeted guests every time he see them.The hotel is located at Tiong Bahru estate, you are actually living in the heartlands. The hotel is near a lot of nice eateries and is near to the Tiong Bahru market where you can try out local food at affordable prices. You can check out the seafood restuarant opposite the hotel. It is known for its seafood and pork ribs.Location is quite ok but it is a bit far from the MRT stations. You need to walk 10-15 mins to the nearest station (Outram or Tiong Bahru) or you can take a bus (2-3 stops away) too. The hotel is quite near to the business district as well as Chinatown. 5-10 mins drive away.There is a Cheers store at the hotel where you can buy your daily necessities and there is also a Japanese restaurant at the hotel. Room is really small and the bed is ok. Bathroom is small and there is no bathtub.There is a LCD TV in the room but very limited channels. No movie channels. There is not much view from the room too. The room does not provide bathrobe, slippers and the toiletries are lousy too. The fridge was empty. No problem with that as I dun usually get anything from there.There is no gym or swimming pool. Basically, there are no facilities at all. The roof top terrace is also not ready yet. The link bridge is not ready too.Price paid (S$230.39) is way too expensive for the location, and for the quality of the room. No breakfast is included for this price. Suspect the hotel is meant for tour packages as I saw lots of guests (mainly from China and India) checking in at various timeOverall, it was a very very disappointing stay. At this price, you can get a hotel in orchard or at a much better hotel around the area with full hotel facilities and breakfasts. Do check out my other reviews.The hotel did provide green apples for guests which I thought was one of the few positive points of my stay.Understand that the hotel is still at soft launch but at these prices, I expect something better. Can still hear drilling and knocking in the noon time.Believe the hotel claims to be 4* hotel but it is more like a budget hotel. You are better off staying at budget hotel which may have a better location and cheaper prices.If you do stay at the hotel, do check out the foot massage parlor near the lobby. It is quite good. The prices for the massages are decent and the staff are friendly too.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3d137953cf7028d3f973d100bb3f6165" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Stay Stayed for a few nights in a Harbour View Premier Room and it was definitely one of the best room I ever stayed in.Room was immaculately clean, spacious and the view from the room was excellent. Each side of the bed has a remote to control the mood lighting systems. The bathroom was amazing and the bath tub was huge. There is even a TV in bathroom! The hotel provides Hermes toiletries which was excellent. The hotel is also generous with the bottled water and have it placed everywhere.I also like the fact that the room has a separate cabinet for them to insert the mails, newspapers and toiletries without disturbing you.I am also pretty impressed by the stationary provided in the room. The hotel considers every detail to ensure that you have an excellent stay.In the evening time, the chamber maid will also prepare the room by laying out the beautiful slippers and play nice music in the room. Additional CDs are also provided in the room if you prefer other musics.If you hope to try out local food, just turn left after exiting the main lobby and walk straight. There is a famous Wan Tun noodle shop 10-15 mins away.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="92ea3bb25334ab98bccc8774d4aa2aab" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel (but discrimination agst the locals) I booked the hotel using the Starhub Rewards. The room was nice and the bed was great. The breakfast was ok and the room service was average.However, there was clear discrimination when we went to the lounge and the pool. No one ask us if we wanted a drink whereas the hotel staff was prompt to ask the foreigners (mainly caucasians). I guess There were a few other incidents that I noticed but I they realise the locals usually dun tip and they focus their attention on the foreigners.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fb1346d72a2447158d62d629bc32b219" url=""><![CDATA[Nothing much to do The Gold Coast hotel is defintely not a 5 star hotel and it is quite far from Kowloon and HK island. If you stay in HK and is in need of a short get away, you may consider this hotel. However, for tourists, the beach in HK is not worth a trip there.The Bad- The bell boy took a long time to bring the luggage to the room. Had to call the bell boy and describe our luggage before they bring it up.- The eateries at the hotel are quite expensive. The breakfasts are quite average too.- The room looks old and there are limited channels available on the TV.- Nothing much to do at the hotel. Can be quite boring. The 'shopping mall' near the hotel only has a few restaurants, eateries and a supermarket. Nothing much to shop. - Followed the instructions on the website but had some difficulties finding the bus stop. Remember to cross the road to find the bus-stop. The sign is too small for us to notice it.The Good:- The gardens are lovely and well maintained.- The room is quite spacious.- The bespectacled driver for the mini-coach was very good. Friendly and helpful. Did not manage to know his name. He is probably the best service staff I met in HK.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>