<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="23f3928a00cdd732b4f4eb28b5b83ba4" url=""><![CDATA[Noise, Noise, Noise Many other recent reviews have discussed the construction that is going on at this hotel. As of May 2008, it starts a 7 AM and goes until 6 PM. It is very loud and annoying - jackhammers, yelling and banging. If you plan to spend ANY time in your room between those hours (like trying to do some work or recover from jetlag), I strongly suggest you find an alternative hotel. It is centrally located, but my driver couldn't even find it because the facade was covered. Renovation in the lobby is complete, but it doesn't make sense. Right now you have to carry your bags up and down several stairs to get to the room elevators. This seems like a serious design flaw. (Maybe they are building other, more convenient elevators that just aren't finished). The rooms are very small and cramped, but thats to be expected in Amsterdam. It meets American standards for a 3-star, but just barely. There isn't a robe in the room and the bathrooms are very basic. I didn't even try breakfast (which was included in my room rate). The restaurant looks like a cafeteria in an old folks home. Maybe once the renovation is complete that will be different.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6fd0896cfefa69b312aa55d89e2987f6" url=""><![CDATA[You won't go wrong with Royal Park My husband and I stayed at the RPH during a 3-day trip to Tokyo. It's located in a more business district of Tokyo, but access to both metro and other train lines are walking distance. If you are looking to be in the middle of the scene, this is not the hotel for you. But if you want a nice base to explore Tokyo from, this is a solid choice.I was a little confused about the difference between the TAC (Tokyo Air Terminal) and Tokyo Central Train station. The TAC is a bus depot - it's attached to the RPH via a covered walk way. The busses to Narita are efficient (like every thing in Japan). However, if you take the train in from Narita, you will NOT arrive at the TAC, but rather at the Central Train Station. Its a 700 yen cab from the train station to the RPH.We were checked in promptly. I had requested a king/non-smoking room. The only one available was on the Executive Floor - so they kindly accommodated us. Except, they asked us not to use the executive lounge, which I thought was strange. The room was small (they had told us it would be at check-in) but for Japan hotels is was fine. Bed was comfortable. The bathroom mirror was heated so it never completely fogged up. The buffet downstairs has a huge selection of western food. Its pricey, but the food is good. Great Scott the basement bar is nice, quiet and a good spot for a drink if you arrive late. We had a little issue with the concierge initially, but when the assistant manager helped us - everything worked out.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="88c0459c3b2c75d730d01580680bf305" url=""><![CDATA[Good Tourist Hotel This is my second time to Tokyo, last time I was here as a tourist and this time for business. Roppongi is a very touristy area, and not very convenient location if you are here for meetings or work.The hotel itself is wonderful. All of the other reviews are spot on. I'll try not to be repetitive. Except to say that the service is impeccable, the concierge is the best I have every had. Rooms are spacious and deliver that Japanese aesthetic. Just a few negatives -There aren't any floors higher than 20 or 21, so if you are looking for that Tokyo view, you won't get it here, the breakfast buffet is a little lacking for a hotel of this caliber. (but again the staff almost makes up for it. The head chef would bring me my usual by the second day), the ambient temperature in the halls and the lobby are a little warm for my American-air conditioned-tastes, (kept about 76F/24C degrees)The positives (that haven't been mentioned) - Wireless is FAST, the meeting spaces are great and conference services are top notch, the black-out shade is the best, fitness center equipment is new and clean, the Japanese restaurant in the hotel (6 FL) is authentic.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="72b1141e2020378259132e66d010e46a" url=""><![CDATA[Can't go wrong at the St Reeg Room
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e5e0cb7ff9d96e9706ffca8c07b9f85d" url=""><![CDATA[Retro Berlin The Adlon is an interesting Kempinski property. The hotel is a total replica from the original which succumbed to bombs and fire and neglect during and after WW2. The building was completely rebuilt in 1997 after reunification as a perfect replica of the original. They even copied some of the poor room designs. Overall its a great hotel with excellent service and staff, beautiful facilities and the location is central [just steps away from The Brandenburg Gate, at the head of the Tiergarten and 1 KM from Potsdam Platz.] My gripes are little - the lights for the WC/Bathroom are in strange locations - outside the door. The room controls in in the night stand - which, unless you get the full room tour from your bellhop, you spend about 20 minutes looking for them. The wireless was fast, only a few English channels (CNN and BBC), laundry was done the same day. Fitness center was decent. Ate in the hotel restaurant - service was slow, but food was good. We had a 2-day business meeting in the hotel and the facilities were perfect. Hosted a cocktail reception in the Library which had a wonderful view of the Gate, and dinner was exceptional.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>