<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a7b67e4e1058ae001541123cf478de22" url=""><![CDATA[Disappointed. Parking a hassle, staff seems to be confused all the time. We stayed at the Equus because our son had to have surgery at Kapiolani. We stayed for 10 days so we needed someplace under $100. At $90 a night, we were surprised to see how nice the entry and decor was (although after climbing the 10 or 12 steps to get up to the lobby numerous times a day we were a little annoyed) and enjoyed how clean the room was. But the parking was HORRIBLE. If you have children do NOT stay here. You have to go down the elevator, down the flight of stairs that they have no elevator for, walk around the corner, through a parking lot, take another elevator into the parking garage, and THEN you can load all your stuff into your car. It seriously took us 20 minutes to leave or return each time. Then each night, at exactly 3:20, the air conditioner beeped about 7 or 8 times. Each time I reported it to the front desk, they said they would check on it. Everytime I asked about whether or not it had been fixed, they said they didn't know. Hmmm...If you can't keep track of what's fixed and what hasn't been fixed, what is the point of customers asking for something to be fixed? Just a waste of time. My 18 month old son woke up everytime it beeped and screamed for a few minutes. THEN...to top it off, I walked in while the cleaning people were there, just to grab something. The woman was wiping our cups out with a white washcloth! (I take it that it was one of ours, since I doubt that most cleaning companies use white hotel towels to clean rooms). After watching numerous dateline nbc-type specials on how hotels don't actually wash your cups anymore, I had told my husband not to use them. He thought I was just being paranoid. Hmmmm... After they left, I smelled both wine glasses (one we had eaten ice cream out of and the other we hadn't used.) One glass smelled faintly sweet with a slightly chemical odor, and the other smelled like nothing. The internet also didn't work (which was a huge disappointment since my husband needed to work from the hotel while we were gone for the surgery) and the parking was almost $20 a night (which made our $90 hotel room not so cheap after all). Basically, if you like climbing stairs, don't have young children or much luggage, and don't mind dirty glasses or not getting a straight answer about simple questions like when the internet is going to be working (we basically got the response of...It's not working to our question of When will the internet be working?), then it's worth staying here. After all, if you'll be at the beach all day, you may not notice these things when you come back. So for that, it is worth the price. But $17 parking when you could valet park at another hotel for $20? I would definitely pay more to stay in a hotel that has more amenities than save a few bucks and get a headache in return.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>