<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="5965706218495f7291bf80d88a6c4dbd" url=""><![CDATA[Great second option for Mexico City When in DF, I always stay at the Fiesta Americana, but on my last trip I waited until the last minute as always to book, and this time it was full, so I went for the next-closest hotel, which was the Camino Real. Food: the great thing about this hotel is that it has several restaurants, so a huge variety of options, and the room service menu includes a little from each restaurant. The La Huerta restaurant has amazing breakfasts. I have breakfast here sometimes even when I stay at the Fiesta Americana. I was lucky to get one of the rooms on the fifth floor, which have been remodeled and are pretty nice. A year or so ago, I was shown one of the older rooms and I really imagine staying there. Check before you book to see what type of room going to get. The great thing about this room compared to the FA is that they have this HUGE desk, big enough for two people to work at. The service was excellent. The gym is pretty good, except no stair stepper, which is really important to me. Also, no spa, or sauna, or steam room, which is disappointing, and a big plus for the Fiesta Americana. I still think go back to the FA on my next trip to DF, but the Camino Real is definitely a great second option.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6de0bfc28cbdd2fd0d63ac96dcd2cc19" url=""><![CDATA[Would definitely consider returning I ended up here after getting stuck without a hotel room at the Fiesta Americana and calling all around and finding NOTHING else in Mexico City. I never would have thought to book this hotel, because really not into huge, high rise chain hotels, but I would definitely stay here again. Location: Not bad, it was surprisingly fast to get around from this hotel. Maybe I was just lucky, but the traffic too bad when I had to get out and around. Service: Excellent. Room: I have no idea what type of room I ended up in (1515, I would ask for something like this if I end up booking this hotel again), but it was massive, really comfortable for working, which is what I usually end up doing all day long when in Mexico City. There was a large desk, large enough for two people to work comfortably. The bathroom was huge as well. Really a comfortable room. Food: Not bad. Not a huge variety, but it was okay. Spa: use it, but there is one. Gym: use it, but there is one, and it looks like a great one.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2fa762c6c2231f8bb9a79d50f9e94b43" url=""><![CDATA[Probably wouldn't return This is another hotel I have ended up at except that the other hotels I usually try to stay at in Mexico City were fully booked. Considering the value for the rates, I probably return. The room was pretty small considering the rate, and the small desk made it uncomfortable for two people to work in the room. I would definitely go with my usual Fiesta Americana or Camino Real instead. Location: ExcellentService: Pretty good, lots of mistakes with room service, but they were good about correcting errors. Internet connection: Great, no complaints at all. The wireless connection worked perfectly. Room: Kind of small, very small desk (only one person could work at a time at the desk). Food: Lots of variety, good food. Spa: use it, but I think there is one. Gym: use it, but there definitely is one.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>