<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="166bac11aeb1c6799a75793521bb5055" url=""><![CDATA[Ocean Blue - Great Time! We just returned from a week in Punta Cana at the Ocean Blue and had a better-than-expected-time, especially after reading some of the reviews here!We got a terrific last minute deal from Expedia (booked on Fri. left on Sun AM). Easy time checking in, asked for a room on the 2nd or 3rd floor and got a very nice room on the 3rd (Bldg. 7, Rm 7305) which overlooked the gardens and front walkways and to the left, the pools and ocean. The large veranda was a great place to have coffee in the AM. Lovely, spacious room with nice dark wood accents and furnishings, colorful bedspread on the king bed and futon. Nice marble tiled bathrm w/jacuuzi tub.The 2 pools are awesome, along with the swim-up bars! (Try a Miami Vice). Friendly bartenders made it fun and we met lots of people from all over, meeting them for drinks and dinner. It's a popular resort for Canadians, Germans, Americans, French Spanish. The buffet food was better than expected and I over-indulged in all the fresh fruits every meal. For b'fast there are several omelet, pancake stations and tons of choices. For lunch and dinner, the pasta stations are terrific. The desserts are pretty sweet but there's always ice cream. The specialty restaurants were so-so, (the Mexican restaurant puts what looks like cheese wiz on everything even tho I asked them not to - you have to remember English might not be totally understood altho it was amazing how many bartenders, etc. spoke several languages). Very nice atmosphere and we were eating 3 huge meals a day so were not going to complain. We had fun at the sports bar playing pool, and the coffee and desserts at Mike's Coffee Shop were excellent. I wished they were open before 10AM but oh well. We didn't try the extra cost restaurants since there were so many choices with price included.The decor and landscaping, pools and all buildings are just lovely. Yes, there are a few missing tiles in the pools, but we found everything spotless, the maid service excellent and loved the Lobby areas- just fabulous and a great place for a drink to meet people. The shows are pretty cheesy, as described in other reviews, but kids might like them. There's enough to do to stay busy: stretching/Yoga in the AM, water aerobics at noon, step at 4. Yes, they might not compare to your gym at home (certainly no comparison to our Les Mils programs at ours) but fun and necessary for us after over-indulging. We had no problem getting an umbrella chairs at any time by the pools. It was pretty windy at the beach so we only hung there one half day. We found the ocean pool temperatures perfect, altho one swim-up bar is in the shade so we stayed submerged while hanging there! The weather was picture perfect except for one afternoon-early-evening rain storm which was fun to watch from the bars or our veranda. An umbrella in the room was a nice touch.For the price we paid (last minute is incredible!) we were more than satisfied and will certainly recommend this resort, and probably return again. My only real complaint was that the bed was not real comfortable - if they upgraded the mattresses (we're spoiled with decent beds at home) it would really help. That would cinch a trip back for us.Oh and one other thing - LOSE the TIME SHARE people who nab you when you check in, insisting on breakfast to tell you about the resort! It was late, we had a delayed flight, were exhausted and alto suspicious, thought it just might be a quick info of what to do. We should have just said NO but they called and woke us the next morning. I finally insisted they tell us what it was about and they admitted it was a vacation plan. They'll try to nab you on your way into breakfast almost every day but it's easy to wave them off. If I were managing this resort I'd insist they either be upfront at the start about what they're trying to sell you, or better yet, be off premises. We're pretty good about choosing places and have heard too many horror stories about these companies going out of business, extra fees being charged, etc. to be interested in any plan. It was a small thing, but if you're like us and don't want to waste a precious minute of your well-earned vacation, be warned!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="20166b6e2cbd938869ce41fe015b2e87" url=""><![CDATA[Lovely Hotel We chose this hotel for it's location and good reputation and were not disappointed. Altho not perfect (the room was small you will hear hallway noises: doors closing, talking, etc). Luckily it was quiet on our floor by the time we went to sleep. It's a beautiful establishment. Lovely contemporary art work, plums and reds and modern-style furnishings. This seems to be the trend in many places we visit and it's nice!Our check-in was prompt and the concierge and staff helpful enough. No waiting for elevators but the hotel did not seem booked to the max.The small room was lovely and the bed was very comfortable. The large bath nicely appointed (except the antiquated hair dryer - a little surprising but worked OK.) Don't expect coffee makers or the like but do expect great towels, soaps, (1) robe and (1) pair of slippers. Cool decor. We hit the hotel bar after dining out (*see below) and it was fun but pricey. Expect this in downtown. The next morning we had a good breakfast in the hotel ($20 BreakFAST) which was huge. Great fresh fruit cup, toast/jam, scrambled eggs, sausage, bacon, French-pressed coffee (excellent) delicious fresh squeezed OJ. The eggs could have benefited from some chopped scallions or something. I'm sure next time we could ask. Way too much food - we should have split it!Note - The day before our arrival I had emailed the manager that it was our anniversary, was my veteran husband's first trip to DC but there was no acknowledge of this.Overall our stay was romantic and wonderful but next time we would only stay if we could nail a discount rate or package special. Very expensive and for that price you want special treatment.*BLUEPOINT RESTAURANT - A MUST! 1299 Pennsuylvania Ave NW 202 783 4545Recently opened, this was so good we ate lunch and dinner there in the same day! See our review under restaurants.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>