<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="947d1140471110a093c5178d31300f0a" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel, Poor Location Harbour View (just!)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a900f900d6f2c134913fb659f00f5022" url=""><![CDATA[Whats the Problem? Great location Having read some of the reviews of this hotel on here we seriously considered cancelling our booking but in the end decided to go for it. Were glad we did, dont know what all the fuss is about. The hotel is brilliantly located just a short walk from darling harbour. An easy walk to central station and the museum station.The bar and restaurant are nice and rooms are spacious. The staff pleasent and helpful (allowing us to check in early which was really helpful as we'd had an overnight flight.There is a shopping centre under the hotel and loads of bars around. We enjoyed our stay here and would recommend it to anyone.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="37f58f10091a3817b0980300b5b04152" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location but overrated hotel The main benefit of this hotel is the locationclose to the upper end of La Rambla and just by the Passeig de Gracia tube station and round the corner from the Gaudi House (very impressive by the way). We were however disappointed with the hotel. We found the staff on reception rather abrupt and unhelpful. The room was dark and the view from the window straight into an office is a building less than a few meters away. There was no bar to speak of in the hotel, and although there was a very limited bar menu scattered around the tables in the foyer area but there was never any sign of anyone serving drinks. There was a guy playing the piano in the reception area that made for a nice area but there was never anyone around to hear it as there was no bar.Overall its not a terrible hotel but overpriced in my opinion and while we loved barcelona i think we'd choose another hotel next time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>