<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="0dbe6e7615b203bd43c5880907198058" url=""><![CDATA[Closed for Renovation My husband and I celebrated our 5 year anniversary at the Princess, Sept 2 to Sept 9. On our last day, guests were being moved to the Bavario since the Princess was closing for renovation on Sunday the 11th. The Princess was also very empty. We are from Orlando, Florida and are big beach people. We thought we could deal with heat. It was unbelievably hot the week we stayed. The night of our arrival we had to eat at the buffet restaurant since we had not made reservations. There are no paddle fans in the buffet restaurant or the lobby and we had to use our napkins to keep the sweat out of our eyes while we ate. My husband also had to wear long pants to dinner once we had made our reservations. It was terrible to see him sweating all the way to dinner at 8:00 at night.Ahhh...the buffet! This is the only bad thing I have to say about the resort. The breakfast buffet was the same just about every day. They have a made to order omlette bar, waffels, etc. But after 2 days the rest of our breakfast was toast and fruit. Lunch was not much better and room service (ham cheese sandwich) was even worse. The evening restaurants were good. The two (tex mex and Italian) located at the Princess were very good. We also ate at 3 restaurants at the sister resort that were also good (La Cava, Sombrero and Chinese). Our appetites were not up to par since the heat was so bad. Toward the end, we booked any restaurant we could get as long as it was air conditioned.The people...could not have been more fantastic. The majority of the guests were from Spain. We speak very little spanish, communicating with them, although sometimes difficult, was a pleasure. They were so friendly and we made some very good friends. For the staff, 4 became very dear to our hearts. They went out of their way to make us happy, be friendly, and to help me work on my Spanish. The ladies of the lobby bar could not have been more wonderful. The best part of our entire trip was getting to know them. Please remember that a tip goes a long way. Change in US dollars is very difficult to get so we took $100 in ones and $100 in $5 and $10. Just their sharing of their culture was well worth a tip.The beach was beautiful. The sand is very soft and light which adds to the turquoise color of the water. There was never a problem with chairs at the beach or the pool. Excursions - we did the Lobster Tour and the Snorkel with Dolphins tour. As I stated earlier, most of the guests were from Spain. We were the only people that spoke english on the Lobster Tour and I thought the bus ride was going to be difficult. By the time we got off the bus later that day, everyone kissed and hugged us goodbye. Our television showed video of the Snorkel with Dolphins tour. The tour was so Not what the TV showed. Once on site, they suggest you don't even wear a mask and snorkel. The only thing different between your general swim with dolphins and the snorkel activity is that they let you float free in the center of the dolphin pool and you can pet them when they swim by.The room was great. Never a problem with water or power. We were in the 5000 series which is the building closest to the beach. I will say that out of all the people that we met, either one or both of them got sick during their stay, as did we. I tried to blame it on the Rum, but it seemed to happen to many people. Please remember to pack any medication you may need. I would not return to this resort since there are many other places that I haven't visited. They would also have to do something about the buffet food. On our last day, we actually celebrated that we didn't have to look at it any more!They estimate that the resort will open again for the Holidays. If you have any questions, you are welcome to contact me. I'd be happy to help.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>