<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="82a1467509136e1f6b870ec96e1ef851" url=""><![CDATA[Good value and location. We stayed here for one night and found the hotel to be a real bargain and very adequate for our needs. It's also in a perfect location just a few blocks from the French Quarter and Harrah's. We booked through hotels.com and only paid $92 for a deluxe queen room. We had a view of the street, reasonably sized room, and a very large and well-equipped bathroom with a very roomy walk-in shower. The radio was playing New Orleans jazz when we entered the room. They had a collection of jazz CD's available to play but the CD function wasn't working on our radio. But it was a nice gesture and I'm sure they would have corrected the problem if we had asked. We had stayed at this hotel previously (pre-Katrina) and paid more than double for the same quality room at that time. So it is obvious that New Orleans needs our business and our support. A previous reviewer mentioned something about a lack of valet parking. They did have valet parking at a cost of $30. We could have parked cheaper at a nearby garage but it wouldn't have been as convenient. After we called for our car, it was waiting for us by the time we reached the lobby. All the staff members were very friendly and helpful. We were even allowed to check in early at 11 am because the hotel wasn't busy. If I return to New Orleans I will definitely return to International House.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="785bb89634a6f691b597d3f54d150336" url=""><![CDATA[Location, location, location! We booked this hotel for a two-night stay prior to our departure on a cruise. We had requested an ocean view room, and ended up with not only an ocean view from our balcony, but also a view of Diamond Head from the walkway outside our door. The hotel is older, so our bathroom was not very plush, but perfectly adequate. The bed and the bedroom were fine - king sized bed with good mattress and ample storage for our clothes. We had a small balcony that looked out sideways to Waikiki Beach. This hotel also features Breakfast on the Beach whereby you can take your little lunch pack down to the breakfast buffet, fill it up, and either go to the beach, on an excursion, or eat it there at poolside. We paid more than we usually do for hotels (we are usually budget travelers) but still found the price was right for this location. If you want to be right on Waikiki Beach, this is a very good choice. The only glitch was the elevators, which were set, for security purposes, to run with room key-card activation. Many people had trouble figuring out how to use them, some even resorting to using the stairs. We finally got the hang of it after a few failed attempts.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>