<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="a21fc66232ea249467310b2ee17d6df0" url=""><![CDATA[warning - is very addictive - perfect, heaven, a week of paradise! wed
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e59f7d8548bcc198996dad769958d8e7" url=""><![CDATA[Not worth the money I just returned from a 1 week stay at the Barcel Punta Cana, with my husband, sister and her boyfriend. We are between the ages of 22 - 33.I would like to start off by saying that this is my 3rd time in Punta Cana and the ONLY time I was ever disapointed.If you plan to go on holidays and enjoy some good food and rest, do NOT go to the Barcelo.FOOD:The food here is HORRIBLE!There is hardly a variety, the same stuff every day, undercooked meat, brown salad which taste funny, soups taste off... Terrible, just TERRIBLE. My husband is not a picky eater at all, and even he struggled to find anything to enjoy. We lived off of hotdogs (which were orange in the middle and odd tasting), frechfries, and bland tasting pasta.ROOMS:We booked the ocean view delux, and were told that our rooms would be in the new building, upgraded rooms, jacuzi tub, seperate stand in shower, ect...long story short... We did not get these rooms.The rooms we ended up in are ugly, run down and in some desperate need of upgrading and a paint job.We complained to the front desk and they stated that we never paid for the nicer upgraded rooms, which surely we DID, we complained to the manager whom was completely RUDE to us, very dismissive and simply told us - nope, you did not pay for the upgraded rooms, you are not getting the upgraded rooms... It was very frustrating.On our last day there I found a cockroach in our room ... Lovely.Then the next morning I noticed that a bunch of rooms had signs/notices up on their doors stating that they were going to be fumigated by the pest control.These rooms are not sound proof at all. You can hear every single sound comming from the hallway, other people balconies, the pool, the pool bar. Since we were overlooking the pool and pool bar, we were kept up every single night by people partying at the pool bar until almost 6am most days. I am totally cool with people partying on their vacation, but the way the resort is set up, the noise really travels and becomes quite loud at night. If you are looking for a more quiet time, I would recomend you request a room NOT facing the poor/ocean side.SERVICE:Service at the Barceo is VERY VERY SLOW!!!If you plan on having a drink with your meal, you are better off getting it from the lobby bar yourself, rather then ask a server to bring one for you - because you will never recieve it.So many times we would ask for a drink, and the server would simpy not bring it - and so we would have to get up in the middle of our meal, go to the lobby and get our own drink.We found the staff and servers here to be very rude and ignorant.No one ever said hola or even smiled. Anytime you asked for something you almost felt bad because they made it very clear that they did not want to do anything for you. We even had eyes rolled at us a few times.One server was cleaning our table while we had drinks in the lobby, and she wipped the pile of ashes from the ashtray all over my friends khakki pants - she looked right at him, then walked away - how rude!POSSITIVES:The resort itself is very nice and cleanThere is two beauitful pools and a swim up bar which wasn't usually too busy.The beach is beauitful, with perfect white sand, blue ocean, clean and has plenty of chairs, BUT very limited spots for shade - same goes for the pool - not much shade. You have to get down very early to reserve your spot.The main pool is quite loud with music and activities, but the 2nd, newer pool is much more quiet. We enjoyed both pools.You are at the end of a line up of other resorts, and it is pretty eatay to take a walk down the beach and sneak into them to check things out.We did not see any weddings at this resort, and do not really see where they would do them. They do not have a wedding gazebo or anything like that.Overall, I would rate our stay a 1.5 or 2 out of 5I would never never go back - not even for free - the food was just way too bad and I could not stand the rudeness from the staff.If you want a good vacation, spend a little bit more and go to the Bahia Principe in Punta Cana - I went there last year for my wedding and what an AMAZING resort.I have also stayed at the Riu Taino in Punta Cana, and that also was an great resort.It really is a shame because the grounds are very nice - but bad service and food really ruined it for us.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>