<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="ba0cd661ce5f2d4e14de091624275e6a" url=""><![CDATA[great location The location of this hotel is perfect, near the centre with shops and bars, just far away from the busiest area so that noise levels at night doesnt keep you awake. I chose this hotel from tripadvisor reviews as it had a high score. I had booked superior rooms, to have balcony and whirlpool bath. The rooms were adequate and very clean. I had trouble operating the whirlpool bath - the reception staff were not very helpful with this. When I found the instructions - it was fine - the instructions were a little out of sight!!Breakfast charge was 15 euros - In my opinion it was poor- along with the service. The food on the hot counter was cold. There were four of us - we decided to have breakfast at a local cafe for the rest of our stay - much better and at half the price. There was no bar lounge - the bar was in the restaurant with just two stools - missed coming in and chilling out over a cool drink or coffee.The plus for this hotel is the location, and I would recommend the hotel for a short stay.4* is perhaps being very kind - I would of thought more like 3*. Madrid is a colourful and vibrant city - we had a great break.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ea5ffc98ffd242cf29ab6f383e2dcce6" url=""><![CDATA[Good Location The Rooms - clean but compact. Only using as a base so not that bothered by the size. Bed was very comfortable - and linen and towels in good condition and clean. Facilities in rooms was good. Breakfast - not so good. When we arrived for breakfast we were seated and immediately they came with orange juice. We thought we would order from the A La Cartre menu - but we were not asked and their continental breakfast was soon brought to the table. When our friends joined us we explained to them to make sure the waitress knows you want to order from the A La Carte. This they did and placed their order, but it never arrived.No apologies from the staff.Next morning we had breakfast in a nearby cafe - much better!The Restaurant Flo attached to the hotel seemed very popular so we tried it. It was good but the quality was reflected in the prices.I suppose you get what you pay for. Reception check in/out was smooth and efficient.For a 4* hotel I would of liked to have had the facility of a bar to sit and have a drink or coffee - the only bar was in the restaurant with pull up stools.I would go back there - but not my first choice.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8ff7ddad57d4a668ddfad0344c8df855" url=""><![CDATA[Glassed Bathroom March 2006 - 4 of us stayed here for a long weekend, we had adjoining rooms which was great. Check in was a little slow as was check out - staff were friendly but slow. The bar staff went out of their way to make our stay memorable, nothing was too much trouble for them. As all hotels the drinks here were more expensive than bars - about 40% more. Breakfast was not included in our rate-we were charged 16 euros each. The selection was fresh fruit, cold meats and cheese, hot grill, cereals,toast,muffins etc. It was as one would expect from a 4* hotel.Dont get too excited about the swimming pools, they are very small but welcoming for a quick dip after a long day sightseeing. This hotel is a 10 euro taxi ride into the centre. Near the hotel was a shopping mall. If I return to Barcelona for a short stay I would choose a hotel a little nearer the centre, but this is an individual choice.The hotel bedroom was very clean, and the bathroom a little different with a glass partition dividing this area from the bedroom - we were on a high floor with spectacular views of the city.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>