<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="f42b6f80a839904cd9744170705b4b79" url=""><![CDATA[Loved the Hipster Belmont Hotel Although i do live in the same city as this hotel I decided to celebrate my birthday there! I am glad i did. This hotel is on top of a hill in an underdeveloped area with great potential.If you are used to brand new, squeaky clean, plush hotels, i'd read below before i make a decision to stay a whole weekend:First off, valet, it's free! Even for guests. You will check in and since some of the rooms are located in different areas the Valet will drop you off with their golf cart. The hotel is atop of a hill and spread out. It is sort of like it's own little village so there are no hallways!Belmont took this old 40's building and rennovated it but left its charachter in place. It has some of the original fixtures, tile, and concrete walls. Props to the owner for leaving it that way but modernizing it with the decor and furniture. I rented the loft suite! I cannot say that i've been anywhere that had a view like this. You could practically touch the Dallas skyline with your fingertips. It's gorgeous!It had 2 floors, downstairs was not large at all only to fit a day bed and wall length desk, flat screen, countertop with sink and a bathroom with a stand up shower. Upstairs was much larger, queen size bed, daybed, wall mounted flat screen and bathroom with standup shower.i read that someone thought it was in a sketchy area, not true. Why would you even walk off the grounds, it has everything you need!The hotel was very accomodating about having guests over. It has the BarBelmont which had flawless service, and a skyline view as well! Like i said i stayed in the loft so i'm not sure if everyone will have a view like ours so ask to be placed in a suite that will. Few more tips:infinity pool, ice machines scattered among the property, landscape was pretty, 5-10 minutes from downtown, 15 min from greenville ($18-20 cab ride one way). CliffCafe for food service. would i stay again? Already thinking about it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="89ee7436b6330f13e2f3e925b1f4211d" url=""><![CDATA[ESJ Towers, an honest review to make your decision easier Overall the experience was not terrible, nor did it curve my enjoyment in San Juan. There are a few things that i was dissapointed in but I'd rather start off with the positive. I did feel their customer service was great. Nice happy greetings when you enter, cab service at the drop of a dime. At checkin we were told that we had to pay an extra charge of $40.00/room if we wanted maid service. If you choose not to use the maid service you simply have to walk downstairs to trade in old towels for new ones. (as well as sheets and pillowcases)The rooms are a little out dated as far as interior design. After a long day of touring around the city i didn't let that bother me. It is a place to lay your head until the next day's long excursion. The pictures on the website speak truly.There is a restaurant called the Happy Apple downstairs, a grocery store, game room with pool tables, a cocktail bar, free internet access room with 3 computers available and a workout room.The Hotels is on one of the most nices beaches, Isla Verde. The water is georgous, blue as blue can be and wonderful sand. There is no bar service so be sure to take a portable cooler down with you. There might be small portables that will sell you drinks but you can always walk about 10-20 feet further down to another hotel who will sell it to you.Here is a list of things you should know:`The Pool closes at 7pm 7 days a week.`There is not beach access from the hotel after 7, I believe b/c of saftey reasons.`you have to walk down the street to find your own beach access after 7pm. (I'm not sure if you can even come back to the hotel beach area)You do have to walk downstairs through the underground parking garage to gain access to the beach, it's not as complicated as others have said.The pool has no swim up bar but a small cabana that sells beer and pina colodas, hot dogs and nachos only.`you do have a small but useful kitchenette, refridgerator, small electric stove, microwave, coffee maker, and average sink.If you are used to luxurious interiors or upscale dining, this is not the place for you. You are next to El San Juan Hotel and Casino The Intercontinental which is a small walk away.Bus stop is right about a block away. There are small restaurants and a grocery store (puebla) within walking distanceI hope this helped! Have fun and enjoy SanJuan!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>