<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="1a782b5644a14d492e73b3cffef169ed" url=""><![CDATA[good for the price My boyfriend and I stayed here for one night in October. We were, as it seems many people are, upgraded to a duplex even though we had booked a standard room. That was a nice touch. However, the bed was in a loft where the ceilings were very low and the air was very stuffy and too warm. (It was unseasonably warm for October.) We couldn't open the balcony doors because of street noise and safety concerns, so we tried to put the air conditioner on low, but it would only blow hot air. When I inquired about this at the desk, twice, the staff told me this was the hotel setting and would not explain further. I overheard another guest complaining about this as well, so something must have been wrong, but they did not apologize or make any attempt to remedy the situation, which was frustrating and made for a very uncomfortable night's sleep before our flight. The design is funky and the room had great light. The very design-y stairs were cool to look at, but I would not want to climb them after an evening of drinking! As others have mentioned, while the design looks cool now, it seems like it will not age well. It's very cheaply constructed, which is why it's so affordable for a city center hotel, which we appreciated, but it will probably be pretty banged up in a year or two. Also, the bathroom is teeny tiny. I kept banging my elbows against the shower glass trying to wash my hair. It's pretty much the exact size of a tall person. Toiletries smelled nice, though.Fantastic location, easily accessible to Plaza Mayor, metro, other central sights. Free Internet access was a big perk, especially given the low price of the room. I also liked that you were rewarded with a low rate for booking 30 days or more ahead on the hotel website--we paid only 108 Euros for the room, which included breakfast. Breakfast was plentiful. Nothing hot, but I don't like hot things for breakfast anyway. We ate fresh fruit, yogurt, tortilla, fresh juice, coffee, and were very pleased with the selection. The heating problem was a bummer, and hopefully it has since been fixed. But the location is great for the price, and it was clean and spacious (other than the bathroom).
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>