<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="16bde63e0c2e53e9b0bd7cb14c66de0d" url=""><![CDATA[Great location! We had the rare opportunity to stay in three different room types in this hotel! I was there for business, and my husband came along for fun. So we started in a standard room with no view. Actually, the view was an ugly courtyard with air conditioner units. But the room was fine. Typical hotel room, and we didn't experience any of the noise others have encountered at the hotel. Good amount of space, had a table and chair. Very polite wait staff, pretty good buffets at Cafe One. But the location was great. Every night, we'd wander the streets of Causeway Bay and soak in the electric lights and lively crowds. You're close to the subway, which we took everywhere. It's very safe and easy to use - and sooo much faster than cabs. Anyways, after my work was done, we stayed for the weekend and upgraded rooms to a Deluxe Standard with Harbour/City views. The city views were magnificent! So much better than the ocean, even. And this room seemed to have been recently remodeled. Cool glass walls around the bathroom (there is a shade if you need privacy), comfy bed, plenty of space. We did experience some noise on our last night in this room, however. We called the front desk and were informed that we were under an event room, so they upgraded us to a suite for our final night! We moved, even though we really liked our room. And I must say, we prefered the Deluxe Room over the Suite. The suite had tons of space. A separate sitting area with flat screen TV. The bedroom is bigger, and there were one and half baths, a stand alone bathtub. So there is TONS of room. However, it was not renovated like our previous room. There was cheap fake wood-like panelling and it was just not very nice. Great view, but no better than our other. It was great to have the space, but unless you need it, opt for the Deluxe Room for the money. Overall, we loved the Park Lane and would stay again. Not fancy, but very nice, terrific service, great location. Oh - another tip. Some Korean friends of mine were visiting and shared a gem with us - near the hotel is a massage place called The Big Bucket. The hotel didn't even know it. It's totally legit (just massages) and cheap. It was like $35 for an hour long massage. My husband had a body massage and I had a long foot massage - amazing! Great way to end a long day of shopping at the Jade Market!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>