<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="6cab155c747e3f7ae3917fe138bc0c7d" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location This is an average hotel, in a GREAT location. Our stay got off on a rocky start when we found out that the roll away bed we had reserved would cost an additional $20 per night. We were also only provided with breakfast for three persons when our reservation was for 4. After taking the matter up with the hotel manager, we were given the breakfast for the fourth person in our room and were not charged for the roll away bed.At a first rate hotel we would not have had these issues to begin with. I found it somewhat odd that the front desk personel had buttons on wanting to make our stay a 10 but could not or would not do anything to take care of our issue until I requested a manager.For the most part during our stay I found the front desk people not very friendly. They would say hello, but only if you spoke to them first. The concergie was very helpful as was the bell staff.Our 3rd floor room was very clean and pretty quiet at night even though we overlooked the city street below.The true beauty of this hotel was the location. A short walk to the Wharf Pier 39 one way and a couple blocks to the cable car stop. We did alot of walking and found it very easy to get around. We would stay at the Hilton again, it was clean and convenient. But the service just is not what you would expect at a Hilton.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f80af29ab5af0bf4b47706ad2b223778" url=""><![CDATA[Very Good Pre Cruise Hotel This is a very good hotel. The desk and bell staff were excellent! The room large and modern, complete with a flat screen tv and an internet terminal at no additional charge. I must say that the beds were the most comfortable hotel beds I can remember. The hotel is obviously upscale and you pay for it. But as in most things you usally get what you pay for.My only negative comments and the reason I didn't rate the hotel excellent would be the terrible service outside by the pool bar. It took forever to get a cocktail. For some reason they had to be ordered through the outside bartender and brought out from inside the hotel by wait staff, and wait you did. All things considered, I would stay here again in a heartbeat. I would just go to the brew pub next door for drinks.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>