<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7c53470d6700b9dd5ae12f74567c9f1f" url=""><![CDATA[Great bed at the Anantara My husband I stayed at the Anantara Seminyak Resort Spa for two weeks + in Oct/Nov, 2008. The reception area was unusual, being two desks in an open area. The reception staff (Erna) was very polite and took us to our suite to explain the way things worked. The expresso machine was a nice touch but we never enjoyed a cup of coffee together as it made only one cup at a time. We stayed in an ocean view room and could not fault the suite or the view. I enjoyed the jacuzzi on the balcony until I turned it on when the stench of drains spoiled the effect and the ambience. I think the bed was the best part of our holiday as it was the most comfortable imaginable We enjoyed the breakfast with the addition of eggs offered a different way every morning ( very delicious )The staff in the restaurant in particular Komang and Ari made our breakfasts very enjoyable I must say the pool was a disappointment as the only seating offered was beanbags. The lounges were so far away and the walk to get there needed footwear as the wood was so hot The restaurant tables were where the lounges should have been. Perhaps they could have used the area for the tables in the evening. Another thing was the lift which had buttons to the 4th floor. We were on the 5th floor so pressed 4 and supposed we had to walk up one floor. Not so. The lift didn't move and other guests told us we had to press 3 to get to 5. Which was ok when we understood. On the last day we had paid extra (well over $200) for late check out to 6pm (6 hours). We had clothes strewn all over the place as one does when packing, imagine our horror when we returned to the room at 2.30pm to pack shower and found staff had stripped the bed, removed the towels and were cleaning amidst our things. Not a good end to our holiday
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>