<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="d20d5fb73815cf614021203ca16d6e69" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Hotel We found this hotel to be wonderful in Venice. Sandro, Walter and the rest of the staff are wonderful and run a great hotel. It is located in a quiet neighborhood, close to a vaperetto stop and just off the grand canal. It is a reasonable walk to activities around the Rialto Bridge (5 to 10 min) and St. Mark's Square (10 to 15 min). We enjoyed the short walk from all of the crowds of Venice to the quiet of the hotel - it felt like we were on vacation from all of the touristy-ness of Venice.The staff had excellent maps of Venice along with great recommendations for dinner. They were most helpful with reservations. Also, Sandro went out of his way to help us confirm our hotel reservation in the next city that we visited. The service from the staff was top notch.The hotel was renovated quite recently (within the last 3 or 4 years) and it is in very nice shape. Breakfast is in a beautiful courtyard and is a typical European breakfast. Hot coffee or tea are served along with fruit, cold cereals, yogurt, rolls and jams. It was a great way to start our day.We stayed in a standard room for one night (140 euros) and a superior room for two nights (160 euros). The difference between the rooms is the room size and the view or lack of a view. I felt that the superior room was definately worth the extra cost for a bit of a view and the extra room. If possible, I would recommend room #5 (with a balcony), with room #6 being a second choice. Ask about the room views as you book your room.The bathrooms were big enough, but we're talking about European bathrooms. The bed was comfortable and we had all that we needed in the room.I would recommend this hotel for the staff, the location, the rooms and the relative value (for Venice). I would recommend against this room if you feel a need to be located close to the Rialto Bridge or St. Mark's Square (after trying to convince you to enjoy the walk and stay away from the traffic).Overall, we would highly recommend the Hotel al Ponte Mocenigo. We truly enjoyed our stay there and if we go back to Venice, we would likely stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>