<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="a7f80cd204d1d95d73abcef3ff1ff686" url=""><![CDATA[Fine hotel Having recently stayed in a couple of small, idiosyncratic French hotels I was ready to dislike this example of large, corporate, standardised fare- but I have to admit staying here for the bookfair was a very pleasant experience.The huge views from the thirtieth floor room, the clean, welcoming room (six pillows on the bed- what a treat!), helpful staff everywhere; I can't really pick fault. The breakfast room was also a delight: call me naive and untravelled, but I've never had the opportunity to have steak and roast pork for breakfast (along with all the more traditional stuff) and couldn't resist. A tip for those attending events at the messe just across the road: if the taxis are as in short supply outside the hotel for you as they were for us, hop on the tram down to the central station just a few stops away and all will be well, with loads of taxis and not too many people after them.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8c9f07dd471b4716bf128f3eaaaf5ce5" url=""><![CDATA[Great conference hotel Last year at the Frankfurt bookfair I stayed at the Marriott (fine hotel, see separate review) but on balance I think this was better: only a ten minute walk to hall 8 for us English speakers, the hotel itself not to be faulted on hospitality, cleanliness, etc., in spite of what other reveiewers might say. The building is striking: a giantlozenge pushed into a tall modern office block. Check-in was pleasant and professional; the lifts numerous and quick at all times; my room on the 14th floor clean, simple and with a rather awesome view, for those squeamish about heights, of the western end of the city.Bathroom perfect, though with bizarre/fashionable red rose wallpaper and window through to the main room; room perfect, with the exceptionof a wardrobe designed for elves rather than humans, so little storage space was there in it. The bar was convenient and service good. The restaurant- breakfast time, at least- was full of helpful staff and the breakfast buffet awesome in its choice of meals, everywhere between healthy and amazingly meat product-filled. This is not a family hotel. It's not a hotel for tourists who want towalk out into the old town of frankfurt. It's not for those who want idiosyncratic, old-fashioned charm. It's modern, professionally run and- I thought- well designed for a business clientele.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>