<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="717c1a0351068cd877c37d1bbe264c77" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect Stay. Amazing Staff. Highly Recommended. Avoid L'Open Tour though. I will reiterate what everyone else has said about the Hotel Duret. My family of 6 just stayed there in 2 spacious rooms. The bathrooms look they were totally remodeled just yesterday - sparkling clean and modern. The elevator is a bit small as is typical of boutique European hotels. The furnishings were comfortable and the colors bright and pleasant.Other than the location which was wonderful (as others have said, a block from the Metro from where you can get anywhere), the desk staff makes this hotel an amazing experience particularly for Americans. Their English is excellent, and they continually go way out of their way to be helpful - mapping Metro routes, looking up bus routes and times, booking restaurant reservations, helping with itineraries. I can't say I've ever had the pleasure of such an outstanding cadre of personal assistants. I highly, highly recommend this hotel. But while I have your attention, a couple of other conclusions from mistakes I made: 1. Do NOT book the L'Open Tour hop-on-hop-off bus. While it's a nice idea, in practicality it was a huge waste of money and an even worse waste of time. The four routes do cover most of the common destinations in Paris; however, you'd better not be in a hurry to get anywhere, because each route has something like 10 to 20 stops, and the driver stops for 20 - 30 minutes at each stop, gets off the bus, has a smoke, or flat out disappears. We were stuck in front of the Open Tours office for 30 minutes with the motor running while the driver disappeared. It took us 90 minutes to get from Hotel Duret to Notre Dame. The next day we did the same trip on the Metro in 10 minutes, including the time it took to walk from the hotel to the Metro station. The drivers are also incredibly rude. I booked the Open Tour for 6 people for 2 days and we used it for half a day and realized it was not intended to be a mode of convenient transportation. The Metro is very intuitive and covers the whole city. Also, we got the Rail Europe museum passes - also a big waste of money. We couldn't possibly have spent, in 5 days, the amount of money it cost for the pass by paying individual admission to the museums. Plus, the benefit of not having to wait in line is simply false. You don't wait in line to get a ticket if you have the pass, but you wait in sometimes an even longer line to get in (waiting with everyone else who has the passes).And finally, get the Hotel Duret staff to explain the French restaurant checks. They are designed to confuse, in that the prices for each meal item have embedded in them a portion attributed to service and taxes. The check totals all the food items, and then separately reports the service and taxes as another line item, in spite of the fact that these amounts have been embedded in the food prices. So you'll likely be duped to pay the check amount, then the service (paying again what you've already paid), and then loading on a tip, which you've also already paid. We overpaid for a couple days before Michael at the Hotel Duret front desk enlightened us.So - stay at the Hotel Duret and you'll be made very happy by highly attentive and friendly concierges, who will treat you like family.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>