<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="3eb62751dd99a28ff5ab27f732a51b1c" url=""><![CDATA[great beach, pool, hotel, people--but queasy stomachs hit 5 out of 8 Our group of 5 adults and 3 older teens visited the Dominicana from April 14-22. This is the 5th all-inclusive we have stayed at. We traveled with Apple on a non-charter flight. Apple was very efficient, waiting for us after our very short trip through immigration, with our own 8 people mini-van. Our check-in packets were ready at the hotel; without asking we had been upgraded to 4 rooms in the Bavaro side cottages. The rooms and grounds were clean and kept up well--my daughter reported watching a maid take a full half hour to clean her room. We left $2 tips daily and our requests for extra water, beer, wash clothes were met with a smile. There were no mosquitos to speak of--spraying was going on constantly. The reservation system for the specialty restaurants was not too bad, at least you didn't have to get up at 7 a.m. and wait in a long line. We really enjoyed the steak house and the non-reservation Star Rock Cafe. The gourmet restaurant was a disappointment--dry lobster, no melted butter, just not that special. We enjoyed the ice cream bar by the beach and the cafe by the beach and pool was handy, though the gristle burgers wre not our favorite. We found all the staff to be friendly and accomodating, they really wanted people to have a good time. Beer and drinks were available easily in many places. You could actually get food at 2:30 a.m. if you wanted.The college age boys really enjoyed the small casino as they are not old enough to gamble at home. They actually made a few dollars.The beach and pools were great, though one had to have an early morning person put out towels at either the beach or one of the pools by 7:30 a.m. or you couldn't get chairs. The no-saving chairs rule is not enforced. There was a shortage of catamarans--you had to book for the next day, which might not be when you wanted to go. The weather was great--hot but not uncomfortable.We took the Kon-Tiki snorkel party boat--shoould have taken the Marinarium I guess as we only snorkeled an hour, in a very limited area, and were required to either wear a life vest or carry a noodle. Never been forced to do that before. While the dancing and music were fun, we did want more snorkeling. Apple was great about changing our reservations at the last minute when one of our party became seriously ill. Should have paid in dollars on the spot--when it showed up on my credit card the conversion rate made it about $10 a person more than advertised and I was charged a $15 currency converson fee.Because we had an early morning flight, we did not have much of a problem going through customs and immigration at the airport. In fact, Apple could have picked us up half an hour later and we would have had no problem. Now the main problem. Five of our group got stomach cramps and diarrhea, though we avoided the water, (plentiful bottled water was provided in the rooms) raw vegetables and salads as we always do. Perhaps the water in the dining rooms was not safe. One of our group became so ill she had to be taken to the (fortunately modern) hospital by ambulance. There is a 24 hour clinic on the premises and it was in use. Quite a few people besides us had at least queasy stomachs. While some of this has occurred before in Mexico, nothing like on this trip. This put a damper on many activities and left us with a negative feeling about the experience. We felt the food in the buffet was the least varied and tasty of any of the 5 all-inclusives we have gone to. One does not expect a gourmet meal at an all-inclusive but the buffet food and the upset stomachs were the low point.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>