<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="b5df4ece1e040f3bbaf6afa767c6bf10" url=""><![CDATA[Please Don't Go!! Call Your Travel Agent Immediately!! First of all stayed in many DR resorts (Riu Palace, Caribe Club Princess twice, Palladium Bavaro twice, Sunscape Punta Cana Grande, IFA Villas Bavaro etc. I even stayed the week before at a wonderful 4 star resort in Mexico before traveling to the DR. My resort choices over the years range in their ratings from 3 stars to 6 stars. I have also visited all-inclusives all over the Caribbean. been faithful to Apple Vacations because their Apple ratings are usually accurate and our experiences in the resorts have been relatively flawless and enjoyable. Something usually perfect but we take the bad and are able to make the best of it in most cases. I always write a review and this review will be the first negative trip review for me. I stayed at the Melia Caribe Tropical several years ago and had a pretty flawless stay. I hated the beach restaurants at that time but was able to find great buffets and restaurants in other areas of the resorts. I also read the other reviews regarding this resort on Tripadvisor and chalked poor reviews up to picky patrons who be satisfied anywhere. Please reread those negative reviews. I was wrong. If you have not taken your vacation yet, please call your travel agent right away!! and change resorts. We traveled to this alleged five star resort on July 6, 2007. The Good1. Check In- Surprisingly and contrary to other reviews, they allowed us to check in early right upon arrival. 2. Resort Appearance- The resort looks great in pictures and in person. The greenery, buildings, lobby and beach are still great to look at. Now for the Very Bad 1. Extremely aggressive timeshare people in yellow shirts harass you in the lobby on the train, in the restaurants, on the beach. They are everywhere and are a nuisance from the moment that you walk through the lobby. We hated them and the last thing we wanted to do was buy a timeshare in that awful resort. 2. The Room-The Jr. Suite that we received looked nothing like the internet pics and did not resemble the nicer room that I had last time. I did see rooms like I had before but we placed in one for some reason. The furniture was somewhat worn and had a butlers pantry instead of a seating area. I noticed little black bugs on the counters and in the bathroom but I attributed them to the fresh flowers and threw them out. We were never able to get rid of the bugs during our stay. They resembled ants but were smaller. 3. Lack of Food -They tell you to call the reservation hotline to reserve ala carte restaurants for the current day and the following day. They forgot to say that no one ever answers that hotline. It rings repeatedly, stays busy or when they do answer, they say are all booked call back later to check for cancellations or book for the next calling many times, we were unable to book a restaurant for our arrival day or the next day. We gave up and went to the beach. We tried the beach grill but there were few choices and lots of greasy snack bar foods. Plain pans of rice with a few carrots. Plain pans of fish, chicken or pork. Desserts were limited out there and it was hot in that beach grill. The tables have no linen table cloths and your dishes will pile up because service is poor to non-existent in there. I mistakenly reassured my husband that they had other restaurants that I enjoyed last time. In the morning, they even have pans of scrambled eggs, pancakes or waffles. that standard?. The omelet line is so long in the morning, you want an egg. 4. Poor Service- After spending a pretty great first day on the beach, we returned to our room only to find that we had no water coming into the bathtub/shower. We called the desk for assistance but no one came after waiting for about 1 hour. Still no answer on that reservation hotline either. We took off in search of restaurants. We saw beautiful ala cartes with well dressed people who seemed satisfied but we found no buffets. We saw signs for the buffets and looked on our resort map but still found no buffets. Finally we were informed that they have torn all of the buffet restaurants down and we discovered lots of construction. Finally we went to the front desk to again complain about the water/food issues. We were tired, dirty and simply needed food. Surely they could have secured a restaurant reservation for us. Those restaurants weren't full. We were simply given the hotline number again and were told that the buffets from the past no longer existed. The signs were wrong. To make matters worse I detected an attitude from the lady at the front desk instead of sympathy. The only place to eat is that awful, hot beach grill if you are unable to secure a reservation. That grill would be used for all meals. Having no choice, we walked back to the beach grill to head off starvation. 5. The room shower was repaired finally but still had very little water pressure. The next morning I tried the restaurant hotline again and managed to get a voice. Everything was booked for our second day already. It was only 9:05 AM! The thought of another day in that beach grill sickened me. We were able to book a reservation for the Japanese restaurant on the third day, however, we were told that we would have to stop what were doing in the middle of the day and pick up a ticket at the restaurant or we would not be admitted. We were also told that we could call back to check on restaurant cancellations after 2:30 p.m. 6. We then noticed water all over the floor of the bathroom on the second day. The toilet had suddenly sprung a leak. I was also beginning to experience flu/viral symptoms that would plague me for the remainder of the week. I could have contracted the illness on the plane but you never know. I was able to live with the symptoms all week but it definitely put a damper on some activities. 7. Spending the vacation on the phone dialing a hotline morning, afternoon and night and walking to various restaurants to pick up tickets was not how I planned to spend my week. I also refused to watch hundreds of people enjoying the very upscale ala cartes while I stayed in the beach grill. I lost all sense of calm and headed to the lobby to find the Apple Vacations rep who normally is stationed in the lobby of the hotel. We found that he would be off for a couple of days. I then went to guest services and requested that Apple Vacations be called. They finally assisted me by making this call. A rep arrived 20 minutes later and we pleaded with him to be moved from that property. Thank goodness, we were sent to the lovely Palladium Grand Bavaro resort. We had to pay an extra $67 and cab fare to move and make the accommodations equal but it was worth it. The nightmare of the Melia Caribe Tropical was completely forgotten when we were able to actually enjoy a great beach, hotel room and eat wonderful foods including normal breakfast choices, chilled wines, salmon, caviar and sushi in a variety of super air conditioned restaurants at the beautiful Palladium for the remainder of our vacation. What a 360 degree turn! I dealt with the illness and still am thankful that we were able to turn this vacation around with a resort move. Other Very Bad Things1 - The resort was huge which requires the use of trams for the patrons. The Melia also allows numerous employees to ride through the resorts on trucks, motor bikes, golf carts etc. I grew weary of constantly stepping aside for the excessive traffic that existed. Our other resort was equally as large and did not allow all of that traffic. 2. Hotel patrons who have purchased the Royal Service option have a lock on the restaurant reservations. They even have butlers who make their reservations, special restaurants, VIP clubs and private beach. Hotel literature clearly indicates that Royal Service patrons have preferential treatment and are given restaurant reservations first. We assumed that these guests were the happy, well dressed patrons who were actually able to enjoy the resort. The Melia has completely forgotten its average client who would not pay or be able to afford additional hundreds for Royal Service. I will never deal with a resort who provides services based upon class and status. While they strive to be six star with rich amenities, we can remember 3 star resorts that outperformed this place in all areas. We give the Melia no stars for our stay. I will return to the Dominican Republic next year but I will never stay in a Melia Resort again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eeac8eaefb052578dc7fdd8c9d6b7d39" url=""><![CDATA[Restful Caribe Club Princess July 26- August 2, 2006 I traveled to the resort with friends for a restful vacation. I originally stayed at this resort when it first opened under the Hodelpa management. At that time, I felt the resort was impeccable with the exception of the service in main buffet. Waiters used to walk all around you with coffee pots and not wait on you in a timely fashion. While we noticed this again during this trip, we managed to use some our Spanish and got to know some of the wait staff. We also tipped well. This seemed to remedy the problem for the remainder of the trip as we continued to sit where our favorite wait staff was located in the buffet. We loved the service in all of the ala cartes. Even though the resort is under the Princess chain now, they continue to serve Dominican specialties in the buffets which we loved. Other resorts seem to lack that Dominican flair when you look at their bland or greasy buffets geared toward certain nationalities. The food is still very good with plenty of variety but plan on repetition during the course of the week. Repetition was a good thing in this case. miss the morning juice bar, the rice and beans, twisted dinner rolls, fried chicken, fried fish, coffee with milk, and lobster night. The two beach snack bars were great. We loved the pizza, crepes and onion rings. The Italian, Dominican and Japanese ala cartes were our favorites. The food was amazing. I would skip the Brazilian which is simply the buffet meats served like appetizers on swords every few minutes. Really strange! We left that one hungry and headed straight for the buffet. We also disliked the Mexican. The sauce tasted like catsup to me.No problems getting reservations each day in our room buildings. We try the Gourmet La Cava or the Seafood place and chose to repeat our favorites. BEACH-The beach is still wonderful although the sand seemed tanner than it used to be. The weather was windy and cloudy for the first three days so there was some seagrass in the water. The water is still wavy. The water was great for boogie boarding. plan to snorkel on the beach. You will have to book a snorkel tour. We took the Marinarium tour with the sharks and stingrays. Warning!! Skip/Reschedule this tour if it is cloudy and or windy. We had a rough time out there in rough water due to weather. Nothing makes you more nervous than swimming with sharks and stingrays in dark water with no sun. There were plenty of beach chairs and palapas on the beach even when we arrived late. ROOM -The room was not without issues on the first day. When I arrived they allowed me to check in immediately without waiting around for hours. However, the toilet was not operational. The television remotes are stored at the front desk and so are the safe keys. I had to return to the front desk in the heat, toting my heavy valuables( documents, cd player, jewelry etc) to get the key and remote. After retrieving the needed items, and returning to the room, I discovered that the previous guest left the removable lock in the safe. I needed to have it removed before I could use the safe. I again returned to the front desk in the heat still toting my valuables. The lobby is about mile away from the rooms. They handed me a bag of safe keys and told me to try all of the keys and then return the bag of keys to them which required one more trip to the front desk in the heat. Now this was strange VIP service!! They fixed the toilet problem relatively quickly thank goodness. I thought they were going to hand me a plunger. I still lost a couple of hours on this adventure and lost some of my beach day with my friends. I a happy camper on day one. The room was a jr. suite with a view of the pool. It was nice. Maid service was adequate, rum, cigars, fruit platter and VIP nightly turn down mint on the pillow service, which began after day 2 and ended after day 6. I liked the fact that the maids remade the bed and replaced towels when they did the nightly turn down service. I wanted to see them do a better job of getting the sand off of the room floor. It always felt gritty. Resort Appearance landscaping was better when it first opened. I was shocked to see a wooden bridge over water at the ala cartes blocked off with red danger tape. The resort grass was completely dead/dry in spots and full of debris( paper, cigarette butts) and rocks. This is not the norm for the DR at all. Ponds are unkempt and brown. Fountains are inoperative. The Dominican music that used to play throughout the mangroves is now inoperative in places. A couple of working speakers blared disco tunes. There were groundskeepers working but they really need to clean up. This resort was gorgeous when it first opened. Landscaping generally improves over time but not in this case. Another Problem- For about 3-4 days of the vacation, the resort which was calm for the first 2 days, filled to capacity with locals and guests from Puerto Rico. These guests took over all three pools and all of the bars. I have heard of this happening at other resorts but never experienced it until this trip. It appeared that entire families with children and extended generations descended upon the resort. We began to wonder what travel deals were available from Puerto Rico and questioned some of the guests. It became a problem because numerous children appeared to be largely unsupervised and continuously jumped into the pools splashing everyone. The also ran, screamed etc. and forced many guests onto the beach. You even reach the swim up bar. The pools were full of loud, drunk people. It was like MTV spring break. Loud behavior could be heard in the hallways at night during this period and I even experienced strange knocks on the door late at night. There are no peep holes in the room doors( a safety concern) so I ignored the knocking. After a few days, this large group of rowdy guests, suddenly departed and a calm was experienced for the final two days of our vacation. ENTERTAINMENT- The entertainment staff is still top notch! They really worked to get everyone involved on the beach and in the available shows. We loved them. The comedy show was hysterical. The dance shows were wonderful and well choreographed. The stage is still the best in Punta Cana with its light and smoke effects. The did preempt shows one night because they brought in a Puerto Rican singing star (coincidentally during the crowded period) in the disco and charged a $10. cover and another night for a disco on the beach. We disco people and felt cheated out of two shows.Overall- I had a good vacation with my friends on the beach and enjoyed some great food and service. Unfortunately, the vacation was not as problem free and as restful as I wanted . I hope the Princess resorts works harder to reclaim the luster that this resort once had. It certainly has good bones to build on with decent rooms, food and entertainment. I will certainly return to the DR next year but will continue to search for a new resort to try.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1fa32d8328731cb20eb13950c26bd8a9" url=""><![CDATA['Cock A Doodle Doo' and Other Birds Too! The pools were beautiful but hot!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>