<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="4adfa79946d85cfbef322e560443aeb3" url=""><![CDATA[Great stay! My husband and myself, along with another couple, spent two nights at the Hotel Vitale the first weekend in October. I made reservations 2 and 1/2 months in advance, reserving two water view rooms. After much research online, including TripAdvisor reviews, we selected this hotel for it location and views of the Bay and the Bay Bridge.Upon checkin, we were quickly and courteously shown to our room. Had a small problem, as it was a room with two double beds and a view of an office building across the street. The bellman called to the front desk and then went downstairs to explain the we had reserved a water view room with a king bed. He returned with two keys and showed us to the next room, which had a king bed and now a better city view. At first we were told that the water view rooms had been overbooked, but when my husband went down to the front desk to explain our very specific reasons for choosing the Hotel Vitale, voila! water view rooms became available for us and our friends. Problem solved and though it involved some time and back and forth discussion, the staff remained friendly and eager to make us happy. By the way, the views of the Bay and the Bay Bridge were spectacular at night. Our first evening we had dinner at the Slanted Door restaurant right across the street in the Ferry Building. We had tried to secure a reservation on our own more than two weeks in advance, but were unable to do so. A quick call the hotel concierge and we promptly had reservations there within 15 minutes of the time we requested. Good job!The next morning we took the F Trolley to Pier 39. The trolley stop is directly on the north side of the hotel. Cost was $1.50 per person. After seeing the sea lions, we took a ferry out to Alcatraz. You must reserve tickets well in advance (in our case, we did this two months in advance) at the BlueGold Fleet website. Lunch at Ghiradelli Square overlooking the water, The Golden Gate Bridge and Alcatraz was quite lovely. Then on to the the obligatory cable car ride (after an hour long wait). Walked through Union Square and then back to the hotel through Chinatown. Dinner that evening was at Hawthorne Lane (quite good), a short 15 minute walk from the hotel. We ate twice in the hotel's restaurant, breakfast both times. A bit on the pricey side, but the food was well prepared and the wait staff was very attentive. In the evenings, the bar is a very lively gathering spot, not only for hotel guests, but for a dialed up crowd of young professionals.The morning of our departure, the hotel arranged to have their towncar transport us and all our baggage to a corporate Hertz location way the heck on the other side of town (we were going on to Napa and wanted to head out over the Golden Gate Bridge which is why we chose this location). It almost seemed as if we were having a private car tour as we went up and down and all around numerous San Francisco neighborhoods before being deposited directly in front of our destination. Total cost - $30 plus tip. Hard to beat that.All in all, we really enjoyed our stay at the Hotel Vitale. Great location with beautiful views, sleek contemporary look to all the public areas and well-appointed rooms and bathrooms. I do agree with one reviewer's note about lack of drawer and closet space, but as we were only there two short nights, we managed quite well right out of our suitcases with little inconvenience. Every staff member was eager to please and we were always greeted promptly with a smile. We would definitely return.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2d9239176e81abab8b0ff27465bbe4db" url=""><![CDATA[In need of a makeover! Stayed with my husband and son for two nights for a large convention in early March. We had stayed at this hotel four years ago and swore we would never return, but as we were hosting seven company employees and they were staying here, we thought it appropriate that we stay as well. Not a good choice.I have to say that check in was very efficient given that there were hundreds of other guests trying to check in for an early afternoon meeting in the adjacent convention facilities. Just by the front desk was a display of what seemed to be newly renovated room decor - minature bed with pillows and drawings of new decor. Much to our disappointment, upon reaching our room, these renovations must be happening sometime in the future. Our room was, as my son commented, not much better than an old Holiday Inn off the interstate. Tired room decor, tired bathroom and, hard to believe, a sink in the bedroom! Haven't seen that in ages. There were the usual hotel amenities and the room was rather large by city hotel standards. We had a lovely view of the nearby freeways and office buildings, though to be fair, that seems to be the case for most city hotels. The hotel is huge - I think over 1800 rooms - and housekeeping seems to struggle with the large number of checkouts and checkins each day. After having been out all day (8:00 am to 4:00pm), we returned to find our room had not been refreshed. I don't need my sheets changed daily (here they will change them every three days unless you specify otherwise), but damp towels are a little much for me. We found a housekeeper down the hall and gathered our wet towels and exchanged them for fresh ones. We really didn't need much more, but it was still disappointing to have to do even that.I will say that the valet employees were right on the mark. Our group of ten needed two van taxis to go to dinner one night, and for about the same price, the valet had a limo pull up and take us to dinner. Very nice and a special treat for the employees visiting Dallas for the first time. As our parent company needs large convention style hotels for meetings and convention each year, we seem to be resigned to cities that can accomodate our large numbers - San Diego, Dallas, Orlando, Atlanta, etc. - but we've taken to booking our accomodations separately based on, among other things, TripAdvisor reviews. On our last two visits to Dallas we stayed at the Hilton Anatole (company choice) and Hotel Za Za (reommendation from a relative - loved it!). When we visit Dallas again, and we will for business, I wouldn't stay at the Adams Mark unless the most recent recommendations from other travelers indicate major changes.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c36fdada85efdb490042e528d4f307ab" url=""><![CDATA[Nice experience My husband and I stayed at the Wyndham Anatole for one night for a short business meeting earlier this month. I wasn't exactly looking forward to staying at this hotel based on other TripAdvisor reviews, but I have to say, we were very pleasantly surprised by what we found. First off, we were surprised at the ease with which we left DFW and arrived at the hotel, despite rush hour traffic. From leaving the plane to entering our room was about 35 minutes. The check-in desk was well staffed and our reservation was promptly retrieved. It was less than a minute before we had key in hand and were on our way to the elevator. Our room was on the sixth floor, reached by the bank of elevators just off the reception area. We thought the room was quite nice. It was pretty much what you would expect for a business/convention hotel. The requisite king bed, chair with ottoman, armoire with TV and minibar, work desk with a surprisingly nice ergonomic work chair - however, this room had clearly been recently renovated. Fresh wallpaper, what seemed to be brand spanking new bedspread, curtains, upholstery - right down to the shower curtain in the bathroom that matched the soft goods in the bedroom (truly one of the prettiest shower curtains I've ever seen in a hotel). The bathroom was well appointed with plenty of towels and toiletries, as well as a coffee maker. Lighting was good throughout the room. There seemed to be a vaguely Asian theme in the decor and I particularly liked the shade on the floor lamp (next to the chair and ottoman) and the lamp on the desk, both which I might have chosen for my own home.While my husband attended a morning meeting, I comfortably relaxed in the room with a Do Not Disturb sign on the door and a good book in hand. I was not disturbed by housekeeping, but the constant door slamming of guests from nearby rooms was quite annoying. For the life of me, I don't understand why people can't close doors more quietly in consideration of guests in nearby rooms! I understand that some guests need to leave their rooms early but I don't think every other guest needs to rise when they do. In general, however, this section of the hotel was relatively quiet despite facing an atrium. Though we travel frequently, we wouldn't normally choose to stay at Wyndham hotels. In fact, my only other experience was staying at the Wyndham Rose Hall in Jamaica with my sister and her family over several spring breaks. However, I do belong to the Wyndham By Request program. That program honors guest requests such as bed size, smoking versus non-smoking room, soft or firm pillows, etc. They also provide an amenity of your choice during each stay. In my case, I have always requested a bottle of white wine and a snack selection (usually a small cheese and cracker tray). Sure enough, upon arriving in our room, there was a bottle of white wine on ice and a small round of gouda with crackers. Another benefit of this program is the late checkout (at this hotel 2:00 pm), which has always been honored.My husband's meeting was in another section of the hotel, which he said was quite a hike from our room. A continental breakfast was provided and he thought the selection and quality was, by large meeting standards, quite good. We ate lunch before leaving for the airport in the restaurant just off the reception area. It was relatively quiet that day despite a large gathering in a nearby meeting room. The food was good and the service was prompt and friendly. As an aside, we had dinner with family who live in Dallas at a restaurant named Fuse in downtown, just across the street from the flagship Neiman Marcus store. The food style is Tex-Asian and quite remarkable. Serving sizes are small, but that's to encourage patrons to try many small plates and share many different tastes. If you go, you must request to be seated in the upstairs open air patio, weather permitting (though even on a chilly evening there are patio heaters everywhere). Though it was very quiet on the night we ate there (midweek), I can easily imagine that this is a very lively scene on the weekends.Our previous stay in Dallas was at Hotel ZaZa (which we loved!), but I wouldn't hesitate to recommend the Wyndham Anatole based on this experience.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ecdfc2e6515d7475ad62b8a4f78f0632" url=""><![CDATA[A solid 4-star hotel My husband and I spent one night at the JW Marriott in Miami last month. The stay was reserved on the Marriott website using Marriott Reward points. This was a very last minute trip (booked on Thursday for Saturday night), so we were willing to consider all Marriott properties in and around downtown Miami or South Beach. This was the property that had availability. By the way, in late January rooms were available starting at over $400 a night. Our stay included the buffet breakfast on Sunday morning and my husband said it was really quite nice. The property is located on Brickell Ave., in the midst of many high rises - both condos and office buildings. I had printed directions to the hotel off of Mapquest and I'm glad I did as it wasn't readily apparent where the entrance to the hotel was. Parking was $27 per night (or $9 per hour - you do the math) and it appeared to us that it was valet only. Valet staff was courteous and quite efficient.The check-in was pretty efficient and the hotel had an accurate record of the points being used for our reservation. The hotel lobby is very spacious and filled with beautiful seating areas. Lots of dark wood and gleaming brass, marble floors. Our room was on the 17th floor, looking out over the city of Miami (which appears to be a city of cranes and partially constructed high rise condos and offices). The room was reasonably large, very light and airy. It had very nice furniture with the lovely new Marriott bedding. Desk with chair (and a computer and keyboard, though we had our own laptop), easy chair, chest with minibar and drawers under a flat screen TV. Bottled water was provided for no charge. The bathroom seemed a bit on the small side, with only a single sink and a combo shower/tub. Plentiful and good quality towels and the type of shower curtain that bows out to give you the feel of more space in the shower. Generous toiletries - be aware that the hairdryer is stored in the closet outside the bathroom. The one odd thing about the bathroom was the open toilet - no closing lid, which I found a bit disconcerting when brushing my teeth at the nearby sink.We were at the hotel such a short time that we didn't have time to use any of their facilities such as the gym or the pool. We did have pre-dinner drinks in Drake's Bar and it was a quiet, very clubby bar in which to wait for family to gather. The single bartender had our table of 6 and another couple to wait on, but seemed to disappear just when we needed something. She was however, very nice and very attentive when she was around.We were able to walk to dinner at a nearby Italian restaurant, though we did notice that there was almost nothing (store, restaurant, bars, etc.) open within the area of the hotel on the weekend. I would assume there would be more during the weekdays, but the area appeared to be virtually deserted on a Saturday. The hotel is not near the beaches or the activity of South Beach or Coconut Grove. This made me think of this more as a business hotel, rather than a place to take the family for a vacation.Lunch on the day of our departure was a bit disappointing, as we ate at the La Terraza Cafe in the hotel and experienced indifferent, extremely slow service. It wasn't busy, so we were a bit puzzled by the inattentiveness of the wait staff. All in all, the JW Marriott Miami served our purpose - a (relatively) free stay on short notice for one night to visit family. For a business hotel, I would say good choice. For a family vacation or to really experience Miami, head out to the water and the beaches. For the rates they charge during our season, I'd consider other options.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8700bfcb886cced26553870116cd03b8" url=""><![CDATA[Had hoped to be able to write a better review My husband and I spent three nights at the Bostonian purely for a quick getaway. I can't begin to count the number of times we visited Boston between 1990 and 2003. Though we live in Florida, we had children at school in New England or living there during that time, and during fall, winter and spring would travel North as often as every three weeks. We had stayed at the Bostonian on several previous occasions, though not in the last few years.I booked this hotel through the Delta website using SkyMiles for the entire stay, pretty much at the last minute. That the hotel was available without much advance notice might have been a clue that all might not go well.First off, the location of this hotel couldn't be better for exploring Boston. It is located directly across the street from Fanueil Hall and Quincy Market with all the wonderful restaurants and shops just outside the doorstep. The Aquarium and the Waterfront are nearby and the North End is just a short walk away. The Government Center and Haymarket T stops are only a few blocks away, which means you can reach anywhere in the city easily. We didn't have a car and walked everywhere, and I mean everywhere. Boston is a very walkable city, so put on those comfortable shoes and just head out and explore. Follow the Freedom Trail, walk through Beacon Hill, explore Newbury Street and on and on.Upon arrival, checkin was quick and efficient. The hotel staff, every single member we encountered, was terrific and this is the great strength of this hotel. The first room we were shown appeared fine to us, but a quick look out the window and its view of a rooftop full of airconditioning units and the expressway, and we went back down to reception to request another room. The second room was better, though not the king we had requested. We accepted that room and spent the first night there. The room had a queen bed, nice sofa with coffee table, armoire with TV, mini-bar, desk, etc. The decor was kind of Colonial floral. The bathroom was very odd - single sink outside the actual bathroom itself, then a sliding plywood? door to the bath. Another sink, etc. and a large tub/shower (not a jacuzzi type) that was very difficult to enter and exit without a bit of caution. OK toiletries and an adquate supplyof towels. Despite overlooking the farmers market, the room was quiet even in the early morning hours when stands were being set up. We tried to use the internet for business in the morning and it didn't work. At first it was suggested that my husband come down to the lobby (which was wireless), but that wasn't acceptable to us, so they said it would be repaired while we were out. Fair enough.After spending most of the day exploring the city, we returned to our room late in the afternoon to find that is hadn't been made up. We called housekeeping and were told that rooms didn't have to be finished until 5:00 pm. To their credit, a housekeeper arrived 10 minutes later and we left for an hour. Everything was great until we tried to use the internet - still not working. The technician who responded said that he hadn't been able to fix the problem and he would find us another room. Packed and moved to another room and all seemed fine - until we went to turn on the TV. TV could only be viewed from two chairs over by the window and from nowhere else in the room. Called down again - on to room #4. Beautiful king bedded room with a fireplace, spectacular view over the markets, the Custom House, the entire Boston skyline. Still kind of a weird outdated bathroom, but everything works, can see the TV and they will even lay a fire for us in the real working fireplace. Final problem - it was a weekend and the noise outside from 12:30pm until 2:30 am (bar closing time?) was astounding. Learned our last night there that the hotel is under new management and will be undergoing an extensive renovation. Their famous Seasons restaurant will be closing after the holidays for renovations as well. We were actually told that not much has been done for the past 20 years. Whether that is absolutely correct or not, it seemed to fit our experience.I really, really wanted to give this hotel a great review. We have recommended it to friends and family in the past (for gosh sakes, we sent my in-laws here a few years back and they loved it!). The Bostonian has two great pluses going for it - location, location, location, and an outstanding staff, top to bottom. I eagerly look forward to future TA reviews that reflect some positive changes for this hotel.I would absolutely be willing to give the Bostonian another try down the road - I have such great memories of stays there.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>