<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="ad1d4bd17408cbd71f5014cc829de2a9" url=""><![CDATA[Loved the location We booked the Swissotel direct online with the hotel (as recommended bya previous Trip Advisor report) for a 4 night weekend stay. My husband and I took his mother for a sightseeing trip to Amsterdam to celebrate her 85th birthday. We wanted a central hotel with good facilities. We obtained a business rate with breakfast and a guaranteed refurbished room, which were both excellent. Although the rooms had no views, they were spacious and comfortable with very acceptable extras such as a large bowl of fruit, bathrobes, tea/coffee making facilities and iron ironing board. The staff in the hotel could not have been more helpful. For my mother-in-law's convenience due to her age, we took a taxi from the airport each way, which cost 45 euros and both drivers expected a 5 euro tip! A little excessive we thought. Had we been on our own, we would have taken the train to Central Station and walked to the Hotel, which was only about a 10/15 minute walk away. We were central to everything in Amsterdam - tram stop across the road - and the report which complained about the non-nearness of the canals had a different view to ours. There was only a 10 minute walk along Damrak either way to reach the canals and those by Central Station included all the canal boat excursions you could have wished. We had a evening meal in the hotel's adjoining Dam Plaza restaurant which was very good and we also dined in the restaurant of De Roode Leeuw two doors away and the Restaurant Reflet in the Grand Hotel Krasnapolsky across the square, both of which were excellent. We did the evening dinner canal cruise which was a little expensive at over 60 euros, but could not be faulted for the atmosphere and experience. The tour company offices for excursions, booked for us by the friendly Hotel staff, were just across Dam Square, which was also very convenient. The Panoramic City tour, which finished at the Diamond factory, was very disappointing and not worth the money but the trip to Volendam and Marken was very good in terms of value and content. We also enjoyed sitting outside in the warm evening temperatures in the bar of the Dam Plaza with the very friendly barmen and people watching all the activities in Dam Square. A most enjoyable experience and we would recommend the Swissotel as a very good hotel to stay at for a weekend break in Amsterdam - just insist on the refurbished rooms!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>