<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="b5510efed44173e3722eb3be7e0d8b76" url=""><![CDATA[Absolutely Fabulous. We stayed at the Casablanca from March 10th till March 17th 2005. It is undoubtedly one of the most charming hotels had the pleasure to stay in. Location is excellent, seconds from Times Square, Theatre district and minutes from 42nd St. Subway station. and Empire State are about 15 minutes walk from the hotel handy when returning laden with shopping. Despite its proximity to the hustle and bustle of Times Square it is incredibly quiet. The staff were excellent and very informative always willing to help out with a dinner reservation and took a genuine interest in our itinerary (especially keen on our reviews of the Broadway shows seen Avenue Q is brilliant). The hotel continental breakfast is better than expected and is a must for the walking required in New York. The wine and cheese was lovely to wind down to after a hectic day in the city and perfect for pre-dinner, theatre, Jazz drinks. This is accompanied with live piano music which sad to say is dying out in hotels now but full credit to the Casablanca for keeping it alive. The room was reasonably sized considering New penchant for human rabbit hutches. We had quite a small bed between two of us but that was more Expedia not explaining the bed sizes properly something to have in mind next time. Thus in summation Casablanca location is excellent, staff are very friendly and the rooms are high above acceptable standard. I will definitely be staying here again and would not hesitate to recommend this it has been eloquently called by previous reviewers to my dearest friends and family.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="371c8729307317a35d7f37e9df40d963" url=""><![CDATA[Great Value and Staff were excellent. We stayed at the Caravaggio from July 3rd till July 6th 2005. It is a charming hotel and was a pleasure to stay in. Location is good, 10 minutes walk north of the Duomo (Florence is not a big city and everything is easily in walking distance). The hotel is only 5 minutes walk from the train station , or if laden with luggage a cheap taxi fare. Despite florence lack of greenery the Caravaggio sits opposite a pleasent green Piazza. The staff were excellent and very informative always willing to help out with a dinner reservation and took a genuine interest in our itinerary (especially warning us about the morning queues for the Uffuzi). The hotel continental breakfast is better than expected and is a must for the walking required in Florence. The room was a good size with a wonderful view over the Duomo (Which unless your extremely luckly you pay extra for).Thus in summation Caravaggio's location is very good, staff are very friendly and the rooms are high above acceptable standard for what you pay. I will definitely be staying here again and have'nt hesitated to recommend this to friends and family.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>