<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="3567e7c1521023c817edf5f30a4ebe49" url=""><![CDATA[Great City Getaway We saw this hotel's Staycation package advertised in the Sacramento Bee and decided to give it a try to celebrate our 45th wedding anniversary. When we checked in I commented that it was a special anniversary celebration and we were upgraded to an Executive King room--a wonderful corner room with two walls of floor to ceiling windows. Loved the city lights at night! The rooms are nicely appointed and very comfortable. The package included valet parking and a daily breakfast buffet for two. The buffet was far nicer than those at most venues--I greatly enjoyed lox and bagels every morning along with a bowl of fresh raspberries, blackberries and blue berries. What a winter treat. The staff was uniformly attentive. The location is quite convenient--very walkable to Union Square attractions, several museums, two multiplex movie theatres, restaurants, shopping, clubs, several live theatres. We trekked to Embarcadero Center--a nice walk. One could even come into the city on the rapid transit Bart train and walk from the Powell Street Station to the hotel. The cost for this package made it a major bargain. We've already recommened the hotel to friends and family.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6eb85f68fb50d0ed8af4527369692c27" url=""><![CDATA[Fun, Inexpensive Place to enjoy the Civic Center Area Really a fun place to stay. Wonderful restaurant on site. We were probably the oldest guests in residence and dining--but felt welcomed and comfortable. Had some concerns about the noise from the patio bar--but it ended amazingly promptly at around 11 PM! Easy walking (away from the Tenderloin) toward VanNess--multi-screen indie movie theatre nearby--many dining options. We were staying because of promixity to the Federal Building, but will return just for fun. It's also a real bargain and we belong to the Joy of Life affinity club for this small hotel chain, so had a couple of extra goodies thrown in for free.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>