<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="1b878e035674858956e8103a7b176dbc" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel, lost a star because of the noisy heater and non-working pool The hotel location was perfect, right in the center of town and just a few blocks to the convention center. I walked from here to Pike's Place market for breakfast, then on to the convention center each day of the convention and found it all very convenient. (Try the Crumpet Shop for breakfast, delicious crumpets, and cheap lattes before 8:30am every day!) The hotel room was clean and everyone who worked here was helpful and perfectly friendly. The bed was too comfortable :). The first night I had trouble sleeping though, because the heater would wake me up every couple of hours. By the second night, I learned to tune it out. There is a coffee maker in the room, by the way (I had read somewhere that there was only coffee in the lobby, and this is not true.) There is also a nice little fridge where I stored away spring water for my week. I had a view of the Space Needle without even asking - very nice.Unfortunately, they were working on the pool during my one-week stay, and that was kind of annoying because I had chosen the hotel for their pool. I did get to swim the first night, and it was a nice smallish pool. There was a lukewarm hot tub attached. All in all, though, nice amenities. Would stay again, would recommend for the rates, the location and the comfy rooms.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6567836dbc6a834ea13c6d90f05348ed" url=""><![CDATA[Prince Conti: Great service, nice rooms, but no coffee If I had to stay in New Orleans again, I'd stay here for the price, the location and the fact that it is very well kept. Can't hear anything from Bourbon street, but did hear the neighbors when they stayed up late partying in their rooms. Not a huge deal. Great, comfortable beds, very nice bathroom, good water pressure, huge towels. Surprisingly luxurious. Except for the no coffee...There is absolutely no coffee in the rooms or in the lobby. We got around that by going out to the convenience store next-door every morning, which opened at 7:30 (a time at which the only people you'll run into in New Orleans are the street cleaners, washing away the stale alcohol from the streets.)The service was fantastic, the front desk clerks were nice and helpful and guided us to some great restaurants (they suggested Olivier's which had yummy, authentic creole food and the best pecan pie I have had to date). Because I was one of the first to arrive for the week, the woman at the front desk gave us one of the best rooms in the hotel, and it was gorgeous and huge!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d2814bb8bc5e6e60580bdb60e56262bf" url=""><![CDATA[Savoy, soon to be Hotel California, clean and charming, just no water pressure We found a great deal through travelzoo - $95 per night which included breakfast, and booked directly through the hotel website to get the deal. The good stuff: 1. Breakfast at the hotel is worthwhile *if it is included*. Otherwise, save your $7 and get it someplace like cafe trieste. It was included in our stay and munching on pastries, yogurt, fruit and hardboiled eggs was a wonderful way to start our days with something tasty and get some energy in the morning. 2. Free wine and cheese at 4pm. We took advantage of this every day and it was really yummy. 3. Clean room with hardwood floors, nice decorations, and just a very comfy feel. 4. Very convenient location - a couple blocks from Union Square, in a safe/peopled part of the city. At the Walgreens nearly next door, you can get any needed toiletries and some extra cash (cash back) without the ATM fees. Also, all of the good Thai restaurants are one block away. (I recommend Ar Roi).The not-so-good stuff:1. Water pressure in the bathroom left MUCH to be desired. 2. No coffee maker in the rooms. However, coffee is served in the lobby for free all day long, so that makes up for it. Gotta have my coffee first thing!The good outweighed the bad and I will return to this hotel if I can get the same deal. Note: the hotel is under a name change and will be called the Hotel California in the future. I think this is a good move as the name Savoy isn't all that memorable.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fb0b771400a0bf1a1522fcd42560c004" url=""><![CDATA[The Drake - Central location in SF, Rooms nice and updated Our recent stay at the Sir Francis Drake was just perfect. The hotel was full of international tourists and wedding guests which was probably because our stay was in mid-August and also because the hotel is central to the touristy area. My husband and I stayed for three nights over a weekend.When I checked into the hotel on Thursday, I told the clerk at the front desk that I absolutely had to have a quiet room. I made it pretty clear that I wouldn't be happy in a room with any noise since I'm a light sleeper and have had trouble at a different hotel. The request was successful :). Our room had only light street noise. I personally do not care about a view and I didn't have one because of my quiet room request.One thing to note about this hotel is the lacking coffee service. There's coffee in the lobby only in the very early morning hours. This worked out for my husband and me because we stayed on Eastern time during our stay, waking up at 5am and going to bed at around 7pm or 8pm. The coffee was usually taken away by 7am or so. My husband conjectured that they might have had a deal with Starbucks which was located off of the lobby. Another thing to note was that the curtains in the room blocked the light from the street incredibly well. It made staying on Eastern time that much easier.The bed was incredible. The room was a bit tight but not by San Francisco standards. The tv stations were lacking; we probably should have brought some DVD's to watch during our down time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>