<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="197ed5541d78d5857650b9f49fa2d59e" url=""><![CDATA[Very nice - but only 1 room (ie not a proper suite) We came to this hotel after a horrible experience at a nearby hotel. We were so relieved to come here! It was lovely, the front desk staff were wonderful, the bell staff came to our taxi and took our luggage to our room. The room was huge and very clean, with wonderful views. My one complaint would be that it was just one room - with 3 small children we were hoping for two rooms (ie bedroom and separate living area), which we expected from a suite. I would called this a studio rather than a suite. It was enormous though with a full kitchen cleverly hidden by folding doors. There were two huge walk-in closets (which could be knocked through and made into a bedroom IMO) and a very nice bathroom. There were two double beds in the room and a nice sofa, TV unit and dining table. Even so there was lots of space left.The breakfast was fine though not brilliant. It was mostly pastries etc given out by a member of staff one at a time - you had to ask. We discovered the nicer items were hidden behind the counter and those in the know asked for them! Very odd. Don't know why it couldn't be self-service - I guess people feel guilty having to ask so eat less! The drinks were self-service though, and there were TVs in the breakfast room, which was an ordinary room basically - but they are so big that the size was adequate.There is a computer next to front desk which guests can use - though it was monopolised by teenagers on instant messenger! Plus there is a guest laundry, though I wouldn't recommend going there alone late at night as it was rather scary - its in a garage-type area.The location of the hotel is great - half a block from a cable car stop (if you can get on one - they were always full when we were there so we had to walk into town and get a streetcar), but its not far and downhill. Later in the day its easier to get a cable car and avoid the hills. We spent most of our time in Fisherman's Wharf, which we much preferred to downtown San Francisco. If we'd have known we'd have found a hotel there! But this hotel was great, and not too expensive for such a big room - just wish it had been a proper suite so we didn't have to creep around once the kids were asleep!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="be72fe6410579cae17fa34bc710689a9" url=""><![CDATA[Good but a few problems Checking in was the worst experience of our stay here - the lady we dealt with was truly hideous - though we discovered she was NOT typical of the front desk staff. Everyone else was lovely and in fact apologised for her. But she did put us off at first. The room was great - nice and big, and most importantly for us with 3 children, a separate bedroom with a door! This is why we love Embassy Suites! We are Hilton Hhonors members and were pleased to see a little card in our room welcoming us with our name on, and also noticed that a crib was already in the bedroom which was a nice touch. The room was really quiet despite the fact that this hotel was so noisy! As soon as you opened the door to the room the noise hit you - wow those rooms are well sound-proofed - also the bedrooms are at the back so no worries about getting to sleep anyway. The hotel is basically a large atrium in the center, with a party going on late into the night and teens running around the corridors. I was using the guest laundry until quite late and I couldn't believe how much was going on - but how quiet the room remained during it all! So inside the room was great - but not outside.The breakfast was also great - downstairs in a lovely setting in the atrium, a proper breakfast, no continental rubbish here! Another plus for Embassy Suites.The other thing that really bothered me about the hotel was the lack of a courtesy shuttle bus that was advertised. When we arrived we saw three buses in the car park and one in the driveway, but when we asked to take the bus they said that it was in the garage. I asked about the other buses, they then said there was no driver. The horrid front desk lady was very rude and told me if I wanted to put my kids on a dangerous bus and risk their lives then I was welcome to go ahead. (Goodness knows who would have driven!) The lovely female manager thankfully made up for this, apologised and called the shuttle bus for the Marriot next door to take us to the nearby mall. Every time I asked for the bus there was a problem - so we got taxis because I couldn't handle the arguments - but it was expensive and annoying considering this was one of the reasons we stayed here, and especially considering the number of Embassy Suites buses in the car park not being used.The most important part of our stay - the room - was great - just a shame about the other problems.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>