<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="c25bdfaecbadab35bc0487375cf726ea" url=""><![CDATA[Shockingly bad... check out within 90 minutes. This is the second TripAdvisor review I've ever written, but I thought it was worth it.I booked this hotel directly through their very sexy website. I live in New York and have had a cocktail or two at the Meatpacking outpost - having said that it's not my scene, but the service seemed good and the hotel gets ok reviews.There is clearly a big difference between running a city hotel and a a beach resort, which I'm not sure the management has got their head around.On check-in we were told we could have a 'really special room' on the 8th floor (the original was on the 5th) so somewhat excited we went to our room (overlooking the builders everywhere and the missing ceiling panels etc.)...The room was special indeed, with a view over the car park and straight into another apartment building. And the Ocean View was there - if you turned your head 90 degrees (we'd be told it was 'head on' - yes, head on a plate).So to the roof deck. The 100 foot bar. Granted the weather wasn't good and the hotel wasn't busy (good job as the deck wasn't finished, their were workers all over the unfinished changing rooms and the wiring for the sound system was hanging loose. I said, let's have a sandwich.Well, I said it to myself as the bar-boy was too busy being filmed to serve us. Finally we ordered a beer and a sandwich. Well at this point the rain really came down and we asked if they could bring the sandwiches to our room as we were going to chill there (over-looking the car-lot)...One hour later, no sandwiches. Call front-desk, line permanently engaged, had to ring the hotels full number, as if calling externally and even then they couldn't figure out where the plunge rooftop bar was. Get hung up on 2 times and woman on roof bar doesn't understand what's happening.Sandwiches arrive, looking like they were made in a bad deli, and of course cold and rained upon. Ring duty manager at this point, room bad, food bad, service bad, hotel REALLY unfinished, she tells me 'There's nothing I can do about the food as we sub-contract the restaurants'. Right, so you can't refund me the cost of these 2 cold wet sandwiches 'I can't do that I'll have to get the food and bev manager'.Not great. They come and move us and as we walk through the building site we move to the 6th floor and face the ocean (well that's a lie actually, they tell me NONE of the rooms FACE the ocean - I reckon they saved all those for the condos)... that's all well and good, apart from the dawning realisation that the beach really is a building site. Mounds of sand, no loungers, no view, nothing. It's like The Palm in Dubai.At this point (and this is a $400 room) I'm done. The hotel is as close to SoBe as Narnia, the service is terrible, they clearly care more about selling real estate than providing any semblance of service and on that point we quit.No real apologies on departure (well we get the 70 dollars back for 2 sandwiches) and we check-in to The Tides. Same price, bfast included and service like you expect. Don't be fooled by the fake cool. This hotel is not ready. Not good and not worth it.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>