<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="e2f37c15d844d139fe8522ff767c8845" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location and Good Value This Hotel is near Darling Harbour and not on the waterfront. The location is excellent and in our opinion better than the Sydney Harbour Holiday Inn. It is less than 5 min walk to Darling Harbour and the excelent eating/drinking establishments there. It is also very near Chinatown, the light rail and the monorail.The staff were helpful and the value for money excellent. The rooms are small but adequate and very clean.We would stay there again and would recmomend this hotel and area for 1st time visitors to Sydney. It was an excelent choice as we were there for 4 days before a cruise.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="98b72681e8b2bde37d619c59d6fbbe0e" url=""><![CDATA[Unit 84954 VRBO Great Value We stayed in unit 84954 and booked it via VRBO site. This is a newly renovated unit and it is excellent in every aspect. The owner Helen is very helpful and she has thought of every little need one could want. She has water in the fridge a bottle of wine some candies and cookies etc. She thinks of everything. She calls to check on the stay very service oriented. Just Great thanks very much HelenWe would stay there again and would recomend this to anyone.The only downside is it is on the 8th floor and the view really is of the parking lot of the shopping center next door. This is the only small negative but this is a great location (away from the main part of beach) The place is very very clean and new.All in all this is a great unit at a great price.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f05e8dfec5f721c6cedba2061e28c48f" url=""><![CDATA[The only Place to stay in Venice We have stayed at this property before and would not stay anywhere else in Venice. I would echo the comments of the last couple of reports.Paulo and Daniel are outstanding as is Paulo 's wine both sparkling and his sweet after dinner wine.This is a great hotel and is great value for Venice
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>