<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="be543a40b6927502da6cd3fc41f8fee4" url=""><![CDATA[Great stay at the Kapok This was a generally pleasant stay for us, certainly different in character to the Novotel Peace Beijing, where we stayed for the earlier part of our trip. The location is excellent, in a quieter area, yet a throw to the Forbidden City and Wangfujing shopping areas. Although sitting in an older building, the hotel interior is totally refurbished and spanking new. The modern, boutique style will sit well with younger travelers and those averse to the overblown and faded grandeur of the older hotels. Reception and related service was excellent, very friendly and helpful although we did have to speak in Chinese to be very effective. The business centre was terrible however staff was un-knowledgeable to the extreme, and although polite, lacked any sort of initiative and helpfulness.The rooms are clean-cut with modern layout (interesting all-glass bathroom), and space was adequate. Overall very comfortable and squeaky clean surroundings. Contrary to previous reviews, the heating in our room worked extremely well, unlike in other hotels in Beijing we stayed in. Some of my fellow travelers complained that the lighting was slightly too dim (sacrificing functionality for design). Opposite the hotel are several local food shops, which are great for an early and authentic breakfast. The Donghuamen Night Market just down the street is a great evening experience. Spa lovers miss Dragonfly Spa just a few doors away massages at a very reasonable priceI would recommend this hotel for younger travelers and those who are pretty self-sufficient (i.e. do not need the huge breakfasts etc of hotel chains). Do remember to bring the hotel card everywhere you go, and use the Donghuamen night market as a reference for taxi drivers who will not know this hotel 99% of the time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>