<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="6">
		<document id="1e54ff93b96701b29e79ff2fcefc2bbb" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel for a quick business meeting. Stayed at the Marriott San Francisco Fisherman's Wharf for a quick business meeting. This is a medium sized 4 story hotel that is between the Fisherman's Wharf and North Beach Areas. Small lobby, small bar area and a small sit down restaurant greet you when you check in. Check in was very efficient and quick. They have only two elevators and there is often a wait--catch them going down to go up! Stairs are not available for use between floors for some reason. Once you get up to your room there can be a bit of a walk to your room.Rooms are average sized--separate bathroom with shower-tub combo, bed, desk, table, chair. Minibar in room, no safe was available. Coffee maker available. I was on the third floor facing Columbus Ave. and was worried about the noise, but did not hear anything at night! Rooms were clean, bed was comfortable.Used the small gym which had a couple of flat screen TVs, a couple of treadmills, single elliptical and a single recumbent bike. A few machines and free weight sets were available. There are two laundry machines in the gym area. Fresh fruit and water were available. No one was staffing the room.Meeting rooms were good for our meeting. Rooms are downstairs from the lobby and they had connecting stairs.Food in the restaurant was OK. The food issue is not a big deal, if you are visiting San Francisco, you will always be eating out!Location is good given the proximity to the Fisherman's Wharf area and a few block walk to the Italian North Beach area. Concierge set us up with a local Italian restaurant--very nice place. If you take public transportation, the hotel is nearby bus routes.Valet parking is available--about $40 dollars a day. There is no self parking.Hotel was very busy when we were there--a combination of conventioneers and bus tour groups. The lobby and the elevators were the bottlenecks in the hotel.Would I stay here if I wasn't on a business trip? Probably not, can think of other places I would want to stay. But for a quick business trip it was OK.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="12f6e7bcbd003079ec5a0cf049a708bf" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel, Great Location Stayed at Grand Hyatt, San Francisco for business meeting and visits with friends and family. Great location just off Union Square, extremely easy access to Downtown and Chinatown areas. Spent better part of time off from meeting wandering around shops.I went to graduate school in San Francisco and remember this hotel being other chains before it became the Grand Hyatt. It is a nice hotel. Staff is attentive, rooms ok. I arrived late and had the misfortune of getting a room on the fifth floor--very noisy with street noise and kind of claustrophobic, would definitely suggest an upper level room, as high as you can get. Request for a change was made and got a room on the 12 floor, which was much quieter and seemed bigger.Food was okay, ate 4 meals in hotel--nothing outstanding, but could be better considering you are in San Francisco! Another tip if you stay here--no self parking, valet is $43/ nite. You can save $20/nite by parking across the street at the Stockton/Sutter Public Parking garage, which is self parking. Parking in San Francisco is a nightmare.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d85814bc9e4535c6b13ca5da92bd4c0c" url=""><![CDATA[quality hotel for business meeting with museum quality art collection Recently stayed at this hotel for the first time. Found the experience to very good. Check in is a breeze, room was very nice, bathroom a little cramped-- sufficient. Food was very good. Tried the gym, lots of equipment, indoor and outdoor pools, indoor and out door track and tennis courts. Meeting facilities were great. Also several shops for some souvenir shopping. Like most hotels in Dallas it is pretty spread out and there is some walking involved getting from meeting rooms and hotel room. What was really surprising was the amount and quality of the Asian art located around the hotel. Found out that it is part of an extensive private art collection by the people who own the property. Don't miss the amazing jade horses in the Nana Restaurant on the 27th floor.Would definitely stay in this hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="df71e8486c1c79e07d5417bbba0c55aa" url=""><![CDATA[A lucky find in San Francisco Had a bad experience at the Beach Motel and started looking for a hotel with parking that was not too far from the UCSF Medical Center, where my father was recovering from surgery. Having lived in San Francisco before, decided to try over by Japantown. Found the Best Western Hotel Tomo, which was previously the Hotel Miyako. They actually had rooms available on a walkup basis on a Friday afternoon! And to top it off they gave us a room for $149/nite with tax and parking included! This was for two double beds. Hotel is cute with a kind of Japanese Anime/pop culture motif. Monitors in lobby were playing Godzilla and Japanese cartoons!Hotel looks brand new with modern furnishings in the rooms. Room was immaculate with a small refrigerator, flat screen TV and toiletries by Lather, a very nice store in Los Angeles. Had a light bulb go out, staff came up immediately to fix it. Overall, staff was really very helpful.Japanese restaurant in hotel, did not try, but looked like there was a fun crowd in evening. Hotel was very quiet and safe.Parking does not accommodate all guest cars, so get back in early. My mother who was traveling with me really liked this hotel, even the Anime inspired wall paper in our room.Location is close to just about everything and it is very convenient for someone with car, as there is little traffic in this area. It is also across the street from Japantown and all the Japanese restaurants and shops.It was a lucky stroke to find this hotel and an even luckier stroke to get a room on a Friday without a reservation. I would definitely recommend this hotel for anyone looking for a good reasonably priced hotel in San Francisco.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b6bdd0e86d55c2ad2185e71f0a72a609" url=""><![CDATA[Laissez les bons temps rouler--let the good times roll!! Had the good fortune to stay at the Country Inn and Suites. Located about three blocks outside of French Quarter. Practically next door, they are doing some construction work--some debris on street, but amazingly enough, did not find construction noise an issue--guess they start work late. There is not anything else on this block of Magazine street, other than another hotel across the street. Hotel looks new and they made good use of an older building. Lobby is well lit and extends to the sky lights in the ceiling, 5 floors up.Staff was very accommodating. Helped us find a a 24 hour pharmacy to get some prescription medication for one of my kids. New Orleans is still getting back on its feet and there are not many 24 hour pharmacies available. Had to take a taxi to this one at 6 AM. No problems calling for taxis at hotel--we did not rent a car. Happy to not have a car, most places can be reached by foot and the street cars on Canal street are only about a block away. Parking available at hotel for a fee. As we were there around time of Sugar Bowl and BCS bowl, traffic flow was restricted in the French Quarter.Suite room had two TV, wall safe, small frig, microwave and two queen beds and a full sized pull out sofa bed. Slept our family of 5 very comfortably. Internet is free, requires a cable in room, but wireless available in lobby. They also have a computer with printer available to print boarding passes--nice touch. Small pool and bar also available, but did not use either one.Breakfast was OK--hard boiled eggs, frozen patty sausage, pastries, bagels, toast, cereal and beverages. Sugar cookies all the time at front desk and a copy of USA today available in the morning. Fortunately, the rest of our meals were outside. We had coffee and beignets at Cafe du Monde, muffulotta sandwiches at Central Grocery and two very good dinners at Bayona and Isabelle's. Ate way too many praline candies. Still trying to work off the calories. Had a good time in New Orleans--wandered around the French Quarter, listened to jazz at Preservation Hall and shopped for gifts on Royal street. Took a tour with Tours by Isabelle--specialized in small tours--ours was 10 people and we went to see two plantations and the Cajun swamp country. This was a great tour with very good guides and I would highly recommend it to see what else there is outside of New Orleans.Saw areas still waiting to be rebuilt post Katrina. I would recommend this hotel if you do not want to be in the middle of the French Quarter and the craziness of Bourbon Street. Close enough to walk there, but far enough away to get some peace and quiet. Very family friendly and a great staff. Would definitely stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="584678477c32ef76f1fe85355c812447" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel and great location in Tokyo Just returned from 6 day family vacation to Tokyo and had a marvelous stay at the Park Hotel. Arranged my stay via Hotel Website after reading accolades from Tripadvisor, very easy to use.Hotel is easily served by Airport Limo Bus Service from Narita Airport. Service is extremely attentive from the greeting at entrance to check in. English is not an issue. In fact, Tokyo is a lot easier to get around now with English translations in buildings, restaurants and subways.Hotel itself is very modern, airy and serene at the top of a 38 story building in Tokyo Shiodome, which is a series of modern skyscrapers serviced by subway and trains below street level and connected via pedestrian walkways on the third floor. Very quiet despite the activity down below. Didn't use the trains, but found the subway connected to the Ginza and Asakusa Lines, which will hit just about every tourist site in the Tokyo area. There is also a monorail that will take you to the seaside development of Odaiba. Hotel is ten minutes from the Wholesale Fish Market by foot--this a Tokyo must see, if you get up early.With my family of 5, got a twin and a triple. Rooms generous in size for Tokyo, bathrooms and amenities were very good. Restaurant services a very good breakfast buffet which our family enjoyed before hitting the streets. Did not eat any other meals in hotel--seemed pricey, but the building is connected to other Shiodome buildings--Carretta and City/Pedi Shiodome had a number of inexpensive and good restaurants offering a variety of Japanese and non-Japanese foods. There is a Family Mart in the basement level of Park Hotel building for snacks. While we were staying in the hotel, there was a free jazz concert every nite in the lobby.Service was excellent. The concierge services were very helpful and helped me to work with a tour agency that had lost our reservation for a tour to the Ghibili Museum on the outskirts of Tokyo. Fortunately, the concierge was able to clear up the problem and we got to go on our tour.Can not think of anything negative to say about the hotel, definitely worth the price, would definitely go back and would definitely recommend it to my friends. Thanks to all fellow Tripadvisor reviewers for the high rating this hotel gets and deserves!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>