<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="8">
		<document id="a8a182e0c7c04b0e13ca38e2f74399c0" url=""><![CDATA[Oasis in the desert View of beautiful inner courtyard
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="008db7ee7c50452428fe840e38d0a801" url=""><![CDATA[Great location but grossly overpriced for quality of accomodations Closet
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="42a5a789d2dd9c72edd487d05c2ccce4" url=""><![CDATA[Very good downtown New Orleans hotel 3609 - Bed
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8cf9da8d7ca83e8ebfdbd03b0a38a11f" url=""><![CDATA[Only if the price is right Hilton New Orleans / St Charles Ave. is the Hilton Corporation's latest high-end offering in New Orleans, having just opened in Spring of 2007. The hotel is actually a refurb of the former Hotel Monaco that never reopened after Katrina. My wife and I spent 2 nights here during Mardi Gras 2008. We got a great rate ($119/night) by booking a full year in advance (our rate was so good that management actually sent us a letter that complained about us booking before they were ready. They honored the rate anyway, but this was pretty low class for a major hotel chain, especially for a customer who has Diamond status in their loyalty program.)Location: This is the Hilton's main selling point. You are about 5 blocks to the Riverwalk. 4 blocks to Harrah's. 7-8 blocks to the Convention Center. 6 blocks to the Superdome. 4 blocks to the French Quarter. You get the picture: this is a very centrally located hotel. Plus for Mardi Gras fans, every parade in the City passes directly in front of the hotel.Rooms: The building that houses the hotel was originally built in 1926. When the conversion was done, clearly the emphasis was on quantity of rooms rather than size because the rooms and bathrooms are small (definitely not any larger than those at the Hampton Inn a block away). The Hilton has largely retained the Monaco's conversion, right down to room configuration and certain furnishings. The rooms lack any of the modern amenities that you generally expect at new, high-end hotels such as plasma TVs and ergonomic desk chairs. The furnishings are nice, not overly worn, but clearly not what I expected for a hotel with a $250/night rack rate.Service: Marginal at best. The maid threw a couple of towels at us on Saturday morning, but never returned to make the beds or remove the used towels. The hotel's snack pantry lacks even the selection you would find at a mid-level hotel such as Staybridge Suites. The bell desk WAS helpful and efficient on Sunday morning.Honors Recognition: Never once during my stay was I recognized as a Diamond Hilton Honors member. Nor was I ever offered access to the Executive lounge or any of the other benefits I am generally entitled to.Other Amenities: During Mardi Gras, the hotel sets up its own viewing platform in front of the hotel for hotel guests only. Tickets for Friday night were $50/person and $75 for all day Saturday. We didn't take advantage, preferring to try our luck on the streets. The stands offered by the City of New Orleans can be had in the $20/person range if you book in advance.Overall, I'd say the Hilton New Orleans / St Charles Ave. is pretty average. We'd return again for the right price but definitely would first consider some of the other high-end hotels in New Orleans such as the W.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9066bdf7a94b4d2895907c50b2890a4f" url=""><![CDATA[Solid hotel but lacks wow factor Sink
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4529b68e702bae2e74d20c47ac52a089" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel - but don't try to go anywhere but DFW Generous closet space
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b302437bfe341482ca08a62e3de2154c" url=""><![CDATA[Great American style hotel in Barcelona Pool area
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5745bc56e4d887aaf80ba71398d3794e" url=""><![CDATA[Superb hotel with a gorgeous location View of hotel from Plaza Santa Ana
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>