<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="c55c2fb9a4d5c6c0faf8b6fbe153919b" url=""><![CDATA[Amazing Hotel, Amazing Price I booked the hotel through a last minute deal and was really impressed with the service and hotel from the moment we arrived. First of a taxi direct from barcelona airport to the hotel was only just over 30 Euros. For the convenience we thought this was great. Because of an early flight we arrived at the hotel around 10:30am (check in is from 3pm). But when we spoke to reception they said they would see if we could check in earlier. 5 minutes later we were in our room unpacking. But that isn't all because we had booked a really cheap deal for 4 nights), although I had asked for a room on a high floor I wasn't holding out a lot of hope, well I was wrong our room was actually on the 26th floor......(You can't get any higher than that).Throughout our stay we found the staff to be really friendly and the hotel was lovely, only thing we heard people say they were disappointed with were the pools. We weren't disappointed though because they look small on all the pictures from the barcelona princess website.The hotel bar was expensive compared to anywhere else we visited (but again you kind of expect that). On our last day they weren't able to allow us a late check out room (we did not need to leave the hotel until gone 7pm. However, they informed us that we could still use the full hotel facilities so we could shower and change in the Gym - so no problems there.Overall one of the nicest hotels we have stayed in (even compared to some 5 stars), location a little out but we actually liked that as right next to open top Tourist Bus stop and also Tram and Metro.We would recommend the hotel 100%, just one word of warning about Barcelona - pick pockets are rife. We were lucky - despite a couple of attempts on my wifes handbag (which we managed to foil) we didn't get anything stolen. But a couple of women staying in our hotel got handbags snatched apparently hotel staff said it happens a lot. So you have to be very careful and security conscious...... But it shouldn't spoil a beautiful city break.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>