<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="8acc49503e1275495cd940bfacc7b8ff" url=""><![CDATA[Universal was FAB! We had a 6 night stay in Barcelona for our 1st wedding anniversary and it was fantastic. Barcelona itself is a great city with so much to see and do, but tiring ourselves out all day we were glad to have such a comfortable place to come back to.The people were absolutely lovely and couldnt have done more for us. I advised them of our anniversary when we booked and we received complimentary champagne on arrival which was heavenly once we got to sit and relax. We had some hassles with one of our credit cards and they were a great help to us. Always smiling and wanting to help.The rooms where lovely and clean and spacious enough to sleep or just sit and relax in. The bathroom has everything you need and it was great to be in a place where they think of giving you things like make up remover, shavers and shaving cream and toohbrush and toothpaste. The mini bar is fully stocked but there werent any tea and coffee making facilities and by about day 3 i was hanging for a cup of tea!Down the road are a few adult places so perhaps not a place for a family, although there were a few when we were there and they werent bothered about them.Dont opt for the breakfast as you can get just as good for much cheaper. However ,if you decied to pop in one morning at least you have the option instead of beng locked into it. Its a buffet so you can fill yourself up with as much as you like and there is a great range of things to choose from, but i still dont think 13 Euros worth.....maybe a man could pack a bit more away!The roof top pool is small and tends to feel quite crowded around it however you can cool off and go up another flight of stairs to the solarium if you want to get away from the folk around the pool. Most people forget its there. The beach in Barcelona is disappointing so we were quite happy to have somewhere to go to cool off after exploring during the day. But as it is a small pool this isnt the type of hotel you would choose if you wanted to lay around the pool all day.If you get the metro (the paral-ell stop is right out the front door of the hotel...very handy) up to where the cable car is, on the walk down to it you will pass the public pool and this was the location for the diving and some swimming during the olympics. There is a small entry charge but it will give you so much space to swim about and no crowds, because everyone else is packed onto that awful beach. You also get amazing views of the city from there so take a camera!We had a wonderful steak dinner in the restaurant and if it fits in your budget you should give it a go, but again there are plenty of great places within short walking distances from the hotel. If you do go to Las Ramblas head off the main street for food and drinks as the price will drop dramatically. A 40 Euro bill for 2 sandwiches and 2 beers or a 50 Euro bill for 4 people tapas dinner and drinks, and there are some lovely places just off the beaten track. Also if you fancy a good old burger head straight to the Hard Rock Cafe, not too badly priced and servings so big you will only need a main!!This hotel is in a brilliant location, about a 15-20 min taxi from the airport (15-20 euros), has a metro stop right at its door and you have a lovely stroll down to las rambas. I would definetly return.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>