<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="333ed23642da47d83f969cb03513d22f" url=""><![CDATA[Very happy with the Athenaeum My husband and I recently got back from a 3-night stay at the Athenaeum in Florence and overall had a very pleasant experience. We really couldn't have asked for something better in terms of price, location, and comfort. The Athenaeum is a new, boutiquey style hotel on a quite street about a 10 minute walk from the Duomo - location wise it's perfect because while it's very central, you're not surrounded by throngs of tourists the moment you walk out the door. Plus there are several restaurants within walking distance which are great for dinner. The rooms are comfortable, clean, and modern, the bathroom is a bit small but not uncomfortably so and provides all the amenities (bathrobes, slippers, vanity kits, etc.) and, if you get the superior room, they have this great little patio which is perfect for having breakfast or a cappucino in the summer months. Price wise it's very good value for money - we paid 150 euro a night for the superior room including breakfast - definitely a good price for a gorgeous city with overpriced hotels. Our only grip was the breakfast - there was a very meager selection, many of the items weren't fresh, juices were of the canned variety - but given that the difference without breakfast was 10 euro per room you figured you couldn't really lose - even if you just have a cappucino and a croissant. We had read that the hotel restaurant was very good but didn't try it... Also worth mentioning, the hotel has on-site parking for 25 euro a night, yes, pretty pricey, but worth it if you're touring the area by car as free parking is pretty much non-existant. We drove into Florence from Rome airport and found it very convenient.Overall I would definitely recommend the Athenaeum, we had a very good experience, and plan to stay there again next time we're in Florence.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>