<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="40e85fb389fa1cf7ed97a37e15029265" url=""><![CDATA[Mostly excellent experience My son (18) and I stayed here the last four nights of our two-week leisure trip to Japan based on Trip Advisor and mostly, we were very pleased.The main negative about the experience is that I thought I had booked a two-bed apt. and it turned out to have only one bed. If I ever return to Japan I will be very careful about beds- it's not always clear in the reservation. They didn't have any 2-beds available, so they provided comforters and extra bed linens, although in the final analysis, my son still had to sleep on the floor 4 nights. Their only other offer was to rent an additional room (on another floor) which was not in my budget.Good things - staff speaks English, in fact most business is conducted in English, location is near Shinjuku subway/train station, rooms are very high tech-we counted 9 control panels to operate everything from intercom to hot water heater, bed was very confortable, huge wall-mounted Sharp HD tv with tons of cable channels ranging from the 24/7 Samurai channel (I LOVED it) , all the Tokyo baseball games, and English language CNN and BBC.Bad things - since it's an apartment and not a hotel, housekeeping only comes twice per week. By Thurs, our apt was in desperate need- rainy season and cramped quarters added to the dirt, Size of apt is extremely small considering there's a kitchen and bathroom in the spaceAbout the Shinjuku area of Tokyo...It's a subcity of skyscrapers and commuters. Very lively but far from the touristy part of Tokyo. Fortunately we had done our sightseeing the first two days of the trip. We were in Tokyo for the second time. So we explored all the dept. stores and liked Takashimaya best. We cooked in the apartment, which allowed us to save. The price of groceries is a lot less than eating out. We also took the train to Akihabara one day. Saw very few westerners which added to our cultural experience of Japan.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>