<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="54d136204d610b5bb8567e3d78d31b80" url=""><![CDATA[Ambar a Good Choice We were originally scheduled to stay at the Punta Cana, but changed to the Ambar at check in. This turned out to be a great move.We were seeking a quiet relaxing vacation and the Ambar is an adults only option. So the hotel, pool area, and beach were just what we were looking for.Our room was nice and the location (6300 building) was quite convenient for the Ambar lobby, buffet restaurant, outdoor patio, and workout area. The grounds were immaculate and very colorful.We enjoyed the Machado (Japanese) and Pechado (Seafood) ala carte restaurants the best. I also was pleased with the quality and selection of the buffet restaurants. The Ambar also provided an exclusive breakfast/lunch option and also a nice outdoor restaurant at lunchtime (with a great view of the ocean.)The beach was beautiful but quite crowded. From the people we visited with, it sounds like the long cruel winter drove everyone to look for sunshine. Punta Cana is no longer a secret and this was evident by the hundreds of people on the beach.We took an excursion to Saona Island. The highlight was the flying fish that accompanied the catamaran on the way to the island. Saona was very picturesque, but I could have done without the music that was blaring throughout our time there.We also took a trip to explore La Cana Golf Course, just beyond the airport. This course is a beauty by the sea.The waiters and bartenders at the Ambar really hustle. They are very polite, pleasant, and have good senses of humor. The Ambar was at peak capacity, so try to keep that in mind when service is a little slow. I brought $100 worth of $1 bills and left a small tip every time we ate and had a drink. The servers and bartenders were very appreciative. My wife and I speak just a little Spanish, but this came in handy. The Gran Bahia is very much an international destination. We heard French, Italian, and German in addition to English spoken there. The only thing that kept this trip from being perfect, was the volume of people and the occasional guest who needed to let everyone know that the 24 ounce mug they brough from home needed a refill. Otherwise the Ambar and Punta Cana is a beautiful destination.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>