<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="2ce215f7bdf05ca7e49da0f022a8346f" url=""><![CDATA[Very disapointing My partner and I spent a week at the Tulip and I must say were hugely disapointed at pretty much every aspect of the hotel.Whilst the location is good and thanks to the excellent Paris Metro, offers great access to everywhere in the city, the hotel itself was in my opinion sub-standard.On arrival our greeting was not terribly warm and it took a considerable time for our booking to finally be acknowledged and to be shown to our room.Obviously the building was not designed as a hotel so there is only a tiny lift or narrow staircase to use. Our room was very small and functional with no real sophistication or specific quality although there was a great balcony. The real issue for me was the bathroom - this had been crammed into the room by putting a very thin and simple dividing plastic/glass wall! Not only did this make the room even smaller, but being frosted plastic/glass it didn't exactly allow for much discretion! The bath and shower itself was also old, tiny and unimpressive. In short the room was terrible in my opinion.Two other issues I had were the fact that the bar closes at 22:00 - the bedrooms are not nearby so I just couldn't see the logic and the breakfast was simply awful! Tepid rubbish that was clearly just left on the heaters since being put out at 07:00! (fine if you want to get up at that time on holiday).I genuinely don't write bad reviews for the sake of it and actually chose this hotel on the basis of strong comments on trip-advisor, but I'm sorry to say this hotel was simply a huge disapointment and I would certainly not recommend it.Whilst the last thing you want to do on a city break is spend much time in your hotel room - it makes a significant difference if it's a room you look forward to getting back to - this wasn't!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9e050f44eed9ecc2f2be58eb9c83caf3" url=""><![CDATA[Chic, sexy and modern Stayed at the Granados on business rather than pleasure and obviously this puts a different perspective on my stay.The most obvious thing to say is simply that the hotel is extremely chic and classy, with some stunning art work throughout. Check-in was friendly and effecient and although my room wasn't ready on arrival, the staff were very quick to sit me in the small bar with a complimentary drink. Communal spaces are a little limited, but I actually rather liked that - may have felt differently if this had been a holiday though.The high quality finishes and style followed through to my room which whilst a little small, was more than adequate for me. Really nicely decorated with quality fixtures and fittings. The view at the back of the hotel isn't that exciting! But what would you expect from an inner city hotel.The restaurant and room service was excellent and whilst it was a little expensive, it was certainly not ridiculous. The staff were superb, friendly and helpful - which in some ways is even more important when you are on your own without family!I must admit, I didn't see as much of the city as I'd have liked due to work, but certainly the hotel is well positioned for the main shopping areas.I think this is a superb hotel for business trips or for weekend breaks. It didn't seem the sort of place for children or families (a plus if I'm honest). I do think I'd want something a little more substantial if I was staying for more than a couple of days and with my wife - but I would have no reservations in recommending the Granados. Overall, it looks fantastic, the service is great and the hotel feels high quality throughout.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>