<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="ebd36d42415b6a8a9364b0cdab73ffee" url=""><![CDATA[Third time and I still love it My Mother and I just spent a week at the Iberostar Bavaro (May 18 - May 25) and loved it! This was our third stay there, which is saying alot since we have never repeated at a resort before. We just keep on coming back every couple of years. We went Go-Go tours for the first time and our only complaint was the flights back and forth on USAirways. Lots of delays and transfers in Charlotte made getting back and forth missrable. USair3000 with Apple Vacations is the best way to get back and forth.We stayed in room 1292 and highly recommend it. Remodled, no smell and very close to the beach. It is a garden view and on the first floor but you are just steps away from the beach. You enter the beach right by the beach bar and there is a foot and body shower right there. The first floor was great for my 75 year old mother. The grounds are as clean and beautiful as ever. You constantly see workers out cleaning, pruning and raking the beach. The only thing not clean about the place are the tourists. For some reason smokers can't seem to get the concept of ashtrays and insisted on putting out their buts in the sand. One lady actually caught her cover up skirt on fire because of careless smoking!We never got to the pool this time because the beach was so peaceful and beautiful. If you are looking for music and action go to the pool. If you are looking for relaxing, snoozing and sunning go to the beach. The sand is great, nothing to step on and hurt bare feet.The water is best in the morning, in the afternoon it got rougher and a little seaweedy. You still could see your feet on the ocean floor at all times.We had great weather. Only one sprinkle and thunderstorm. Nothing really to speak of. It is very hot and humid this time of year but there is a breeze that comes off the ocean that makes it bearable.As repeat stayers we received some extra perks so e-mail the resort ahead of time and let them know you are coming back again. Everyone who works there is friendly and as helpful as can be. They try their hardest to make your stay enjoyable. We never wanted for anything. The lobster salad at the gourmet restaurant is great and I adore the Japanese restaurant. Look for the baby peacocks when you are at the Japanese restaurant. By the end of the week I was ready for home cooking, but all in all, for an all inclusive the food is very good.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>