<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="728e23bfa34ae5f859a53c137154769d" url=""><![CDATA[great place with a few problems We stayed at Ocean Blue February 2nd through the 5th, 2008, having booked a last minute trip through Travelocity. been to Punta Cana twice before, staying at the Melia Caribe and the Palladium. The Resort is beautiful and nicely laid out, the public areas are clean and in good shape. After checking in and getting our keys we were told to sit down at an adjacent desk where they would tell us about the resort. The guy was very nice but this was just to schedule a 90 minute breakfast the next morning where apparently they would give us the time-share (they say VIP) spiel, we go. Our family had two rooms in building 1 on the first floor, rooms 1101 1102. It was actually a pretty good location as we were up by the lobby and restaurants for the evenings, days were spent down by the beach which is very nice. The resort is very attractive, plenty of lounges and shade at the pools and the beach. They told us they were fully booked but it was not crowded, and we did not encounter lines at the restaurants. Some of the prettiest buffets and restaurants seen at an all inclusive, and bars everywhere. The bars have premium liquors and they even had bud light beer at the lobby and sports bars (might have been because it was superbowl time). Food was plentiful, but not our favorite. We ate at the Italian, Mexican and Dominican restaurants, reservations are not required and you can do an alacarte restaurant every night. Our daughter loved the bowling alley so we went twice- it was just like home but only 6 lanes, but we never had to wait for one. Bartenders and check in people were great, maids and management are another story. Mosquitos were horrible at night. Our first morning we awoke covered with mosquito bites everywhere we covered.We asked to be moved and when they told us they were fully booked, each morning they told us to try again tomorrow. We bought mosquito spray at the resort shop but that help at all, we also sprayed down with the skintastic we carry with us each night and that help either. I know if this was because we were on the first floor or our just because of our location but we got slaughtered every night. The kids took to sleeping fully dressed but were still bitten all over their faces and hands while they slept. Our room was apparently the last one cleaned each day, usually around 4 pm. Maybe the maids were just wore out by the time they got to us but they do much. The first night we noticed the sheets had not been changed from the previous guests, there was hair and stuff on them. So on the next morning my wife removed the sheets and purposely spilled some pepsi on them, she left a $5.00 tip and an apology for the spill assuming this would get us clean sheets. That evening we pull back the covers and the pepsi stain is there, we believe they made up the bed with the soiled sheets that were on the floor. We ended up finding a maid and getting sheets and making up the bed ourselves. On our last full day, we came back to the room after a great day at the beach and pools to get ready for dinner. While getting cleaned up some people enter our room with a key, and after a confused look they apologize and leave. Ten minutes later they knock and ask if almost done, they need a shower.. Turns out the front desk gave them our room to use while they waited for a late check-out. We told them it was our room so they went back to the front desk and told them people were staying in the room. The desk then gave them keys to our other room and they went through the whole thing again. I went to the lobby to see what was going on. A manager told me that we were to have checked out that day. I told him no, we leave tomorrow. He again said we should be gone. I asked him if like me to go get our trip paperwork to show him we were paid up through tomorrow and he said no and left and went into the back office. After standing there for about 30 minutes with the desk personel smiling and shrugging their shoulders at me I asked one of them if the guy was checking on our situation, they said yes and I continued to wait. After about another 30 minutes a clerk called out my name and handed me two sets of keys for our rooms. I asked if this meant the problem was resolved and she said yes. I still believe the guy never came back out and said anything. So, while we thought the physical resort was great I would make sure on check-in that they have all your details correct. I know what to do about the mosquitos and the dirty sheets, could be a freak thing that just happened to us but the problem was we get anything done about it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e70b9ac3c434b233ed72352eaf6ffa80" url=""><![CDATA[great location nice hotel Other than the sign, you'll think you're staying at an Embassy Suites. The location is great, you're only a couple of blocks from I-635 and the Dallas Pkwy North (toll Road). You can take the toll road straight into downtown, we also took it to connect to the 12 loop to go over to Cowboys Red River, (we had to try a cowboy bar). Both are only 15 minutes away. Going North we went to Carson's Live in Addison a huge nightclub up the road about 5 miles ($12.00 cab ride). And of course the Galleria is across the street, so it was pretty easy getting around for our first trip to Dallas. The people at the hotel were great. Note that there is no smoking at the bar. While it feels like an Embassy Suites, we thought the rooms/suites were nicer. The place is very clean, all the people were great, everyone seemed to really care about our stay. A great value, a fun weekend, we'll stay again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>