<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="13be50e2a70a4318b5f1aadd71848d3e" url=""><![CDATA[Some good, some bad, Mostly good! We were at the Majestic Colonial for a week, in early December 2008. We were blown away by the sheer beauty of the resort, the rooms, the beach, the pool and the delicious food. The pictures honestly do the place no justice, its just gorgeous. All of the servers, bell boys, maids, etc. were totally wonderful to us during our trip. We took our toddler along with us, and everyone was so welcoming to him, bringing us high chairs, blowing him kisses, giving him high fives, and we always heard Hola Baby everywhere we went. We, as parents, were thrilled to see the staff interact with our child. We spent a lot of time on the beach, during which we met Denny, the Beach Consierge, who was very helpful, friendly and wonderful. Our party was constantly sending him back to the bar with more orders for more drinks. Each time, he was more than willing to get what we needed and wanted, and we always saw him smiling. In the buffet, we all enjoyed everyone. We had the nicest bus boys, whos name I wish I could remember. He told us about how he had a son close to our son's age, and was so helpful and polite. The maids barely knew English, but always smiled at us and said Hola as we'd walk by, especially to the baby. In every single restuarant, my son made friends who were so wonderful. Even willing to take photos with him, I was so impressed with how kind they were to him, and that they treated him like their own son. The only name I remember is Jinny because he spent a lot of time helping us. I wish I remembered more names becuase all of the staff was so wonderful, and I'd love to thank them all personally. The staff in the mornings at the Buffet were just speldid. Im so greatful to have met such wonderful people.I had a few things that really frustrated me during our stay - some days we had the coffee refilled in our room, other days we didnt. We were there Sunday-Sunday and didn't get a facecloth until Thursday. We had several power outages, and one even made the AC not work for about 36 hours. Also, one day we couldn't shower because the shower was not working at all. We had no hot, or cold water. When I dialed down to ask about it, the front desk staff were not very helpful and basically hung up on. The lights and ac are all hardwired so that they shut off when you leave the room, which was fine - but the alarm clock constantly would reset itself, which was a pain to us. Perhaps that could be on a different line. During our stay, we were there for a wedding. The wedding was beautiful, and gorgeous, and the staff did a lot to make sure it was that way. However, due to a power outage, the reception started almost an hour and a half later than it was supposed to. When 11 pm came around, the night was over, even though the bridge and groom had paid for so many hours, and lost out. I did not think that was fair at all, especially since we were in a private area, and not causing anyone inconvience. The next day, there was a wedding right next to the pool, and they were still partying after midnight, and someone was singing into the microphone, so it was really loud and echoed through the entire resort. I phoned to ask when it would be stopped, and the front desk hung up on me. I continously called back as I had needed a wake up call for the next day, and never did get through. I thought that was horrible of them, and I was very angry about the wedding being so loud and allowed to go so late in a public area, and being hung up on. I was not pleased with the front area staff during the entire trip. The one time we did have a wake up call to get up to leave for an excursion, it was 15 minutes late. The entertainment was great, I loved the shows I did get to see, the bars were amazing, the music was wonderful, the vendors market was a good safe way to shop, the pool was clean, the free programs were amazing. I did the aqua fitness class with a young man, I beleived named Romeo. He was originally from Haiti, thats all I knew about him. He was very involved with the group, had a great sense of humour and was excellent with the participants. I enjoyed everything about the entertainment and things that were offered to the guests.I went off the resort for the Safari tour, and I'd highly recomend that to anyone. It was worth it to see how Dominican life is. Im so thankful that I was at the Majestic Colonial, despite the few problems that we had, we had a great trip, we met a lot of wonderful people, and we as a couple had a great time, as well as our son. We were so happy and comfortable all week, we loved the food, the drinks, the whole atmosphere. I would recomend this resort (and have already) to anyone interested in Punta Cana. My only wish is that the week went on, and on, and on.. and wasnt over already!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>