<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="fd9dd6d1d40ca4b14415fff99bab61c2" url=""><![CDATA[Great location My husband and I stayed at this hotel in July and found it to be an ideal location for exploring Hollywood and Los Angeles. I have just read a review about unhelpful staff and wish to say that our experience was just the opposite. We too found ourselves in a room facing the wall of the swimming pool. I could not sleep and felt very uncomfortable in this room . On the second morning we asked to be moved. The staff could not have been more understanding and helpful. We were able to move immediately. Having said this I could not have stayed another night in this basement room. It should be made clear when booking that the rooms are inferior but the staff are not to blame. By the sound of it this is probably common occurance! Breakfast was a plaesant experience with the food continually being freshly topped up by a lovely lady who seamed to be running it on her own. All in all out stay here was very good and we would definately return just making sure we dont have a pool wall view!!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dbf7a52e1bd22734a9af96b3bfeef932" url=""><![CDATA[good location Stayed here for 3 nights in July. Hotel is clean and welcoming and extremly well situated but I have to agree with reviewer who complained about the expensive parking charge and the fiasco over breakfast. Although as usual the breakfast is included the room rate was expensive compared to other Holiday Inn Express hotels we have stayed in. The breakfast area was packed out and often nowhere to sit. Many peopel looked around and then had to take breakfast back to their room.Staff seemed to find it difficult to keep the shelves stocked and we were left disappointed with the remaining choice. Because this is a very large, busy hotel perhaps a bit more thought needs to be given to the layout of the breakfast area- moving toastersetc..Overall I would still recommend thsi hotel as the situation was excellent and the majority of staff extremely helpful.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>