<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="19fa5939d03bc5d9937e71665571d399" url=""><![CDATA[Great Little Find My family and I spent 3 days at this hotel in May 2007. The rate we payed was cheap and the hotel was great for the price. The front desk staff spoke very good English and was very helpful. The room and bathroom was a little small but very clean and everything worked including the hi-tech toilet. The hotel had washing machines and dryers which is very handy if you are travelling for a while, vending machines, (some full of beer) and free bottled drinking water in the foyer. There were plenty of cheap restaurants in the area and the subway was nice and close. We found it a little hard to get to the hotel from the airport by bus, but we managed. Overall if you want to spend too much on your accommodation this is a great hotel, and I would stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2307bad971c16c70f129dd5762b8dbda" url=""><![CDATA[OK My family and I stayed at the Schoenhouse Apartments in October 2008. We stayed in room 209. The reception was friendly, but just pointed the way to our room. If you plan on arriving late, reception closes at 20.00hrs, so you might have to make arrangements. The hotel is located in the old East Berlin area, so the surrounds are a little bland. It is located between two U Bahn stations, only minutes to the Rosa Luxemburg station. There are two supermarkets just down the road. The hotel can do your laundry for you, but can be a little expensive. For a small load 4.50 Euros to wash and 4.50 Euros to dry. The rooms are a good size with a large bathroom and a reasonably equipped kitchen. The room was clean, but the 4 days we were there not once was our room cleaned. We were only given one small bar of soap between three of us for 4 days. It would have been good if they supplied a small amount of coffee, tea, sugar and milk for the first day. There was fast wifi available in the room. I think I would try somewhere a little more central next time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>