<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="45fc22d0c2fc5b3facab0c95b72fc8e2" url=""><![CDATA[Great boutique hotel We chose this hotel because of the reviews on this site and were not disappointed. We were given a room at the back of the hotel on the ninth floor (quieter). The room itself was on the small side but spotlessly clean and very comfortable. Location-wise this could not be better, right on Union Square with a Cable Car stop right outside. We bought the 3 day Muni passes ($18) and used them for travel throughout the city. You do not need a car! The staff were friendly and helpful, especially the breakfast staff who remembered us after the first morning. We also found the tour desk very helpful and really enjoyed the half day tour to Muir Woods and Sausilito. You can also book shuttle buses here to the Airport for around $15 per person. Nice touches included the free coffee and fruit in the Lobby plus the free internet access. Overall great value for money, excellent helpful staff, and the best location in S.F. What more could you want?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ff46cceb607346c270379f5adcd27d69" url=""><![CDATA[Great value for money Stayed for 3 nights in this impressive hotel which anywhere else would merit 5 stars. Large lobby/check in area with a huge marble staircase and fountain. Very helpful staff and no delays checking in or out. The room was a superior room with views out over the harbour. (Fantastic) It was large with a huge king size bed and plenty of room to move around. The bathroom was also huge and both were very clean and comfortable. There are a choice of restaurants in the hotel plus an excellent small coffee shop. The choice and quality of food is extensive, especially in the downstairs buffet restaurant, but it is a little on the expensive side. I was concerned about the location as it is a bit away from the action in downtown Kowloon but I need not have worried as there is a free shuttle bus every half hour to Nathan road and the Star Ferry, plus the other ferry over to Hong Kong Island is only a five minute walk away. There is also a lovely roof top pool and Fitness room on the top of the Hotel with fantastic views over the city. Overall this place is excellent value for money offering a standard of comfort and service that you would pay at least three times as much for in central Kowloon or on the island. I would recommend it to anyone.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>