<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="2cf275939048892d96136ea9f0b983f9" url=""><![CDATA[To Each His Own We stayed at the Muse for 5 nights from 8/31 thur 9/5 andcontrary to the last review we were quite pleased. We bookedthe Muse based on a very good rate found on Travel Zoo andthe reviews of others at this website. Our room located on the14th floor was on a front corner of the hotel giving us windowson two sides which made it both bright and we had a satisfactory view down 46th street. The room was large enough and very clean although somewhat sterile. The bathroom was more than satisfactory with nice soaps and lotions. Our only real compalint was only one chair in the room. Of course, with two people, one person must sit on the bed if you spend any time in the room. According to the receptionist, Kimpton plans on refurbishing and upgrading to their standards towards the end of the year. which hopefully will improve the decor and fix the chair situration. They don't need to do anything with the bed, linens or pillows which are all above average. Also, the room was made up promptly every day. The wine reception every evening and free coffee in the hotel's restaurant(except Monday's) were nice touches. We would definetly return to the Muse and highly recommend itwith the caveat that a higher floor might improve your overall perception..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9959bf8006216e785e5883670285442d" url=""><![CDATA[What a Gem! Its nice to find a business that's operated with the satisfactionof it's clientel in mind. The Orchard Hotel certainly is one ofthose businesses. We spent 4 days at this charming hotel.Since our flight from Atlanta arrived in San Francisco around11AM, we arrived at the hotel around 12:30PM. My wife procededinto the hotel while I took care of our driver and by the time Igot inside we had already been set up with a room on the 7thfloor. Not only were there no hassles regarding early check-in, the front desk acted like it was their pleasure to take care of us.Our room was nicely decorated and good sized. The bathroomwas marble and tile and also good sized. The bed was verycomfortable with 4 large pillows. The location of the hotel wasnear the corner of Bush Powell, within a few feet of the Powellstreet cable car. Union Square is a 3 block walk downhill. Buythe 3 day metro pass for $11.00 and you can ride any publictransit including the cable car back up the hill. All hotel personnel were extremely pleasant and helpful. Our maid evenmade it a point to thank us for our daily tip. My hats off to theownership, management and personnel who operate this hotel.Wish there were more like you.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>