<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7d43a6f3658e714d7aacd17126e784a7" url=""><![CDATA[GREAT LOCATION My friends and I had stayed at the Parc 55 Hotel to celebrate New Year's. We chose this hotel because of its reasonable price and its close proximity to Union Square and various restaurants. I have read previous TripAdvisor reviews about the hotel being in an undesirable or seedy location. I found the hotel's surroundings to be fine, especially during the day. Cyril Magnin Street, where the hotel is located, is very busy with vehicles and pedestrian traffic. However, as with any vacation, it is always important to remain vigilant and aware of your surroundings. The check-in process was quite easy. This is a rather busy hotel which is heavily used by the flight crews of various airlines, convention attendees, and business travelers. The hotel staff was courteous and helpful, except for one of the bellmen who seemed to be having a bad day. The seven elevators were rather efficient, timely, and spacious. Our ninth floor room was typical but very accommodating. The bed was very luxurious to sleep in. The bathroom was clean with sufficient ammenities. Street noise was heard throughout the day and night, mainly from police and fire vehicle sirens. But that's typical for any downtown hotel. A temporary fitness center was created on the second floor while the regular fifth floor location is being renovated. It is heavily used by guests and only offered five (5) cardio machines. Free weights and/or resistance training equipment were not available. The only complaint that I had was the hotel's valet parking. Guests are charged $40 dollars a day (plus tax) with in-and-out privileges. This fee could add up if you plan to stay several days. Also, allow between 10-25 minutes for the parking valet person to obtain your vehicle. One day that I waited about 20 minutes. After complaining about the long wait, I was informed by the valet supervisor that my vehicle had been parked at an alternate lot because their hotel garage was full. If you arrive back to the hotel late in the evening, chances are that your vehicle will be parked at the alternate lot. If you're looking for a convenient hotel that provides affordable daily parking, you might want to consider the Cathedral Hill Hotel, just a few blocks away on Van Ness Avenue. They provide a discounted room/parking package. The daily parking fee would be about $10. Better yet, you park it yourself and leave at your own convenience.Overall, my friends and I had a pleasant stay at the Parc 55 Hotel. I would recommend it to any traveler who would like to be in the heart of Downtown San Francisco.TRAVEL TIP: Rather than travel across the busy Market Street to get to the San Francisco Shopping Centre, a quicker and possibly safer way is to go through the underground Powell Street BART station. A Starbucks Coffee is located at the mall's entrance.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>