<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="acd1bc7d4d0b55b917c7ac9143dd8990" url=""><![CDATA[Family Run Hotel, Great Attitude, Great Location My wife and I spent 9 days here while I was attending a business meeting and she was sightseeing. Our friend from Zurich and two of my business associates from the UK also stayed here. After my meetings, I also did some sightseeing, and we all had some great food. The larger rooms are quite nice in the European manner -- not huge like US chains, but well appointed and very pleasant. We had two different larger rooms -- one for two nights, one for six, and a much smaller standard interior room for one night. The standard rooms are small (like those in the Westpark in NYC), but still nicely done -- a bit like the old vaudeille gag -- I didn't have room to change my mind! But that's only part of the story. What makes the smaller rooms quite viable is the very large and pleasant common area and sitting room, with a dozen or so tables and very large windows looking out onto the street below (this room, and the hotel desk are on a very high second floor. The hotel is also computer-friendly. There are two computers in the common area for occasional browsing use, and my laptop found a free WiFi connection to the internet, both in the common area and in both of our larger rooms. Didn't try it in the small room. Others have mentioned the 24-hour buffet as a nice plus, and it is. My wife and our Zurich friend especially liked it. There's even beer and wine, and it was nice to be able to offer it to friends who met us in the common area before going out to dinner together. It was almost like greating your friends in your living room! The coffee is a weak point -- if you like it strong, you'll be disappointed -- but there's a great coffee shop and bakery about five blocks up the main street. The location is very good, especially if you want to get around on Barcelona's excellent bus or subway systems. My business meetings were in the new CCIB, which is on the oceanfront in a rather out of the way part of town, but there is a direct bus route only a block away that got me there in 20 minutes. There are also direct bus routes to virtually all of the tourist destinations and restaurants. There are stations for several major subway lines within about three blocks. Important hint: go to the transit office in the nearby Universitat subway station (a few blocks southwest) and pick up the EXCELLENT bus map. Map makers around the world should be studying this map -- it's the best I've seen, both for the busses and as a map of the city. And it's FREE! Also, go for the 10-ride ticket, a real bargain. It's good on the fine subway system too, and you can transfer, but it's far nicer to see the city on the busses. For this reason, we rode the subway only once. The only downside of the bus system is that the last run of the night is often before you've finished dinner (restaurants don't open for dinner until 9 pm), so you may be in a cab for the ride back to the hotel. Oh yeah -- the bus back to the airport stops only two blocks away, making it very easy to get out of town (but with a separate fare, roughly 5 Euro, as I recall). Barcelona is a great city -- can you tell we loved it? Great energy, friendly people, lots to see and do.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>