<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="552075906b2692f3df1aca40b6c45d7e" url=""><![CDATA[All Round Good Hotel! Unbeatable Location!! A girlfriend and I booked a weekend away and chose the Marriot when our first choice in a hotel turned out to be unsuitable. We were not dissapointed.Having been to Sydney many many times, the hotel is in an unbeatable location. Within 50M walking distance is Circular Quay, which will give you access to ferries all over the harbour, as well as Manly and the North Shore. The Circular Quay train station is also 50M away and will give any keen tourist access to the rail network.We were pleased to be able to walk down to the bars and have a nice drink. On Sunday we also ventured to the markets, and though heavily geared towards non Australian tourists, they were nice to wander through and probably an easy 500-600Metres walk from the hotel.The package we received included valet parking, and upon arrival we were greeted and the car was quickly taken away. A big relief that we didn't have to navigate a parking garage ourselves.The staff were lovely, and we were given a room, as requested, with 2 double beds. The room was tastefully decorated, and very clean. The bathroom was very clean also with lots of space. A nice treat when 2 women are travelling together. There was also a small desk and lounge chair.A buffet breakfast was also included the next day and it was lovely. 1 of the best i have had. Espresso coffee/ hot chocolates / lattes were included. This is very rare. Champagne was also available and included. A pancake, omlette and egg chef was also on hand, and plenty of everything. There was however a long line when we were leaving, so probably best to get there before 10.30 am on a Sunday morning.We also sampled room service when we got home after a few drinks and though a little pricey, it was absolutely beautiful and delivered very quickly. In fact, they have a policy that if it isn't delivered in 45 minutes it's free.Overall, a great hotel in an awesome location. We will definitely stay again and reccommend to our friends.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>