<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="8f01ca3e3556291ef6a6a6a6a96edf45" url=""><![CDATA[looking tired I stayed here for 1 night on the club floor. I booked through ichotels web site and asked for a king bed. Check in was a bit slow but i was upgraded to a kind of suite. This had a hall, bedroom and tiny living room with gravel balcony. The decor was early 80's and not that well maintained,stained walls from water seepage, battered paintwork and the tiles around the bath had holes for old fittings drilled and just left making it look a bit dirty. A nice touch is the senseo coffe maker in place of the usualinstant sachets. The club lounge is pleasant enough for a drink but didn't eat anything there. For the 180 euro i paid i guess it is ok for this city but i would pay the usually higher prices
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e2c96a6efc3e274e6baec62b192d88f9" url=""><![CDATA[Lovely Stay
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1104fde683648338aa801b840ccd3bf5" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel, Good location I booked here at short notice through a website for 109 euro which is good for Amsterdam at the moment. I had a room with a view over the flower market and Muntplein. Reception staff were freidly and efficient. The room was smallish butcontained everything needed inc. tea/coffee and safe. Both room and bathroom were clean and well maintained.The bad points were the queen bed was 2 singles which drew apart during the night(very romantic!) and the shower going from perfect to scalding to freezing, that they really should fix. If not for this i would give 4*
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2328f9f0fe0b10ccc5111547b4824f7c" url=""><![CDATA[Pretty Average I was in Berlin for 5 nights over Easter and spent the first 2 here. The Lobby and bar ismodern and pleasant though the service to get a drink was very slow. .on going to room the was noone to carry luggage . The room itself was clean and modern but quite small. With the usual facilities. The bathroom was small with hairdryer etc, though the towels were small and coarse. The king bed was 2 singles with flat pillows and no pillow menu and surpringly the bedding wasn't changed daily.After 2 nights I was more than ready to go to the Intercontinental, which is often available for about the same price as the Sofitel
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="81e3d1578eb5adbc2e0b591daea46467" url=""><![CDATA[Freezing cold A 2 night stay in a suiye on top floor of hotel, on arrival all heating in the suite was switched off. This in January with -3 C temp !!. The bathroom is heated only by a towel rail so never warmed up and on 2nd day just as the room was comfy housekeeping came in and switched the heating off again. This is unbelievable behavior in any hotel let alone a 5* one. The living room had a view of a dirty terrace with old fireworks and cigarette ends on it. The bedroom no view. Tried afternoon tea in the lounge, the food and tea not great and the service so bad it became a comedy. Good points, most staff were friendly and the hotel is clean, the location is also great.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>