<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="c2ffd1f6b9301b6c217ca4bd8a15f5fc" url=""><![CDATA[The room was great, so was the location! I stayed here after a carnival cruise. The location of the hotel to the port was THE BEST! I literally walked off the ship, out of the port, down and across the street to the lobby of the hotel. My luggage was 66lbs and the weather was hot and humid! The location was great!The room was great spacious and comfotable. I stayed in a smaller hotel before my cruise, and I could literaly fit my first hotel room, bathroom included, in the the bathroom of the Sheraton.The staff was nice and the location of the hotel in Old San Juan was perfect. Everything was in walking distance (food, scenery, shops etc).I would reccomend staying here if you are going on a cruise or just visiting San Juan.Also, I would reccomend eating in a resturant that is close by. I am not sure of the name, but it is on the same main street as the Sheraton (to the left, facing the water), the next block after the coldstone creamery (yum). They have tables outside and a small eating area inside. The food and service are excellent!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="731ff1a609c6b86294e8b6cf811357a3" url=""><![CDATA[Birthday Vacation The staff was wonderful, friendly, and oh so helpful.Although not allowed I tipped the staff and I did receive the royal service.The lobby and beach were beautifulThere was construction when I visitied.There is always the beach and the activites were not available because of the weather. Other than the beach the activites are limited. So it was more of a realxing vacation as opposed to an adventurous one. I really enjoyed myself. I would reccomend the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b49b6b9563777fdcecbd7e9cdac5e85d" url=""><![CDATA[Small but Great After a night of partying or after a walking tour of the french quater, the bed in this place is FANTASTIC. The rooms were small, but well worth it. The hotel is located within walking distance for everything. I recommend this hotel for long stays, short stays, over-night. We stayed in the river tower. We had a view of the mississippi river and Canal Street. Like I said the rooms are small, I wouldn't recomend more that two people to a room.The lobby area was always lively, plus the drinks and the food in the lobby were tasty.Although frowned upon by many reviewers and some people at the hotel, I love the elevaor and the concept that you get on the elevator that is not going to make frequent stops.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>