<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="8ee20690980cea874619a3efa31d6a1b" url=""><![CDATA[Home away from home Well, let's see. This hotel in my opinion is the flagship hotel for the shangri-la group. We alwalys stay at shagrila when we travel (if there is one in the country where we are traveling to).Since this wasn't our first trip, i was surprised that the staff remembered us and they knew exactly what fruit we liked and had it waiting for us. As for service, we can find nothing to complain about (and we are very fussy people)There is a painting or tapestry that is 15 floor high and it is just beautiful. The breakfast at cafe Too is unbelieveable. There is a variety of fresh fruits, fruit juice, cereals, breads, pastries, yogurt, cheese, selection of eggs, chinese dim sums, soup, congee, coffee, tea, noodles. This is breakfast by the way.I didn't use the health club so i can't comment on it but i did have tea at the lounge and i had a good time. While we were there, there were some princesses for Saudi Arabia.(so one would think that the staff would forget about other guests and only entertain the royal family but nope not at the shangrila, they treated everyone very well. and if you didn't read the newspaper and saw the picture of the princess you wouldn't know there was royalty staying at the hotel) Therefore, this has to be one of the best hotels in Hong kong. The rooms of this hotel is excellent. The size is huge for hong kong (38 sq.m.) and the view of the harbour room is wonerful...you can actually spend hours just looking out the window at the traffic of the harbour.(yes there is traffic at the harbour in hongkong). However, if you stay at the peak view room, the view is also beautiful. The bed is fantastic. I slept like a baby and when i woke up in the morning i was ready to face another day with full energy.The mini bar is well stocked. and the range of coffee and teas available for you to make a drink for yourself is also huge.There is LCD tv not only in the room but the bathroom too. The toiletries in the bathroom is top notch. Do not fret if you forgot your comb, toothbrush, toothpaste, laundy detergent or razor as you will find all of this in the bathroom. You have a iron and ironing borad in the room too......and there is lot sof space to hang your clothes.Juat below the island shangrila is the Pacific Place which has almost everything. It is really a one stop shopping.The staff at the hotel is simply wonderful. We needed to make reservations for dinner and i am so depended on my secretary that at that moment i actually missed her and i asked the concierge for help and they were so nice and told me to contact them for anything i needed and only did they make the reservations for me but also faxed the confirmation to my room. A friend needed to have photographs taken to apply for visa to china and we were plesantly surprised that the business center of the island shangrila offers this too. If you need to top up your prepaid mobile phone chip.....do not worry, you can do that at the business center of the island shangrila.There is really nothing that this hotel doesn't do. I can guarantee you that on our upcoming business trip to hong kong in september we will be staying at the island shangrila and make it our home in hong kong. As the staff say welcome home as we checked in. Not very many hotels say that to you.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4c398ce7a7115d66ae50e7cbdcc98132" url=""><![CDATA[Will be back I travelled to hongkong on a business trip and the Island shangrila was full therefore i had to opt for the kowloon shangrila. I was a little skeptical to say the least. The service was almost as good as Island shangrila. I will be staying there again this september........did my bookings a few months ago
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>