<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7841c085fcc0dbde8e22fb2b5201073a" url=""><![CDATA[Go with an open mind and you will have a fantastic time This review is a little late, but I couldn't resist writing it after reading the last review.Eleven of us, ranging in ages from 14 - 70, enjoyed two great weeks here in March '04. So much so, that we are all returning for the same in 2006, only going Platinum this time.Yes, you will find things different in the Caribbean than North America, but isn't that what most of us go for? Superb weather, beautiful white beach, Dominicans that treat you as you treat them - a Hola, a smile or a tip for the young waiter who works so hard for the lunch crowd or the fellows that constantly raked the beach and (if you took the time to ask them their name and about their family), remembered your name the rest of your holiday.The food is different from what we are used to - Caesar salads are not like anything we have had before, but order a green salad instead. Most meals we really enjoyed. Dominican night in the Hispanola was not a favorite, but we found fried chicken, french fries and green beans, so didn't go hungry. The pasta station was always excellent with a good choice of ingredients.We did have tiny little ants in our room the first day, but were prepared from reading previous reviews and spread pennies around. Don't know if it was a result of that or not, but not an ant was seen after.If you are having a cup of coffee in the room, take a minute to rinse the cup out before setting it down - no bugs! The same if you are having room service, whether putting the dishes outside or leaving them in the room. Warm climates have unexpected critters, that is a given.Towels and bathing suits don't dry well with the high humidity. Taking an extra bathing suit along and exchanging your towel each day will alleviate that problem.We have holidayed in Florida and had a cockroach crossing our carpet and the odd lizard sharing our balcony. And, lots of those inch long bugs with a million feet, all in an expensive condo.If you are looking for a holiday where you are guaranteed great weather, fantastic beach, good food, lovely apartments, friendly natives who look you in the eye when greeting you AND you can accept the small things that maybe are not up to your standards, then this is the place for you! If not, try one of the beach areas in North America.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>