<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="4ab3f04e44da3d2fc3ea658e8809b0bf" url=""><![CDATA[Majestic Colonial is Awesome! Stayed at the Majestic March 1st -6th. We were impressed with the hotel from the moment we stepped off of the bus. Before we could even make it to the check in counter, our bags were taken care of and we had frozen drinks in hand.Our room was available upon check-in, we stayed in 2351 (Ocean Front). Room was absolutely beautiful and the view was breath-taking. We spent a number of nights on the terrace enjoying a drink and the sounds of the ocean. Jacuzzi on the terrace is awesome, however, takes a good 20 minutes to fill (well worth it once you get it going!)House-keeping was great and had no negative expereinces. Mini bar was refilled daily with water, beer,and snacks.Pool and beach are awesome, we typicaly arrived at the pool between 8:30-10:00AM and always found chairs available. The entertainment team is great! I found all of them to be very personable and professional. Most of the team spoke 2-3 different languages. Our favorite was Paublo who took the time to introduce himself not to mention he is a great Spanish instructor!The Spa was very good and reasonably priced, we enjoyed a 55 minute couples massage. I found the massage to be equally as good as one might experience at a Spa in their hometown.We found the food to be average / good with many choices to select from (Breakfast Dinner meals we enjoyed the best). The beef pork taste very different than here in North America (although some enjoyed it). Service was always excellent, our glasses were never allowed to go empty and we were always greeted with a smile.The shows in the evening (especially the Michael Jackson Show) were very enjoyable, followed by time at the disco with the entertainment team. The casino is small but enjoyable.Outside of the hotel resort grounds there is a small shopping plaza. I DO NOT recommend shopping there. Extremely high pressure, none of the items are marked with pricing, and you are usually quoted prices much higher than the items are worth. We always offered 70-80% less than what they quoted and they always took the offer. All the items at the shopping plaza are also offered within the hotel resort, properly priced and marked accordingly with no pressure.Overall we found the Majestic Colonial to be a great resort and a good value for an all inclusive. You won't be disappointed at the Majestic!If you have any quesions feel free to send me a note and I'd be more than happy to try and answer your questions...Ray
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>