<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="aa525406950741a6028593ac29bb495b" url=""><![CDATA[If the location only matters... If your want to stayi in Waikiki and to be close to the beach, and near all the 5 for $20 t-shirt shops... this place is for you. The lobby is nice and so are the staff, and that is where in ends. The rooms are small, and walls and doors poorly painted. They have tried to brighten the area up with blue an yellow colors, but failed. Other than the fitted sheet, the bedding appeared dirty or soiled and needed to be replaced. If the wind was blowing, the windows whistled... I check the door to the lanai, and everything (believe me).Now, they do offered valet parking, which is convenient when you are tired and want to relax, BUT the enterance is opposing traffice, and can only fit at most three cars at a time! Very fustrating as it is right next to a bus stop.Great place to stay if you are only looking for a place to sleep, and are on a budget... but if you are planing to relax in your room, and enjoy a slow paced atmosphere... try again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ef0c684916010a3e5434c20b16d9085b" url=""><![CDATA[Ahh... Relaxation and comfort We had the pleasure of staying at this resort in early May. Very beautiful, and well taken care of. The staff were pleasant, and welcoming. The restaurants were great, yet you will pay for the comfort. We had lunch at the Rainbow Lanai and it was over $50 for the two of us, no dessert, and one drink. There is plenty of shops to visit and look at, and even one of the thousands ABC stores on the island. The beach area was beautiful and relaxing. The noise of other areas of Waikiki was gone... just the sound of waves and walkable beaches (no rocky shorelines). A little recommendation... save yourself the headache, and once you get into your room, immediately throw away any card, flyer, note, brochure that refers to free items or scratch-off prizes. Unless, you like to sit and listen to timeshare presentations all day and like to say no alot. I did so, and glad I did (after seeing the faces of many friends who were curious).Also, spend the extra money and take some type of formal transporation. The hotel has arrangements with taxi companies, including Charlie's which for $12.00, took us to the airport in a limo. I took the city bus one day to go see Pearl Harbor, and lets just say, Tyenol and a comfy bed was my friend the rest of the day.Great place, great atmosphere, beautiful views, and several photo opportunities. Even if your not staying there, walk down one night and get some photos.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>