<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="fb4dc3541ff197135f81065d39978021" url=""><![CDATA[Jazz a favourite We stayed at the Jazz for 5 nights at the end of May, largely based on the reviews on this site.I found most hotels in Barcelona expensive (and unavailable) when I was booking in April, so don't regret the 160 euros excl VAT which we paid. We couldn't get a booking through the hotel website (it showed unavailable) but managed to get a room through Venere.com. The first welcome surprise was that the Airport Bus stops in Plaza Universitat. Very convenient - you simply cross the square to Calle Pelai, walk a few metres, and you're at the hotel.The check in staff were amongst the top three hotels for friendliness and helpfulness in our entire 5 week trip in Spain. They were also very helpful when we wanted to organise a day trip to Montserrat.The Hotel Jazz is a brilliant location. The Metro stop at Universitat makes getting around the city very easy (buying a 10 trip ticket was perfect for 5 days), its a short walk to Las Ramblas or across to Passeig de Gracia. Across the road on Pelai is a great little cafe for breakfast - Viena - and there are lots of bars and restaurants around. The room was large, clean, in a contemporary design - just like the website. We were on the 6th floor and had no problems with noise.There is free internet access in the bar - two PCs there - which was very welcome to holiday makers who had determinedly left their laptops at home, but by this time were going through email withdrawal!Although it was still quite cool in Barcelona, the pool area was busy whenever we checked it out. Kids loved it, and the roof is a nice place to relax after a hard day sightseeing or walking the city.I have no hesitation in recommending the Jazz.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0aa6db8a629efe9743affb3072c8b7d2" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Hotel We stayed at the Swissotel in January for a week, based on recommendations from this site (and the Michelin guide).The Swissotel is well located on the Ku'damm shopping street, with plenty of restaurants nearby, U-Bahn, S-Bahn and the major Zoo Garten train station only a block or so away. (So close a taxi refused to take us there on arrival in the rain, but it didn't matter!) The Story of Berlin is just up the road, the Kaiser Wilhelm church just over the road, and in the opposite direction is the famous KaDaWe department store.The breakfasts are excellent, there is free internet access in the lobby for those who aren't business travellers with laptops, an espresso coffee machine in the room, large comfortable rooms, good security for floors, etc. Do bear in mind however that this is a business hotel - which means there will be convention/conference groups. With no offence intended to the previous traveller, they can tend to take over the lobby when you are there, and it is difficult to get a quiet drink in the lobby bar at certain times of the day! A note - as we left, it again started to rain. We were heading for the train station, and the doorman asked us to wait, and reappeared with two large Swissotel umbrellas. When we protested that we could not return them, he shrugged and said never mind! That is the kind of service you expect from an excellent 5 star hotel like this.We booked on the Swissotel website, and got a good rate of 165 Euro for a business room, with a street view, bkfast included. It was worth it - we felt we might have felt claustrophobic with the courtyard view rooms. I would recommend Swissotel to anyone travelling to Berlin.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>