<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="58666575ada100ba206d96ec17b8f395" url=""><![CDATA[Incredible London Value Contacted the Sumner after reading all the excellent Trip Advisor reviews. Right away I knew we had made the right choice because of the efficient, courteous and professional manner in which they corresponded with us.We stayed 5 wonderful nights in a spacious and most comfortable king room. The driver and car we requested was right there to meet us after customs at Heathrow and take us to the hotel. The location was great...it took us about 3 minutes to walk to the Marble Arch Tube Station. (If you are going to ride the tube quite a bit as we did, I suggest purchasing Oyster Cards before you go. They reduce the fare for each ride per person from 4 pounds to 1 1/2 pounds. You can purchase them online from the Visit Britain website). There are several restaurants within two to six blocks of the hotel...I would recommend Prezzo and Seaport...they were both excellent...Prezzo very reasonably priced and Seaport a little expensive but well worth it. You are also only two blocks from beautiful Hyde Park, where you can walk forever.We paid 145 pounds per night and besides the lovely room, that also included a very nice breakfast with both hot and cold items, Wi-Fi in the room, a computer with internet access in the lobby, room service at anytime for tea or coffee, and the assistance of one of the most helpful staffs we have encountered anywhere in the world for absolutely anything. You can pay twice that in London and get a tiny room with a cold breakfast in a not so good location and then have to pay extra for computer access.The bathroom had a shower only, which we prefer, with fantastic water pressure, instant hot water, nice toiletries and soft, fluffy towels. The room had both heat and AC, both of which you could adjust to suit you. We had two floor to ceiling 12ft high windows, which you could open, but when closed you could not hear the street traffic.I can't imagine a more pefect place to stay in London..we will definitely stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>