<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="40929c92d77ae062accc084751af4b0f" url=""><![CDATA[Classy, clean, perfect location, great staff. This hotel is beautiful.Although it has a small lobby and the room is not that big, the quality of the room and the service makes up for it in a big way.I got here and everyone was very polite and check-in was a breeze.The room had a great workstation with a leather chair and a printer/fax. The internet is wired which sort of restricts you to the desk,The TV is in the perfect spot. The bathroom and shower were impeccable with great soaps and gels that smell superb.The towels are nice and thick and the bathrobe is very comfortable.Although there is only a bar and no resto, your in NYC and there are great places to eat no matter what direction you head in.This location is a few blocks from broadway and a bit less to 5th for shopping which is super becuase time square is so noisy.There is a concierge downstairs who is willing to help you with all your requests.The bellhop ran directly into traffic to get me a cab.....( he's still alive too!!) There is a small workout room with low impact machines (all new)I have been to plenty of hotels in NYC and spent more on other places but this place has been the best gem yet.If your in NYC and your looking for a great place to stay where it's relatively quiet, this is your best bet.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fbca4209a42dc82fcc301faca1f1fcb2" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel, Nice people- perfect stay I read some of the reviews and was a bit nervous about what I'd see....but I was pleasantly surprised.I stayed there for 2 days....(1418 faces the city)My room was beautiful, facing the city. large and very comfortable, clean heavenly bed with a dual head shower.The TV is at an akwward place but if you pull it out of the armoire your good to go, the only thing was that since I use my laptop on the desk , My back was facing the TV which I did not like.The People there from the front desk to the Valet were super nice and very helpful. The bar was OK....but the bartender was a grimacing little man who could not smile if you gave him the winning powerball numbers.Workout room was nice, with brand new treadmills, free weights, and other new peices of equipment.I recommend that if you stay there, you rent a vehicle because the hotel is more then just a few minutes from the west end and uptown. Besure to check Vino100 in uptown if your into wines...Good for Business people and honey mooners....kids will not be as happy because there is no pool, there is however a skating rink in the plaza that connects directly to the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="edbdad3f5c4891974896753b4b60dd8a" url=""><![CDATA[Super Nice place..BIG ROOMS!!! Nice place...very clean.Pool area is great for the kiddies.Lounge is nice and big with a few TV'sFree WI-Fi in the whole building...Room was super big (Ask for a corner King)Bed is really comfortable with 6 pillows.Bathroom has whirlpool jets but I'd never soak in there....I was upset with the room service adding 18% + 2.00 delivery and then you have to tip the waiter. C'est la vie....Paid 80.00 for this room and it was worth every cent.A couple of minutes from DFW and across the highway is a theater and some chain Restos.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>