<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="08a30dac177c3be2d857b546aa9a60ce" url=""><![CDATA[Paradisus was Wonderful! My BF and I stayed at the Paradisus, PR and were Royal Service guests, from May 28 - 31 and on the overall, we had enjoyed ourselves tremendously!Pros: The grounds and landscaping, albeit still very young, were nice enough and weren't an eyesore; for the most part, the staff aimed to please, there were enough activities that were pretty good to keep guests occupied, the pool was beautiful, all the restaurants were operating fully, the casino was a happening place, the bars were packed (also due to the fact that the Resort was fully booked that weekend); our requests for specially prepared foods were obliged; the buffets and foods served at the specialty restaurants - Bamboo (the best Hibachi I've ever had cooked by WingLock!) Romantico - were not bad at all for an all-inclusive; the gym is one of the best most equipped in any hotels/resorts we've ever been to; the Spa was wonderful though pricey; Jennifer and Leslie at the Royal Service had made on-the-spot decision to drop us off at the airport when our transfer had left without us.Cons: Some front-of-the-house staff needs to learn to speak English, especially in a popular restaurant like the Avocado; the Paradisus should cater to those with restricted diets (i.e. fat-free, low-fat diets); the staff needs to get their act together when it comes to managing big groups or a lot of guests staying at any one time; the transfer bus had actually left us behind despite the fact that we had confirmed our transfer at a certain time and were waiting at the lobby (this was soon rectified)!; room service for breakfast didn't arrive; the marble floors can be very slippery when wet (from rain).I have to mention that Pablo, Leslie, Jennifer and Yoshira from the Royal Service, and Luis from the Mirador Grill had made our stay all the more enjoyable! Thank you keep up your good work!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>