<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a3e4f8ec6f8e5ddd8160c143643a873f" url=""><![CDATA[Amba: Beautiful and Immaculate! My husband and I and our friends and spend a lovely week at the Ambar. We flew west jet and the flight was smooth, great staff, very friendly, everything was on time.Our transfer was very efficient, 7 of us to Bahia Principe and then a quick transfer to the Ambar for check in. We were not checked in on the bus but it was quick and efficient when we arrived, the place was full and all week there were offers to go to other resorts owned by BP; later in the week it switched to offers to go to the Majestic. We had requested a corner room in a front building in advance and knowing that there are no guarantees, we got a ground level room in the back. The door was broken so we did not feel safe leaving our belongings, they tried to fix the door, poor guys did not have the proper tools, my husband was holding a pocket flashlight for them. Anyway the room was a bit musty so the next day we requested a move and were moved to building 64 second floor, we loved this room and location, mere minutes to the pool and beach! The room was so clean and lovely, requested more water and diet Pepsi and no problem! We got a welcome gift, rum and t shirts. We left tips (American money) and small gifts every day on the pillow, one day I hope by mistake, they took Canadian money my husband had left with his things on the dresser, plus the gifts I had left for them. So be careful what you leave lying around. Saw the butler the first day, he did not introduce himself, only later did I figure out that is who it must have been, never saw him again even when I went looking.The resort is beautiful, and the cleanest I have ever stayed at, the food was medium, it was good but not great. Always something or usually too much to eat. I was disappointed in the drinks, the mixes were very sweet and not the variety we experienced other years. On the Punta Cana side and Bavaro side the drinks were much better, the drink of the day was better and more variety, not sure why? The drink I liked the best A Dirty Monkey, they would not make at the Ambar, I asked several times. I found the staff very reserved, this could be because many did not speak English well, we did try out our terrible Spanish, and they appreciated the effort and found it humorous. The beach was beautiful, lots of people but did not seem crowded, we walked for miles. The water was so pretty, nice surf, sand so soft. The pool was the cleanest I have ever experienced, lovely.We tried several of the a la our favorite was de Paris, nice atmosphere and good service. Next was Don Pablo, again nice atmosphere. We liked the Mexican because of the atmosphere, the food was not great. We had fun and really liked the food at the Japanese, it was a bit confusing they have two Japanese restaurants, with very similar names, we checked at the lobby to make sure we were in the right place and they told us we were, of course we were not and had to hustle to find the right place, several other couples made the same mistake. We also tried Garden grill, and Portofino, the worst by far, had to go the buffet to eat after that one, it seemed to be the consensus of the guests here this week that the Portofino was having problems with food and service at dinner, breakfast was great here, and it was closed for lunch. They tell you there are no reservations but the restaurants were never more that half full usually less that that. They are very fussy about the dress code for men at this resort, we go to 5 stars all inclusive every year and this one was by far the fussiest, you could not go to the buffet in the evening without long pants and closed shoes, and not for lunch or breakfast without sleeves on the shirt. On the other hand women could go with a see through beach cover up with boobs showing and it was not a problem, the standards were inconsistent. One couple arrived and their luggage was lost and the gentleman had no long pants, no exceptions, they would not let him dine at the buffet. They were too rigid in my opinion.The towel game has not changed, but since my husband did not mind getting up early it was not a problem for us.Entertainment, the night we arrived we made it to the disco because we wanted a drink and everything was closed. Not our style but people seemed to enjoy it. We went to the karaoke bar later in the week but it was too smoky to stay. The outside area in the square was nice but we were up early so only made it there once. Went to two shows, Michael Jackson and Lion King, I enjoyed them but my husband was not so keen.Used the internet to keep in contact with home, no problems, a bit of a wait, usually never longer than 20 minutes, depending on the time of day. Other comments: would be nice to have more no smoking sections, there was a lot of smoking and you could not get away from it, the pool and all the bar areas, the lobby did have a designated non smoking area but open air so still exposed to it. Safe: not so safe all you had to do was push reset and anyone could get in to it.Never shopped or did any excursions, we were happy to relax on the beach or by the pool. We found the guests to be friendly and happy, only saw one incident where a guest was being horrible yelling at the staff because he was not happy that there was no pizza ready, give me a break!The resort is huge and a bit confusing, I was addicted to trip advisor so no surprises for me but I think that color coding the different sections would be helpful, easy to get turned around.We liked the Ambar side because it was quiet, people were more sedated, we saw a number of party animals on the Bavaro side.Met lots of wonderful people! Pictures do this place justice! We like to try different resorts but would consider going back some time in the future, have been to Sandals and the service here is not on the same level but then again either is the price.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>