<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="2316c1f8fc662fce62c7ed1376d7a151" url=""><![CDATA[Good Standard Stop Over Hotel Firstly, I've read other reviews on this property and had to ask myself what do I expect from a hotel directly relating to the purpose of my visit .I see Mercure Hotel Sydney Airport as an overnight stop over before or after travel and have used it on three occassions now with very little complaint.These reviews are to rate a hotel as you see it and not to try antanticipate what others standards are and what they may want from the place. I appreciate that peoples standards vary with experience and needs etc. Please read my review based on this.To us the Mercure Hotel was clean, comfortable and reasonable value with a park and fly deal for seven days booked directly through the property.Yes, the restaurant is a little expensive but they don't try to hide their prices which are clearly displayed at the entrance. We didn't have breakfast there so won't comment. The bar was disappointing. The barman on the night we stayed appeared uninterested and unfriendly and the drink prices were excessive. Fortunately, little of our travel time is spent hanging around hotel bars. There is a perfectly good club venue with meal and bar facilities within a short walking distance of the hotel. The front desk staff were found to be courteous and efficient. No more could be asked and no more was looked for.The twin standard room we booked was clean and comfortable. Fittings were a little tired or well used but again quite adequate for a short stop over. Beds were comfortable and linen conducive to a good nights sleep. Towels and toiletries etc were also fine. No complaints for the money paid. We were not spending a lot of time in this room so have to be fair in judgement. Mini bar is from a machine in the hallway and charged to your room card which is one way of short cutting those that take delight in abusing the usual system.A wake up call booked for 0430 was on time and the shuttle service to the International terminal was efficient and also on time. (No problem with the return shuttle service either). We have stayed here before and also at Holiday Inn Sydney Airport and would rate both similarly. The only disadvantage of the Mercure is that long stay parking is in the open whilst that provided by Holiday inn is usually undercover. In general, few complaints compared to others. If you are not overly critical and discerning and fairly laid back in your approach to a simple airport stop over hotel than Mercure will do you just fine.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2c170e51b2aaaca681956a71a156f82f" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel We needed a one night in stay in Sydney to attend a concert at the Entertainment Centre. Holiday Inn Darling Harbour could not have been any closer to the venue and is very handily located for other activities in and around Darling Harbour and Chinatown.I believe the hotel has undergone a recent renovation and had additional floor(s) added. Starting with reception everything was excellent. Desk staff were extremely courteous and efficient. The Concierge had an excellent knowledge of the city and was able to give great assistance with driving directions etc. Parking is limited and we were accomodated in the Entertainment Centre Car Park which was a short 3 minute walk.The room we had booked several months back direct through the hotel was a queen deluxe with breakfast package and we were pleasantly surprised to receive an upgrade to an executive suite on one of the new upper floors. The room was great in every regard. Spacious, spotless,modern and well furnished. As we were on a high floor, monorail noise mentioned in other reviews was not an issue.Eating options at the hotel included a restaurant that served an excellent breakfast buffet and a bar/grill with a limited but good quality and well priced menu and drinks. They cater well for people attending evening concerts at the Entertainment Centre across the road. Meals are light with a reasonable choice on the special show menu.It was hard to find fault with this hotel and based on this experience we would most definitely stay again. Accor hotels often receive mediocre reviews for the perception of generic brand or sameness but to some of us there is a certain comfort in knowing what to expect quality wise. This is the case with most Holiday Inns we have stayed at. The same concept of familiarity seems to work ok for McDonalds !!. 10/10 Holiday Inn Darling Harbour.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>