<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="8eb6563e0fa66fc69ebf2a418f38f49e" url=""><![CDATA[Stylish hotel in great location Good clean hotel with boutique style -great location 5 mins walk from Marble Arch. Stayed in room 107 which is on third floor front facing Upper Berkeley Street . Two nights bed breakfast cost in king room- shower only -no bath. Original sash windows with secondary glazing kept out the worst of the traffic noise - my husband tells me I slept through a thunderstorm so street sound wasnt a problem.Lounge area was very welcoming - the whole Hotel had an ambience of staying with a well healed friend with an eye for detail.The breakfast room was in the basement and part self service style. Tea Toast was brought to your table you could help yourself to cereals,continental style ham cheeses, crossants,preserves, juice,scrambled poached egg,sausage beans - dont think I missed anything... Breakfast area could have done with some more air conditioning as no windowsWe read in an earlier review that the poached eggs were like bullets - yes they were more like boiled eggs but the scrambled was perfect!London itself was busy as half term holidays - avoid Oxford Street if you can. Take in Regents Park, take tea at the Ritz (book in advance wear shirt tie) have a stroll round Fortnum Mason the old victorian arcades of Picadilly - we walked to all these areas from the Hotel.Go in The Sherlock Holmes Museum Baker Street and have a laugh at the letters he still gets.The hotel kept a list of local restaurants with 15 minutes walking distance which was a welcome nice touch.Thoroughly recomend Hotel would stay again - maybe next time they would have tea coffee making facilities in room
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1627f038fa0093f00ec073e19cfea296" url=""><![CDATA[A jewel in the Amsterdam crown You will find this lovely hotel a peaceful retreat only 2 minutes walk from the busy Rembrandtplein. As previous reviews state the rooms hosts are welcoming the breakfast (served at 8am as requested) superb with warm croissants, cheese,fruit, yoghurt, choices of breads with jam butter (we requested no meats which was noted) and a choice of tea or coffee. We had coffee again to repeat previous reviews it was the best we had ever tasted - all served on a clean matching china set.It does feel like you are a welcome guest in a very nice canalside private house. We stayed in attic room 9 (150 euros per night) right at the top of some very winding steep stairs- choose a lower room if you have a heavy case! The room was better than expected as had a T.V a newly installed fridge cleverly disguised as a marquetry bedside cabinet - sweet touch. Everything was clean in order as shown in the pictures on their website.Mosquitoes were mentioned in another review so did take repellant although we only saw one in the room.The hotel provided a very useful map with the hotel a few sites ringed - we walked to most areas in our three 3 night stay.We caught a taxi from the train station (11 euros) but took the tram (no 4 from Utrechtsestraat) to return @ 3.20 euros for both for the return journey. Highly recommend would stay again on returning to Amsterdam - may be to room 5 as passed the room on the way down stairs looked in as the door was open - as well as the opulent furniture,mirrors rugs they had a large flat screen t.v small courtyard garden- great stuff! Hope you enjoy your stay as we did.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="896ef71572c98b16fd2fdef9eb433af6" url=""><![CDATA[boutique style hotel near arc de triomphe just off champs elysees Booked romantic package for 3 nights in superior room costing 975eurosChecked in at 11am left bags behind reception with friendly advice that check in was after 2pm.We returned at 3pm after a stroll around Eiffel Tower which was 15 mins walk away from the hotel waited 5 minutes to find luggage had been taken up to our room (41 facing north) . Pre ordered music candles half bottle champagne, small fancy cakes,- rose petals arranged in heart shape on bed was lovely - we were here to mark 20 years of being together.Well decorated clean room with huge bed, seperate bathroom to WC felt like a small apartment with french windows opening inward - we sat in window with champagne baguettes (bought at nearby convenience shop) looking on to beautiful french townhouse - no city views from hotel.Breakfast in small area close to reception - got busy with smartly dressed French business guests -very good selection - pancakes syrup, pastries, toast, scambled eggs, fruits yoghurts,juices, cereals (plus more) although milk for cereal not chilled there was a small fridge with cheeses boiled eggs.Found Paris very expensive due to exchange rate but worth it especially in the lovely sunshine we had.All the tourist sites had large queues but recommend the hour wait for Notre Dame 7.50euro each to go to the top (queue down left side as you look at the cathedral - the queue in the front entrance is for looking inside for free) and dont miss the eiffel tower lit up at night.Metro similar to london underground 5.30 euro each for all day pass.Go to small Orangrie gallery on the place de la concorde for Monets huge water lilie canvases - get there @ 9am be the only ones there No sight of upgrade or parting gifts as other guests mentioned but good superior room with bathrobe complimentary slippers Recommend
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>