<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="ad79ff02d6619310f186dc057d2f413d" url=""><![CDATA[Four Seasons George V I decided to surprise my mom and take her to Paris before Christmas to do some shopping, having fun, and get in the holiday-mood.I heard George V is the number one hotel in the world so I expected number one service - and we did not get a bit of it.I must tell you, I was really disappointed about it.Location is good, flower decorations just amazing, rooms grandious (a bit funny though, there are lots of prisms and drops missing from the chrystal chandeliers - i guess memorablia for previous guests...), but thats all.Upon arrival our taxi could not take us to the entrance as drive-way was full with cars. We got out on the street, pulled out luggage from trunk while 4 personell was watching us at the entrance - no one helped us, even not, when going towards the entrance!! One just let us in, did not ask if we need help...After check-in, the guy came out from behind the desk, took the luggage from my mom and asked me if i dont mind bringing my luggage myself... What a service... :(We usually got out of the room around 9 am and got back around 4-5 pm. One day when we entered the room after 4pm we just realized a made is just working in our room - there was no sign outside! As we were very tired, I asked her just to do the beds and leave us, she did not understand it in English, had to call Housekeeping to ask them to translate what I need. Even after that she did not do it, just simply started to vacuum clean - whilst we were already in the room and asked her to leave!There were no appoligies later, nothing at all, it was like nothing happened.I tried to use the swimming pool one evening, but I had to leave after 15 min or so as it was full with kids (at least 6), jumping in the water, and being so loud like hell, nobody from staff asked them or the parents to stop this.Concierge was also strange, gave us just wrong information and was not helpful at all.The only place where I got the special Four Seasons touch was the tiny gift shop, the boy was really nice, helpful, fun, offered assistance way beyond his duties.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>