<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="43d192d240018d4b4c17473d07607a31" url=""><![CDATA[5-Star Hotel w/ 5-Star Price This is an unexpectedly very nice hotel located on a quitter side of Bali though it's a bit far from everywhere. It's indeed one of the 5-Star ones. I'm rating it above average instead of excellent because it absolutely has no beach though it's located right across the Tanah Lot temple. The beach is there, but don't count on being able to sunbathe or walk along its not too sandy shore, as the wave is pretty strong most of the times. Besides, Tanah Lot is one of the most famous tourist spot. All the vendors will immediately run after us -tourists- as soon as we step on the beach. From the hotel, you can cut through the scenic golf course route, landing at the entrance of Tanah Lot market to visit the Tanah Lot temple. There are many small cafes along the Tanah Lot market and there are 2 larger restaurants, one of them is called Melasti. Though it has the best spot in the area, I will not recommend having any meals there due to the very unstable prices. The hotel has a 54 meter slide that entertains all adults and children. There is a smaller/shorter slide in the side/kiddie pools as well. These slides are comparable to the ones in waterbom-kuta, so it's best to save your money and time spent travelling to kuta.BTW, there are free hotel shuttles that go back and forth between the hotel and kuta area. Don't bother stopping by Bali Galleria Duty Free Shop. It's a waste of time. The price is on average 3 times as much as whatever we pay in the US (New York tri-state area), and they're fixed.Handy Tips: Tourists will always be asked to pay more than local Indonesians. With that said, don't hesitate to bargain in the local Bali market (that is if you can stand the smell). My mom scored a 3-feet tall mahogany wood carving of a lady carrying a jackfruit on her head for a mere $30. The asking price was well above $300. :) And don't hesitate to ask for local prices/menu when dining out. In Jimbaran bay, the local price is Rp.55,000/kg (US $5.50-6) of catch of the day (fish). While the tourist price is Rp.19,000 (US $1.90-2.20) per 100gram of catch of the day. My jet-lagged head is currently thinking that 1kg=1000 gram. Don't forget to double check...Feel free to contact me for other travel tips to Bali.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>