<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="a6398dd6aa64695b9c78f41d09b4154b" url=""><![CDATA[Great Rooms The rooms at the Intercontinental Boston Hotel are on a par with the best luxury class hotel rooms, such as Four Seasons and Ritz Carlton. The only thing this hotel lacks is the level/quality of service and attention to the little things. The rooms are fantastic. Spacious, well designed and very comfortable. The bathrooms are even better. Great tub and a separate shower; both with great fixtures. The sliding window between the bath and room is an innovative design that we enjoyed. But here is an example of a little thing that separates the great hotels from the very good. The IC linens are a 60/40 cotton/poly blend. Why not spend a few extra bucks on fine quality 100% cotton sheets? Other reviewers have made points about there not being a coffee maker in the room. I can live with that....Ritz Carlton and Four Seasons don't have coffee makers in their rooms either. I was glad to find complimentary coffee available in the lobby on Saturday (between 5:00 am and 7:00 am). However, when I went down on Sunday morning, I was told we don't put the coffee out on Sunday. Why not? Another little thing that separates the great from the very good.Some other pros and cons.Pro: Nice outdoor area on Boston Harbor with an outdoor restaurant and benches for relaxing. Con: Music from outdoor restaurant was annoyingly loud.Pro: Great Location: Close to South Station MBTA, easy walk to North End.Con: $39 overnight parking. Tip: If you are there on a weekend and don't need your car, skip parking at the hotel. Drive cater-corner to the hotel to International Place. $9.00/day covered parking on the weekend and after 4:30 on Friday.Con: Most (not all) of the front desk and just about everyone else we encountered were not overly friendly. Not rude, but certainly not warm. Just sort of disinterested.Bottom Line: We thoroughly enjoyed our stay at our Priceline rate. Had I paid rack rate, I might not feel the same way.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="50a58e8d6bbe330541fb03073e5e2b01" url=""><![CDATA[The Library delivers - again! This was our sixth stay at The Library, and this will be my sixth review. I only wish I could give it 6 Stars, because this hotel deserves it. All of the reviews that rave about this place are absolutely correct, and I can only reiterate their compliments. For this review, I will focus on the friendliness of the staff. Upon our arrival, the bellman recognized us from previous stays and gave us a hug. It was like we were coming to visit friends. During our visit, we spent some time in other, very high-end hotels. The stuffiness of the staffs with their noses up in the air only reiterates that The Library gets it. Provide a superior product with great customer service and your business will be rewarded. Well done Library - again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>