<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="2c4c71029dc60ece706582d13b748b55" url=""><![CDATA[TA Scores Again Our family (two adults and two teen agers) were steered to this hotel by other TA reviews and, as usual, were not disappointed. The room was large; for New York, very large. The decor was stylish and attractive. The beds were very comfortable and luxurious. We had plenty of closet space, the bathroom was great and first class. Really a nice and comfortable space.The hotel staff was way beyond what I expect in terms of service. Unlike many, I find New Yorkers friendly and helpful as a lot, but the staff here was as helpful and attentive and fun as any I have ever experienced (and that is a large database). The common spaces were somewhat tight, but typical for Manhattan. The exercise room had everything I needed..good, but not the best. The location was good for us...just on the edge of the busiest part of Midtown east...a short walk to either MOMA, theaters or the delightful residential neighborhoods near the East River. If I had to pick on something, it would be that the kitchen was a little downscale from the rest of the room. Given that we received a free upgrade to a room with a kitchen, I can't complain. And it was fine, but just a little on the cheap side relative to the rest of the room and hotel.We paid about $300 per night in high season for the four of us...not too much by Manhattan standards. In short, unless you are going budget with price as the necessary and primary concern, this is a great hotel and a great value.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="21de0e28c38f967336909418f1c9216d" url=""><![CDATA[Super Value We paid less than $100US for a room in a luxury hotel in the center of DT Toronto. If you can get in on the less expensive rates at this hotel, snap it up, as it is an extraordinary bargain. The room we had was fairly large with a small view of the lake from the desk in the corner. Very tasteful decor-- think Restoration Hardware furnishings for those who are familiar...great kitchen facilities, too. The bed was a dream. Out the door and three steps is the King subway stop and everything DT is in walking distance.On the other hand, i agree with those who say the hotel is learning. I paid $5 a day for high-speed internet and unlimited calling in N America (I don't like getting nickeled and dimed at hotels, but this was a reasonable price for the package). The high-speed internet never worked. The very nice young man who came to fix it put a hole in the wall moving a heavy armoire to get at the connection. And that is when we discovered the thermostat that we couldn't find to turn down the air conditioning. The curtain out to the lake view was stuck and hard to move to and fro. I found the staff very attentive and enthusiastic, but there were a lot of little things that a more mature hotel would have worked out. All of this is small potatoes when you pay Comfort Inn prices for a beautiful luxury hotel.Drivers Note. Parking is $25 a day. If you are staying only a day or maybe two, or if you need access to your car while you stay, that is market rate for right around the hotel. If youare staying several days and plan to leave your car alone, and you don't mind hauling luggage a few blocks, you can get $13 a day or so for parking down on Front Street. Prentiss CoxMinneapolis-St Paul
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="561691961f7f02e4ab4f9c4237d757ab" url=""><![CDATA[Stylish and Pleasant The hotel is stylish both in its common areas and in the rooms. The lobby has different sections and levels that make it intimate, with comfortable and attractive furniture. The rooms are beautiful. The beds and desks are set in an unusual, pleasing style facing the window and balcony. The bed itself-- way comfortable. The setting of the hotel was less pleasing. It is off by itself between an elevated highway exit and a canal/river. This provides a nice river terrace, but set in an isolated concrete jungle that is hard to get out off. I am not familiar with Miami and so my complaint here may be more about this rather unappealing downtown than the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="74f25efe919043485d812b1ac5a33aa5" url=""><![CDATA[Great Value This may be the best value in the US for a hotel in the tourist center of a tourist city. The Chancellor has a 1920s feel. The rooms are nothing fancy and on the smaller side, but they have a lot of character. The bathroom, for instance, has a real high-sided tub with shower, not a modern shower. If you want luxurious and up to date, best go elsewhere.If you like an older feel and want value, this is the perfect hotel. I booked online and paid $89 (pretax) for my room-- not a special rate. The room had a partial view of Union Square. The wireless access was free-- I was on business and this was very useful. The hotel has an arrangement with a neighbor health club for free use. The staff was friendly and helpful. Everything was clean and well-kept. If I had paid $200 a night, I would have been satisfied. I was almost a little fearful of what I would get for the price, but wow...
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>