<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="8f9f99b9594ccff4e1b41e7897db89f2" url=""><![CDATA[Comfortable hotel, but couldn't care less staff... I stayed 3 days in this hotel before heading home after nearly 3 weeks of solo travel in China. The hotel is very new and modern with most comfortable bed and I had a very enjoyable bufftet. I did not have any problem with taxi drivers as they all knew about Financial Street and InterContinental, which was one block from Westin.However, I did come across a few unacceptable responses from the hotel staff/service. I asked for direction to the nearest metro station, can you believe it ? no one knew, doorman, concierge plus one just shake their heads, may be Westin guests never use metro ! Eventually, I was pointed to a direction which would take me 20 min on foot, so I ended by taking a taxi to where I was going. The following day with a map, I strolled to the nearest metro station Fuchengmen in 5 min. This lack of basic local info from doorman and concierge is unbelievable.I am a Gold Starwood member and normally expect a newpaper in the morning. This did not happen on the first day, but even after reminding the guest services and they apologised for the oversight, it still wasn't delivered each morning, so I gave up.The hotel offered a shoe shine service. My shoes were returned in less than 5 min in the same state, is this Westin ? I have taken the trouble to write these comments on the guest feedback form. It has been over 10 days and I had no reply from the hotel management nor guest services, just like the paper !
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="96dc1b43a6c8d331f9c91750ded31a21" url=""><![CDATA[Sadly, I have to report less pleasant experiences about this hotel We are frequent visitors to Hong Kong and are aware of this this hotel in an eye catching location of Kowloon. I booked a standard room there for 3 nights using my Priority Club points, and that maybe the reason of our treatment.I am a Platinum member normally treated at least cordially, but this hotel seems to treat reward stay guests as a act of charity. We where given the smallest room (according to the floor plan, only one such room exists on each floor) on the lowest floor more suitable for a single, with barely enough space to walk pass each other. I expected standard room for reward night means standard like anywhere else I stayed, but not here. We had to call for a tea tray as it was not provided in the room, a kettle was delivered with some sachels of 3 in 1 coffee. Since I do not take sugar and my wife does not take coffee, that was not much use. My wife called the next day to stock the tray with some tea, some tea bags were delivered but without milk...One would think such 5 star hotel can at least provide a well stock tea tray...makes you wonder was it incompetence, or deliberate policy to provide the bare minimum for reward night guests...The view from the hotel is excellent, but if you know Hong Kong, there are countless 5 star hotels with just as good view. Hotels need to provide more that just view/location to attract returning guests, I certainly will not.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>