<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="8ba7032e7a539761b3a05493c868a4e9" url=""><![CDATA[Would not return - Very Rough Around the Edges This is the place that you want to send someone you do not like to. They will be guaranteed not to enjoy their stay. They will also be guaranteed to hear the Bahia Principe theme song at least 4 times a day.We are both American, I am 28 and my girlfriend is 26. We both are very active and like to work out. We were there from June 30 - July 9. We have been at numerous all inclusives in the Carribean and this does not even come close to any of the others.Try to learn some Spanish before going because it will greatly assist in communicating with the staff. We know enough Spanish to get around, so that did help us.LET'S START WITH THE POSITIVES.+ + The beach and ocean were awesome. Get there early in the day to save a good spot.+ + The housekeeping service was also very good. We tipped our maid a buck or two a day and they made cool towel oragamies and got bubble baths ready for us as well as stocked our mini-bar with extra drinks if we left notes.+ + We did not need bugspray, in fact neither myself or my girlfriend got one bug bite the 10 days we were there.+ + The cocktail waitresses at the lobby bars provided good service as wellTHINGS THAT WERE SO-SO* * Needing reservations to do anything on the resort. You will need to make reservations to use any of the watersports that are free. We needed to make an ocean kayak reservation 2 days in advance. You will also need to book reservations to the theme restaurants. Save yourself a headache and do this the first day you get there. I highly recommend it because it is a nice change of pace from the buffets. Also, if you are Gold or Diamond club book your reservations through them instead of the general guest services. Be prepared to make booking your restaraunt reservations a procedure. The resort has about 1800 rooms and only 6 restaurants. * * The pools are off of the beach, but they are close to the beach and pool bars. The further you get from the beach, the hotter it is on the resort because the beach breeze does not make it past the palm trees on the beach. Also, they are very crowded and loud. They play their only CD that has about 3 songs everyday and the CD is on repeat; I kid you not.* * The gym is located in the spa. It is small, but servicable. It is open from 8AM to 8PM, so you can't get there early if you are an early riser. It has 5 stationary bikes, 2 treadmills, dumb-bells, and a peice or two of nautilous machines.NEGATIVES- - The service at the front desk. We needed to get our room changed because it was located next to a part of the resort that is under construction. This took half of a day to resolve this matter while they left us sit in the lobby. They lack motivation and don't really care about the guests because you can't really leave the resort once you are there. After we got our rooms switched, we had to carry our own bags to the new room. It doesn't sound like a big deal, but it is when you are carrying 2 fifty lb suitcases through 95 degree heat with humidity, no wind, and the sun beating down on you.- - The Buffets could be much better. The first two days we were there we thought the food was good. The problem with the buffets is that they serve the same dishes of food every day for every meal. I will say that the breakfast buffet was good. Also, the wait staff would take your plate even if you still had a few bites of food left; it was like they got a commission for every empty plate they took back to the kitchen. It is also very difficult to get a drink in the buffets, soda or alcoholic. The trick is to have one person stay at the table to order while the other gets their food.On about day 6 we both started to have stomach issues. It may have been from the theme restaurants or the buffets. We did not eat a peice of lettuce or any of the salads the whole time we were there to try to prevent it. Go armed with peptol and immodium. Remember when I mentioned about making reservations at the restaurants; that doesn't coincide very well with upset stomachs.Other guests. We were very surprised how few english speaking guests there were. The majority of the guests were either French or French Canadian. Along with the French language comes some visuals that you do not want to see. I am talking about topless sunbathers that have no self-awareness or decentcy. I know it is another culture, but some things just shouldn't be shown in public. It is like taking a gun into the airport, you just don't do it. Also, for all the ladies the fine men like to flaunt their speedos or even thong speedos. I think I have said enough, I still have some nightmares. There was also a large number of guests from South and Central America. Some of the lack of self awareness goes on to their children because they would releive themselves right on the beach or by the pool in full public view. Again; I kid you not.The Spa. We both got messages, which happened to be reasonably priced. The problem with the messages was that I came out of it sorer than when I went in. I really don't think they had any formal training. The Spa is also a long walk from most parts of the resort.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>