<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="4e38892c122bb5905b91933d80a6024c" url=""><![CDATA[Windows wouldn't open, view of hall and air conditioning machines This is the prettiest horrible hotel I have ever been to. Possibly the casitas in the old section are what gives it its rating. We did not see one.Our corner Plaze suite was BIG and an extremely long walk through two courtyards (my heart began sinking when I saw the first courtyard. I had an idea what we were in for as I saw open windows and the people in the rooms and closed windows along the dark halls I was walking in). The door to our room opened to a large, lovely living room with loud, admittedly pretty, stereo music greeting us. All blinds were closed, here and in the bedroom which adjoined. When I opened them, I realized why - The bedroom looked out on the air conditioning system - six huge compressors. I tried to open the window - not a chance!The living room looked out on a dark hall and blank wall with a table against it to stop the eye. Those windows didn't open either. We were in sunny Arizona with no way of breathing the air unless we propped our door open and craned our necks to see some sun and sky. When we turned the stereo down we could hear the roar. Even when we left it on, as we did all night, there was still a strange high-pitched noise we could not obliterate.I walked the 10 minute walk back to the front desk, with a wonderfully patient bellman working his second job while trying to get a real estate license, to ask for a different choice. My husband, who had just broken his elbow horseback riding, waited. I was told I had booked the new Plaza area. I had never been told the difference. The only other available room, I was told, was a deluxe room (no living room, which might have been OK with me in exchange for air) so we went to look. That had a balcony, and an opening door, overlooking...the parking lot.I didn't bother trying other choices. Actually, supposedly there were none. There were rooms that looked across a courtyard at other rooms. Not much of a choice. If your room faced the road and the hall, the other option, your windows did'nt open because it would be too noisy. We actually could still hear the cars through the fan vent in the bathroom ceiling.As mentioned in other letters, the pool is too crowded. The restaurant was fully booked for dinner when we got there, but no one had suggested when I reserved a room that I also reserve for dinner. In a way, we turned out to be lucky as it was mostly closed in like the rooms.I could go on as our daughter and her husband and two sons, for whom I had also booked a room, had sililarly difficult experiences.What did I learn? Always ask if the windows open. Just because American Express says it's a Fine Hotel, don't believe it! Don't believe the pictures. Saving grace, our room faced east and a lovely sunrise wakened us.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>