<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="73a81a146b1e954ba456397e12b210b4" url=""><![CDATA[Why we were blue at the Ocean Blue We (a couple in our 40's with 2 teens ) just got back from a week at the Ocean Blue yesterday. I will rate our vacation according to the following categories.1. Arrival- We flew in from Cleveland on Delta. No problems at airport, except we had to buy a $10 tourist card for each person prior to clearing customs. We had transfers included via funjet, which contracts with VIP tours in the DR. Found the VIP tour rep, who sent us with a porter and our bags to find bus #44. After a 10 min trek thru the parking lot, finally found the minivan which took us on our 40min drive (with ac) to the hotel. So far, so good.2. Check in- We had only internet confirmation of our reservation, which confused the clerk at the front desk. After a 15min delay, he got a supervisor over who figured it out. We were assigned to our junior suite, #2109 and pointed in the general direction. Got a map of the hotel, a voucher for 1 game of bowling, and were told to tell the bellman where to send the bags. Some language barrier, but both my daughter and I speak some Spanish, so we were OK. No welcome drink.3. The room- A very nice 1st floor large room with 2 queen beds and a sleeper sofa (twin). Nice sized balcony with 2 plastic chairs and a table. Working TV with satellite (had cnn as well as movie channel), small fridge with water and soft drinks, small dresser, adequate closet with inadequate hangers (but I had brought extra, so was OK with that). Safe didnt work so called front desk who said they'd send someone in 15 minutes. Bathroom was nice sized with 2sinks, shower, and jacuzzi tub (which we didnt use).After a half hour, luggage still not there. After 45 minutes, someone came to check the safe and confirmed that it wasnt working, and said they would get someone to fix it. It was about 3pm by now, and I sent my starving family to the buffet to eat while I waited for luggage and the safe to be fixed. Luggage came in about an hr. (tried to get bellboy to fix safe but he couldnt). Family came back and I went to eat. Someone else came to fix safe while husband was in room, but couldnt. Came back just as safe expert arrived with some kind of recoding machine and finally fixed it.Well, at least we were all unpacked by then!3.The pool- 2 beautiful large clean pools, uncrowded, unheated (but didnt real need to be). Everything is very close together, but they have trams running for those who dont want to walk. A swim up bar in each pool. One jacuzzi (We didnt go in). One free standing bar in between the pools, a bar at the beach, and a buffet and bar combo between the pools and the beach. Adequate supply of plastic lounge chairs in good condition, with some umbrellas and tables.Waterpolo area in pool. Shallow kiddie pool area. 4. The beach- Lots of canvas lounges (often full tho) covered by some poles with canvas coverings (you can see photos on other reviews). Ocean was full of kelp and water was quite sandy. Not much swimming room-rope barrier was in place to protect us from many boats,etc. ++ fumes from boats. Rock climbing wall on the beach (very limited hours). Bocci ball, volleyball on the beach. Shack set up for water sports, rentals etc. Drink service at pool and beach was entirely self service, tho there were some busboys going around picking up used glasses. We were issued a towel card (one per person) at the front desk. Often, there was a lack of clean towels and we learned to reuse our towels rather than risking taking back our towel card. They keep saying Quince Minutos (15 minutes) for a new towel, when it can really be and hr or more.5.The food- Dont quite know where to begin.The buffet at the pool is open from about 10:30 to 5pm and has hamburgers, hot dogs, fruits, basic salad, pastries, icecream, and several varying hot dishes and breads.Fruits were very good. Otherwise, food there ranged from ok to terrible. Very little seasoning to foods, heavy on the starches. Often ran out of ketchup. Strange icecream flavors (very heavy on the rum raisin, prune?!, and coconut, and a pink one that we think was bubblegum). Other buffet was open for breakfast, lunch and dinner. Food was better there. For breakfast, there were made to order omelets and pancakes, donuts, pastries, fruits, breads, lox (no bagels), cheeses, and a hot table with different meats, cooked items and again lots of starches of varying types. Oh, also cold cereal, juices and juice drinks. Lunch was similiar, except no omelets of pancakes-different meats etc instead. Ditto for dinner, with the addition of a pasta station and sometimes a psuedo-asian section and some grilled meats (sometimes steak, chops, etc.). Fair to good quality in general. Had to eat at the buffet the 1st nite, after that could reserve specialty restaurants every day from 7am-3pm at a manned computer at the entrance to the buffet.6. Specialty restaurants. Food was quite variable. Dominican was the most pleasant, as far as service and speed of service. Dominican food in general was very starchy and not very seasoned, but it was interesting to try it. Appetizers were the best there, as was the drink they brought (kind of a fruit punch with alcohol). Mexican was not authentic at all. Soggy tortilla chips, OK salsa, an appetizer buffet that was OK. Main dishes were made with (I kid you not) Velveeta cheese and were one step down from Chi Chi's. It was here that we waited half an hour for dessert while our waiter made himself up a food plate from the buffet and ate it. American restaurant not too bad but service was OK. Velveeta cheese again here, on the hamburger. Italian- avoid the pastas- get the shrimp tempura (dont know how that became Italian, but it was good.)7. Coffee shop- Very good. Good cookies. Pies and pastries not so good. Coffee and coffee drinks are good and the service is fast and pleasant as well.8.Service- This is where the place fails miserably. With the above noted exceptions, and some friendly bartenders , for the most part the service was simply awful. Tables were very slow to be cleared at the buffet. The staff would watch you looking for a table, sit in a section, not bring you any silverware etc, and then finally redirect you to another section, only to make you wait again for silverware, coffee water, etc. Several times my husband or I went up and got our own silverware or coffee, only to be rebuked by the same waiters who couldnt be bothered to get it 1st. I often felt invisible while waiting for a drink at the bar-no acknowledgement at all while they either cleaned something, rearranged the glassware, or left the area. Of course, sometimes they were serving other people (who got there after me).Service in the room was no better. My daughter did sleep in late (til about 12 to 2pm) so we didnt expect the room cleaned early. However, it didnt get cleaned at all.We had to make several calls to the front desk on 2 occasions to finally have the room cleaned by about 6 or 7pm by the poor night maid who got left with the work (we tipped her). This was after tipping the day maid $5 to get us enough towels and water for the 4 of us,and $2 on the night before.Finally, we were stood up by the bell boy on the way home- waited a half hr and finally carried our own luggage to the lobby. No apology was offered.9. Activities- Bowling was fun, however the scoreboard malfunctioned and it was $15 a game after the 1st free one. There were 2 air hockey tables (one working), several pool tables, and 2 foosball tables (with some broken parts). There was a disco that opened at 11pm (OK per my dtr), a casino (dont go there) that opens at 7pm and closes at 3am),shows at 10pm-11pm (contests, song and dance, one folkloric act from Santo Domingo- they tried, but were just ok to terrible), vendors one night at the resort (bargain very hard- dont pay more than one third of what they ask), ping pong at the pool, and a kids center at the pool. No organized teen activities. Dance lessons at the pool, and water aerobics-pretty good. The music at the pool was very repetitive and annoying. The activity staff seemed pretty hardworking, but were mostly friendly to only very attractive young ladies and men, if you know what I mean. My 17 yo daughter was hit on by an employee at the disco who gave her his phone # and asked what her room # was. She was completely creeped out, especially when he showed her photos of his family.10.Insects and other wildlife. Mosquitos at dusk, mostly attacked just me. Lots of millipedes crawling around the room. Crickets and grasshoppers in the halls. Bats flying around at night. Most excitingly, my daughter discovered a large tarantula while attempting to open our safe one evening. After a bloodcurdling scream, my husband ran over (we all ran the other way of course) and killed it with a shoe. We asked the maid about it, and she said they were very rare, but then we saw them mounted for sale for souveneirs at the beach!11. Shopping- There are vendors at the beach. Again, they ask exorbitant ammounts of money($11 for a keychain) and then seem insulted when you offer them a fair price. It is possible to bargain, but there are really no bargains here. We took a cab to Plaza Bavaro which was even worse- stall after stall of the same souveneirs at inflated prices, and people yelling at you to come into their shops for the 1st sale of the day where everything is 50-99% off.12. In summary, I would not return to this resort or this island. They both have alot of potential, but for the price we paid (close to $7000 US for our family of 4 on a holiday week) we could have had a much nicer experience either on a cruise or at an all inclusive in Mexico (which we have done in the past).
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>