<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="720eaec06a45a99725d5a730ab4fb928" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel in Decent Location To start I booked my stay (over rememberance weekend) using points and I am Hilton Honors Diamond.Check in was quick and efficient. Our room was not ready but we were able to use the exec lounge while waiting. We did step out to have some lunch at a Thai restaurant across the street, Surchard (or similar to that name) but it was only average and slighty expensive. When we got to the room was pleasanty surprised with a very modern looking and although slightly small room but still very modern and well appointed. We did have lunch in the bar area one day and the service was good and price was not bad for a hotel. Evening drinks in the lounge was nice and although busy never too full and the liquor offerings were good. Lounge breakfast was basic but did have some eggs and bacon each morning so a few hot items.There are a few restaurants in the area, the two we dined at and liked quite a bit where http://www.dimt.co.uk/ and http://www.strada.co.uk/ which are located right behind the hotel and nice view of the tower bridge. There are also several nice looking restaurants and bars that are on the tower bridge road but we did not try any of those. Also, the HM Belfast is right behind the hotel as well and it was nice that we got to take the tour of the ship and it made it even better since it was rememberance weekend.For transportation to the hotel we just took the tube. It took about one hour but with the oyster card it was 3.50gbp to Heathrow on the way tot he hotel and only 2.00GBP on the way back since it was off peak. I am sure there may be quicker ways to the airport but the price was right! From the airport just take the piccadilly line to the jubilee line and transfer at green park. Pretty easy. Green park does not have escalators but has elevators if you have much luggage.In closing, definitely would like to stay at this hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="852fe79a8079e4177f92dd8800a4aa62" url=""><![CDATA[Nice property with excellent service Me and my wife took an around the world trip for our two year anniversary which also served as the honeymoon we never took. We had a 3 night stay in Honolulu on the way back from Japan and elected to book the romance package on the hotels web site. I had stayed at this property before on a priceline stay and remembered it being a nice property. I have done a lot of business in Honolulu and have stayed at almost every hotel it seems and service is always spotty so I decided to go back to the Prince. The service was luckily as I remembered it which was excellent. Everyone from bell desk, valet, check in and restaurant are really friendly and eager to please. Best service of any property I have been to in Honolulu.The room we had in the package was an Ala Moana suite which is a 1 bedroom suite with 2 full bathrooms with a TV in the bedroom and living room area. There are spa style amenities in the bathroom. In the living room there is a dining table with 4 chairs, sofa, coffee table and some end tables. Nice except for the sofa which looked very dated and could go but other than that it is a large room and nice to have the extra space. Internet it also in the room at 10.95 from noon to noon (not 24 hours). Both rooms have somewhat dated furnishing but still nice and the carpet seemed relatively new and it is extremely well kept. The view gives a view of the ala moana park, the marina and a partial view of the ocean. I actually think I like this view over a full view as it adds some contrast. Our package included a $100 dining credit and free breakfast. The dining credit is good for about 1 meal for 2 people and although that lesser expensive meals are avaialable the Prince Court restaurant had great food and great service as well. The menu in the evening is limited to price fixe menu options and a buffet which range from about $35-55. I had one of the fixed menu options as I am not a big seafood lover and my wife had the buffet as she loves seafood and we both went away very satisfied and full. There was also a great wine selection. We also had breakfast each morning at the Prince Court and since breakfast was included I dont know the cost but it was good with a pretty good selection. I actually expected more asian breakfast options but there was a few items there. We did not eat at the Japanese restaurant while there. If you do not have breakfast in your room rate there is a Mcdonalds across the street if you want a cheape option than the hotel restaurant. I do believe ala carte is available for breakfast well but didnt look at the menu. There is a lounge area in the middle of the hotel but lacks any real character for me so other than a quick sandwich or quick drink with friends before heading out is about all I find it usefull for. I think a nice bar/lounge in the middle would serve the place better.I did not play on this trip but did play golf at the hotel course on previous trips and the rate is decent given the rate that out of state people normally pay and it is out in Ewa which is a bit away and tends to be drier but the course was nice and never crowded in the times I played. I always had a car but I think they have a shuttle that runs between the two. They also have a shuttle to waikiki so you really dont need a car if you dont want to deal with that, it runs about every 30 minutes so I would say it is convenient. The location of this property is right at the entrance of Waikiki and to me that is a plus. I really dont like staying in Waikiki as it is such a hassle to get in and out as your are going anyplace on the island but its location allows you to easily get to Waikiki when you need to go but also easy access to the rest of the island such as north shore or return the the airport. There are some good restaurants and bars nearby so you dont have to walk far if you dont want to go into Waikiki. Chart House is always on our list.I think the $199 rate I see at the property is borderline to what I would pay for this property but for a priceline bid it is a bargain for sure. Any discount from that rate in the future and I would definitely make this my regular property here. I just like the convenience and the service that much. I definitely recommend this property to anyone thinking of staying here in the future.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a23e8af43f0bfe867202e362b378a113" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel in a great location This property is one of the better in Singapore I think. I like the location even though most people prefer to stay in the Orchard Rd. area if they are on a leisure trip this hotel has some excellent rates on the weekend and you get a top notch hotel. There is a mall next door to the hotel that has some excellent dining options if you dont want to eat at the hotel and there are some dining options in the street in back of the hotel as well. The workout equipment is a bit old but fine for a workout and the pool is large and seems never to be very busy. Service at the hotel is top notch.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>