<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="93ff5f5d2d1a09a47e641f34b4b8824a" url=""><![CDATA[Absolutely Loved it My fiancee' and I stayed there from June 24-29, and we also stayed at the Hilton Hawaiian Village 29 - July 4th. We wanted to split our trip so we could enjoy driving the island and exploring while staying at the Ilima and enjoying the beach and Hilton property during the latter part of our trip. In fact, I proposed to gf the first night we were there. I did the deed at La Mer so be sure to read my review. We absolutely loved the Ilima b/c its centrally located in Waikiki. We had a Superior room on the 14th floor overlooking the canal, golf course, and mountains. The room was big and clean. Yes, it was sparsely decorated but it was everything that we needed. I like the kitchen which afforded us to make breakfast and prepare two dinners. Oh yeah, let me not forget the free high speed intenet connection and free parking; we kept family and friends informed with the daily pictures and emails. We didn't have any problems with parking b/c we made sure that we made it back to the hotel by 5pm everyday. I really like the free stuff b/c you get nickeled and dimed at other properties in Waikiki. We would definitely stay there again.Even though the Ilima and the Hilton are in two different classes of hotels, they are both awesome in their own rights.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="51a2133798732595971eb04209ee2a49" url=""><![CDATA[Place is still a Dump I've read some of the most recent reviews, and I can't truly understand why people give this place high praises. I live in the Marshall Islands and have to travel through Hono several times a year. This place is still a dump and nothing has changed. Yes it's close to the airport, but that's it. I only wish the Kwaj community would write reviews concerning this place b/c it wouldn't be pretty. It's so bad that even Priceline, who is normally liberal with their Star Ratings, downgraded it from a 2* to a 1* hotel; I wish TripAdvisor would do the same.Good luck if you choose to stay there.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>