<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="c444befdf65d8b4ce82aa1960e7155bc" url=""><![CDATA[Everything you need My girlfriend and I stayed at The Stratford for one night in May, a Thursday. Arriving into the Oakland airport late (11:30), we had no trouble finding the hotel and checking in. The staff was very helpful in directing us on where to 1) park, 2) get a late nite dinner, and 3) find a cool bar to have a nitecap. Parking was conveniently located a block away (Ofarrell Mason) in a public garage was predictably expensive ($26 for 18 hr). Once the car was parked we went to Cafe Mason, right near the parking garage. This was an excellent choice for a respectable delicious late nite meal. Afterwards, on the way back to the hotel we stopped in Johnny Foley's Irish House just around the corner for a few drinks and to take in some San Fran nite life. Highlight of the night: the transvestite lounge singer who takes requests at the pub.The room was admittedly small, but was clean had nice design to it. You could defineatly feel the vibe. Why do you need a big room, if your just going to sleep in it? The bathroom was clean and decorated sparingly with style. The elevator was slow at times, but it wasn't too much of a hassle to use the stairs as we were on the fourth floor. Breakfast was nice and light, granola, yogurt, muffins, tea, coffee, juice. The breakfast room overlooks Powell St. and the hustle bustle of the city. Hearing the cablecar go by every few minutes really made us anxious to get out and explore the city. Of note; as we were staying in the standard room, wi-fi was not included and was only available for a fee. Fortunately, there was a free hotspot at union square that could be accessed from the hotel (yes, that is how close it is to Union Square).The best thing about this place is the central location to EVERYTHING. BART, Muni Metro, the F Market Streetcar, cable cars, buses run constantly within a short distance of the Stratford. Before checking out that morning we walked around the neighborhood. Two blocks down Powell is Market St., where the cable cars turn around and a convenient place to buy your Muni pass. Low and behold, what store was right next door? A three story Forever 21, alas my girlfriend was in heaven........also nearby is a giant Macy's fronting Union square and numerous art galleries. While there are quite a bit of panhandlers around, they are not aggressive and shouldn't be feared. They can even be of help to lost or confused tourists.All in all, The Stratford was done right. Cheap rates ($90 in high season), nice accommodations, polite helpful staff, in an awesome neighborhood in the middle of everything. What more could you ask for? I will definitely stay at the Stratford next time I'm in San Fran.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>