<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="592b800a1d692d39bd77284a087d2c7d" url=""><![CDATA[Would return in a heartbeat We spent three wonderful days at the Komaneka over Thanksgiving '07, and I can't wait to return. Although I booked a standard suite room, we were upgraded very unexpectedly at check in to a valley view pool villa, and wow, was it nice. Having our own plunge pool was the best part of the stay - we were in the pool 3-4 times a day, and it was a great way to cool down after a hot and dusty excursion to town. Loved the outdoor bathtub and the comfortable room and bed - plus the fact that once you walk in your compound and shut the door you are completely shut off from the world. the outdoor bale is a great place to read or nap, and the room feels almost outdoors with the glass walls all around. A great impression of being in the middle of nowhere and total privacy. The friendly staff will do anything you ask, but do know that it will happen slowly. That's ok, though, because part of the pleasure of Bali is the pace.The hotel is far from Ubud, but it isn't a significant problem if, like us, you were relaxing rather than strenuously touring or shopping. The hotel has a shuttle that runs all day, typically 10-15 minutes behind schedule ;-) We had the special candlelight smoked duck dinner at the main pool and it was good food and well worth the splurge to have the flowers and hundreds of floating candles and flowers. What a treat! We also booked a rice paddy walk via the hotel which we totally enjoyed - reasonable prices and really knowledgeable guide. I suspect that their other excursions are similarly worthwhile, and reasonable. I also had two very nice massages while there - the spa facilities are smallish but very pleasant.We're reccomending Komaneka to everyone we know -- and plan to return ourselves. Oh, and if you are dithering over the price for the pool rooms - just do it. I will next time, the privacy of your own pool can't be beat.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>