<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="d6858b3d515915d57c7c13375216b342" url=""><![CDATA[Great little Hotel Plaza Mayor Just returned from a weekend here. Very central location, only a few steps from the Plaza Mayor itself, and a short walk from the nearest metro at Sol (we flew into Barajas T4, just under 1 hour from landing to arriving at hotel, with the connecting bus between termini (?) taking a fair bit of that time). A clean, small but well equipped room and very helpful and friendly receptionists night porter. We followed their recommendations for places to eat out and were not disappointed. A comprehensive (for such a small hotel) hot and cold buffet breakfast is available - and at only each, a bargain. If you like a firm bed, room 305 certainly had one, together with a view out on to Calle Atocha. Usual city noise out on the street, but the closed windows eliminated most of that. There is no heavy passing traffic (as in say Gran Via), just local stuff, although the fire station and police HQ were nearby, so there were a few sirens about.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d11d19411b5fdc17bfe178b7223f34e5" url=""><![CDATA[Centrally located Centrally, but quietly, located in a pedestrian street just off the Ramblas, the Petit Palace Opera Garden Ramblas was an ideal location for a few days in Barcelona. It was 5 minutes walk from Plaza Catalunya and the airport bus terminus, a minute from the Rambla, and 2 minutes from the Cathedral. We requested a quiet room and were given one overlooking the rear garden. Our room was upgraded to a Hi Tech room, which included a massage jet shower, flat screen TV installed laptop (free connection). The bed seemed bigger than king size, and was very comfortable (room 1305), probably the best night's sleep ever in a hotel. Part of the Hi-Tech group, I believe the hotel was recently refurbished/opened, and is decorated in a modern minimalist style with a colour scheme of black, white and orange! Safe boxes in the room were free, and operated with your own credit card. The breakfast room and other public areas were a bit on the stark side. Comprehensive buffet breakfast. We paid euros 113 plus taxes for 2 of us, per night including breakfast. The published rate at reception was euros 275 (not sure if that was a standard room or hi-tech price). Overall, a good choice for a short break, where central location and a good night's sleep is important!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>