<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="7fcdb9e75d238caf75e7e7a8c9dd3f8c" url=""><![CDATA[Good average Reasonable size rooms, medium standard, OK as a good base for a few days explorationStaff efficient and friendly, although we did witness one incident where they were rather short and curt with two typically loud and crass americans who seemed to think all foreign countries should adapt to american 'standards' and speak English, and appeared totally unaware of the offense they caused as they trampled over centuries of culture and tradition. The reaction of the staff was totally justified and may explain similar incidents of rudeness listed in these reviews
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4160a361bc6f9f17749e36da1f0ddb97" url=""><![CDATA[Old and Interesting Stayed 2 nights as part of a tour. An old hotel (around 1910) but very well re-furbished in recent years. The original architect must have had a sense of humour, or crumpled drawing paper, as the internal corridors to rooms go up/down/around and provide quite a combination of possible routes, but this adds to the charm of the place compared with the many modern hotels based on repetitive designs of austere grey blocks lacking character or interestThe rooms also have character but probably wouldn't appeal to the more fastidious, sanitised travellers who fear stepping out of their plastic wrapped cocoons into Europe and cringe at the thought of a cracked tile or the possibility of a few germsThe rooftop restaurant has stunning views of the many centuries of Florence's architecture and provides an excellent buffet breakfast and good evening meals.Location is also excellent - easy walking to all the main sites and within 5 minutes by a subway from the railway stationThe hotel is popular with people from many countries, particularly America - which tends to up the noise level and give surreal sights such as discovering an American in full Stetson and Cowboy Boots (I assume this was his rather unfortunate take on dressing to blend in with the local population ?) in the reception area. But such misfits lacking any understanding the country they are visiting all add to the amusement for the locals.On the downside, the porters apparently lack a job description which says they should actually move luggage - they refused to carry bags to our coach (a mere 30 yards away)- and insisted it moved closer to the hotel, thus causing even more disruption to the local traffic, but other staff were well trained and efficient.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>