<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="ac503f1a569b7a547c938b56a8f75e2a" url=""><![CDATA[Great Berlin Hotel I recently stayed at this hotel for 5 nights.This hotel is great value for Berlin. The rooms were modern, clean and good sized for an European 3 star hotel. As a single, they will always give you a twin or double. Unlike many European hotels of the same class which will often give you a tiny room with just a single bed.The hotel is centrally located. The bed was comforatble. Continental breakffast was included in the hotel price. Free and reliable high speed internet available in everyroom. The reverse cycle air-con was reliable and kept me warm. I would recommend this hotel to others coming to Berlin. Its one of the best 3 star hotels I have ever stayed in. One major down side is there is no room service or restaurant serving lunch/ dinner at the hotel. However, there is a great little italian place opposite the hotel. Good menu, yummy food and extremely well priced. There is also an ALDI supermarket and parmacy 100metres away where you are equip yourself.There is also no in room iron, had to ask for it and it came within 5 mins so it was not a problem. Im also not a fan of the body soap and shampoo, 2 in 1 provided through a dispenser in the bath room. They should provide real toiletries. Overall, it was a nice hotel to stay in and extremely good value for money.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="00c82e4c3617b322bc7900120cf485ce" url=""><![CDATA[One of the BEST!!! I spend over 3 months of the year in hotels and this is one of the best I have ever stayed in. We checked in at 10pm were upgraded to a Club room. The oceanview club room was amazing with a large balcony, 2 bathrooms both with showers and a seperate lounge area.The Ritz property is amazing. 3 pools and a private beach. I particularly liked the salt water pool on the cliff. The pool side service was fantastic. You must try and watermelon juice that is served in a full sized watermelon.The service was excellent and staff were extremely well trained. There is so much attention to detail at this hotel and was beyond my expectations. Firstly, at the pool, I was provided with a selection of ipods, each ipod has a different music genre. Secondly after walking up the nasty stairs from the cliff pool, we were provided with cold scented towels to cool off. I did not eat at any of the restaurants but we had (2 of us) room service twice and pool side lunch and the total was approx US$100 which I thought was very reasonably priced. All the food we ate at the Ritz were really tasty. The Nasi Goreng was the best I have ever tasted. The hotel is popular with asian luxury tourist and NOT groups. I spoke to one of the people at the hotel. It is approx 35% Japanese, 15% Koreans, 15% Russians, 10% Taiwanese, 10% Hong Kong, 15% mixed Australia/ French/ German/ Singapore. You will find that most of the staff speaks Japanese. I was told none are groups except for the Taiwanese.Being a popular destination for non sun bathing asian tourist is quite an advantage as it leaves plenty of deck chairs available for sunbathers. The diversity of different nationality also means breakfast was a smogasbord of western, japanese, chinese, scandinavian breakfast available. Yummy!There were 2 locations for breakfast. One was the buffet and the other was a-la-cart. I personally prefered the a-la-cart next to the pool.On the downside, i did notice the thin walls. I could hear next door's tv and some coughing from my lounge room. I also thought the private beach was overrated and the internet was disgustingly expensive US$7 for 30mins.Overall, I thought this hotel is well maintained, well runned and its people are well trained!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ddeae6f7e0c2361c37e87382ab7a8f6f" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel But Not Amazing I visited the Alila Ubud and had a nice stay. The hotel felt eco and organic.I had high expections on the Alila as previous reviews boast about its scenery and its mangnificant pool. However, the hotel did not give me the 'WOW' factor. In summary:The rooms are on the small side. The view wasn't really that amazing. The pool was nice but I was expecting it to be hanging on the edge of the cliff but this was not the case. I personally would not rate it as the top 10 pools in my world.The food at the restaurant was good but it was a little pricey. They boast all ingredients are organic. They can deliver breakfast to your room and you can eat it on your balcony. Highly recommend this.On the last night, we left some chocolate out next to our bed and in the morning, it was swamped with ants. We didnt care as we were checking out that morning. There were plenty of pool deck chairs for everyone during my stay. The turndown service every night was one of the best with different surprises everynight.I recommend you having your own driver as the property is a 15min drive from the town centre. (which i liked)The SPA was professional and staff were well trained.Though the hotel did not deliver the WOW factor I was expecting. Overall, I had a nice stay at the hotel and I would recommend others to the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6c69cfb66905c78bda57e01489db611e" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location but in need of renovations You couldn't be more central than this hotel. Right in the middle of the action. The lobby looks nice, but the rooms are a little small especially the bathroom. It looks like there has been attempts to upgrade the room furniture but I really think all the rooms need to be completely renovated. The rooms were clean with nice bed linnen. Only 2 bath towels were provided and there was no in-room safe. Internet was free. This is not your Grand Hyatt and certainly felt like a business hotel. The hotel service was ok. The reception did not greet or speak until she was telling me what my room number was at check-in. The view from the breakfast view was amazing. The quality and variety at breadkfast was average. You have to ask to get your bread toasted. The hotel has an overnight bag courier service and can send your bags to Narita- very handy if you have large suitcases and pick them up at the airport.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="27416b44a2d4959a998d6ac8756c81ac" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Hotel!!! This is a well run, well maintained hotel. The rooms are clean and spacious. The lagoon view rooms have a glass partition between the spa and bedroom (you can see into the shower/ spa from the bedroom) and loved it!!!!The hotel hosts the best buffet breakfast I have ever experienced in the world. It was tasty, fresh and presentation was good. We also tried several restaurants including room service and they were all exellent in terms of food quality and service.The pools at the hotel were great. There are so many of them!!!One negative about this resort would be that they do not have enough deck chairs for everyone and alot of people would put their towel out at breakfast time to reserve their seats. The situation is a particular problem with the half a dozenof bales available. There is a hotel sign advising guests against this selfish act but is often ignored by guests. Overall, it was a great experience and I would highly recommend this hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>