<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="af4eabad1f352873924093958d11a4c7" url=""><![CDATA[Great for travellers or business! Despite a few finishing touches being tended to, and training of staff still ongoing, this hotel was an absolutely great spot for an overnight stay and should appeal to a wide variety of clients.The rooms are well designed for longer stays with a microwave, dishwasher, washer and dryer, iron and board.....and a hairdryer (*if you look in the cupboard below the sink). The bathroom has a walk in shower and separate tub so the one sink vanity is somewhat small, but glass shelves add to the storage potential.As well, the bed was comfy (though not heavenly) and the glass desk/work area with 2 chairs, one an swivel leather desk chair, was good for our morning Starbucks fix...located right across the street. In our suite there was an electric fireplace, with a television on top, a glass fronted armoire for clothing (thank you for skinny mirrors!) and a lounge chair and ottoman. I forgot to ask for a higher floor so we were on the 8th, but besides the odd street noise, we found the suite quiet. There was a faint smell of paint in the morning at the elevators, but besides that, you wouldn't know there was any construction going on.The lobby is spacious and tastefully decorated, with two main entrances on opposite sides of the building for easy access to public transit right outside the door. We found all staff very friendly and helpful, but they are still training people and it's obvious from the previous review, they may not have all that worked out quite yet. But our experience was above average in that regard. We did make use of the courtesy cars and had a ride in a '72 Rolls to a restaurant in the Distillery District (Boiler House .....fantastic meal, great jazz) which was wonderful. We didn't visit the cafe on site and the restaurant is still under construction, but there is a room service menu and nearby eateries so that wasn't a problem. If you are looking for a more luxurious, spacious suite for a romantic getaway, this might not be the place for you. Otherwise I think it's a real find in downtown Toronto!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>