<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="bd5bae85e6b4c02f7edff534687d7448" url=""><![CDATA[Really enjoyed the Swissotel Stayed at the Swissotel on business in a Premier Corner Room. I had stayed here in the past but stopped because of service issues and the smoking that used to be permitted in the lobby bar many moons ago.But I'm glad I tried again because this hotel is in an unbeatable location for both business and holidays, right in the middle of the city. The room was fantastic in that it was large, very airy and bright, well appointed and quiet. The bathroom is also a joy for those who like a spotless space with room to move about.I also found the service excellent. I typically dont like hotels that only offer a doona for bedding and dont provide a top and bottom sheet. But luckily for me they did offer alternatives and surprisingly it didnt take housekeeping long to realise I didnt use the bed as they made it and they quickly changed the way the bed was made up to suit me, without me having to ask. Quite impressive.Overall this hotel is a great option for people who enjoy a sense of space, comfort and high quality and really want to be in the centre of things. I think I have found my new base in Sydney.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2e82ca1d9b7be88be3bd9a6fcde4d18f" url=""><![CDATA[Everything I hoped This place is in a great location, literally over the road from Pike Market and about a 5 minute walk to the centre of the city. We originally werent sure whether to stay in the city, but given the Inn turned out to be so close to the city and that the Pike Markets are so colorful, it was a great choice.We didnt feel unsafe at any stage and in fact the mafority of the stranger types appeared to mainly reside in the city itself.There are plenty of places to eat very close by, from quick snacks to nice restaurants, so again location was excellent. We had breakfast at a small French patiserie about 2 minutes away that served great coffee and fantastic pasteries at a reasonable price.We were also impressed with the hotel. Although it doesnt look much from the outside, its been decorated modern but refined and the room was great. We tend to try and get a room with a view and in this case stayed in a Parlour Suite. While expensive, the room didnt let us down with both the view and quality. We were very happy and comfortable.Didnt try the hotels restaurants, but they always seemed to show up on the best in Seattle lists.So overall we couldnt have been happier at the Inn at the Market and would recommend it to anyone.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c11ffc4208818d76f85137e0e466f658" url=""><![CDATA[Very happy Almost didnt stay here because of the inconsistent reports on the hotel, but was glad we did. Contrary to some travellers we really liked the upgrade done on the hotel and found it to be modern, fresh, light and very attractive. Its also in a great location if you particularly want to stay at Fishermans Wharf, with the cable car right by behind the hotel. Stayed in a Deluxe Room which we would recommend because of the extra space, the fact its on the top floor and therefore quiet, plus the reasonably good views from the room. There is no doubt that its a little expensive and the parking fees are a rip off, but everywhere of similar quality had similar costs. So we were really very happy with our selection, very comfortable tstaying here and would definately stay again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>