<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="6e252238faddc3a3c28477b21fdcb78b" url=""><![CDATA[Everyone keen to please We spent 3 nights at the Crowne Plaza Berlin whilst visiting the Christmas Markets and other sites. It is very handily placed for the main transport infrastructure near Zoo station and especially the excellent No 100 and 200 buses. Buy a Welcome card for 15 euros ( 48 hours) and you will easily recoup your expenses on travel and some other amenities. Everyone at the hotel was very keen to please and the service was outstandingly good. We could not fault the hotel room, reception and cleaning staff, breakfast facilities etc in any way - everything was first class. It was a pleasure to stay at the Crowne Plaza and we would thoroughly recommend it. The taxi from Tegel airport to the hotel ( and return ) was 15 euros - very reasonable. It took about 20 minutes. We would recommend a city bus tour at 15 euros each for a 2 hour bus journey round the main sites - hop on and off all afternoon. We got on at Brandenburg Gate and returned there, although there are 15 stops altogether. Another bonus for us was the self service restaurant on the 5th floor of the Galerie department store in Alexander Platz. Superb choice of food, help yourself and very good value. They have a great children's area ( Stieff teddy bears etc) on the 3rd floor.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="77e41d94fb9e548e0d81946943818f7a" url=""><![CDATA[Worth another visit Stayed here for 3 nights and was impressed by the helpfulness of staff, the large pleasant room and high standards of cleanliness. Breakfast was more than adequate and not too crowded while Dinner was good on the 2 nights we ate in the restaurant. The service could have been better and the menu was a little uninspiring for Paris. The hotel is well placed for travel into the centre of Paris (best Metro is Pasteur) and there are several restaurants nearby. The best that we found was the Pot au Feu in Rue Pasteur, 300 yards away. A taxi back to Charles de Gaulle airport was 62 euros although this is better than travel via metro and RER, with luggage. All in all, a very pleasant hotel with a good rate of 98 euros per night, inc breakfast but no cancellation.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>