<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="f4ee544fd0f0f7c69886925696b67813" url=""><![CDATA[Quiet but central location Recently stayed with my wife and two boys over the holidays. Hotel is in excellent location. Quiet near the museums, but very central to everything. Hotel staff is very friendly. Breakfast is very good. For English speakers Amsterdam is a great place. Nearly everyone is fluent in English. Recommend the Quinto restaurant near the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7101647c4728e4868b43bdbbbbb1971b" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic Location Fantastic location directly across from the Pantheon, and a few steps from the Jardin Du Luxembourg. Note Dame is a ten minute walk, 15 to the Right Bank. Staff is very friendly and all speak excellent English. Rooms were larger than expected and nicely decorated. Bathrooms were quite spacious with our a very large tub in our bathroom. We had a superior room and our two boys had a twin room. Splurge for the superior room, larger room and with a better bathroom (tub ). Best dessert I've had at Mouff Tartes on Rue Mouffetard. Organic bakery near there was excellent.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c346798e300dbe186f5ce805815ae63f" url=""><![CDATA[Great location and exceptional room Stayed at the Argonaut over the Memorial Day weekend with my wife and two young boys. Can't ask for a better location with lots of attractions and public transportation nearby. The room was large with a very comfortable bed. I filled out a survey, raised a minor point, and the manager personally replied. The hotel staff was very attentive. We had dinner and breakfast at the restaurant, the blue mermaid, and the food was excellent. A limited menu but well prepared food. I thought the price of $229 for a double queen deluxe room with a nice courtyard and transamerica building view was a great value. Clearly the best hotel in the area.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9efb3ac6ea53048cf47d19c2998bfe40" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect Resort My family of four (two boys ages 10 7) stayed at the Kahala over the 4th of July holiday. The service is the best we have ever had anywhere. The property is beautiful and situated on its own quiet beach between Diamond Head and Koko Head. The hotel upgraded us to an ocean room without us asking. The room was large with a spacious bathroom. The bed was sagging and the hotel immediately switched the mattress. The staff is very pleasant and efficient. We used the convenient hotel shuttle and transferred to city buses, The Bus. The Bus is a great system and easy to use. Highly recommend restaurants Town, Spices, and Champa Thai.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>