<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="edb15f42d44c3d89dcde7a6dbd761878" url=""><![CDATA[Good Value and Location Bathroom
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="14863a8524b486bb11de10eb76243119" url=""><![CDATA[a very GRAND hotel indeed ! Handed over to Grand Pacific 4 months ago by Le Meridien.I can't recall a Hotel anywhere where there were so many eager young staff members in the lobby at all times ready to help you with anything at all, always with poise, politeness and a smile. Check in/ out and concierge were very good. The latter even sent a new Kabuki brochure under my door as soon as she got details about show times !Grand and very spacious....public areas and the room too. Was upgraded twice to a luxury room having booked a terrific rate I caught on Travelzoo. The decor is very classic....lots of cut crystal sconces, chandelier in the room (!). The door separating a roomy foyer/ makeup table closet and bathroom from the rest of the room gives extra sound insulation ...not that that mattered. Very roomy bath with separate shower, lots of counter space and a Toto washlet toilet seat! Tons of bathroom amenities, I still haven't figured some of them out ! Comfy beds and pillow, good blackout drapes. The hot water dispenser in the room was nice for making coffee and tea.Free Internet in the business center but no wireless (found virtually no wireless in Tokyo to my surprise).The Monorail to Odaiba Island is about $3 US per person/ trip but the Hotel runs a shuttle ever hour on the 1/2 hour starting at 930AM to the sister hotel in Shingawa, The Grand Pacific, where you can catch the rail line that makes a big loop around Tokyo. It seems anywhere you stay in Tokyo you have to commute to sightsee since things are spread out. I found Hotel restaurant's breakfast and menu very pricey but we did have the buffet one night at Le Bouquet but the quantity/ quality was excellent for the $39 per person (no extra tax/tip).There's a 24 hour convenience store just outside the hotel and plenty of mall type restaurants at Aqua City or Venus Fort.Note the last Airport Limousine bus from Narita to Odaiba is around 630 PM. We got in later than that so you wind up taking the bus to Shingawa at $28 each and then hoping a cab for another $35. Ouch !
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="74e42fdb61c6bdf411d708f215987c10" url=""><![CDATA[Just terrific ! My 5 night stay must have coincided with the traveller from Boston; their very comprehensive review says it all! I would agree completely and would add....The service in the Alexandra restaurant warrants huge praise. Someone has Ritz-Carlton training and has brought it to Guanica. Politeness, attentiveness and an unintrusive well-paced and leisurely efficiency were on tap nightly no matter how busy. The prices are steep but the all-inclusive (especially from Expedia) was a remarkable bargain (and includes room tax and resort fee to boot). The breakfast and lunch staff were also terrific.The front desk staff was also cooly professional and responsive to every request. A noisey A/C was replaced within an hour with a new and quiet unit !!!A deep tissue massage at the spa was satisfying. The small facility looks carefully planned but I was surprised there was no spontaneous invitation to partake of the steam room and outdoor shower, which I was offered once I inquired. The small gym is nicely equiped and has a 42 Panasonic plasma TV (though I don't think anything was transmitted in HDTV).Having been unimpressed by tepid hot tubs elsewhere the high temperature of the two on the grounds of this facility was wonderfully relaxing.While satellite trouble prevented the use the first night, the free WiFi was pretty fast once up and running.My only minor quibble....the door to the adjoinging room is not much of a sound barrier. It was easy to hear conversation, snorring and their TV. A couple of small towels stuffed the door under helped a bit, and the A/C drowned out the rest.And being an avid TripAdvisor user I must point out that few establishments seem to read and respond to comments. Copamarina apparently does. They care and it shows. Bravo!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="64bf1779a8f9edae7003ec0f2ba185bb" url=""><![CDATA[Cl;ose To Perfection ! Why is it so rare to leave a hotel feeling as satisfied as I was with MOMi? From arrival to departure the staff seems to want only to be sure you are having a perfect stay. Their apparantly liberal policy regarding upgrades and late check out won me over. Isolated (which is exactly what I wanted) on Brickell Key your dining options are limited to the Hotel but breakfasts and dinner at Cafe Sambal were excellent. The AM buffet with coffee and juice for $20 is well worth it. Dinner (did the tasting menu with paired wines) at Azul for a birthday was excellent: entertaining and delicious (am a fish lover but the veal roullade is out of this world) with flawless service and an engaging, informative sommelier who knew exactly when not to intrude!They do not have a resort fee , a policy I detest, and use of the gym and the lockers/ showers/ sauna and steam are free to guests as it should be. A Deep Tissue Massage was done right though the very comfortable high tech mechanised massage table was amusing.My only gripe would be the steepness of that valet parking fee but didn't bother with a rental car til the night before leaving.Note breakfasts/ lunch and poolside barservice incur a standard 18 % tip but I found service almost flawless and (be aware) many Miami establishments routinely do this as many foreigners are used to service compris.Will return.......a worthwhile indulgence!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>