<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="4bfecba81fa5cbb5745329ddc4ecd822" url=""><![CDATA[BEWARE: "The Foxes Are In Charge of the Henhouse After having experienced the Ambar personally, I feel the one thing that was consistent at this Hotel was the inconsistency of just about everything. Having said that, when we checked into our room, there was NO flat/plasma tv that everybody else raves about. Ours was a very small screen (perhaps 19) and much older than other guests have reported. As a matter of fact, every day when I walked past other rooms at the Hotel, (main floor, bldg. #61) it seemed to be a hit or miss depending on what room you were in. Some had flat/plasma tv's, but most didn't. No big deal, however, Ambar advertises flat/plasma tv so we were disappointed that there wasn't one in our room.Speaking of the room, I have to agree with the majority of the people who said it was beautiful well-appointed. That was at first glance... However, I also have to agree with a previous reviewer who said the workmanship was shoddy. M. Holmes would have a thing or two to say - especially about the way the tiles in the bathroom were affixed to the walls and the fact that there is no ventillation or window in there. Talk about humidity - I cannot imagine how much mildew is under the false ceiling - yikes!!! Oh yeah, our bathtub worked, however, big crack in it so I guess that's what caused the leakage.Libations were also inconsistent; even when the same drink was ordered whether it was the lobby or pool bar. On several occasions we ordered the same drink which you got as a 'frozen' or sometimes came with two ice cubes. When I ordered pina coladas at the pool bar, I had to ask for the rum to be added. In other words, they're serving 'virgin' coladas unless the customer requests the rum be put in. Must be why they were going down so 'smooth'....While we're on the subject of the bars, I've got to mention the fact that I have a more extensive bar at my own home than they do at this 5 star Hotel!!! They have huge areas to hold lots of bottles, however, the shelves are practically empty!!! What was really odd to me too was when you ordered a drink, the bartender would disappear behind a door then reappear minutes later with your drink. Why does he go in the back room to make my drink, why not make it there at the bar? Also, perhaps the Hotel should check into the demographics of their clients. I witnessed many Canadians, some who have even gotten on this website and mentioned a love for Canadian Club as one of their favourite drinks. Not all of us live on beer , wine the frozen drinks.. Why not 'loosen the purse strings' and buy a few bottles of a decent rye and other spirits!As for the food, the Ambar has a far way to go to achieve the 5-star status. First of all, I don't recommend salting any meats before the cooking process. I don't know what that's all about, however, it's just not healthy! Every time I watched the chefs at the buffet restaurants at the Amber cook meat, they salted it. Let me be the judge of how much salt I want on my meat.One other thing the restaurants should invest in are some decent grills for the meat. The buffets all had a flat stainless steel surfaces which the chef would place the meat on; only after they had poured a good amount of oil. I can feel my arteries clogging as I write this!I also agree with a lot of the previous reviewers: the best meals were at the buffets and not the a-la-cartes. We were also disappointed that the Japanese Restaurant was booked all week; even before we had checked in!!! Go figure!I must say that the one thing that was consistent at the buffets and restaurants were the smiles of the staff; especially a woman by the name of Rosa who greeted us at the door. What a sweetheart she was! Every day we looked forward to her smiles and kind words.I feel I must mention the beauty of the Hotel and the grounds, including the beach. Absolutely lovely!In closing, I would also like to mention that we had some money taken from our locked safe/room the night before we left the D. R. We reported it to customer service who apparently followed Hotel procedures. They took us back to our room, checked our room and our luggage then said they would write a report. We were then dismissed. I've read other reviewers who reported things missing from their rooms too. As a matter of fact, since our return from the D. R. I've researched this subject and have found numerous articles about the same topic. My boss tells me she found herself in the exact same circumstance when she visited the D. R. four years ago! Like I say, BEWARE!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>