<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="369085f5318e17af92ff21a45ce117f3" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel... cannot fault this hotel at all, we were pleasantly surprised by the decor cleanliness of the hotel. The staff were very helpful - some guests I saw were quite abrupt rude.....politeness costs little. The pool area was great, has a fantastic view, and the overall situation of this hotel is excellent. Very close (within easy walking distance), of a shopping mall (Coconut Walk), and you can safely walk around the area. The only negative we had was - with being English - we prefer self-parking to valet parking, and the valet's didn't seem to quite understand we wanted to park our car ourselves......rather than pay excessive amounts for the privilege.Overall the hotel was great, we did get a good bargain from Skyauction, and would definately go back to this hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="754489437a15969e1ecfeb5304d9dc44" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel Cannot quite believe all the negative readings of this hotel. Yes, it does need a little TLC, but it is an older hotel, the lobby is lovely and spacious, the grounds are great as well, and you can walk along the boardwalks in either direction at night, overlooking the sea. You have to be quick to get a poolside lounger, but doesn't that happen all over the world !!! ....we decided to pay the $5 for a lounger on the beach, which was great. The snack bar by the pool do nice food during the day, and we had dinner twice in the hotel ($20 for a buffet - but you get to eat as much as you can), great food - we enjoyed it anyway !!! We did have quite abit of noise from the road (as our room overlooked the entrance), but it didn't stop us having 10 hours sleep each night !!! Would of probably liked the Hotel to be nearer the action on South Beach, but you pay extra for that, and it can also be quite noiser there. If you drive, the only problem you have is trying to park, but you'll always find somewhere. Valet parking was OK at $9 per night.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>