<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="3a15cccd21a8383f59aac07332ff1efb" url=""><![CDATA[Very Good Hotel But Not For Families I was at the Sheraton Waikiki solo for a week-long conference after Thanksgiving. If I were rating it simply as a business hotel, I'd give it four stars, but as a family hotel, I'd give it only three stars. When I come back to Waikiki with the family, I'll likely look elsewhere. The hotel is upscale and expensive, the service as friendly as you'd expect in Hawaii, and adult and business amenities very good. But there seems to be no place even to take a family to eat on the property. The restaurant on the 30th floor is very upscale, and even the restaurant that is oceanside only offered a thirty dollar buffet at 5 PM on a Tuesday. If you stay here, you probably have to take the kids to a food court that is across the street from the Sheraton or a MacDonalds a block away. The pools seemed smallish and not much else for the kids unless you enroll them in a daytime program. The four largest hotels on Waikiki are the Hilton Village, the Marriott Beachfront Resort, the Hyatt resort, and the Sheraton Waikiki. Each has 1200 to 3000 rooms. The Hilton, Hyatt,, and Sheraton all indicate they offer daytime children's programs, but I'd be tempted to bring the family to the Marriott because of its location. It is on the south (Diamond Head) end of Waikiki, only a block from the Honolulu Zoo, and near a major park, and the Aquarium. It is also a block from the local Catholic Church if you are inclined to go to Sunday Mass. The Hyatt is a few blocks further away from these, while the Sheraton is about a 15 minute walk, anfd the Hilton Village is way on the other side of Waikiki. By the way, while there are no bargains on Waikiki, the Sheraton and Hyatt seem to run more expensive than the Marriott and Hilton Village. The Sheraton draws many conventions and conferences while the Hilton draws many tour groups. Of course, there are many smaller properties at Waikiki which are additional alternatives. Note the Sheraton is next to the historic Royal Hawaian Hotel which it owns. It is worth walking over to the pink-colored Royal Hawaian if only to take a look. In short, the Sheraton seems like a great place to go for a business conference, but not particularly suited for a family stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a21651a16e1addb47ed84d8e9c8771bb" url=""><![CDATA[Would Definitely Return With the Kids Some resorts are great for adults and others great for kids, but this resort seems to do a good job of pleasing both. I came to it solo for a business conference but would definitely come back to it if I return to Phoenix with the family. Most of the hotel rooms are clustered in the front of the sprawling property at its North Pointe and South Pointe. The rooms in each pointe surround a courtyard with a small swimming pool. The conference rooms are between the two pointes but the hotel desk in the South Pointe. I was in a nice suite in the North Pointe that would comfortably handle a family of four. There was a living room with a pull-out couch, desk and widescreen for TV/Internet, a bathroom and walkway in the middle, and a bedroom next to a balcony on the other side. In the back of the property are a four-acre mini-waterpark to the north which is exceptional, a kid's daycamp Casitas suites in the middle, and a spa which includes a lap pool to the south. The casitas seem to be two story town house-type suites. The restaurant which is off the front parking lot was not real fancy but good food for a hotel and fine for a family. Note that the waterpark has its own restauant, ice cream shop, etc. The property has lighted tennis courts but if you want to golf, you have to go four miles away to the sister Hilton property. That other Hilton property also has a fine upscale restaurant (A Different Point of View) which is highly recommended for adults but not really for kids). The staff was nice and my stay very pleasant. I'll probably be back with the family in the future.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>