<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f1a2ee6931dc3469fadb522bfc9b8816" url=""><![CDATA[Incredible Resort!!! My daughter and I had the opportunity to fly to Punta Cana on April 18th for eight days in conjunction with the wedding of her daughter/my granddaughter at Excellence Resort just down the beach, leaving Minnesota during a snowstorm! How awesome is that? Our flight to Punta Cana went without a hitch for the most part -- connecting flight was on time from Atlanta, and we arrived to be met by sunny 80-something degree temps and LOTS of people, including the photo gals (hola!!) and dancers trying to get our attention as we made our way to our luggage. We paid our $10 on arrival -- crazy tax if you ask me considering how much we spent in country as well as traveling there! Kind of confusing getting to our transportation through Viator, but made it, and then on to the hotel. Our driver was excellent in negotiating the roads (and potholes) and we arrived to the resort being met with cold washcloths. On arrival, there was some confusion regarding our reservation, and in the process of check-in I lost a purse with my Spanish translation dictionary and $25 cash for tips in it. That was never located even after several attempts through the front desk and concierge. That made us rather angry, but not too much could be done about it -- someone just lucked out. Our first room was on the ground floor towards the beach, musty smelling, and we were greeted by a centipede crawling on the floor. It was obviously not the picture that we saw when we originally booked. In addition, the fridge was not working and neither was the A/C. Maintenance was called but no luck there in solving the mechanical problems. We called the front desk to change rooms but were told the resort was full and it was not possible. My daughter however did persist in the request after going to the beach and pool later on with it being obvious the resort was not full judging by the amount of people we saw. The second day we inquired again, and after two visits with the concierge, were able to transfer rooms after 3 p.m. to the other side of the resort, third floor, ocean view. Then our vacation kicked into gear! The food was fantastic, the drinks awesome (just be sure to tell them you want liquor in the drink), and the beach and pools wonderful! Even the afternoon grill by the beach for burgers and brats was great! Plenty of fresh fruit all the time even from the fruit stand by the pool area. The restaurants (5 of them) must have excellent chefs -- our food was always presented beautifully, and tasted great! The staff was for the most part very friendly, and seemed to want to please us whenever they could. We loved the Three Amigos who serenaded us every night at dinner (except for the Chinese restaurant) and the theater activities every evening were incredible. The children were always a part of the theater evenings, and the staff was very gracious in including them with their music and dancing. One could tell that the Explorers Club kept the kids very busy, and they must have had lots of fun judging by their interactions with staff on stage at the theater in the evenings. We loved walking on the beach and felt very secure with the security staff always in attendance, even in the evenings. The beach area was nice and clean, and we knew their was coral a little ways out, so had water shoes in case we went out that far. Other nice areas down the beach for swimming though, so no problems with coral for us. We were a little bummed out that we could not use a hobie cat because of not being certified which also included extra cost, as well as any use of the spa which would have been over and above. It was nice not to be continuously approached by vendors on the beach, although the guys trying to sell the horse rides, got to be a little annoying. Don't know if they got takers for the 120 horses they said were just up the road. The gounds of the resort were very beautiful, and it seemed like gardeners and other staff were always busy doing something. All in all, our stay was incredible, and I would go back again. We would just know to request a room off the ground floor, and midway between the beach and the main building of the resort. I would also inquire about the suites the next time -- I think that is what we were supposed to have, but could not seem to get that across to the gentleman at the front desk. This is a very family oriented resort, although we did see a couple of wedding parties there with a wedding at the gazebo one evening. I would also perhaps book my stay in a different way than an online service such as Hotwire.com. When we needed some answers, it was virtually impossible to get a satisfactory answer, and were in more wonderment after the phone call to Hotwire.com as to how to proceed with getting our questions answered. In the end, we just read a lot on the internet at different sites, and hoped it would all turn out okay -- which it did.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>