<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="5112ca976a8b805b5d36d47d7aaac539" url=""><![CDATA[Sublime blend of luxury and "wellness." We also selected Como Shambhala after previous experience at a sister property - Umu in nearby Ubud. The setting high above the Ayung River is exquisite and its relative remoteness makes it ideal for those who wish to relax, rather than party - or get fit and get well.The professional staff were particularly impressive: I selected the optional get fit program and my wife selected the ayurvedic program - both for a very modest addition to the package. One can make the schedule as busy as one likes - there are many optional experiences to choose from, including early-morning yoga, pilates, walking, trekking and cycling, lifestyle guidance or even bird watching. There are also many add-ons in the spa, as well as fitness challenges further afield; I particularly enjoyed a two-hour walk through ricefields and villages down to Ubud, followed by a pleasant cycle back.A particular delight was a morning spent down at the resort's exclusive rockpools, fed by a natural spring 100 feet above the river. The staff deliver a superb picnic lunch - a kind of antipasto of Balinese food - and discreetly offer cold water and towells when required.Two aspects of our stay surprised us: the sheer value for money (two susequent nights at the Bulgari Resort cost more than five at Como) and the unobtrusive service. Whenever we left our residence for a meal or activity, it would be serviced - used clothing disappeared, only to be returned three hours later washed and pressed; towells were replaced, the bathroom tidied, fresh drinking water supplied. As good as we have enjoyed.And don't miss the marvellous Taksu massage - the best I have ever had!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f8eadff6571e1c7b58e0940e133e1989" url=""><![CDATA[What a perfect breakfast! Front lounge
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>