<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7c2ce36ae779afe36519fb01678b1cbd" url=""><![CDATA[Fabulous Weekend at The Grand This is the second time I have stayed at The Grand, the first being approximately five years ago. I chose it this time because I have tried other hotels since and they have not come close in matching the standards of this hotel.This trip was from Friday till Sunday and was a birthday present to my StepMum for her 50th birthday. They have never been to Amsterdam before and I wanted it to be memorable for her.We arrived at lunchtime and felt special as soon as we entered the extremely elegant courtyard. The doorstaff welcomed us and we entered the beautifully maintained lobby area. My parents were very impressed. I love the fabrics and choices of furniture in this area and how it blends so perfectly through into the lounge bar. The reception staff welcomed us with very friendly faces and manners and told us they had upgraded us to a deluxe room. As only one room was ready we decided to have a quick look at the room and go out exploring this beautiful city.The room was perfect. Huge and square and with very high ceilings it made the room feel even bigger. We had a huge bed with feather pillows and quilt that was a dream to sleep in. The bathroom was spotless with everything you needed and perfect white towels. The shower is one of the most powerful showers I have ever had the pleasure of using. Our room had a view of the canal which was truly beautiful whilst my parents room had a view of the inner courtyard which again was beautiful.The staff in the hotel are obviuosly trained to a high standard and it shows on every single level. They are courteous, helpful, professional and extremely friendly without being intrusive. They are also courteous to each other. Nothing was too much trouble for them and never once did I hear the word 'no', it was always 'of course'.The concierge team that they have are very knowledgeable and helped us hugely with many different things all of which was done with what seemed to be no effort or bother at all.The Hotel itself is steeped in history and is maintained and restored to a very high standard. The public areas are spotless and very tasteful and elegant. The lounge bar is a pleasure to be in. They also have a business room where you can use the computers and the internet if needed.Once you retire to your room it is quiet and very comfortable and after many miles of walking, the bed is a welcome retreat.I can now honestly say after staying in two other hotels I will only ever return to this one, this is truly my favourite place and I can be one really fussy traveller. I recommend this hotel and it is a rareity in that it is truly deserving of it's star rating.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>