<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="5a607b6d338b73fcb59c91e6f9e5b6f1" url=""><![CDATA[Great Value, Great Vacation Arrival in Punta Cana and transfer to Dreams - Once you arrive inside the airport you are immediately put into a line at the front of which your picture is taken with two girls in traditional Domincan dresses (which can be purchased for $8 when you depart Punta Cana). After this you are sent to a desk to pay the $10 per person entry fee. Our luggage was already off the plane when we reached the baggage claim area and an attendant took our bags to the transfer area. We booked our trip through Liberty Travel and the attendant took us right to their desk. The representative was very helpful and instructed us where we could find our bus to Dreams. The bus was a huge charter bus, seating about 50, however, there were only about 10 of us so we were very spread out. The driver explained that the trip would be about an hour so he would stop at a local market where we could purchase drinks for the ride. The market was right outside of the airport and the girls working at the market had bottles of El Presidente waiting to be purchased. Stopping at the market was a nice treat for the long ride ahead. The ride, despite what many reviews have previously stated, was really not that bad. I think it seems longer than it really is just because of your excitement to start your vacation. Yes, there were potholes, but our driver did an excellent job of trying to avoid them whenever possible. There is no highway, only local roads, that are shared by buses, trucks, mopeds, pedestrians. It gets a little crowded, but again, the driver did his best to make it as smooth a ride as possible. Check In Room- no issues here. Rooms were ready as soon as we arrived. We were in building 5 which I think was a good location. It was closest to the lobby/main building area, so we didn't have to walk too far for breakfast or the shows/casino/disco at night. It also wasn't a far walk to the middle pool area or the beach. The room was a typical hotel room - beds, bathroom, closet and walkout patio. Everything was very clean and the maid did an excellent job everyday and every night for turndown service. Pool - one of the best parts of the vacation. It's huge and only 3ft throughout so the water was warm, yet still refreshing. Despite other reviews, there definitely were enough lounge chairs even if you did arrive later in the day. The rafts in the pool were scarce and people did get greedy and hoard them by their chairs all day instead of keeping them in the pool for others to use. Not really a big deal for me though. Service by the pool was excellent. We consistantly had waitresses asking us if we wanted drinks, which were delivered within 5 minutes. You have to consider they take a lot of drink orders, and depending on how busy the bar is depends on when you'll get your drink. But again, it was always received in good time. The swim up bar was a bit crowded with only 2 bartenders at a time, which again, could cause you to have to wait a few minutes. But the wait is nothing crazy, and afterall you're waiting in the pool. Nothing wrong with that! Beach - We spent everyday at the pool and only walked on the beach once. The water was nice and blue, but the sand was rocky. I think you would definitely need to wear water shoes going into the ocean. Food - Excellent. We ate at the buffet every morning for breakfast and there was a ton to choose from. Orange juice was delicious and sweet which made the Mimosas even better! For lunch we generally ate from the Beach BBQ where you could get hamburgers, hotdogs, nachos, etc. There was also take out pizza available from the buffet. For dinner we generally ate a little earlier around 6:30 right when the restaurants opened, otherwise there was a wait to be seated. Our favorite by far was Bordeaux. We ate there three times during our week stay. We also tried the Mexican restaurant where the Margaritas are great and they have a mariachi type band singing at each table. The Italian restaurant was really a section of the World Cafe buffet and again was good. We also tried the Japanese restaurant at sat at the hibachi table. The chef didn't have many tricks while cooking, just basically cooked the food and served it. But there was a lot of food and it all tasted very good. Overall I had NO complaints with the food. Everything was delicious, and the portions were just the right size. Service - the best! From the moment we arrived for check in until we left a week later, the service was amazing. Each of the staff work very long hours and will do whatever they can to answer your questions, and provide promt, courteous service. Tipping is not necessary, but sometimes we found that we wanted to give something just because the service was great. Every employee we encountered was very personable, asking where we were from, etc. The service is definitely a reason I would go back to Dreams.Entertainment - Excellent. The entertainment staff work very long hours. You'll see them by the pool during the day leading the activities and again all night for the nightly show and dancing at the disco. The shows for the most part are entertaining/funny, and the dancing is great. Negatives - there was only one negative aspect to the entire week and that was the vendors. I think they set up about three times during the week we were there and would not leave you alone! They set up their tables near the lobby/main building area so it's impossible to avoid them. They constanly nag you to have a look at their products. Once you get away from one table another is only a few more feet away and you're dealing with the same thing. This was my only annoyance during the stay.Summary - overall I would definitely recommend Dreams to someone travelling to Punta Cana. The hotel amenities were great, and the food, service and entertainment made everything that much more better.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>