<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7d491ed62201f83b7d6abded3f47b3c0" url=""><![CDATA[Good place to rest your head The Wiechmann is in a great location, on the Prinsengracht, walking distance to everything. We had a room on the 3rd floor and getting our substantial luggage up there was a dreadful experience. The stairs are steep and twisted and not contiguous so you're switching from one staircase to another mid-trip. We were later told that normally someone would have carried our bags, but there was only one new person on desk duty that evening. They did find someone to bring our bags down when we checked out. We were there for three days and enjoyed the hotel and the location. We had the only room with a balcony and, although it was cold and rainy during our stay, this was a feature we enjoyed. Otherwise, the room wasn't memorable; in fact, there was mold on the bathroom ceiling. But everything worked well and we were happy there. We took advantage of the free computer use on the main floor every day of our stay. Breakfast is included in the price and there were boiled eggs and equipment to toast your bread. Other than that, it was the standard breakfast served in these kinds of places....lousy lunch meat, lousy cheese, a basket of winter fruit., cheap bread, canned peaches and, of course, abundant coffee and tea. We encountered great variation in the helpfulness of the staff. When we asked for additional pillows the first night, we were asked to come down and get them! We told the guy that he was younger than us and should bring them up! And there were a couple of women at the front desk who knew nothing about the surrounding neighborhood...even telling us to go as far as the Leidseplein to find a public telephone when we later found one around the corner! There's no excuse for untrained, uneducated front-desk staff at a hotel that charges 140E/night. On our last day, the owner of the hotel, helped us locate a hotel in Brussels for our last night, and we were very appreciative of his assistance. He did, however, charge us for the phone calls he made to Belgium.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>