<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="18fe3ad9caa446c52bc68da3d7136765" url=""><![CDATA[Eixample location is great We spent 3 nights in Barcelona. Loved the city but hotel was not great. It was the most disappointing of the hotels we stayed at during our 2 week vacation. However it was the least expensive of the hotels we stayed at as well. The Hotel Claris is rated a 5 star GL hotel but it does not exude a luxury hotel feel. The Hotel Majestic one block away exudes that luxury hotel feel. The public spaces in the Majestic had a 5 star feel where the Claris did not. The Claris is a 19th century building that has been completely gutted and converted into a very modern hotel with interesting design and modern atrium in the middle to provide light. Our junior suite was very dark with a separate livingroom with no window and the sole window in the bedroom was on a courtyard with very little light. The roof top pool and lounge area was nice but the gym is poor. just 3 cardio machines in a very small space.We totally enjoyed our stay in Eixample as opposed to staying in the more touristy Las Ramblas area. Within easy walking distance are the fine shops on the Pg. de Gracia (1 block away) and many of the fine Gaudi architectural treasures are within walking distance. I love art nouveau design and there is great examples all around. I enjoy walking and the old city is a good walk away but for those that don't enjoy the long walk it is just a short cab ride. There are also many great restaurants and cafes just a short walk away. We spent 3 nights there but we could have easily filled 6 days in Barcelona. There is much to see do and experience. Also the city is every bit as sophisticated as the top European cities.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a5640ef61a1a1134cbf018ab971e7034" url=""><![CDATA[Refreshed and Rested at the Palace We recently spent two nights at the Westin Palace. The Hotel delivered on what we expected. We wanted a comfortable hotel to catch up on our lost nights sleep after spending the night on a transatlantic flight. Positives: at check in we were offered a room upgrade through the Amex Platinum fine hotels program and we were put in the hotel's largest suite for the price of our deluxe room. This was no Junior suite but a full suite with separate living/dining room and extra half bath. The bedroom also had a separate dressing room outside of the bathroom. This was the most elegant room of our 2 week vacation but certainly not the most expensive. The bedroom was quiet and the a/c worked very well and we were able to catch up on our sleep. Included breakfast was a full breakfast buffet and good quality. The public areas of the hotel are very nice and well maintained. The location is great, especially if you are interested in seeing the major art museums which are only a short walk away. Negatives: the hotel staff was professional but always left me with an impersonal feeling that this was a big hotel chain. Of course this is a minor complaint since the staff gave us the great room upgrade on arrival. The gym is reasonably good and I got in a great work out one morning.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>