<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="185fbd96854be99b8c5ff74b5e3e9ffe" url=""><![CDATA[Bustling Nightlife, Friendly Staff, Perfect for a wknd trip The El San Juan is a great hotel if you are looking for a quick, fun trip to PR. In particular, it is perfect for groups of friends looking to party. I actually went down with my wife, and we had a great time. I would not recommend the El San Juan if you are looking for a quiet stay. The club at the hotel is hopping, and it's not just tourists in there, a lot of locals partying as well. The lobby is bustling at night, and the casino has a lot of activity as well. If you are looking for a slower scene in PR, I would recommend either the Ritz (right down the road), or the El Conquistador. The hotel has just finished being refurbished. I had visited in June of this yr, and was very impressed with the improvement this time around. The La Vista class room basically looked exactly like it does on their website, and the bathroom was much nicer than than one that preceded the refurbishment. The only potential negatives I would point out are :1) The walls are kind of thin, so if you may get unlucky with a loud neighbor. We were thankful we had a neighbor that only made noise during the day.2) Although the El San Juan has the best party scene, the Ritz has better restaurants (including Il Mulino, which was very tasty btw) and a nicer casino.3) If you're looking to explore Old San Juan it is not walkable. You will need to take a cab r/t, which will run you about 20 each way. More important than the money is the time though, traffic can be an issue. I would not really recommend the hotel for more than a 3 day stay. All in all we were very happy with the El San Juan but would not recommend for all types of travellers.One other quick point on San Juan. Last time I was here I went to a restaurant called Marmelade, which was fantastic. This time we tried Parrot Club, and were unimpressed.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="deda08adce19e1616308d0e127005631" url=""><![CDATA[Terrilbe/Non-Existent Management is the Downfall of the Hotel My wife and I have been to the Domican Republic several times before, and even got engaged there, so I feel we have a good sense of what can be expected in this country. In fact, we had a soft spot for the DR. We were on a family trip this time, celebrating an aunt and uncles 25th anniversary with both our parents and siblings. The Occidental has some positives, but overall our experience had so many negative aspects to it that I doubt we will ever return to the Dominican. I will start with the positives:The hotel layout is nice, the staff does a good job of keeping things clean.The bartenders do an admirable job of hustling despite the fact very few people tipThe late night pizza (available until 6 am) was surprisingly goodThe club Mangu is by far the most happening club we had ever seen in the DR Sadly - On to the negativesThe first problem we encountered was with the quality of our room. Our room had 2 twin beds pushed together (rather than a king which would be more appropriate for a married couple), non functional AC, a non functional fan, and a shower that was better described as a slow drip that alternated between ice cold and scaldingly hot. We were pretty miserable this first night, since neither the AC nor the fan worked. We subsequently found out we had been allocated a non renovated room. The rest of our group had all been allocated renovated rooms. Getting moved to a renovated room ended up being a major challenge. We kept being informed a manager was not around and they could not move us without approval from one of them, Finally, when a manager did arrive the nect morning, he tried to stay back in his office and have the reception attendant try to pass messages back and forth. It made us feel ridiculous. We insisted on speaking to the manager directly. He tried to say the resort was full, which was a complete lie (later we found out they were at 60% capacity), and that no renovated rooms were available. This was after seeing many many people wheeling suitcases from all the different buildings all over the resort that morning to check out. Finally, after 3 more trips to the reception culminating with asking for a meeting with the General Manager, a renovated room finally magically appeared for us. There really was no reason for the situation to get to this point, however. Given there were 4 problems with our room and there were plenty of rooms available, we should have been moved immediately. Our experience with the management on this issue, or lack of since the managers were rarely available, was repeated in other scenarios several times over the remainder of the trip.The staff often has a stop bothering us, we are just chilling attitude. For example, the day before we left I was trying to find out what time our bus would pick us up for the airport. I was informed I had to speak to the person that coordinated the bus, and that they were currently in the back of the lobby. I went to try to find them, they were not there. When I told this to the rep at the front desk, I was told they might be at the theatre now, but in any case would be around the property for a couple more hours and I should just wander around trying to find them. This was pretty annoying the day before we had to leave, and I wanted to get back to the beach. I asked them to just find the person coordinating the bus themselves, or make a phone call to find out the bus time and just send a message to our room with the time. Although this experience was not so terrible in its own right, I think it just shows the pervasive attitude of the staff.There was a constant stream of people complaining about various things at the front desk, which created a negative atmosphere and quickly eroded our confidence in how things were being run. The food is not good. A consensus quickly emerged that the buffet was the best choice (as opposed to the specialty restaurants). It was an interesting phenomenon to see all the restaurants nearly empty but a line out the door for the buffet. Most of us had issues in the bathroom from the second day onward.The reception staff, and lack of constant manager presence, leaves guests with the impression there is nobody to turn to about problems. A quick example here, I was working out in the fitness room one afternoon. The employee on duty approached me and asked me where I was from, after which he told me that God was number one for him and asked where he ranked for me. He then told me he was a Christian, etc. I was a bit at a loss at how to respond but I just smiled and returned to my workout. After this exchange he proceeded to go to the corner of the fitness room and chanting various prayers at the top of his voice I Spiritu Sankti, etc. This went on for the next 20 minutes of my workout. After the earlier frustrations at the front desk, I thought if I told them this story they would just laugh about their funny colleague, so I never ever bothered to tell anybody about it. Another negative was the quality of the nighttime entertainment. We actually had very low expectations from our previous trips. However, the Occidental took things to a new low. For example, one night the MC spent 45 minutes playing the I am thinking of a number between 75 and 95 game and then 120 - 140 after the first one was guessed and so on and so on. We had a problem with the staff ignoring the do not disturb signs. Twice, they walked on on us taking a nap.A final issue I will discuss is not completely the hotels fault, although they played a role. We asked at the concierge how we could book deep sea fishing. They recommended a company. We spoke to the owner in person and arranged a very specific deal. We wanted to keep all the fish we caught, have it cleaned by the staff and then have it cooked at a local restaurant. He quoted a price for this type of package, and told us that a friend of his that owned a restaurant had agreed to cook the fish as a favor as long as we bought drinks and side orders from his restaurant. We went out and caught 2 large Mahi Mahi that we took back to shore after which we had a series of unpleasant episodes. First, the boat staff told us they usually get to keep the fish, or at least one fish. So we had to argue about the fact we already had agreed with the owner to keep all the fish. Then, none of the staff wanted to clean the fish without additional tip, although we had already discussed this point with the owner as well. Finally, the restaurant owner told us he would not cook the fish unless he got to keep all the extra fish we could not eat on the spot (this was no good because we promised cooked fish to our wives and girlfriends). So it made us feel like everybody was constantly trying to scam us and take a piece out of us on every possible chance. We finally got the fish cooked at another small local place nearby for a reasonable sum, but we should not have had to pay anything more since we had been very exact in our negotiations. The owner of the boat was not available for all this time for anybody to call. Despite for success of the trip in terms of the fish, we actually returned really bummed out about the DR since we felt everybody was trying to scam us. We resolved not to leave the resort for any other trips. I would really suggest avoiding leaving the resort. Finally, it actually ended up being a funny joke to us, but the staff managed to incorrectly spell happy 25th anniversary on the cake we ordered for my aunt and uncle! To conclude, I would just avoid the Occidental. In order to improve matters at the property, I think they would have to completely overhaul the management and rethink how they organize everything at the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>