<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7c1cc91c4bd71fcdfdda131735b6ed05" url=""><![CDATA[A Pleasure It must have been our charm and good looks (I jest), but our recent four days at Las Casitas was terrific. We somehow missed most of the horrors noted by other TravelAdvisor guests. Las Casitas is a mini resort within a big resort and worth the extra bucks. Our room was private, clean and spacious and although it did not have all the toys and ameneties found in many other resorts (internet, etc.), it was fine by us. Our ocean view and intimate/private balcony was complemented with an adjacent swaying palmtree that quietly swooshed 24 hours a day and acted like white noise that made us totally oblivious to anyone or anything that might have disturbed the tranquility and the ocean view. Yes, many of the restaurants were overpriced, but there were less expensive options on the property that offered local cuisine that we have have always enjoyed (from many visits to Puerto Rico). What we thought was a complementary continental breakfast at the Las Casitas' pool cost us $50. We are quick students and the next day enjoyed a nice $7.50 (for two)breakfast at a Micky D's down the road. We made it a point to eat out as often as we could; not because of the prices, but because local, neighborhood restaurants (all over the island) offer a vast array of traditional foods that are usually a highlight of a visit to a different or unique culture. We can get prime steaks, Italian delights or deli sandwiches at home but can't duplicate the crispy but tender roadside barbequed pig (on a spit) you can find at a roadside shack in Luquillo. Back to the hotel: The boatride to and from the beach (Palomino Island) is part of the beach experience. It's a neat ten minute break with a bar on shore at either end (if that's of interest.) This was our first visit to this property and probably won't be our last. We enjoyed our stay and made the best of the few speedbumps we did encounter. Relax and leave your attitude behind.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>