<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="b3f364e5174091398fa7a4d42953d3e0" url=""><![CDATA[Great!!!! Booked this hotel for one night directly through Hilton's website, at a rate of USD 229 ++.This is one of my all time favourite hotels. It is simply a great hotel. I have stayed at many top ends hotels around the world, and even though Hampton would not be able to compete in the same segment as FS or MO, I must say that the unpretentious level of service and the lavish rooms are highly comparable to the snobby service and tired rooms of many of the top luxury hotels.I was checked-in early by a nice receptionist. The doorstaff took care of my luggage. My room was large and modern, it had a great and comfortable bed, sufficient lighting, a large LCD tv, a laptop safe, walk-in closet, a comfortable desk and ergonomical chair, a cosy chair and footrest. The bathroom was large and had a lot of quality amenities. The bathtub was large enough and the water pressure from the shower head were okey (could have been stronger, but not really a problem). I stayed on several hotels in New York during this trip: two nights at the Westin and three nights at the Sheraton Towers. Unfortunately I stayed only one night at the Hampton, because it was my last night in New York. Hampton were way better than the Westin and the Sheraton, both in terms of service/staff friendliness and in terms of room quality/amenities. I was so surprised by this, and I do wish all Hamptons could be like this one. Every staff member were warm, friendly and smiling - those includes the door staff, the elevator staff, the breakfast staff, the front desk staff, the housekeeping staff and so on. They provide a casual and comfortable atmosphere to the hotel. One of the managers called to my room to hear if everything were fine and in order. This usually happens in high end hotels only. I was pleasantly surprised to experience this in a Hampton Inn! There was complientary wireless internet throughout the hotel, complimentary local calls, complimentary coffee/tea/hot chocolate both in the rooms and in the lobby (a very nice feature), complimentary apples, complimentary newspaper delievered to the room and complimentery buffet breakfast. The breakfast was not my style of breakfast - only sweet things like cookies, donuts, cakes....not very healthy. There was a very limited selection of fruits and yoghurt. But it was all complimentary, so I can't complain about it. Starbucks and Subway were just across the street.Great location too!! One block from Times Square.I will return to this hotel anytime!!! Thank you Hampton Inn!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bfac69ecfc2c1648d62b9535080ce9f1" url=""><![CDATA[Decent Sheraton Booked this hotel via Hotelclub.com. Paid 100 USD per night, which was very reasonable.Located in walking distance to the historical centre....a short 10 minute walk to the Zucalo. The hotel is pretty new, and the public areas are airly and stylish, which a lot of things going on. There are many restaurants, lounges and bars in the lobby.The room was large and modern. The bed were very comfortable. TV with many channels. Coffee and tea making facilities. The bathroom was large with a large bathtub. Seperate room for the toilet and bidet. There were wifi too, but at a charge.The service was fine. Greeted by doormen and front desk staff. Security also good at the entrance, by the elevators and around in the lobby.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e2e0e81733430530a61284fad6b8114d" url=""><![CDATA[Stay somewhere else - waste of money! This hotel is not up to the guiding lines of the Mandarin Oriental hotel chain. A waste of money. Stay somewhere else.My stay was a huge disappointment to my sister and me. We were staying for 5 days. Already at the check-in they assigned us to wrong room. We had booked a deluxe twin bedded room. And we got a king bedded room, but had to change it into a twin bedded room, which they managed to do - after a long wait!!Further on, there were not much deluxe over the room. On the positive side the room was large and had a nice balcony. But it had only very basic things; like an old fashioned television, a cordless telephone (which did not work) and a radio. There were no dvd/cd-player in the room. No international plugs. Nothing extra at all!!! The beds were fine and good size (but I have experienced better beds). But lightening in the room were terrible, no bedside reading lights, and so on. Also, terrible bathroom solution...I mean the bathroom in itself was beautiful, but only thing that seperated the bathroom from the bedroom was a single, thin and sliding screen. So it was impossible to have an early morning shower without waking up my sister. Cause all the bathroom noise goes out to the bedroom. Not very smart solution!!! I prefer privacy when I am in the bathroom and beside this stupid screen there were no locks on the bathroom doors....The housekeeping in this hotels are the worst ever housekeeping I have experienced in any hotel. And it is such a shame that a hotel like Mandarin Oriental offer so poor service to their guests. The second day there were no towels provided, the third day there were no toiletries provided, the fourth day there were no water provided, and the fifth day there were no newspaper provided. I had to call for everything. This is not up to the reputation of the Mandarin Oriental. The business center was nice, but kinda pathetic that they charge you for using the internet there. I think it was 6 USD per 15 minutes, which is very expensive. Food was so-so. Tried the food at the beachside restaurant and in the Sambal Cafe. The sandwich at the beachside restaurant was very plain and tasteless, but the lunch in the Sambal Cafe was quite good.A nice feature on turndown service is that the hotel provides complimentary water from Voss. The onsite spa and pool was very nice, and the best thing about this hotel, I think.The service here is very slow and extremely inefficient. It took them like 30 minutes to get some towels to my room. The doormen outside are more busy talking private stuff, than opening the doors for the guests, you have to stand in line to talk to someone the front desk (which is unusual for a MO-hotel), the concierge is good (when he is actually on his desk). I also find some of the employees to have attitude-issues, which is not proper for a 5-star property. The concierge for example was kinda unpatient and rude when I wanted to ask about the limo-service. And an evening in the pool I was approached by a member of the security staff, and he told me in a very rude way: You have 10 minutes to leave the pool, I think it is kinda rude to talk like this to guests. Where are the humble hospitality?? I was told at the check-in by the manager on-duty that I the pool was official closed at 9 pm, but I could use the pool at my own convenience after this. So, I did at 11 pm. And then this happened. I tried to explain to this guy that I was told something else by the front desk. But he told me something else, and that I had to get out of the pool. I think this guy was very rude, and it is incredible that this can happen. All this made me very angry. I also notified the front-desk about the phone in my room was out of order. They said they would send someone up to look at it right away. But it never happened. I think I reminded them about 4-5 times during my stay, but NOTHING happened.The location of this hotel is depressing and out of nowhere. There is nothing to do there. You better have a car, or prepare use taxi every time you want to go somewhere. You can still walk downtown or to Bayside shopping, which is 25-30 minutes walk away. This was my first visit to Miami, and next time I go to Miami I would rather stay in South Beach/Miami Beach area (Delano Hotel/Setai/Loews Miami Beach Hotel), cause there you will find the points of interests. There is nothing to do downtown, and there are no good shopping options around (except Bayside). You have to go up North Miami or down South Miami or to Miami Beach:)I think this hotel are on a very wrong course, and that the management should be replaced. This is far by the worst 5-star hotel I have ever stayed in, and it is incredible that this can be a member of the MO-chain. Well, I will never return to this hotel. I'd better stick to Four Seasons Miami - which is a beautiful and a serious hotel. Great service at the FS too!! Miami was an amazing experience and a wonderful city, and I will go back without doubt, but not to the Mandarin Oriental!!!I sent a complaint to the hotel manager, but did not receive any reply at all.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f5da7aa0d225c287fb9129504dbddd00" url=""><![CDATA[The best hotel in Singapore MO is easily the best hotel in Singapore, after staying at RC and the Raffles. Whilst RC is cold and soulless, and Raffles are touristy and noisy - the MO is a warm and calm oasis and retreat. Check-in was very smooth, and got my room right away (at 11 am). The room was a superiour (I think it's the lowest category) on the 12th floor, it was newly refurbished and lavish, and very nice and comfortable. A bed to die for, and a large bathtub with seperate bathtub and shower. Large 42 LCD television with 80 or so international channels. Interactive telephone and also a cordless set, which was very convenient. The room had a large balcony overlooking Marina Mandarin. Not the best view, but it was nice to enjoy a cold cocktail in the sunshine.The staff and the service was great. The best service I have experienced in Singapore. Doorstaff and reception always greeted me by my lastname, and they were always smiling and very hospitable. The way MO should be:) The hotel does not have a grand lobby area, but they have a very nice bar on the 5th floor with a stunning view, overlooking Singapore harbour. There is also another bar, and 3-4 restaurants. Tried only the lounge and the bar - service, drinks and food were great. The breakfast (included in the room rate) was amazing, one of the best breakfasts I have ever had. There was a large selection of Asian and Western options, cold and warm, sweet and sour, light and heavy. You must try the breakfast when staying here. The juices are always fresh - made on request. Delicious.The hotel is located in Marina Centre - right next to the sea. I am not afraid of using my feet, so I walked everywhere without problem. The only times I used the subway was when going to Orchard Road and Chinatown. But you can easily walk to the harbour (just across the street) , the historic centre (10 minutes), Raffles (10 minutes), Singapore Flyer (5 minutes), Suntec City Mall (5 minutes), and so on... You can easily reach the subway if you walk through the mall that's connected to the hotel. All in all, the location is very convenient for sightseeing, business and shopping.If you love seafood you should visit Esplanade Mall across the street - there you'll find No Signboard Seafood. Strange name for a restaurant, but the food is absolutely delicious. It's quite inexpensive as well. Highly recommended!!I will return to the MO when going back to Singapore.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ecbe84d61fd8c06680e0d393b0cd2d78" url=""><![CDATA[Not up to the usual Westin standard Booked the hotel for two nights through Starwood, got a very favourable rate at 229 USD per night. When entering the hotel I was forced to let the doorman have my suitcase, even though I really prefer to take it by myself. I tried to check in at noon, but was told that there were no rooms available, and that the check-in time was 3 PM. I went out, and came back at 2:30 PM. I was told again that my room was not ready, so I sat in the lobby waiting for 3 PM. There were several guests waiting for the same. At 3:05 PM I went to the reception again, and was told that my room was not ready. Several guests tried to check-in but everyone was told the same. Then I asked to confirm that 3 PM was check-in time, and the rude receptionist told me that Check-in started FROM 3 PM. I told here that this was nonsense and demanded to speak to the managere. At frist, she would not get me the manager, but I insisted. After 5 minutes the manager came out from his hiding place (behind the reception) and told me that they had a room for me. What's the purpose of this??? I can understand that the hotel have a strict check-in policy and won't check in guests before check-in time. But I do find it rude and aqward what they don't even want to check-in guests AFTER check-in time. Westin did not show any kind of flexibility, so I will not do so either.I got my room on the 26th floor (I think). It was large and airy. It had a large LCD-tv (with a library of on-demand movies) and two very comfortable twin beds. However it was very dark and there was not enough light points. The bathroom was Westin style (e.g. very small, cold and crampy). The bathtub was too small to have a proper bath in. I do find the bed heavenly, but the bathroom is not heavenly by any means! I had a nice view over Times Square and Empire State Building, which was very nice. The housekeeping is highly inconsistent. My room was not serviced for turn-down service the first night. And my room was not serviced the following morning either. I returned to my room at 6 pm, and found my room to be just like I left it in the morning. I called the housekeeping and complained.However, the hotel is TOO big and TOO inpersonal for my taste. There are huge lines everywhere, and the hotel are not capable to offer their guests tabels at the restaurants or the bar, cause everything is full. The public areas of the hotel are well kept, shiny and nice, but it looks like a mall and are very business oriented. The location of this hotel is GREAT, just one block from Times Square. Many restaurants and shops at the doorstep.I will not return to the Westin again. New York City have a lot of other and better options. But you should definately go with Westin if you can get a rate like I did.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>