<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="aa0ce5af083350c41654f1987cad6dfa" url=""><![CDATA[Did the job nicely! We stayed here as part of a two day stay in San Fran and have to say it was perfect for what we were after, Close to Fisherman's wharf Pier 39, the vintage tram (a must!) which takes you to the shopping haven that is union square, and also close to the alcatraz ferry (one of the highlights of our 2 week stay in the US!).The hotel itself was well presented felt modern. Apart from the poor view from our room, I was pleased with it overall, the free wireless was a bonus and the complementary continental breakfast hit the spot. All in all I would definitley recommend this hotel for a short stay in San Fran.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1098adb7684f9f227057b50e1971043c" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel - the personal touch Having had the Magic Castle hotel recommended on trip advisor, I decided to book the hotel for 2 nights as part of our honeymoon to california. I booked directly through the website, and made the comment that it was our honeymoon stay (as I did with all the hotels - just in case!). When we arrived the bed had rose petals and there was complementary red wine a conrats card from the hotel which I thought was very nice touch!The hotel its self is in a great location for discovering Hollywood LA - if you really need to! We were very dissapointed with LA (in comparision with the other places on our trip, San Fran, San Diego etc), Hollywood was the wiredest mixture of freaks and disposible camera wielding tourists i have ever seen. However I am glad we did it as we seen all the sights form the movies etc. and was nice to have 'ticked the box'!The breakfast in the moring was more than adequate and the free drinks/snacks from reception were another unique plus point. Along with free wireless access friendliness of the staff we were more than happy with our choice, and if this hotel was in a different city - we would definitley be back!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>