<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="756893a7f6e66347a464ebebacdbd053" url=""><![CDATA[So very comfortable I stayed there for three nights in late August and had an excellent time there. I want to add that I am a female who was travelling alone and everything went smoothly. They have a lovely little pool and hottub on their roof at which I hung out until my room was ready.The room was large and tidy. I had a regular room not a suite so the interior was not spectacular, but served its purpose. Bathroom was nice, with stuff from Bath and Body Works. Plenty towels. I had a huge flat screen TV with DVD player and a Bose stereo system with remote. The AC worked flawlessly. At 6pm every nicht thei have complimentary cheeses, crackers and wine at the terrace which is great to kill the hunger before dinner.Their courtyard indoors is beautiful but bring bugspray (mosquitos everywhere in PR).I was also able to go online on their guest PC and check in and print my boarding pass the night before my flight home - very convenient.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="47caa57c147b2a818126359b53b3794d" url=""><![CDATA[Nice people I stayed there for three nights in late August and had a good time there. I want to add that I am a female who was travelling alone and everything went smoothly. The guys at the front desk where extremely helpful in suggesting restaurants, beaches, booking me into a biobay tour (even drove me there in their private car when the tour bus forgot me) and getting me a rental car.The room was big and tidy (I had room No. 7 with a nice bed with posts. The maids did a great job. They have a store downstairs so you can always get basic food and drink supply and they also rent snorkeling gear for $10 a day. The rooms are simple and basic, so don't expect any amenities, but for the price and location (Esperanza is best) it is a great deal with very helpful people.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>