<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="0ea473789ac2fbe81e3eac498c48c8fd" url=""><![CDATA[Incredible... Best shower ever
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ab079fecd75672def56b8548c27da95b" url=""><![CDATA[Great hip hotel -- very comfortable The reviews on this site are pretty right on, except for the part about the techno music. You can barely hear it in the hallway next to the elevator. I stayed in a corner king room on an upper floor with a great view of the bay bridge and surrounding bay to the south. It's the most peaceful urban hotel room that I've ever stayed in. The really fun part of the hotel is that when you're ready to leave the calmness of your room, it's a short elevator ride down to the 2nd floor bar or the 1st floor cafe/bar, both of which get a large crowd of urban young professionals seven nights/week. The bar staff were not pretentious at all; they were very friendly and approachable. The drinks are expensive, but the atmosphere is great, so long as you're into the hip/trendy setting. The room is set up really nicely, and the bed, as at all W hotels, is probably the most comfortable hotel bed that I've slept in. The sitting area beside each of the windows was also great. It was large enough to curl up on and read a book. The bathroom is large and the shower is pretty decent (nothing like the shower at the carneros inn, but the water pressure is strong and adjustable...it's also not cramped). I understand some of the reviewer complaints about the bathroom door. You can't see through it exactly, but it's not opaque. In a King room it makes sense. In a double room, I'm not sure why they wouldn't switch to an opaque door (if you're not sharing a bed with your fellow traveller, I really doubt you want to see a sillouette of him/her on the can) but then again, it let a lot of natural light into the bathroom. Some reviewer mentioned that the wooden shades didn't block the light. I guess their shades must have been broken, because I found that they worked great, and I like my hotel rooms very dark. I also ordered room service one morning and it was brought up in about 10-15 minutes and was very good. Yeah, it's expensive...it's hotel room service, so what. The pool and workout area are also very nicely done. I wish that the outside patio that extends from the pool were on a higher floor rather than just the 3rd, but then again it was raining most of the time, so it wouldn't have mattered for my stay anyway.The only piece of advice I have is this. If you're getting to the hotel by cab instead of your own vehicle, don't drag all your luggage in through the main enterance at the corner of 3rd and Howard. Instead, go down Howard about 100 feet to where it says Wheels and go in that way. If you go in the main enterance and it's after 5pm, you will feel like an idiot b/c you'll be dragging your luggage through a mob of people and probably try to check in at the bar. The hotel is a great retreat and you'll have fun as long as you like the hip/trendy type of hotel. Check out their website and know what you're getting into...if you're older and don't want to be around a bunch of young professionals, probably better off at a Union Square hotel, which is really only a few blocks away.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="03b5230204e4760dc19404506fc8bba4" url=""><![CDATA[Great location with a great corner room -- feels very business though Another view
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0aa2b3607d23645dcaac3ee339638982" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic choice -- Deluxe Room w/ View great choice bathroom
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>