<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="1e688b072dcb85734754534c85ecf3e9" url=""><![CDATA[Charming Property, Great Value, Highly Underrated The York Hotel is a wonderfully charming property, that is without a doubt highly underrated and great for the value. I booked my room via Expedia for $89, which included a free breakfast (didn't take advantage of that so I can't comment) as well as free Wifi. The York Hotel is about to begin a huge transformation into the Hotel Vertigo (it is one of the filming locations of Alfred Hitchcock's Vertigo), and I was given the model room, which was an already renovated room as a preview of what the new rooms will look like. For $89/night, I was blown away. Service wise, every staff member was kind and courteous, and willing to help with anything possible. The room was very modern, with an extremely comfortable bed, very modern nightstands, and a cool bathroom, as well. Beautiful plasma TV, the only thing that didn't work was the AC/heater. This was not a problem, as the window could be opened and closed and I quickly found a nice temperature. Since I can't comment on the current rooms, I'm not sure how applicable this review is to those visiting in the very near future, but if possible do request the model room and I'm sure you will not be disappointed. I enjoy the decor of places like The Clift of The W, and the room was definitely on a par with those properties.As other reviews say, yes, the walls are paper thin, but are nowhere near as big a problem as other people point out. Definitely not enough to keep you awake. Parts of the hotel that are already renovated are very chic and modern, others still have that old/floral design, but personally I didn't find this bothersome. The surrounding area, while a bit of a hike (let's say a 10 min walk) from Union Square was through a very interesting area (very artsy), I felt safe no matter what time of the day or night.I have no complains at all about this property, and while it certainly isn't a 5-star property like a Four Seasons or Ritz Carlton, it's a great option if you're on a budget but want something nice.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>