<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="04deaa38c2cd2b1544f4450c056fc491" url=""><![CDATA[Fabulous hotel, a little out of the way The Amsterdam Art is a little bit outside of the city centre which does restrict you to following bus timetables, however there are busses every half hour which drivers who love their city and love giving you tips for stuff to see and do! At nighttime we felt perfectly safe travelling on the night bus back.The actual hotel is lovely, very clean and modern. The bathroom is just amazing, probably my favourite part about the whole hotel to be honest!What did concern me was the fact that we had a double bed, which was actually two singles pushed together with two single duvets. What was strange was that there was no space for the beds to be seperated to convert into a twin room, so we didn't really understand that.Apart from the beds, I don't have anything to fault the hotel about to be honest, it was fabulous!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4ce1c223f826f9ddd89fc3bb077c61f1" url=""><![CDATA[Fabulous hotel, great location! With a metro station a few minutes stroll away, the Opera de Noailles was located perfectly to explore Paris!The room was fantastic - really clean and spacious, a little too hot, but management came and sorted out the air conditioning for us which was great! The only gripe that we had about the room was the shower, which you had to hold above your head which made washing hair etc a bit tricky. Apart from that the bathroom was lovely.Our favourite thing about this hotel was the continental breakfast which was fantastic! There was so much choice of food which was all replenished regularly so nothing went cold/tasted stale.The only thing is, the lift in the hotel is tiny, so not sure it would suit anyone using a wheelchair. And the bar closes at 10pm, which was a little early for our liking. Overall, with the friendly staff, big, clean rooms, we found little to grumble about and thought that it was a fantastic hotel which we'd definately recommend!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b5707b2c28a3019563e7f5479fa6c6af" url=""><![CDATA[Faultless I had a fantastic short break in New York at stayed at the Millenium Hilton, while it was quite expensive, you definately get your money's worth. We had a junior suite which was immaculate, the maid service was excellent.I found the staff to be very helpful and polite and nothing appeared to be too much trouble for them. The pool and sauna were lovely, although the water was very cold! The restaurant was lovely, although I struggled to find something I wanted on the menu, ended up with a salad which was very nice.Location was excellent, the subway was right nearby and taxis from Times Square (for when we were feeling lazy in the evening) were reasonably cheap.It was a great base to explore New York from and I totally enjoyed my stay there. I'd definately recommend it.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>