<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="bc9b7fd0e0cbe10d0550c2ff5984691d" url=""><![CDATA[Well worth the wait! After a long wait and numerous negative reviews, it was well worth it and I will keep it as short as I can and to the point as most of this you have already read.The rooms are very nice, clean and spacious. The open bathroom was never a problem and there were 7 of us in 4 different rooms aged 25-49. The food was good in all restaurants, especially the Asian. We went twice and had no problem getting a seat at the Hibachi. The first time we waited in line for a hour for the 6:30 seating and the second time we made reservations at 8:00 for the 9:00 sitting. There are 3 Hibachi grills, ask for Pedro, a young guy with a great sense of humour and an excellent cook. For breakfast, Felix's omlettes in the buffet are a must.The pools and beach are as beautiful as they come.The entertainment was as good as I've seen at any resort and is very professional. The costumes and acrobatics are as good as you will get without actually being in Vegas.The entertainment committee itself work very hard, especially John, Jose and Evelyn.We found the drinks somewhat inconsistant at the pool bar, however the Lobby Bar and Tantra bar made the best. Look for Sandra at the pool bar for the best drinks there.Overall the staff throughout the hotel were very friendly and helpful and work very hard.The only things we would like to see change are at the lobby were when cashing US travellers cheques, you can only get Pesos and when buying gifts whether at the resort or off, the price always seemed to be higher in Pesos than in US dollars.The other, we would have liked to see more music around the pool, even though it seemed to get better later in the week. I understand the whole ambiance thing, but the music just adds a little flavour.I would rate this resort a 4.5*, but that is not an option, so I picked 5, as they are not quite perfect, yet.A special thanks to John from the entertainment team for making the trip special.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>