<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="f7aaf4a07cfe2bcf0d1d481870855987" url=""><![CDATA[More than adequate I first stayed at the Cathedral Hill -- it was then known as the Jack Tar -- nearly 40 years ago. I stayed in it again for two nights this month. The hotel was OK in the 1960s; it's still OK.Rooms are large and well kept. Bathrooms and closets are tiny (as were those in most hotels decades ago), but clean and supplied with the essentials -- including abundant hot water -- as well as an automatic coffee maker. A good-sized television set sits in a large cabinet with three or four large drawers.The Cathedral Hill has a good enough restaurant and a nice bar. On the patio (4th) floor there's a large Japanese garden that is a nice place for snacks, drinks, and just lounging about. (Some fourth floor rooms open directly onto the garden, or patio.)The hotel also has a newsstand and other shops. Parking is available; at US$22 a night -- not expensive by San Francisco standards (and the price allows unlimited ins-and-outs).Being at Van Ness and Geary, the Cathedral Hill is not located near San Francisco's main attractions; but the city is small enough that most are within a (somewhat long) walking distance. There are several decent restaurants in the area and Japantown, with the most reasonably priced sushi (and other dishes) in the city, is a five-minute drive away.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8428122c590ec49ff0ecdc39176f2e65" url=""><![CDATA[Fine Hotel, Fine Location The Cartwright is just four blocks from Union Square, with theaters and shopping nearby. Standard rooms (and bathrooms) are tiny but nicely appointed and well maintained. Parking is at a commercial lot a block and a half away; validated by the hotel, it is $25 a night. A decent, self-service breakfast is complimentary.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e5be107972e0c5ee1542a19606eb0b5e" url=""><![CDATA[Beware of scam According to one clerk, a couple in a room near mine had complained of tobacco smoke and she had had to refund them one (1) night's lodging. A little later another clerk said he had refunded them two (2) nights' room-rent. That they couldn't get their stories straight was evidence of a scam. In either event, they insisted that I -- a non-smoker -- would be required to pay $250 for a clean up. This is a scam that would be outrageous even in New Delhi. (I refused to pay and will contest it if I find a charge on my AmEx bill.)Otherwise the motel is just all right. My room was clean and good-sized, though I've had larger bathrooms in Tokyo. Rooms facing Lombard Street -- about half of all rooms -- are noisy to the point of disturbing sleep. Though the inn advertises covered parking, fewer than two-thirds of the spaces are -- and even those are only partly under the building.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>