<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="579164d2bff2d3fd4ec4192dd5c87203" url=""><![CDATA[The ultimate "home away from home" with Class! My sister and I just returned from staying at the Windsor Court Hotel in New Orleans last week. It was a lovely experience in every way. I booked double beds in a grand suite on a Membershiip Rewards special package that included a complimentary continental breakfast. We were given a beautiful suite with a great view from its balcony. The complimentary continental breakfast was delicious, albeit, somewhat small, with a choice of pastries, toast, freshly squeezed juices, and coffee or a selection of hot teas. The wait staffers were very polite and attentive at all times. We always treated like very important guests. We also sampled drinks in the Polo Bar in the evening where we happily listened to a marvelous piano medly played by a very talented pianist. Service in the bar was also top notch. We ended our visit to the Windsor Court Hotel by partaking of the high tea which is served in the restaurant space downstairs every Friday, Saturday, and Sunday afternoons. It was splendid! After eating a tasty offering of different kinds of finger sandwiches and drinking an unusual cherry/cranberry black tea, we sampled fabulous fresh-baked scones and fruit pastries served with a variety of spreads. To top it all off, we were brought a third selection of scrumptious cakes, candies and chocolate-covered strawberries. The location of the Windsor Court Hotel is very convenient to both the River Walk, the Harrah's Casino, the Central Business District, Lafayette Square, Canal Place Shopping Center, and only a few blocks from the French Quarter. In addition to the Windsor Court's fine Grille, there are many choices of restaurants located within walking distance nearby. We never had to use our car to get around, but enjoyed the close proximity to New Orleans' marvelous historic tourist sites.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>