<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="73c08a98106dc309c2186a8305f916ad" url=""><![CDATA[Stay for the atmosphere and people It really is too bad this hotel is located where it is, smack in the middle of downtown San Francisco. That means you'll encounter a lot of homless persons, and some of them can be downright rude. I never felt unsafe with the alcoholics and beggars, as I'm used to much worse in Oslo, Norway. But there were a lot of them, that is true.The hotel building is very nice, and has a lot of style. I have travelled a lot in the US, and it is one of the more charing hotels I've seen as for the style. It is nice to stay a place where there is actual history and the staff don't brag about columns dating all the way back to 1970.The biggest asset of this hotel is clearly the staff. They are very friendly and professional. The evening concierge went out of his way to help me find a decent Chinese take out place and provided menus. The front staff were effective and friendly, as were the maids. Unlike other hotels in the US, they actually followed the on the rack, don't take it back rule but left the towels there to be reused.The bath was very small but very clean, much newer than the rest of the room and with nice accessories for soap, shampoo etc. My double queen size room was small, but stylish. Also, something that people often forget, the roof was very tall. This means better air and a more spaceous feeling in the room.After evaluating the neighbourhood during the day and observing at night I walked outside in Market St. and was not harassed by any of the numerous beggars. But I can see how some might feel uncomfortable. No biggie, San Fran has good public communication and they are right outside the hotel door. Very nice.If I have to complain about something, I'd say the hotel room needs new doors. They show their age more than anything else there. Also, they do not provide a lot of noise insulation so there's some noise from the hallway. But I had no general noise problems aside from that. The WiFi was a bit flakey, and the parking was very expensive at $28 per night plus tax. That, however, included unlimited valet.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ca788a2626b7b523acdc83b182ff439b" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel, need to iron out some faults The Hotel 1898 is located in the former buildings of the Philippines Tobacco agency of Spain, a trading company. This makes for a truly nice and genuine old building, where the insides have been ripped out and redone completely. Absolutely everything inside is new, including the newly carved out parking garage.We arrived to check in without any problems, after first having some quarrel with the GPS. The street La Rambla is not a valid GPS destination for this hotel, after calling the hotel we were told the street address is Pintor Fortyun 1, and the GPS guided us to the front door.The location is on the main tourist street in BCN, apart from the scores of cheap-flight tourists hanging around the location can't be more perfect in BCN.After check in we ordered parking for the car a bit pricey at 23 night. But the garage is right under the hotel, amazing for such an old building and I was guided in by the bellhop. The room is probably too small for its price category, but very tall and nicely done. Very clean, and always magically cleaned when we were out. The A/C was found inside the closet not difficult to find but a bit difficult to read the screen. After shivering through the night with an overzealous A/C I decided to read the manual and discovered how to run it proper.Room was quiet, apart from some low hallway noise. Not a nuisance.There's plenty of channels on the TV, but not all of them were as according to the manual. Nice to have Fox Series to watch in the evening after the spa.We did not feel the 20 was a good enough value to eat in the hotel.On the roof is one of the major assets of this hotel, a smallish pool and a very nice bar. The pool is good for a dip in the heat and there is several beds along the rooftop. Ample amounts of towels and a complimentary bathrobe makes the lack of changing area near the pool a non-issue.In the bar, there's no a lot of perfection, in spit of the staff effort. They are courteous and friendly, but not very professional. Also, the drinks are very off on the recipe, like the strawberry daiquiri. Nice selection of cheeses on a plate along with a bottle of good red wine is a much better bet in the not very comfortable large divans. The spa in floor -1 is nice, with a warm and comfortable spa pool. Steam sauna is still out of order, and the Finnish sauna was not hot enough at 70 degrees Celsius and low humidity.At the business centre, there's the usual Americans hogging the computers chatting along with home base in Kentucky or where ever but fortunately there is enough of them to go around. I had to print, sign and fax a contract in the evening and none of these actions were an issue. WiFi in the room was very slow and needed a login and password from the desk to function.All in all, this is a 4/5 because there's some issues that need to be corrected. They have an almost perfect building and location but partly fail on details and prices. This does not mean that the hotel should be avoided, however.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>