<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="6">
		<document id="61b624ed118fc2bd45927c9240696384" url=""><![CDATA[Great stay in Waikiki! We spent a night in Waikiki on our way to the Big Island. The hotel is quite large and even has two ABC stores (similar to Walgreen's/CVS) on the poperty. Upon check-in, the front desk attendant presented us with a gift since we were celebrating a special occasion. It was a nice touch and we found the staff to be very accomodating and friendly.Our ocean-view room was spacious with a lanai that offered side views of Diamond Head and Waikiki Beach.The beach is easily accessible as are several quick-service, fast food, and sit down restaurants. There is also a Seattle's Best coffee shop downstairs where we grabbed breakfast.I had read reviews of loud music and noise but we did not hear any of this during our stay.The bed was comfortable and the shower had a detachable head. Parking is expensive but we chose valet for a few dollars more rather than seeking a spot in the self-parking lot.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="07722c118e37ffa5daac8554e9c5d371" url=""><![CDATA[Staff went above and beyond! We decided to take an in-town vacation and celebrated a special occasion at the Ritz-Carlton Dallas. The service was impeccable. Every staff member greeted us and went out of their way to make our short stay special.The spa was fantastic - even if you don't get a service, I highly recommend buying a day pass to use the whirlpool, steam room, pool, and sauna - don't forget the relaxation room!The staff must have realized we were celebrating, because they sent up a special treat for us to enjoy during our stay - it was these small gestures that really showed the dedication that the hotel has to it's guests. There is construction going on but we heard absolutely NO noise whatsoever. Our room was large and had a fabulous bathroom with a great amenity kit. We didn't want to leave!The hotel is quite close to several wonderful restaurants and museums. We will be back soon!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="14bede607b185cb41e6761b53b170158" url=""><![CDATA[Weekend Stay in NYC We arrived on Friday afternoon and had put in a request for a club level room which was unavailable. We were told that we had been upgraded to a better room but I couldn't see anything out of the ordinary. The lobby was extremely crowded. We had a leak issue in the room and reported it to the front desk. Someone from Engineering called to confirm the situation and promptly took care of it while we were out to dinner.Our room was on a higher floor and provided a spectacular view of the river. There are two entrances to the hotel (one facing 42nd and one facing 43rd) which provides easy access to the subway system and Times Square.Overall, the location was great and the accomodations were comfortable. The hotel decor is very modern and clean. Our room had a stainless steel sink and counter area along with two shower heads in the shower. The beds were the signature Westin Heavenly Bed and the room had a beautiful flat screen television.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c84f71f6e5b62f5776a91d35563a86ea" url=""><![CDATA[Right in the Middle of it All View from the Hotel
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="57acb47e42d627fcbb9b15c500b45d09" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful weekend at the W! We stayed on a Friday night for an in-town getaway. The night began with drinks in the Living Room and a fantastic meal at N9ne Steakhouse across the street. Be sure to let your server know if you plan to visit Ghostbar. He gave us a special item and it allowed us to skip the long line. We jumped right on an elevator up to the top. The view was fantastic!Each staff member was extremely friendly and helpful during our short visit. The Bliss products in the bathroom are awesome as well. I only wish we'd had more time to visit the pool and Craft!Maybe next time!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7dd5b92e64f6fae6272093ae99ac7498" url=""><![CDATA[Nice location/ average stay We visited New Orleans for a wedding and stayed at the Chateau Sonesta for two nights.A friend who had arrived the night before suggested we ask for a room that faced the inside atrium of the hotel and we're glad we did after hearing complaints about street noise from other guests. The rooms are spacious with very high ceilings. Beds were comfortable with extra large pillows. Bathroom was okay, somewhat dingy, with hardly any water pressure.Luckily, the location was fabulous. We were just a street away from Bourbon Street and within walking distance of Harrah's, Cafe Du Monde, etc.The hotel also has a restaurant and the Clock Bar. We took advantage of the lobby self-serve coffee cart in the morning.The staff was friendly and courteous as well.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>