<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="5ee82c9ce537c4e73d5ebe805924850d" url=""><![CDATA[Nikko Not So Great My boyfriend and I stayed at the Hotel Nikko on our first trip to San Francisco. I seriouly researched a number of hotels on the internet and phoned them for questions. Nikko seemed like the best value for location, size of room, trendiness and price. The location was good. Close to Union Square, public transport, restaurants and shopping. And from the entrance, lobby, and front desk appeared to be nice, clean and modern. Our room was a different story. The size of the room was not bad, considering most hotel rooms in San Francisco seem to be on the small side. I think we had a Delux Queen room. The bathroom was small, fit for really just one person. My biggest complaint was that the bathroom was pretty grungy. As a previous reviewer mentioned, they had what used to be white tile grouting on the bathroom floor and sink, that was so dirty it was dingy dark grey. It made me not want to walk barefoot in the bathroom. You could still see where it was the original white in the corners. We had to ask for extra bathmats to put down to walk barefoot in the bathroom. The tub was also dingy. The carpet gave me the creeps too. Also, each day that the housekeeping staff cleaned the bathroom, there were stray hairs left behind in the white sink and tub. They clearly were not from my boyfriend or I, wrong color. I am not super picky, but a clean bathroom is something I would expect from a 4-star hotel. I could live with a not so perfect bathroom if it was at a motel, because at least then I would know I was getting what I paid for. And it rubbed me the wrong way that they wanted guests to pay for extra toiletries left in the bathroom. And you had to pay to use the pool and workout facilities, which is kind of cheap of them. An they were not so great anyway.Our bed was large and comfortable. A few other reviewers had mentioned that they could not get the internet in the room to work. We had the same experience. Complimentary in-room internet access was one of the reasons I chose this hotel, but my boyfriend could not get it to work from his company laptop, which he never has problems with anywhere else. The front desk and IT person they connected him to were no help. We never got it to work. Upon checkout, they attempted to charge us about $40 for mini-bar items, but we hadn't touched a thing. They took the charges off without protest, but there was another customer checking out the same time as us with the same complaint. Overall, it was too expensive for what we got. If the rooms are going to be grubby anyway, I might as well only pay for a Best Western. We will not stay there again. We viewed a room at the W Hotel one night while we were there for dinner, and we would rather pay just a little bit more next time and stay there, where you get your money's worth.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>