<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="d980b58f11566388ababe5e3e1e1c9bb" url=""><![CDATA[I enjoyed the stay very much Axel advertises itself as a gay hotel, and the clientele did seem to be mostly gay men (of all ages). However, it is in a quiet but very central location in the city, and the hotel is comfortable enough to suit most open-minded travellers. It is just 10-15 minutes' walk away from the main hustle and bustle of Las Ramblas and Placa Catalunya, and there are quite a few gay bars and restaurants within one or two blocks of the hotel. The staff are also very friendly and helpful.Sure, I have to admit that the reception area seemed small and the decor at the entrance didn't grab my attention straight away. But the room was simply but stylishly furnished, and there were plenty of unusual and pleasantly surprising touches (such as the unlimited free bottles of chilled water on each floor, and complimentary packs of condoms among the designer toiletries in the bathroom!)The rooftop terrace seemed to be a focal point for many of the guests. There were a jacuzzi/hot tub, a swimming pool, a small gym, sundeck, and a rooftop bar serving drinks and cocktails. On a nice summers day, it was very easy to meet and chat with other travellers, and the atmosphere was friendly and relaxed. On different nights of the week, there were various events and the rooftop bar became a stylish drinking venue for non-hotel-guests as well. The hotel also had a restaurant on the ground level, which other hotel guests highly recommended (although I didn't get to dine there).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f63b6f8fdfc862645547ce71ecb2fcb6" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel in a fantastic neighbourhood I have just stayed at the Villa Mazarin for one week, and would definitely stay there again in the future. Sure, the hotel wouldn't suit everybody. If you want a bar, breakfast room, room service, plenty of amenities, or a quiet, leafy neighbourhood, this hotel is not for you. It is a boutique hotel with a very discreet entrance (blink and you would miss it) in a very hip area of Paris. The front entrance is locked most of the the time, and you need to be buzzed in by the receptionist. You walk past the reception desk in a narrow hallway, and into a small central courtyard to go up to the rooms. There is no bar or restaurant, and breakfast is delivered to your room directly (although there are plenty of options in the multitude of cafes around the hotel). However, the rooms are very comfortable and pleasant, and comparatively spacious for the price you pay. I had a room on the second floor facing rue des Archives, but there wasn't too much noise from the street. The reception staff (all the ones that I interacted with) were polite, friendly, efficient and helpful, and all spoke very good English - and there was a personal level of service that many bigger hotels lack (e.g. whenever I got back to the hotel, I rarely had to tell the front desk my room number before they handed me my room key - even new staff members that I hadn't met before knew which room I was in!) I initially felt a little awkward when I was heading back to the hotel in the early hours of the morning after a fun Friday night at the bars and clubs, wondering what Monsieur at the front desk would think or say ... there was no need to worry really, as he couldn't have been more friendly or courteous when I pressed the buzzer at the front door. The hotel is located in a street with good restaurants, brasseries, cafes, and quite a few gay bars (you wouldn't feel at ease staying in the area if you're prudish about gay people). However, it is not a gay hotel, as the clientele is remarkably diverse, with families, young couples (straight and gay), younger and older singles, elderly tourists, etc. It is across the road from the very popular BHV department store (which has a separate building for men, and another smaller store for pets!). It is around the corner from the Hotel de Ville metro station - and five minutes walk down to the Seine. Centre G. Pompidou, Chatelet and Forum des Halles are about 10 mins walk away - that area is a bit too hectic for my liking. And the beautiful and tranquil place des Vosges as well as the boutiques and interesting shops in the Marais are very close by also.All in all, a very good hotel experience!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="71e6c46e704e81a2192884a5b9c76e69" url=""><![CDATA[Good value for Madrid This is a great boutique hotel which compares very favorably to higher starred establishments in Madrid. The location is very central - just steps away from the Opera metro station and the Palacio Real, and about 10 minutes' walk from the Gran Via and Sol. However, it is situated in a narrow, quiet street. I had a standard room, but it was clean and spacious with a rather large bathroom. A decent breakfast was included in the price, and served buffet-style in the breakfast room (until noon on weekdays, and 1 pm on weekends - suitably civilized hours for a vacation in Madrid!). Reception staff were young, but very helpful and friendly, and spoke perfect English. Sure, there was no restaurant or bar or swimming pool or gym - but all the night life, sights, and restaurants were only moments away from the hotel. I had friends who were staying in a much more expensive boutique-style hotel nearby, and Mario room-mate was in no way inferior to their accommodation. If catching a cab to the Hotel, just ask the driver to stop at the Teatro Real (Opera House) or it is just as convenient to get the metro to Opera. This hotel chain is opening a new establishment in Chueca (Oscar Room-mate). It wasn't quite ready to open when I was in town, but it looked great from the outside.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>