<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f454f6c06c25b2f4fda8c305f31720e9" url=""><![CDATA[If you don't like timeshare touts give this resort a miss Graham Lin, Worcester, EnglandMy wife and I stayed from 19th. April, 2007 till 4th. May, 2007.The hotel is very spacious and open, perhaps they removed too many trees when they built it compared to ther resorts along the coast. The beach also is very open, with the sunshades offering little shade even when properly roofed. No shortage of beds though. The beach bar was excellent with Omar providing real entertainment, when you get to know him.The beach is wide, and one can walk for miles in either direction from the hotel quite safely. Take a couple of bottles of water with you though.The main areas of the hotel are kept spotless and there is always someone in view with a broom or mop. The pool areas are particularly well furnished. Two very large swimpools, a light smattering of jacuzzis, and two swim up bars, more than enough to keep the pool persons happy.Toilets throughout the resort were generally very clean and well maintained even with the large volume of usage.The nearby golf course and clubhouse is well worth a visit, although only a 9 hole course at the minute plans are for a full 18 soon. Just a ten minute walk from the front of the hotel.Restaurants on the resort were average with the beach restaurant the best by far,followed by the Italian and Mexican, neither the Italian, Mexican or Route 66 seemed big enough to satisfy the demand. It was difficult to get into some of the restaurants on occasions, and a waiting system did not always work as we were left until it was almost too late. We had been forgotten about, but an apology was given and accepted.The main buffet restaurant was very good with a good variety of offerings most times, with the breakfast omelettes a must to try.In the buffet restaurant one evening we had a tour of the kitchens to collect our food and they were absolutely spotless, a novel idea which can only be rated as a good move.Mike`s Coffee is the 'jewel in the crown' of the resort, and they do a mean Irish and Caribbean liqueur coffee, together with every other coffee or tea you can think of. The little biscuits/cakes are very tasty and we whiled away many a happy hour in there.As for evening time, there seemed to be an ongoing contest between the nightly show and the acts in the lobby bar to see who could be the loudest. The lobby entertainment which varied consisted of male or female vocalists, or a very capable saxophonist and keyboard player, and they all insisted on amplifiers, which magnified the sound way beyond what was needed, so much so you could not hold a quiet conversation anywhere in the lobby, except between tunes. We often sat outside 'Mike's' where the noise became background music as it should be.This hotel does not provide a quiet place in the evening where people can sit in easy comfy chairs with a bar, perhaps some background music, to just chill out, and enjoy the company of new friends.Our room was well furnished, and the maid maintained it without fault for the whole fortnight, we did help her focus her mind though with a daily tip and treat. Lighting in the rooms is very poor, so don`t bother trying to read in the room before sleep time.Hot water was also an issue on occasions, but with a spa bath in every room the call upon hot water must have been huge.On our departure date a 4 hour delay in travel was posted the day before, and we were being kept on resort. We all made enquiries with the hotel to be able to pay the $10 per hour charge to keep our rooms but none were successful. The reception staff were most unhelpful, and very abrupt. We managed with the use of a courtesy room for half an hour.Our main gripe relates to the Timeshare people, they replaced the mosquito as enemy number one. They are in your face from the moment you arrive to the time you leave. Try ignoring them and they make snide remarks, tell them no and they follow you, you have to be as insistent you are not interested as they are persistent in trying to sucker you in. Perhaps a sticker on the wrist band to say that you have been zapped by them or are not interested in being zapped by them might be a way forward. Most resorts have these people but in this case they are easily the worst, and provide my wife and I with more than enough reason to never go to this resort again. I am saddened to say that the star rating flatters this resort somewhat, and I find it difficult to assess who it is better suited to other than people who like noise from breakfast to bedtime, with the evening time being the most difficult.My wife and I enjoyed our holiday very much, and we met some very nice people, but all things considered (even without the timeshare people) this resort is not for us. Back to the Melia Caribe or the drawing board.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>