<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="7d19721ce7bd9086a54a5c669ef4d1ab" url=""><![CDATA[Good, but could do better. My husband and I stayed in room 305 in April 05. The location is excellent and the staff were very friendly and helpful. We arrived at the Hotel at 1.30pm but could not check in until 3pm, but we were able to leave our luggage and so off we went for a well earned drink! We had trouble with our shower - when we returned to the room on Sunday night we found a foul smelling black sludge had come up through the plughole (not nice). We reported it to Reception immediately - the chap on the door came up with us to take a look. We couldn't shower on Monday morning, but by the time we returned to the room in the afternoon the problem was fixed and the shower showed no signs of the sludge! So we could not fault them on this - blocked plugholes happen at home too! - and there responsiveness to the problem was appreciated.Our room was directly opposite the lift and it did ding a fair few times - but it wasn't loud enough to wake us. The rustling of plastic bags at 6.30am by, we assume, Housekeeping made us laugh rather than annoyed us. We couldn't work out what they were doing since it seemed to go on forever, but whenever we went out of the room, there was never anyone to be seen.I did find that the hairdryer only blew cold air - a pain, but overcome by showering as soon as we returned to the room in the evening, and letting my hair dry naturally for half an hour. The only other disappointing thing was that the room was not very clean. The sink, loo and shower WERE clean but the top of the times that ran round the bathroom were not, neither was the ledge on the loo - in fact it was revolting. The lamps by the bed were also really dirty. The walls in the bedroom and the bathroom were worn - a new coat of paint wouldn't go amiss. And the pictures above the bed weren't even hung straight. Now these little things certainly did not spoil our time in NYC (we loved it) but I was a bit disappointed since most of the other reviews we had read said how pristine the rooms are - ours wasn't.I would stay at Hotel 41 again - we know what to expect - but I would insist this time that the room was cleaned.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>