<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="5aa8fdfab4696fb602ffe6e05e1e3bdf" url=""><![CDATA[Great holiday, great time!! We have just returned from the Palace, this being our third visit, but our first with our family (our daughter, her husband and their two children aged 8 and 5). We had been looking forward to this holiday for a long time and the children were very exited. This visit did not dissappoint - the staff are still as courteous and very helpful. The reception desk staff are very efficient and extremely helpful. The entertainment team included my grandson in the majority of the games, he is naturally very competitive and was over the moon to be able to play alongside the adults. We all enjoyed the food, we only used the buffet restaurant as this gave the children the freedom of choosing their favourites, rather than having the set meals in the speciality restaurants. We found the food to be very good and we certainly never went hungry. The children loved the pool, it was never crowded and as the weather was very hot we all appreciated the sunshades supplied in all the area's. The beach is beautiful and the sea was lovely and warm. The room's were large and spotless and very comfortable and we were grateful for the air conditioning which was very efficient. We all used the Jacuzzi, and had some interesting conversation with many nationalities, English was spoken by all, luckily! Our only one complaint, was that there was no solid division between the smoking and non smoking section of the main restaurant. As we are non smokers we asked for a no smoking table for our evening meal. However, at the lunch time sitting we had a restricted no smoking area which meant we were sitting very near the smokers. On a couple of occasions, some very inconsiderate smokers, smoked inbetween each course and smoke drifted over our table. This completely spoilt those meals. We would suggest that Riu implement a no smoking policy in all their restaurants in the future. I am sure that a smoker could go without a cigarette for the length of time it takes to eat a meal. Apart from this, the holiday was wonderful. Lovely weather, lovely food, lovely people.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>