<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="275bedc04854ad7565dea2c054126eb2" url=""><![CDATA[Colonial Charm Be prepared for a treat!!!My girl friend and I stayed three nights at the Fullerton and found it a great place. It was reasonably priced (and we managed to get Buffet Breakfast included) at $260 AUD per night - for weekend nights and $380 per night for weekday nights.We stayed in a courtyard room and it was a good size. Well set up for business travellers (altho' I had dumped the lap top for our short break). The rooms have the tallest beds I have ever seen! Magnificent bathroom, huge shower, separate toilet and double bath.The food was excellent, and just a 5 min walk away are many great eateries, great historic sites (Raffles Landing). Taxi's were in abundance at the front door. And you can get a water taxi for a few dollars just at the back of the hotel.The staff were always smiling and only too willing to help.The hotel facilities are excellent and its worth spending time and exploring the hotel. Some beautiful Chinese antiques can be seen.Oh the pool is excellent, great to destress in.The Fullerton used to be the site of the post office and the upper floors were business offices. $400Million Singapore dollars have been spent on renovations (The outside of the building is 'heritage listed' and cannot be altered - thank goodness) and each room is a different in layout. I cant wait to go back!!!!Hints;The concierge area have visitors maps available and will help with directions.You can get late checkout until 2pm. Normal checkout is 12.Luggage can be left with the concierge in a locked area.The in house laundry facilities are pricy but prompt.If you fly Singapore Airlines keep your boarding card stub and you can get cheap all day bus travel.Be ready to be baffled by the taxi charging system!Be careful when getting a taxi - the mercedes charge limo prices.Go to the Esplanade (a few minutes walk)Oh just go and be pampered!!! Its great!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>