<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="dc7824cff403d96898d20a343440baf9" url=""><![CDATA[First Class all the way My husband and I stayed at the Marriott Marquis for his birthday weekend May 2-4. We were greeted the minute we walked into the hotel and were directed to the correct bank of elevators to get to registration. There were many Marriott employees providing this service which I thought was really nice if you were unfamiliar with the hotel. Check in was a breeze and very friendly. They comped us an upgrade to a stripview room for the birthday celebration. The rooms looked to be very recently renovated and the bedding was beautiful and oh so comfortable. The bathroom area looked completely renovated as well except for the tub and toilet. The only thing missing that I think would have been a nice touch for such classy rooms would have been bathrobes.The elevators can be a long wait at busy times but not a major thing. Location can't be beat. Even though it is in such a busy area, the soundproofing is wonderful. Even the corridors and noise from other rooms was minimal. All in all a wonderful stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4b359a2069da577aa13f6bb268efb970" url=""><![CDATA[Another great Kimpton hotel My husband and I had a gift certificate for a free stay but I think this hotel is well worth paying for. Check in was very friendly and attentive. As stated in previous reviews, the rooms are small but very comfortable. The bathtub is nice and deep, great for soaking. The afternoon wine reception was fun with red and white wine and organic beer. We had some appetizers and drinks at the attached Ponzu restaurant and were very pleased with the quality and the service. For anyone wanting to rent a car for the day the hotel is right around the corner from the car rental agencies on O'Farrell St. For people who like a great breakfast, the hotel is also only a block from Max's at Geary and Mason and the famous Dottie's True Blue Cafe on Jones.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="35d8945e3852e4e0985e4445488ff25b" url=""><![CDATA[Pleasantly Surprised We just visited NO this past weekend and was very satisfied with the Omni Royal Orleans. Unlike past reviews, there were numerous doormen to greet guests, take luggage, direct guests to elevators etc. Check-in was a breeze and we were assigned a King Bedded room with a courtyard view. Our room wasn't overly small and it boasted a massive jetted tub with nice showerhead all in one. I don't know what room type it was but it met all of our needs. All of the staff at the hotel were extremely friendly and, as with all the locals we ran into, were very thankful to have tourism back to NO. I have to admit that the tourist areas of the city including the French Quarter look even better than they did before. I am a travel agent and would not hesitate to send my clients to New Orleans for a leisure or business purposes.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>