<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="3e9fdbcaebdd58727bace1312f31c814" url=""><![CDATA[junior suit We stayed 3 nights here, originally meant to be staying in the superior double but then decided to go for the junior suit as it was only 40 euro extra a night. Lovely hotel, overlooking Dam Square. Shops, cafes and bars located outside hotel. Red light district 5-10 minute walk away. Small amount of noise can be heard from outside whilst in your hotel room but nothing to disturb you at night. Overall a very pleasent hotel in the heart of Amsterdam. I will definetely stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3dd4ddaa73718fd6ecb8ead878c23254" url=""><![CDATA[We will not stay here again We stayed here for 5 nights on floor 21, rooms 17 18 (junior suite). Room 18 has a balcony but if you have young children, I would not recommend letting them outside on the balcony without an adult. There is a CD player in room 18. Room 17 has a bath with a shower. Room 18 has a shower with jets which, is really nice and relaxing to use but unfortunately, the water leaks out all over the bathroom floor and I don't mean drips, I mean a lot of water so you have to shower really quickly and then use 2 or 3 towels to soak up the water. We had a view of the sea from our rooms. The drinks in the fridge in your room are free. Water, coke, lemonade and cheap beer.On Friday night, my husband and I got woken by really loud music and some guy talking really loud on a microphone. This was around midnight. The music did not stop until 6am. The music was coming from one of the buildings across the road. To put it into perspective, my husband never has any trouble sleeping where ever he goes so for him to be kept awake, well you can imagine! I went to reception the next day and asked the lady behind the desk if the music we had heard on the Friday night was a one off or did it happens every weekend. She looked at me blankly and said that it had not happened before and must have been a special occasion. On Saturday night, the music started to build up from 11,30pm and again did not end until 6am but this time fireworks were also let off. My husband and I could not believe it. Wherever you stay in the hotel, you will not be able to avoid the loud music or the guy talking on the microphone. My husband went to complain the next day. The receptionist advised him that the hotel have complained to the Council regarding the noise but have been told that there is nothing they can do, There were a number of people complaining in the hotel regarding the noise experienced. I am not sure if it is a regular occurrence i.e. if it is a nightclub or it happens every few weeks. On the second night, we even wore ear plugs but could still hear it slightly. The loud bangs from the fireworks woke my son up and not even the ear plugs could shield us from that noise.AC hotel and the Hilton hotel are close by. The AC hotel is even closer to where the music was coming from than Princess hotel!The pool on the 23rd floor was from what I saw mostly for sunbathers and adults. The other pool on floor 3 was shallow and more suitable for children. The water in both pools was very cold and we only managed to go swimming once as he water was freezing. In my opinion, not suitable to swim in. The hotel should have the water heated in the pools.We went to take my son into the Jacuzzi as the pool water was too cold. The Jacuzzi was absolutely discussing. It was a slimy dirty yellow colour. If the jets were on, you would probably not see this and get into the Jacuzzi, god knows what germs and bacteria you pick up!The gym is located on the 3rd floor in a room just off the pool, it was small but adequate.We put a do not disturb sign on our door but the maid still went in and did our room when we were out. On 2 separate occasions, she forgot to put duvet covers on our duvets. The beds are quite comfortable and are on wheels. You can put the brakes on the bed to stop them moving, something we did not discover until our third night.There is a tourist bus which takes you all around Barcelona. This costs around 19 Euros for 1 day or 23 Euros for 2 days. You are provided with earphones and can listen in various languages to interesting facts regarding sites around Barcelona. You can get on and off the tourist bus as many times as you want. You are provided with city maps and a discount booklet. Children under 4 go free on the tourist bus. Be sure to ask what time they stop running. I think around 8/9pm.The metro and tram are also very easy to use.The shopping mall is right beside the hotel. There are various stores and a big supermarket. If you take any shopping into the supermarket, be aware that you have to place it in a plastic bag and seal it prior to entering the supermarket. There is a table with the plastic bags and a machine to seal it in the supermarket.There are a number of nice places to eat in the mall.The sea is about a 10/15 minute walk away from the hotel. There are no sun loungers on the beach or umbrellas. You can purchase straw mats (2.50 Euros) and umbrellas (4.99 Euros) from the supermarket in the mall. The beach has soft sand and showers to wash off sand when you are finished.In terms of taking food back to the hotel room, we never had any problems with this, we kept ham, butter, yogurts and beer in the fridge and crisps + water on the side. Personally I will not stay at this Hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>