<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="6d237d9d9710a0bbe8a6f126cff219b5" url=""><![CDATA[Location, Location, Location! We had a prompt e-mail response from the ** Hotel de Gerstekorrel with a fair price quote for our nine day visit to Amsterdam. I had read all the hotel reviews available on the web, and was looking for what would fill our needs....simple, safe, quiet and within walking distance of reasonably priced restaurants with good food, local sights, as well as Central train station for day trips.The Hotel de Gerstekorrel filled the bill! Our spacious room with private bath and tv was mostly quiet as requested (#27). The only time it wasn't quiet was when other guests were noisy arriving or departing which can be true of any **** hotel. The room was simple and clean, with thick white towels after a hot shower in the private bath, The twin beds were almost a human cocoon of cozy, comfort for my husband and me. Upon arrival at the hotel (long before actual check in time), from a 3 hr drive and 9 hr. sleepless flight, our luggage was cheerfuly secured, and when the room was ready we fell into the beds and slept like babies til late afternoon. This nap was not on our agenda but we never regretted it one bit!The entire staff was always friendly, and helpful; they seemed genuinely interested in making our stay memorable.As for the location, Hotel de Gerstekorrel was tops! Hotel de Gerstekorrel is situated within walking distance of the Central Station where we could walk to board and travel to nearby villages as well as an economical, timely assurance of getting back to the airport later for an early morning departure. Within blocks were various restaurants and easy walking to the tram or many of the sights of this lovely city.Note, the hotel stairs are a little steep, but normal for most European buildings where space is at premium. At 63, I had no trouble making it up to our room.The breakfast was not like home ( the only disapointment) but certainly kept us full til our noon meal. The strong coffee and orange juice were most welcome.After many, many years of foreign travel, we recognize a gem!When we return, we will no doubt stay here again, for a simple, safe, convenient, clean and comfortable stay.Thank you again, Lisa, and the whole staff for making our 44th anniversary so memorable!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>