<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="9d5f4def53d769af95b4b416eb70aa38" url=""><![CDATA[Gorgeous room, poor service First, the positive: the two room suite we booked was gorgeous, clean and comfortable. The neighborhood is very quaint and the shops and people, very friendly. I love the way everyone has a dog and the shops put out water for them at nearly every store front. The Chinese food at Country Sky restaurant across the street is absolutely wonderful, I highly recommend the fish, dim sum and hot and sour soup. All Star Donuts has delicious early morning pastries and for late night dining, Mels Drive In, was very clean and tasty. Now, the down side. The desk clerk upon our arrival was very rude. When we arrived at 3:15pm, he very quickly informed us that our suite would not be ready until 4 or 4:15pm. When I pointed out that our printed reservation sheet said 3pm check-in, he insisted that did not apply to the suites (the most expensive rooms in the inn have the latest check in time?). Finally, he decided to pick up the phone and check with housekeeping to see if our room was ready. IT WAS. He never apologized, simply acted as if we had really inconvenienced him handed us our keys and sent us on our way. I can't recall when I have ever been treated so poorly at a hotel, especially when I have reserved the most costly room on the property! The only other contact I had with the desk was when I called to inquire about a morning newspaper. Again, the same man, in a very disinterested tone said, the manager will bring the paper around 7am.... I waited over 30 minutes then finally walked to the newspaper stand and purchased one myself. Don't expect great service at this hotel. In closing, I would like to give the highest praise to the Colors of Christmas performance at the Symphony Hall. If you get the opportunity to see it, you won't be disappointed!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="be712dabc9ee204eb645d0fc0f207906" url=""><![CDATA[Charming, small hotel My husband and I booked this hotel based on it's location and positive reviews. We stayed one night and attended the SF Ballet's Swan Lake. The ballet was beautiful and the hotel was only a short walk away. The staff is friendly but the rooms are extremely small. I would estimate about 200 sq feet. Our room on the 4th floor had a window that looked out to the alley but it was nice that we could open it for fresh air because it was unseasonably warm. The bed was comfortable but unfortunately we did not discover the ear plugs in the drawer of the nightstand until the next morning. We were awoken at 1:30am by an extremely loud garbage truck in the alley emptying the garbage bins and found it difficult to sleep due to the noise for most of the night. The bathroom was so small it was difficult to find space to put out toiletries but the shower did have adequate pressure. The complimentary breakfast in the morning is continental style, with very few choices. It is rather strange that the waiters hand out tip portfolios at breakfast, but since they were nice enough to refill our coffee cups for us we left them a few dollars. The parking package we booked via the internet was $142/night. Although the hotel was adequate, we felt the accommodations were simply too small to be comfortable. Next time we visit SF we will seek a hotel with larger rooms, even if the location is not as convenient. We enjoyed a nice dinner at the Hayes Street Grill but be sure to book advance reservations on performance nights because it gets very crowded. I would recommend any of the grilled fish, the french fries and of course the wondeful creme brulee! As with most restaurants in the area, it is expensive but the service was absolutely wonderful which is made it a lovely meal.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1340547555478a36b6b48a4253017a92" url=""><![CDATA[Holidays at the Parc Stayed at the Parc 55 for two nights, Dec 22-23, and couldn't have been happier with our accommodations. Prior to our arrival, I spoke to Donna (at the front desk) who was very helpful and made arrangements for two adjoining rooms with lovely views of the city. After reading many reviews about small rooms in the city, I found these rooms to be quite spacious with a sitting area where we could enjoy our coffee in the morning while enjoying the view. We found the beds very comfortable, the bathrooms good size, and the water pressure for showers was good. They had a great holiday room rate, $119/night, which was appreciated since parking is expensive $38/night. Everyone at the hotel, from the bellman to the room service waiter, was very courteous and friendly and we would definitely stay there again. We walked to Union Square and did some shopping and took in many San Francisco events. First, be prepared, everything in SF is EXPENSIVE. The first night we attended a concert at Davies Symphony Hall (excellent venue and fantastic musicians). Afterwards, we had dinner at the Italian restaurant across the street from the hotel(Panetti's)and it was very good. I recommend the eggplant parmesan. The second day we attended the 2pm performance of the San Francisco Ballet's Nutcracker at the War Memorial Opera House. This is an experience you don't want to miss. Beautiful scenery and dancing, it was truly breathtaking.I think we should have stopped with those two events, because the last one (Holiday Lights Tour) on the motorized cable car was a bummer. First, the only holiday lights you see are at Union Square (which is where we boarded). It's the standard (canned) tour of the city, nothing more, which we may have enjoyed more during the day, but at night, you miss a lot. Not recommended. After the tour, we couldn't find a place to eat that wasn't packed to the gills with shoppers, and it was 9pm. We finally got a table at Johnny's, where it was cramped and hot and the server had an attitude. Expensive and not very good, I wouldn't recommend Johnny's either. I think we would try and make dinner reservations next time we visit.All in all, we had a wondeful time in San Francisco!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>