<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="09c90cc7c9cea9b2b0d68fb1cf0c4a90" url=""><![CDATA[very dependable business hotel' great for price!!! I've stayed at this hotel off and on for over 3yrs now, when going into SFO for business.Sheratons as a whole are always a mixed bag; it is the one Starwood brand that doesn't really have a good definition. Sometimes they are very fancy and lush, sometimes they are very budget feeling.This is a very nice hotel, that if located in SanFrancisco proper, would cost well over $250/nt.This property is right outside the airport, within walking distance of one of the best restaurants in the area (Kincaid's), as well as short drive to at least 5 or 6 others, ranging from El Torito to Max's Opera Cafe. It is at least 20min from the city itself though.Place is clean, nice rooms, great bar, and you are on the Bay with walking paths everywhere. It's hidden out of the way a bit, but is a great value for the money.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="de610725aa3f4828a1a46b58f45c325b" url=""><![CDATA[if you can afford it, hard to beat Stayed there several times when was a 4Seasons, and once since became a Fairmont.Lovely property, almost a bit overdone (as 4seasons tend to be).Fantastic oyster restaurant on the property - Shuckers.Great location, walking downtown area.Great rooms, great service. Main drawback is that it's also one of the most expensive properties in town, and for the money, might want to look at unique Seattle properties like the EdgeWater.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b01504d1bfb43d105007fe5af3efa92f" url=""><![CDATA[Great little hotel, good price, potentially rough location I stayed here based on the reviews I read on Tripadvisor, plus my knowledge of San Francisco.Everything I read was true, so be aware.For a ridiculously low rate, you will stay in a wonderful little boutique hotel. You can pre-negotiate room costs parking with them; I got free parking in downtown plus a nice room for $105.Parking at most hotels is $35-$40 in and of itself.The hotel is cute, small, nice.The location will make or break it for you.It is 3blocks from UnionSquare, one of the nicest and most visited parts of SanFrancisco.In 2blocks the other direction, it is some of the roughest parts of Market.So, go one way, you're in super tourist white light land, the other, and it people smoking dope and sleeping in the street.If you're used to living in a big city, won't bother you. If you're not, it will freak you out.For the money, I don't think there's a better hotel in SanFrancisco.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>