<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="fea65c4dd98c011a3fc8d66fa4a538ee" url=""><![CDATA[Great end to our holiday at the JW Marriott SF View from the room on the 18th floor (2)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f586e115d5dacd783565127afa4bfc01" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel - just so big! Note that I'm a Marriott Platinum member (I stay 100+ nights/year in Marriotts so my experience might not be typical)Stayed here for the start of a 3 day holiday around California. First impressions were very good, a busy lobby (busy any time of day as I later noticed) - swift check-in (even though we arrived a few hours before the standard check-in time due to our flight arrival time. Had a room on about the 18th (Conceirge) floor, had a nice view down onto the convention centre below where they were putting up tents for Oracle World (A convention) in a small park. The room was small but cosy, lovely Marriott bed (as always) and a reasonable size bathroom. The TV was a nice high definition one which you could enjoy from your bed easily and also swivelled. Other than that nothing special - would be ideal for business but probably not a luxary stay. The concerige lounge was nice enough, though surprisingly busy, had a nice view of the same park and a nice breakfast.We also tried to go to 'The view', the bar on the top floor of the hotel, but it was too busy (We had chosen about 8pm on Saturday) - but it looked nice and quite dramatic, would have been nice to have an informal drink here before dinner I'd have thought. Finally, we also used the pool - it wasn't busy at all (we were the only ones there), although it wasn't that warm. Strangely all the people on the 4th-6th floors can look into the pool area. More to mind, if this hotel has 1,500 rooms then the pool can only accomodate about 15 people easily, so, it could get crowded. Sadly the jacuzi wasn't working on our trip - but the same concept applies in that it is small for so many people.On our last day we picked up a car from Hertz in the lobby - easy and simple though we were surprised that there was a compulsory $10 fee for the valet to pick it up (normally this is why you pay extra for Hertz for a hotel pickup?), but, leaving was then easily acomplished straight onto the street - though the valet parking is hidden away inside the hotel so you can load/unload rather than being on the street as with other hotels in the area.I also stayed at the JW Marriott during the same trip, as it is smaller I would prefer that for any future stay - though if going to the Moscone convention centre, as this Marriott is right next door to it, that would be an ideal place to stay, or for business, rather than a special holiday.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="43d618fe89089d51d88bb10e05f69257" url=""><![CDATA[Stayed here on recommendation and wasn't disappointed My wife and I stayed here for a single night as we wanted to get out of LA easily the next day down Highway 1 - I'm a Marriott platinum member so tend to get better treatment than the average guest so bear this in mind with my review. I was staying on points and had read about this hotel on tripadvisor/other sites as being one of the best in LA - hence deciding to stay here for the night in question - we we're disappointed.Arrived and found the hotel easily, put our car into the parking garage (cost about $23/night with check in/out privileges). Check-in was a breeze, pleasant receptionist thanking me for choosing their hotel etc, made me feel very at home and happy. Lobby also looked nice.Our room was on the club floor (11), and had a nice view of the airport (as requested prior to check-in so that was noted and acted upon). The room had a nice flat screen high def TV and the usual great Marriott bed. Felt at home and enjoyed the nice bathroom too -although huge disappointment that later in the evening there was no hot water, so no bath, we didn't report the problem though as we didn't want to watch someone fixing it late in the evening. It was working by the next day.We had arrived a little late (~8pm) and after freshening up went to the club lounge to try 'deserts', which were very tasty (and free). The prices in the club lounge aren't cheap I admit, but, the offer of cocktails for about $9 isn't too bad for this class of hotel imho, whilst you can enjoy watching the planes land.For food there wasn't anything nearby apart from a Burger King across the road, as such we asked in the club lounge for a recommendation for a nice Italian. They gave us a name of one a short drive away - it was tasty, and it was also Zagat rated we noticed, so definitely a positive recommendation from the staff.Next morning we checked out and left, but, had a good time overall and if I was near LAX in the future I'd try and stay here.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>