<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="bd20c8dd195894047d20f3f18e59d8c2" url=""><![CDATA[Utterly wonderful I read a review on here to ask in advance for a room facing the canal and to be above level 2. Well we asked and we received ! We were in room number 316 and the view was wonderful as well as the lovely smell of Chinese food from our neighbours !The bed was a double and very large indeed. Yes the room was small but you have to remember at the end of the day u are on a ship ! The shower was very poweful and in some cases too poweful. We had to stop showering now and again for the water to drain. When sat on the toilet u are touching the sink as well, but who cares ? not us !On arrival the man at reception was not over friendly and we had to pay for the three nights in advance. Once in my bedroom I noticed only two pillows on the bed and went back down to reception to ask for some more. We went out for the evening and I was a little upset as they hadn't arrived and then there was a knock at the door and two more pillows !In the stair well they have vending machines for soda, beer, crisps and snacks, but the bar on the ship stays open until 12.45am and also has a snooker table, pin ball machine, cd juke box and arcade games. The barmaid did inform us that we should tip her as well when she told us the price, which I thought was a little rude.The breakfast is not worth getting up for early if u have had a late night. Breads, cheese, funny bacon and weird tasting small saugages, with hard boiled eggs and a toaster to 'do-it-youself'. For drinks it was orange guice/apple juice/coffee. Don't even think about a good old cup of tea !The t.v. is good and they have 24-7 great porn on it, as well as all the dutch stations.No air con in the room, so good idea to keep your window open when u go out in the evening. Its so safe as remember u are on a ship !The view is wonderful and u can see all over Amsterdam from your window.I slept the three nights with ear plugs in and apparently my partner said he was only woken up once by late night party people.You need to take shampoo, soap and take your own towl, as theres are kinda thin. Also the loo paper is thin, so might be handy to take some tissues as well. At the end of the stay I did ask if the hotel could look after our bags as we had an afternoon flight back to the UK and we had to leave our rooms by 11am. We they took us to a very small room that was so full of bags on top of bags that it didn't look safe at all so we carried them around the town with us.This is the second time to Amsterdam and I will 110% want to go back to the botel and to be honest it made our holiday going there. How many times do u get to sleep on a ship ? Go give it a try and enjoy Amsterdam.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>