<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="2ac2f1d670c63b0285e6f36f938b17fe" url=""><![CDATA[You will love it, We did I know this is a little late, we stayed from 4/17 to 4/24 and all I can say is this is the best place we have been to in the Caribbean, we have stayed at Grand Lido Negril, Breezes Runaway bay, Hedo II, and Grand Sport Villa Ocho Rios. Over the past few years we thought that Jamaica experience was not what it was, so we gave Punta Cana a tryAnd we are glad we did. When we got to Sunscape we were greeted with cookies and rum punch, we arrived before noon and our room was not ready, no big deal, I bought a cigar and hit the pool bar and we were greeted like we had been there for weeks,After about 2 hours one of the desk staff was walking by us and ask if there was anything she could do, I lightheartedly said we could use a room, She stopped what she was doing and walked up to the front desk with in seconds we had our room, and the wait was worth it, form our balcony we could see the beach and the pool bar. I cannot say enough good things about the staff. My girlfriend and I have never had service like this in our life. Every worker we ran into would say hello and the bartenders would stop us to ask us how we were doing, even when they were off duty. I tipped a buck when it was my turn to get the drinks not because I'm tipper, because they deserved it, at times we would just be sitting around without a drink and Nicolas (Rum and cookie greeter) would stop what he was doing and go get us drinks.The me just say I have spent a lot of money for less quality, we did not have one bad meal, and the beach dinner was A1 food in a A1 setting, I over heard people complaining that the night of the beach dinner they closed the other restaurants and they had to eat on the why did you come to the Caribbean if you did not want to enjoy a vary nice dinner on the beach. The burgers on the beach were not a Wendy's but they were not a White castle, it way worked for me after 4 hours in the Vary hot sun, drinking beers.The rooms were ok nothing to brag about, bed was hard (beers will take care of that problem) and speaking of beers if you put a few bucks under the empty beer bottles every day, the maid will load up your frig with beers for you, I never opened the frig with out seeing at least 5 beers in it.Also one day I left my safe key in the lock, the maid found it when she was cleaning the room and took it to security,I called down to the desk and they had the head of security come to our room with it, he had me make sure all our stuff was there and gave it back to me. Nothing was stolen and I had a few hundred bucks in the safe. If you like Lobster you must go to the Green Parrot (located on the beach) you will have to pay for it but you cannot beat a grill cooked lobster on the beach to end the day. I have only a few minor negative things that bugged me. The first, kids at the swim up bar, I do not like waiting forThe bar tender to get me a drink because someone's brat is playing motorboat while the bartender is making a drink for them, The kids should have there own pool away from the swim up bar.Second is the slime ball rude lazy bums that feel the need to get up at 5:00am to go down to the pool or the beach put out towels on chairs and go back to bed or to breakfast, every day we had a hard time finding chairs, there were no people in sight, but all the chairs were taken, we ran into a person that put towels on chairs down at the beach at the pool then went on a 4 hour off resort The third is the adult pool does not have a swim up bar, is void of music and is stuck on the backside of the resort where you get no wind and no view of the beach.And the last is, if you have a room near the Tex Mex it does get noisy in the early AM. The staff uses carts to move the food to the restaurant and you will hear every crack in the pavement it then again if we got up early this would not be a problem.Bottom line you will get your bang for the buck and have fun doing it.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>