<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="7abd1de3396f6166a51232cffef33914" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel, great location The Sheraton Boston wasn't in itself anything incredibly special, although it was comfortable. The rooms are smaller, but you can tell by the area that it's probably no different than other hotels around it. The ottoman in my room had a questionable stain on it; other than that, the room was very clean. At $20 for the duration of the stay, the gym was a bit expensive given the quality of equipment. I didn't use the pool, though, which probably adds a lot of value to the cost. I went to the bar for dinner, which is right off the lobby. The service was good, the food tasty. A big bonus is the mall that's attached to the hotel. It had everything from fast food to Armani and high-end stores like it. It gave me something to do at night. There's also a few great bars within walking distance to the hotel. The location really can't be beat. The only complaint I have about my stay regarded room service. The room next to me got room service one morning, and left the tray outside...it took the hotel almost 2 full days to pick it up! It wasn't anything smelly, so it wasn't a big deal, but it showed a lack of attention. Overall a nice stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="37a0c91f856073339cd0bca42c87152e" url=""><![CDATA[Great view, great location! We were in room 4236, had a nice view of downtown. We could see a little bit of the lake, not too much though. Still, the views of the mountains and city were unbeatable. The location was great, right near everything. The walk to Pike's Place Market was short, and there were so many restaurants nearby. We also saw a movie theatre just a stone's throw away, but who wants to go to a movie theatre on vacation? The room was smaller, but well appointed. The bath was standard hotel bath, with nice countertops though. The room itself was very clean. the linens were crisp, not wrinkled at all. The best part about this hotel was the concierge service. It's got to be tough to deal with newcomers all day, every day, but Judy and Ted (I think that was his name) both did an excellent job. They were courteous, friendly, and very willing to help. Overall, an amazing stay to make it an amazing trip!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>