<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="8">
		<document id="41f2f7c98aac0ade4c87c690e82d88b0" url=""><![CDATA[Grand Dame of Paris This review will reflect the service offered when staying in the Presidential Suite ...and of course as with any hotel if you stay in the biggest suites, they really look after you. Booked for extended family of 8. Presidential Suite is enormous although 1 half (bedroom lounge) dont really 'match' the other half (bedroom lounge/dining). The styles are quite different. In general the hotel is quite mumsy (flowery, old fashioned). The bathrooms though are def. not up to the standard - nice, clean but old and not 5 star certainly not for a presidential suite. Bathrooms were the same in a deluxe junior suite deluxe room. Bit strange? Service was good although the hotel knew our arrival time we still arrived to a dark suite, no lights on, no flowers etc. Also work is on going at the hotel as they expand into a neighbouring building. This at times affects ones stay including dirty corridors workmen cabling in the passages etc. Breakfast is superb! Absolutely perfect. Room service too is very good. The pool is a delight at the end of a long shopping day. Location too is very good.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3da267dd8329c7f33874828c7d748d3e" url=""><![CDATA[Good, not great This is a grand old hotel. The rooms are large, bathrooms are modern but the communal area's are dated and staid. The staff uniforms are dated. The whole places lacks something ...those little touches that take an hotel from 4 stars to 5. Simply not chicc or polished. We (7 family members) stayed for 6 nights in a large suite with 2 additional rooms interleading rooms with views over the Arno. Found hotel to be just outside of where its all happening ...only a 5 minute walk away.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6f7b1ab5932adbd328b01c6570961128" url=""><![CDATA[Much nicer now its been renovated Hong Kong is not my kind of place. You either love it or hate it. I hate it. I have only visted twice in 6 years and on both occasions I stayed at this hotel. The first visit was nothing to write home about but after the recent renovation, the rooms are very chic, almost sexy. I still find it annoying that they put guests in a smokers room without asking. And equally annoying that they give you a room with no view when in fact they have several with views. Are they trying NOT to impress you? After asking for a non-smoking room one preferably with a view, I was given one. So what were they thinking at reception? Very silly. Breakast also starts very late - too late for business travellers. Dinner was very pleasant in the Chinese restaurant on the top floor... even with a step into the restaurant that has most patrons tripping on it. The staff make you aware of it, in which case why not light it accordingly and save your patrons from embarrassment. The bar, also on the top floor, has superb views. Not sure this is the best place to stay in Hong Kong, as I have not stayed anywhere else but having said that it is without question a luxury hotel with 5 star service and few but silly faults.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9eaf6d9bc0619f96bdc36943ed4b7f52" url=""><![CDATA[Great views over The Common. Four Seasons = Top quality. You know what you are getting whehn you book at one of these hotels. Upgraded to a suite which was massive; service was top notch instantaneous (!) and wonderful views over Boston Common. Highly recommended! Note though that you are a few minutes drive to the financial district.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="724e2b4dac6aea45a8729977a235979d" url=""><![CDATA[Returning guest ...because it cant get better in NYC! Once again, top notch! Well worth the money (and its a lot!). Ensure you get a room as high up as possible - stunning views at dawn when with European jetlag you lie awake staring out across the trees! Only draw back is hotel lacks a fine dining 'option' and as such no glam breakfast room either. But space is limited in NYC and this hotel, as far as luxury location go, is top!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="805082257a371db6cdeb1045a0805686" url=""><![CDATA[Best for Singapore City Centre Worldwide traveller, critical of top hotels and their service. I have stayed in this hotel, both on my own, with my wife and with my extended family of 8, ages from 7-80, for several years now! To date, in 2007 alone I have spent around 30 nights here. One is spoilt in Asia when it comes to service however as a return guest one feels the service offered and the friendliness is real. This hotel has great staff, a clear reflection of good management and it wins top spot in Singapore year on year. Rooms are large - request Quay side rooms - views are more interesting. Great choice of restaurants although both the Chinese (one of Sing. best) and the Italian are freezing! Afternoon tea is superb with live music. This hotel has a lot of WOW factor, great location for CBD/Raffles Place and grandeur. Raffles Hotel may be unique but its no longer what it is. You wont be disappointed at Fullerton eventhough they are lacking in small little details (no turndown choc's).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="46f8cb3a54955301c3ada355df2a402a" url=""><![CDATA[6 stars, no less! One is spoilt when in Singapore for great hotels and indeed there are another half dozen 5star+ hotels coming soon. The St Regis is the first of the 'new breed' and it has left even my old favourite, The Fullerton in its shadow. All rest of the 5 stars are dated ..doesnt matter if its Ritz-Carlton, Fullerton , the gawdy Sangri-La or the very 'institutional' Sentosa....they have all been left behind by the arrival of St Regis. The staff and as such the service is what really sets this hotel apart from the competition. True first class service: no issue, no problem, no matter, tiny details! The rooms and suites are absolutely the best in Singapore - style, class comfort! The bathrooms are luxurious - loads of stunning rather unusual marble and heated mirrors (so they dont mist up!). The Spa too is superb although management of the Spa is the truly only weak link at the hotel. The Spa staff offer the best hotel treatments in Singapore and they have no competition! None! The Chinese Restaurant must be one of Singapores best. The Italian is boring and feels like a bit of an after thought while the main dining room works well for breakfast and lunch but dinner is a bit 'Las Vegas' with coloured fountains that are simply too active and busy for a relaxing fine dining experience. Management of the hotel is top notch. The Concierge Team headed up by Ian Tan cannot be faulted - perfect every time! The decoration of the hotel in general is very good although there are a few over the top 'artistic touches' which hopefully in time will be toned down. I am happiest when in Singapore ....and happiest when in Singapore to be at The St Regis. Well done - you certainly have my business!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4ef0ee54ed40cc8e402d9d001f41413e" url=""><![CDATA[Nice views but off centre The hotel offers the usual Mandarin Oriental high standards found throughout this chain but in addition it offers wonderful views across Central Park (albeit they are not uninterupted!). Didnt manage to make breakfast. Rooms service was good although clearing trays from the room took hours. What was uncomfortable about the hotel is the distance from 5th Avenue. Yes you are closer to the theatres and you have shopping dining options downstairs (the hotel is on the higher levels of a Columbus Circle building) but its a stroll to 5th a stroll back with shopping bags. The Ritz and Plaza beat it for location though. The bar is though a great place to meet enjoy the views. What is also unusual is that the hotel 'starts' with its lobby on the 35th floor.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>