<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="04770ae1ec1b4cf6a65de3348fa8c20a" url=""><![CDATA[Recommended I stayed for 4 nights with my girlfriend as part of a road trip around california, and it was great.Clean, friendly, safe and enjoyable.As mentioned in previous reviews, this place has a fantastic location, just off Hollywood Boulevard and all the tourist stuff, you know the deal. There is also a convenience store selling basics liquor just across the street.The staff were some of the most helpful we came across in over 2 weeks. They helped with directions, maps, advice...... you name it. And they did it with a smile too.The pool wasn't as heated as expected, but the cold water certainly helped freshen me up in the morning anyway!Free internet access, free underground parking for about 25 cars (one of the main bonuses for us).The Suite was a good size, and the kitchen and dining table a nice bonus.Only slight problem was a bit of noise in the mornings coming from the Renaissance Hotel...... trucks reversing, skips being emptied etc, though I think this was due to some specific construction work being done at the time, and not a permanent problem.I would definitely recommend this hotel to anyone, and would stay there again myself.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="018e16f673efa159053a45c41589abfb" url=""><![CDATA[Does the job I agree with the previous reviews on this place. . . . its nothing special, but hey its about $70 a night!To me, it was a place to stay for opne night that was clean and the location right at the entrance to chinatown is great. Slap bang in the middle of the action, and only a couple of blocks from Union Square. You also get pastries, muffins coffee in the breakfast room which is included in the price.My Girlfriend wasn't too happy with it but she's a clean freak with high standards! Some of the people working on the front desk weren't too helpful ether, but we were only there for a night so it wasn't really an issue.All in all, great location, good value for money. .. . but for me its only a place I would stay for one or two nights for a bed and a shower.Sure if you don't mind where you stay you could stay for longer if you on on a real budget, it would suffice.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>