<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="7">
		<document id="f874ea6387fcc88f1552eb547170c401" url=""><![CDATA[1980s Luxury in an Unbeatable Location My review title suggests my one medium-sized complaint about the otherwise-excellent FS Sydney: the dated overall feeling and decor. I stayed there from 1 through 5 May 2006, having booked a buy three nights and get the fourth free package for a junior opera-view suite. I arrived at the FS around 9 a.m., after an overnight flight from Bangkok. My first pleasant surprise came when the check-in clerk upgraded my room to a full harbour-view suite on the 30th floor. Having only slept a few hours on the flight, I appreciated the prospect of the upgraded suite and harbour view before taking a late-morning catch-up nap. I wasn't dissappointed: the view out of three windows, including a double-pane corner one, was spectacular, encompassing the Harbour Bridge, Rocks neigborhood, Circular Quay, and of course, the Opera House. It was a brilliantly sunny day, and the whole harbour and surrounding areas appeared to sparkle. I reluctantly drew the curtains and slept soundly for 5 hours on a supremely comfortable king bed.Upon waking, I took a closer look at my suite, which was fairly large (52 sq. m.), nicely furnished, and comfortable. No problems, other than the sense that I was in an immaculately preserved 25-year-old hotel room: the furniture and decor, while very clean and fairly luxurious, were nonetheless plain and more suited to rooms I've had in Hyatt and Sheraton hotels. The mostly mahogany wood furniture and trim were in good shape but showed some scuffing and other signs of wear and tear in some places. The TV, while adequate, was large and rather old, with not many channels. The bathroom, however, was fabulous: huge; beautiful white, beige, and cream marble; double sinks; large separate shower stall; and ample L'Occitaine bath products. I took very long and leisurly showers every morning and evening, and the water pressure was prodigious, right up there with a full-throttle jet-ski. The only problem I had with the FS's service came on that first day, when I had to ask three times for the room to be made up. Granted, I did sleep in very late, but housekeeping is 24 hours, and it wasn't until I went to the front desk and complained in person -- after having called housekeeping twice -- that the room got made up. After that first time, though, the make-up and turn-down service were faultless, with generous restocking of bath amenities. I also took in more of the hotel's public-area decor that first day, noting more mahogany (everywhere, really, from the wall on each guest floor to the multistory pillars in the lovely lobby) and lots of 80s brass (some, again, rather worn and dull). Again, this is a subjective aesthetic quibble; I'm sure many guests would find the FS's decor to be very fine indeed. It's just less than what I've experienced in other FS hotels, such as those in Hong Kong (one of the best hotels in that city and probably the world) and Bangkok (also a former Regent but very different from and -- to my eye -- lovelier than the FS Sydney).I didn't avail myself of my suite's so-so minibar, but I did use the so-so coffee service, which was also an 80s (if not 70s) throwback: electric kettle with packets of instant coffee and cheap nondairy creamer. When lesser hotels provide french presses and the like, a hotel of the FS's calibre should do better. But instant coffee it was, and it got me out the door, through the lobby, and across the street to the handy Starbucks, which had better coffee than any hotel option. I breakfasted (well, brunched) there every day, as breakfast wasn't included in my package rate and would've been expensive (as with any five-star room-service meal). Other travellers have mentioned the FS's so-so swimming pool. It was small and outdoors, but also heated and very clean -- and little-used by other guests during my stay. I usually had it to myself at the end of the day. It's an old-fashioned painted concrete basin; a smart granite infinity pool is what it should become. The spa was also small and nothing to write home about, but it was clad with attractive dark-green slate or granite and well stocked with fluffy towels, cold facecloths, and other amenities. The sauna and steamroom, however, were both very plain and small. The spa and pool need a complete makeover, and I hope that when it's time for that, FS turns to its Hong Kong hotel for inspiration.The staff on both the front and concierge desks were excellent, always available, resourceful, and helpful. The concierge staff, while young, were very knowledgeable and always gave good dining and sightseeing recommendations.The FS's location is unbeatable: across the street from the Circular Quay and ferries going everywhere one wants or needs to go. The Opera House is a 10-minute stroll to the far side of the Quay, and the Harbour Bridge is just a few minutes' walk more in the opposite direction. (If you're in at least average health/shape, do this one thing while you're in Sydney: take the Bridge Climb; it's absolutely exhilarating and gives you the best views of what must be the prettiest city harbour in the world.)In sum, I quite enjoyed my stay at the FS Sydney and would consider another stay there, even though it does mean going back to the 80s in some ways. The suite was great and the panoramic harbour views stunning. It's an expensive hotel (what FS isn't?), but one does get one's money's worth, especially if you book a good package. I did visit the nearby Shangri-La Hotel, and it is even nicer, in some ways. But it's up a hill, a bit farther away from the Quay, and the more modern, light tones of the guestrooms may not be to everyone's liking. It's probably worth checking out reviews and rates of both hotels before booking if you're looking for the best high-end hotel in the best location for sightseeing.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e1e8e22b32641f62b64987b0d539b58c" url=""><![CDATA[Fine Stay I chose the Intercontinental for a last-minute 2-day trip to Singapore in early November, and I'm very glad I did. I've stayed in some of Singapore's top hotels, including Raffles, Ritz-Carlton, and Mandarin Oriental; and I was a bit concerned that the Intercon would suffer in comparison. Happily, it did not.The only minor sour note occured when I was checking in and I asked the clerk about the 4 p.m. late checkout (subject to availability) mentioned as part of the weekend rate I'd booked. The clerk said there was nothing in the system about this, and a second staffer, who'd come to take me up to my room, reiterated the availability line (of which I was already aware) and said she'd let me know later. I politely but firmly asked her to check and let me know before heading up to my room, as my return flight was not until after midnight on my checkout day. She quickly confirmed the late checkout availability, and all went very well from that point on.Hotel: The Intercon is a 13-year-old midrise located in Bugis very near Raffles and a short walk or taxi ride to most of the city's attractions and interesting neighborhoods. All the public areas are attractive and spotless, and the hotel's decor is very smart if rather generic. The Intercon eschews the grandeur of the Ritz-Carlton and Oriental and is more reminiscent of the simple luxury of the Four Seasons.Room: I had a standard (Deluxe) room on the 6th floor, and while I thought that that might be a bit lacking, I was again pleasantly surprised. While not huge, at about 35 sq. meters, my room was just right: very comfortable, spotless, and more understated luxury -- in short, the Intercontinental mien at its best. The large bathroom was done in marble, with a big, separate tub and walk-in shower. The room had a large, triple bay window; and the view of the surrouding buildings in Bugis was quite nice. The bed was very comfortable, as one expects in Intercons. The hotel had even provided a small bowl of complimentary fruit and a bottle of Evian. The only drawback to the room was the internet service: wired (no wifi, at least from the hotel) broadband with adequate speed but an annoying feature: having to reopen the startup pay-as-you-go page with each new session, even after paying for a 24-hour block of time. Nor was this cheap: SGD 30 (about US$ 21) for the 24 hours. But the Intercon's not alone in charging high ratees for internet access. I'm hopeful that five-star chains will follow the Peninsula's lead in providing complimentary internet service in all rooms. But this was a minor quibble, and overall, I was very satisfied with my basic Intercon room. My rate of SGD 220 included breakfast and the aforementioned late checkout, and it was actually cheaper than the cheapest room-only rate at the time I booked.Staff and service: With the small exception of my initial checkin query, all of the Intercon's staff were very pleasant, friendly, and helpful. The concierge recommended an excellent seafood-speciality Chinese restaurant (Jumbo) on the waterfront for chili crab; out of this world, and I highly recommend it. The staff at Olive Tree, where I took breakfast, were equally helpful; and the food there was excellent, with a wide choice of fresh western and Asian dishes.Bottom line: I'd recommend the Intercon to anyone visiting Singapore. It's a true five-star (maybe even plus) hotel that, at least at promotional or weekend rates, is a real value compared to more famous Singapore properties that may or may not warrant their higher prices. The Intercon feels smaller than it is (I think it has close to 500 rooms), and the staff make guests feel welcome and special. Well done, Intercontinental Singapore.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="27df0021cb5b098c67a04c76535b8ca0" url=""><![CDATA[Stay Here If You Can I lived in Japan for 4 years and was able to stay in some of the country's -- and region's -- better hotels. When I recently returned for a visit to Tokyo over Thanksgiving Weekend '08, I'd found a very good limited-time offer rate for the Grand Hyatt, which made the hotel all the more appealing. As others have noted, the GH is an oustanding hotel, which is saying a lot in a city with some of the world's finest. Located next to the hyperbusy and flashy Roppongi Hills shopping, dining, and office complex, the GH is an oasis of sophistication, luxury, and restrained Japanese pampering. From the soaring minimalism of the lobby to the hushed elevators -- the end two of which are glass-enclosed with views over the city and Tokyo Tower -- to the stunning rooms, the GH is a destination in and of itself. My basic (Grand Deluxe) room was large and luxurious, with contrasting woods, bedside remote controls for the window sheers and blackout panels, a huge natural-stone bath and separate rain-shower stall, and super-comfortable king bed. I was on the 20th floor, and while part of the view from the huge window was of the adjacent Mori Tower office building, I also had a fine view of Tokyo Tower and nearby skyline. The room couldn't have been quieter or more comfortable. The hotel's fast and faultless internet service, both wired and wifi, was included in the basic room rate.As a Gold Passport member, I had free access (otherwise around $20) to the GH's beautiful, hushed spa facilities, which include a red-granite swimming pool with a contrasting translucent white round whirlpool.Other reviewers have mentioned the GH's very expensive restaurants, but the prices are in line with similarly high-end restaurants in Tokyo. I only visited the French Kitchen, where two glasses of champagne and escargots (delicious) set me back around $50.Japanese service is second to none in the world, and the GH staff met every request and need quickly and graciously. I changed my return-flight reservations twice; the staff took care of both complicated requests within a few minutes each time. When the concierge made a dinner reservation for me at a nearby French restaurant I'd read about and wanted to try (La Lune; excellent), they also sent a note up to my room with a detailed map showing the exact location of the restaurant in relation to the GH. While the GH is perhaps resistable at normal rates (I was quoted a rate of over $400/night for my room if I were to stay an extra night, about $200 more than I was paying), it's a beautiful hotel with unbeatable rooms, service, and ambiance. Treat yourself when in Tokyo.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3040c4fe7dc8ff79f16de1863b309b1b" url=""><![CDATA[MO S'pore: Beautiful Hotel with Bad Feng Shui? I stayed at the newly (and majorly) renovated Oriental in Singapore three times in 2005. The first time, in February, was very shortly after the Aesthetically, the redo is a huge success. While the hotel retains its rather nondescript exterior shape and square windows in a big white block of a building, the interior of the Oriental is now arguably the most striking of all hotels in Singapore. While most hotels built around an atrium recall the 80s even more pointedly than, say, Duran Duran cassette tapes and hair bands, the atrium is now dazzling, with mica-flecked black marble, pin-lighted water feature, and gorgeous dark woods everywhere. The staff are immaculate, the ladies in particular: their uniforms are very Singapore Airlines-meets-Asian Bond girls. As one often does in Singapore, I arrived very late in the evening and was tired. The sleek new interior and flawless staff immediately soothed. The front-desk clerk talked me into an S$90/night upgrade to a Club room, which turned out to be the same as a regular room but on a higher floor than my original room. Staff scurried in to replace stock MO amenities with Hermes, and someone else brought hot tea and a scented face towel. Aah. (Actually, the last two services come with all MO rooms.) The room, while smallish (34 m2), was beautiful: more dark woods and black marble, and an up-to-the minute bathroom with separate, walk-in rain shower; and glass wall with wooden blinds separating bed from bath rooms. My room had a dead-on view of harbor and attractive CBD skyline. Room service food was delicious and not overly expensive. Problems began the next morning (Saturday), when hammering and other construction noises began fairly early (shortly before 9 a.m.). I called the front desk to ask what was going on and was told that renovation work was still occurring on the uppermost floors would become the real Club rooms outside. I headed to the Club Lounge for breakfast, hoping that I might be able to sleep a bit more afterward. The lounge is brand new and spectacular: two-storey windows overlooking the city from the 21st floor, and rich yet muted Asian-modern The breakfast buffet was fresh, luxurious, and plentiful, including fairly good champagne (Piper-Heidsieck). Sated, I returned to my room and was able to sleep some more, as the construction crews had mercifully scaled down the pace and decibel level of their work Later in the day, I stopped by the front desk to discuss my concerns about the noises and what I thought had been a bit of a hard sell for a Club room that was only partly so. As is usually the case with MO staff experienced in Asia, the duty manager was thoughtful and responsive. He took the supplemental club charge off of my room rate (for 2 nights), apologized for the noise, and assured me that I could move to another room if the work for a shorter period on Sunday. I went for a swim, and some laps the new pool put my cares behind me. The temperature-controlled infinity pool overlooks the city skyline, and the spa facilities and wet area are every bit as lovely as the rest of the hotel. When I returned to my room from my swim, I found a bottle of Shiraz and a very nice note from the duty manager, again apologizing for earlier problems.Sunday was just fine, with no construction noise and a good sleep. Upon returning home, I had a very nice e-mail from Ms Cindy Kong, the guest-relations manager. She again apologized for the problems encountered and asked me to contact her directly concerning future stays to ensure proper care.I did contact Ms Kong again, as I was planning another visit to Singapore at the end of April and first week of May, bookends to a week in Bali. She assured me that construction work would be finished and that I would have an excellent, quiet room. That proved to be the case; this time I stayed in a Club room on the Club floor, and everything was great. I was looking forward to my return a week later. Ms Kong e-mailed me while I was in Bali to let me know that a new construction project (this time, a municipal endeavor at adjacent Marine Square) would be taking place during my anticipated stay, and she offered not only to help with a booking at another hotel but also to have me picked up upon arrival at Changi Airport and taken in an MO car to the alternate hotel. Again, outstanding customer service impressed.My third stay with the Oriental was in September, and this time the hotel offered me an ocean-view room at a very good rate. Unfortunately, I timed my stay to coincide exactly with a weekend of daylong F1 speedboat races the water, well within earshot of the hotel. I contacted the Front Desk, and staff offered to give me free use of a City Room, away from the water-facing sides of the hotel, for sleeping during the day. (I note here that the standard City rooms, while pleasant and comfortable, have noticeably blander and furnishings than the Ocean and Harbor View rooms. Staff advised that City rooms are usually assigned to package-tour customers. In any event, my City day room was a blessed respite from the constant whining of racing speedboats.) I joked with the duty manager that perhaps I have bad feng shui at the Oriental, given my star-crossed stays to date. Unfortunately, the joke or bad FS continued a bit further: later on, while I was relaxing after the boat races in my Ocean room, a harsh chemical smell seeped into the room. I opened the door and the reek of kerosene in the hallway or similar brought tears to my eyes. I flagged down a maid, who reported that a maintenance worker had spilled paint in the storage room at the end of the hall and had dumped a large quantity of turpentine on the paint still to try to clean up. A few other guests had also been flushed out of their rooms, seeking the source of the fumes. I informed the front desk of the problem and then went for a long swim. When I returned to my floor, the paint-thinner odor had subsided a bit but was still fairly harsh. I had a message on my room voicemail from guest relations. When I called back, the duty manager apologized again and asked me whether the hotel could move me and my things to a City View suite. I readily agreed. The suite was wonderful huge (about 70 m2). Rather than replicating the drabness of the regular City rooms, the suite was very sleekly furnished and decorated, with a separate bedroom, two bathrooms, and expansive city views. Well done, Oriental! Oh, I had breakfast (included in my room rate) in the just-opened Melt restaurant, which has several huge food stations featuring dishes -- all fresh and very delicious -- from all over the world. The Indian station was my favorite for savories, and the Western breakfast-y baked goods were to die for.Although not yet stayed again at the Oriental stayed at Raffles on my most recent trip to Singapore probably would stay there again. It really is a beautiful hotel, and the staff are perhaps the best encountered (with the possible exception of those of Peninsula Hotels). I still attribute the problems I had at the Oriental to bad luck, or possibly bad feng shui, which perhaps one take lightly in a predominantly Chinese culture. Nonetheless, the Oriental richly deserves the very positive rankings and reviews received since its very successful makeover. If one can get a good corporate or promotional rate (my cheapest stay was S$188/night), the Oriental may be the best hotel stay in Singapore.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a26f9a6871fd98a5a4b17957665e746c" url=""><![CDATA[Peninsula: Reason in and of Itself to Visit Hong Kong I live in Japan and travel fairly frequently in east Asia. Of all the wonderful hotels at which I've stayed in the region, the Peninsula in Hong Kong (PHK) is my overall favorite. I stayed there most recently on either side of Thangsgiving (22 and 26 Nov. 2005) and had my best PHK experience yet. Upon arriving the evening of the 26th evening from Singapore, I checked in, and the front-desk staffer said the words all travel buffs love to hear: We have a very nice upgrade for you. I'd already asked for a deluxe room in the original PHK building, which dates from 1928 and is just fabulous in every respect. But the upgrade to the Peony Suite -- wow. The suite was huge and immaculate, with high ceilings and huge windows giving a full view of the Hong Kong Central skyline across the harbour. Now, mind you, a regular PHK room is already a special place: minimum 40 sqm, marble bath with TV above the soaking tub, separate glass-walled shower, plasma TV in the bedroom, etc. The suite, however, more than doubled the regular room's size and pleasure. It was beautifully decorated with Chinese antiques and art, and there was a full yet tasteful chandelier over the dining-room table. There was also a huge, new plasma TV in the living room, in addition to the similar TV in the bedroom.Everything about the PHK soothes and delights. On a visit with a friend a few months ago, we had a regular superior room, with a street view. That was fine, as it was still very comfortable. A problem arose on Saturday morning, when construction sounds awakened us fairly early. They were clearly coming from somewhere inside the hotel, and somewhere fairly close. We got up and had a tasty American breakfast (included in my room rate) in the PHK Lobby cafe, which is an airy, sunlight-filled, haute-colonial destination unto itself. Meanwhile, I'd spoken with the front-desk staff about the construction noise and asked for more information and a possible change of room. Within minutes, the guest-relations manager herself came to our table, apologized for the noise -- which we learned was coming from the remodeling of the Louis Vuitton store in the hotel's shopping arcade -- and said she'd have two alternative rooms to show us after breakfast. The first room was in the tower, which was built in the 1990s, directly over the original PHK hotel. The room was fine but a bit smaller than and not quite as charming as our room in the old building. The second room was a deluxe with a harbour view in the old building, and we took that. Problem solved, in a manner that should be a model for similar situations in all luxury hotels but, sadly, usually isn't.I could go on and on about the PHK and all of its amenities -- incredible pool in the tower, with full views of the harbour; great room service; fab food and mod decor at Felix Resto Bar atop the tower -- but I'll stop here and recommend that anyone who wants to enjoy an unforgettable stay in the great city of Hong Kong will do him or herself a huge favor by staying at the PHK. The only downsides: it is expensive (but reasonable if one gets the lowest advance-purchase rate or a good corporate rate), and staying there will spoil you for anywhere else.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5554471d48f93d4c44fefeb3a1d52bbc" url=""><![CDATA[Small and Gorgeous: HK's New Hotel Standard I've stayed at the LMO twice -- once in late 2006, and most recently at the end of January 2007 -- and may I just saw, Wow! The LMO is in a three-way tie with the Peninsula and Four Seasons as my favorite HK hotel. For my first stay, I booked a suite deal package for the L900 suite, the hotel's largest (and worth the extra HK$), for me and a friend. The package included round-trip airport transfers in the hotel's Mercedes S-Class, breakfast, and other amenities, all for about HK$3000 less per day than the regular, non-package suite-only rate. The airport pickup service is perfect: as others have described, you're met at your gate, seated in an electric cart, and whisked past all the other deplaning passengers to immigration. HK's airport is already the world's best airport, and the LMO meet-and-greet service makes a pleasant airport experience all the more so. Arrival: The LMO is completely hidden in a tasteful but otherwise anonymous high-rise building that forms part of the new Landmark Centre complex. Upon pulling into the hotel's short drive, however, the MO's service and unique touches begin. Glass doors are opened by very smart-looking attendants, and the already-famous golden staircase greets you. Upstairs, the reception area is small and beautiful, and given that the hotel only has 113 rooms, I don't think there's ever more than a one-person wait. I was, of course, greeted by name as soon as I approached the receptionist, and she quickly escorted me to my suite, which was on the the top (15th) floor. L900 Suite: And what a suite -- the entry foyer is a black-marble catwalk flanked by smooth white and grey stones. The bedroom areas is to the left, the huge bathroom in the center, and the living/dining room and office to the right. Everything in the suite bespoke careful attention to the principles of fung shui, first-rate acoustics, and the best possible materials (dark woods, marble, glass, stone, fabrick) everywhere. As others have noted, the views from whichever room or suite you take are of other office building; after all the LMO is in perhaps the busiest section of Central. The in-room technology is of the highest standard and excels that found in the Pen or FS. The bathroom alone is sufficient reason to book the L900 or one of the L600 rooms: 7-foot round marble tub, with large, separate glass booths for both the toilet and rainforest shower. Fabulous. The A/V system in the suite (and all of the rooms, I suppose) caters to every need or desire; my friend and I particularly enjoyed the FTV and Amsterdam HD fashion channel (free; other HD channels offered for pay-per-view). Dining: My friend and I only had breakfast in the Amber restaurant (included in our suite package), and it was excellent. The food was copious and uniformly fresh and delicious, and Amber's atmosphere at one invigorating and relaxing. We loved the thousands of soft-gold metal reds suspended from the ceiling.Spa and pool: The LMO's Spa is the best I've seen thus far in a hotel: all manner of hot-and-cold water treatments, from a large-yet-intimate hammam to scented arctic showers to a tropical rainforest (which, oddly, features only a short trickle of water once every 5 minutes, preceded by a soft red glow from a sculpture that looks as though it were purloined from a old Trader Vic's restaurant). As with everything in the LMO, the materials of which the Spa is fashioned are all of the highest quality and maximum aesthetic appeal. During my first stay, there was no swimming pool, but the LMO had put one in before my second stay. The pool is the only feature of the hotel that is not superb: It appears to have been hastily installed and looks like what one would expect to see in the basement of a 3- or 4-star hotel. The pool is a decent size (though not 25 metres), but it's just a plain cement bowl with minimal decoration. No matter; it serves to make one's return to the rest of the LMO all that much more welcome.L450 room: Just a few words on the basic LMO room, in which I stayed last time, the L450 Superior: in any other hotel, this would be a top-of-the-line room; in the LMO, however, it's a wonderful bargain. It wasn't even a let-down after the L900 suite, as I was by myself this time and found the L450 more than adequate for all of my needs. Rather than providing a full seperate living/dining room, the L450 includes a mini-seating area next to the bed and in front of the floor-to-ceiling windows (which extend into the bathroom area). The bathroom was still very luxurious, with a lovely hourglass-shaped tub replacing the round version found in the larger room and suites. Otherwise, the smaller room was delightful, with lighter woods and the full range of audio-video options (including a small, perfectly placed for tub viewing LCD TV in the bathroom) I'd encountered in the suite.Bottom line: Hotels in Hong Kong are expensive, even by large Asian city standards, so why not spend your money on something really special? The LMO is a rare find: a small luxury hotel that offers everything its much larger high-end competitors have and then some. The LMO is very modern, so if you want more traditional European or Chinese decor and ambience, you'll probably not like the LMO as much as the Pen or Ritz-Carlton. But if you like ultramodern aesthetics combined with timeless Asian service standards and attention to detail, check out the LMO first. Enjoy.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2ee40eacfd5673a8f4e0c4d05c600e8b" url=""><![CDATA[FS: The New It HK Hotel I stayed at the new Four Seasons in Hong Kong from 17 to 20 February 2006. It is, without a doubt, the It hotel in the SAR; I found that, in overall appeal and service, it just edges out my two other HK favorites, the Peninsula and Ritz-Carlton. The FS really does have it all: (1) Location - perfect, attached to the IFC Mall and adjacent to the HK Airport Express Station. It's a short walk or taxi ride to anywhere, including the Star Ferry, in Central. Yet it's also somehow set apart. The property comprises two towers: the hotel proper and residences. (2) Rooms: I stayed in a Harbour Deluxe room, at a promotional rate that included HK$500 toward in-room or hotel-restaurant dining. While it was mostly foggy or rainy during my 3-day stay, the view of the busy harbour and Kowloon was inspiring. The decor is smart, sleek, and new-millenium luxurious: lots of dark woods, marble, and glass. The main TV is a huge plasma unit, with a smaller LCD screen over the bathtub. The bathroom is very luxurious, with a large soaking tub and walk-in rain shower. (3) Spa: the best I've seen to date in a hotel. (4) Pool: ditto, with two outdoor infinity pools and jacuzzis overlooking the harbour. (5) Food: room service is the usual FS excellent, and Caprice Restaurant has to be one of the best French restaurants in Asia. The staff -- particularly the maitre d' and his assistant -- pampered me, discreetly yet thoroughly introducing each of the eight mini-dishes comprising the degustation menu, which was out of this world. They advised me that they'd come from the FS George V Hotel in Paris with the goal of establishing the best French restaurant in Asia. Mission accomplished, I'd say. While the meal, with champagne and wine, cost almost half of the nightly room rate, it was more than worth it. (6) Staff/service: impeccable -- not only do the mostly young staff do everything right and go out of their way to help and advise, they are beautiful, as if they'd just come from HK fashion runways. I've really nothing bad to say about the FS HK. It's a new standard in the SAR, and I can only hope they'll run promotions similar to the one I enjoyed again in the near future. Even at regular rates, the rooms are a decent value. Well done, FS.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>