<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="e81fcf5793e507e7adc39f6db7757cf2" url=""><![CDATA[A nice trip overall .... We took a quick, last minute trip to the DR and stayed at the Bavaro Princess from July 7 - 10. When I looked at this site prior to the trip, I didn't see many reviews from folks with younger kids, so I wasn't sure how my 11 and 7 year olds would like the resort. Overall, I'd say the experience was very good. It definitely helped to read the reviews on this site, since I am pretty picky about hotels (cleanliness, bugs, food, etc.). Because of the reviews (even the bad ones) I wasn't surprised by anyting I ran into on the trip. We traveled through Apple Vacations (our first time) and by the end of the trip decided we'd use Apple again. We left out ot Newark, NJ on USA 3000 and experienced a significant delay. We were scheduled for a 6:00 am flight (figured we'd sleep the entire way), but when we left for the airport and called the airline, we learned that we were delayed until 7:30. I remembered that with USA 3000, seat assignments are on a first come, first served basis, so we went to the airport anyway. The good news is we did get seats together; however, the slight was delayed further and we didn't leave Newark until 8:30. We were all exhaused since we were up since 3 am, but got some sleep at the airport and on the flight and were fine once we hit the resort.The resort was beautiful. Hot, but that was expected in July. Checking In I remembered that the check in line could be long, so while my husband dealt with the luggage, me and the kids headed for check in. This was a wise decision, because within about a minute there was a long line behind us in a very hot lobby. We asked about a courtesy upgrade to platinum, but were advised of a $30 per day/per person charge and we decided it wasn't worth it for a short trip. The RoomWe got a room (752, I think) that was a 30 second walk from the beach and main pool which was very convenient. Everything I read about the room was pretty accurate ... clean, no bugs, room key for the lights, a slight musty smell (but I was prepared with disenfecting spray and febreeze, so no big deal), the beds were very hard (but by the time we went to sleep, who cared), no washcloths in the room, but I did bring some from home. There was bottled water in the room fridge, but we did bring bottled water from home and used it to brush our teeth in the room. Also, I noticed that the water left my hands feeling a little grimy after I washed my hands so we kept hand sanitizer on hand as well.No bugs in our room - thank god - and only one little lizard on our room wall one night. There was a hummingbird that hung out near our balcony which was cool.The Food / DrinksUnless you got up very early, getting reservations was tough. As a result, we mostly ate at the buffet off the lobby or at the beach grill / buffet which was fine. The selection was good, but my kids stuck with burgers (which tasted different ??), pasta, fruit, they didn't like the pizza. We did get a late reservation at Sakura one night and found the food ok. (Note: A late reservation with kids was a bad idea, but we thought we'd give it a try.) The Apple rep told us that the water and ice in the resort was filtered, so after the first day we drank it and had no problems while at the resort. On our last night at the resort, my son experienced a stomach ache, so I'd suggest bringing Pepto Bismol or Immodium with you as I did.The BeachBeach was great. We did bring cheap beach toys in our luggage for the kids, which they enjoyed for hours. The water was clean and my kids enjoyed the waves. If you are traveling with kids, give them a heads up about the topless situation, because they will see some sights on the beach !The Pool The pool was clean and there always seemed to be activities going on for the adults. Nothing for the kids, though. There was a shallow area of the pool which the kids enjoyed.The staffThe staff was very friendly and helpful. The one thing I was surprised about is how little English was spoken by the staff. At each of the main areas (main pool bar, lobby, etc.) you could find one or two members of the staff who spoke English well, but not many. Communication was more difficult than I expected, but if you worked at it, you could get what you needed. Even speaking a little Spanish helped. The shows were introduced in Spanish too. Entertainment for Families/KidsI was not aware of any organized activities for kids at this resort. My kids did enjoy watching the Lion King performance one night and the Festival show as well, although that one was more of a variety show. Again, no big deal for us on a quick trip, but if I had stayed longer, I would have preferred a resort with some activities for kids (outside of the kids (babysitting) club during the day.Overall, the Bavarro Princess met or exceeded our expectations in every area. We would probably not go back to the DR, because there are other destinations we want to experience. Also, I will say that when we returned home, my husband and I experienced stomach issues a few days. If we did decide to return to DR, we'd consider staying at the Bavaro or maybe try the Paridisus which I hear if really nice, but more expensive. Feel free to contact me with questions and enjoy your trip ! angjohjoh@yahoo.com
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>