<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="263935d3d401c4c13cd2a255bde8f505" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect Choice We stayed 4 nights at the Orafi at the start of June. We booked the actual Room With A View (room 414) from the book/movie of the same name. I was last in Florence 22 years ago, and when I was there then I watched the movie being filmed - so it came full circle for me.We paid E480/night. Expensive but we loved our stay there. The room is not large and there is very little storage (3 tiny drawers in the wardrobe) and simply not much room to spread out. But the patio out the French glass doors of this room is large and beautiful - and you simply can't beat the view! If you don't want to spend alot of money you can also enjoy most of the same view from the patio bar next floor up. The bar has a nice house wine and little bowls of munchies perfect for replenishing yourself after a long day of museums and shopping. The setting of the patio bar feels intimate and special, and it is a nice opportunity to meet other hotel guests from around the world and share stories.My favorite thing about this hotel is the location!! It is adjacent to the Arno by the foot of the Ponte Vecchio, a half a block from the Uffizi and a few minutes walk to what I think is the best piazza in Florence, the Piazza Signoria. I did not stay in the absolute center of things on my last visit and that was a mistake. It is wonderful to be able to pop in to your hotel to drop off packages or freshen up. Our weather was lovely but if you stay in Florence in the summer it can get extremely warm and uncomfortable. You will love that your hotel always seems to be convenient to where you are.My only concern when I booked was that it may be a bit noisy being by the river and the Ponte Vecchio. And the hotel's rooftop bar was above our room. The opposite was true - we could have heard a pin drop! The lungarno is a roofed walkway so the potential noise of all the people below is blocked. And the architecture of the surrounding rooftops and archways bounce the sound away and keep this hotel very quiet. My second favorite thing about this hotel is their breakfast (and the dining room it is served in) and I am not really even a breakfast person. In all of my extensive travels I have never experienced such a full array of wonderful foods as part of a complimentary breakfast. The pastries, the specialty cakes, the eggs, bacon, salmon, salads, fruit, champagne, etc....... was super!I strongly recommend this hotel and will stay here again on my next trip.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="95633f87762a711e93b3147ec3125f45" url=""><![CDATA[Sydney Harbor Marriott worked out great! We stayed at the Sydney Harbor Marriott between December 28 and January 2, 2005. We booked our reservation almost a year in advance because we wanted to use Reward points and we wanted to have the New Year's Eve experience at the Opera House. Our room was of course free with points, but we paid out of pocket $110US/night to upgrade to a suite facing the Opera House, and it was definitely worth it.Granted, I certainly cannot complain about the hotel since the majority of the cost was free. But even if we had paid full price, it was a lovely place to stay. The room was very clean and attractively decorated (though the suite is not large as suites go). The hotel (as many of the large hotels) is very conveniently located to the key tourist areas. A Starbucks is right across the way. An Avis branch is located in the hotel which made things very convenient for taking a trip to the Blue Mountains. The service from the staff was quite good as well.Make sure to have access to the concierge level. The alcohol was free, and the hor d'oeurves spread was more than enough for a dinner if you did not want to go out. There was a wide selection of foods offered both in the evening and in the morning for breakfast. New Year's Eve was everything I had hoped it would be. We had gotten tickets on-line for the actual NYE performance in the Opera House, and we could view the fireworks from viewing platforms in the Opera House, so we did not have to deal with the throngs of people jockeying for position. Although our Marriott room had a direct view of the harbor, you would not want to stay in your hotel while this world-reknown visual extravaganza is going on. Unfortunately for them, some people thought that would be the best way to enjoy the fireworks. It was said that the harbor had 1.5 million people viewing the fireworks, and it probably did. But the crowd was so happy and well behaved (no alcohol can be brought in) that I felt very comfortable and safe - and would have felt safe walking back to the hotel without my husband had I needed to.Marriott is not the Four Seasons, but then again they don't charge like them either. It was a perfect place to land for 5 days, and I would definitely stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>