<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="e2a779892ba6e9c5310a1dfcd7f8484e" url=""><![CDATA[Awful This Hotel is one the worst I've ever had the misfortune to stay in! However, it holds the Hotel of the year award for 2001 for the chain. But hey do not appear to have any clean bed sheets.I found black hair and big yellow puddle stains on the sheets, mattresses and comforters. I requested to move rooms and the new room had the same problems. Housekeeping came and tried to clean the bed but had to open new sheets because the replacement sheets also had stains.This Hotel is one the worst I've ever had the misfortune to stay in based upon the quality of the bedroom.What a disgusting Hotel!I checked out the same day.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="be652f4ed569ec509a862a6419f7b2ea" url=""><![CDATA[My goal of pure relaxation was TRULY fulfilled!! There is only one word to describe this hotel: BREATHTAKING!!The highlight of my trip to BALI was definitely the hotel, which infuses the essence of the Balinese culture. Absolutely STUNNING. The hotel has won some of the finest hospitality awards and is consistently ranked in the top 5 resorts in all Travel industry awards, this shows.I arrived at Depansar Airport in Bali from Hong Kong, after a wonderful plane ride from LHR. I had booked a car pickup from the Four Seasons Hotel (highly recommended) Immediately upon leaving the Airport, I was warmly greeted by a Four Seasons Hotel representative dressed in white traditional Balinese wear. He was holding a Four Seasons sign. Unlike other pickups, the hotel did not display my name for discreetness.He immediately picked my luggage and we proceeded to the waiting air-conditioned Four Seasons Toyota 4x4.When we reached the vehicle the driver came out and gave me a warm greeting, took my bags for the other person and loaded the 4x4. When I got inside the vehicle, I was presented with a cold towel and chilled bottle water. Immediately we proceeded to the hotel (absolutely stressed free). The driver called the hotel to inform them that I was on my way.Prior to entering the Four Seasons property, as a security precaution heightened by 9/11 and the KUTA bombing, the vehicle was screened by 3 security guards. The entrance to the hotel was magnificent and grand. I was greeted by two gracious hostesses and shown to the sofa where I was offered a fruit punch and cold hand towel. Everyone wore traditional white Balinese clothing. Registration was done by a check-in agent as I sat on the sofa, enjoying my drink The assistant manager came out and welcomed me and he was happy to inform me that he was able to secure villa 281 that I had requested.Once done, I was given the map to this wonderful resort and was whisked away in a buggy to my villa.The drive through the villa was amazing. Once I arrived at my villa 281 another person was waiting inside to guide me through my villa.The VILLA:This wonderful resort does not have rooms, but ratter resembling a Balinese hut/village compound (totaling 2,200 Square feet of pure luxury). The 147 villas is located on a hill and overlooks Jimbaran Bay. All the villas have gorgeous panoramic view of the bay and are modeled after a Balinese village.The living and dining rooms are open air. On the dining room table was a tray of exotic fruits.There is a huge plunge pool, which is about 5 feet deep. I love the pool and used it frequently to cool down from the hot sun thing in the morning and afternoons.The bedroom is in a closed building and is well air-conditioned. Inside this building is where one finds all the luxurious Four Seasons amenities like the fabulous FS bed, the large standalone bath tub for two, floor to wall marbled washroom, and luxurious toiletries. Complimentary bottled water was provided. It was not recommended that guest drink or brush teeth using the tap water.The bathroom has two showers (one indoor and the other outdoor.SERVICE:What can I the Four Seasons way: FABULOUS. I was always addressed by name. With a staff ratio of 5 staff to1, you know service will be outstanding!!I ordered room service and decide if I wanted fries or salad with my lunch. They brought me both! One time, I ordered breakfast from room service. The food was delivered. I forgot to asked him to bring what happened? The poor guy ran all the way back to the kitchen and within 2 minutes brought me straws as he panted to catch his breadth.There were countless other examples like what can I say, OUTSTANDING, Simply Four Seasons.The gym, connected to the SPA was superb! One afternoon, I decided to pay a visit the the gym and have a workout (well I visited every day but I don't want to show off), after feeling guilty from eating way too much Indonesian food!! In the middle of my run, the gym attendant saw that I was sweating like a waterfall, came over and offered me a nice cold face towel and chilled bottled water. When I had finished running, he came over to help me stretch! Boy did that feel good. The dressing room was also amazing. Each guests using the facility received a personal locker. Each locker had a sarong, cotton bathrobes, slippers, large towel, and plastic bag for dirty clothing. There was a sauna, steam room with aroma-therapy (which I used extensively), two whirlpools (one warm one cold), and two shower rooms (which had the typical shower head and an additional rain shower head). The facility has everything one would need in terms of toiletries: Molton brown Hair Gel, Aftershave, lotions, Foot spray, Talcum powder, mouth rinse, shaving razors, combs, addition to the gym, the resort offers cooking classes, complimentary morning workouts, bike rides, tennis, and water sports of all kind.The four days went ever so quickly and I regrettably had to leave this little piece of heaven. I booked through the hotel again the transportation back to the airport. The 4x4 and driver were waiting for me at 1400h and the Four Seasons representative at the airport took my bags all the way through the immigration clearance.Jimbaran beach is excellent for swimming, as it is very calm (rare for Bali), and also has some very good fish restaurants on the beach. I don't think that it is particularly noteworthy otherwise. One one poor note, I was particularly disappointed with FS beach facilities, which consist of closely arranged chaise lounges and a few scattered umbrellas. There is basically no privacy and if you don't get an umbrella before they run out, you will boil.The hotel is a very good place if you prefer a plunge pool to the beach, and are likely to spend most of your stay in your villa. The villas are in fact excellent, beautifully landscaped and most comfortable. I think that if a spectacular beach is a must though, FS is not the place for you. Although it is a fairly large property, if you are in your villa you never see or hear anyone else and all the lush landscaping makes you feel very private. Built into the hillside with little winding trails, rice paddies, flower gardens, and sunken villas - a rushing little river complete with small waterfalls and minor rapids, and the only groups we saw were people occasionally at lunch because it seems that when in Bali, everyone tours around looking at the Aman resorts and different Four Seasons in their hotel cars, having lunch or dinner at the different places. We went to Amankila one day and I agree that is it indeed spectacular and reminded us of the Caribbean!This is a truly an outstanding RESORT.. I will certainly return.My goal of pure relaxation was TRULY fulfilled!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="58a133de99e7d67db98e2acd23038e50" url=""><![CDATA[Overall a good Ritz Carlton but not as good as the RC Tokyo or RC Osaka As usual, we are never disappointed by the RC Carlton service. The ambience, the staff, the service, everything is provided with diligent, flawless and attentive service. Amenities were superb, the LCD TV, the DVD player. The view is also lovely. The landscape is great.We arrived at Singapore Airport from London and a private car (provided by the hotel) was waiting for myself and my partner. Our bags were taken off us and we were escorted to the car (we never saw our luggage until we arrived in our room)The weather is very humid, together after a long flight from London and the tiredness it was nice to receive a friendly smile from the driver.Located in front of the seats were 2 cold towels and 2 bottles of perfectly chilled mineral water which was nice and refreshing after the long flight.The journey to the RC hotel was comfortable. It seemed that the journey took no time at all, maybe we fell asleep!Arriving at the hotel, both passenger doors to the car were opened and two members of staff appeared and escorted us to the club lounge to complete the check in process and have refreshments. Doors were closed, and we were escorted through the hotel. The main doors were opened, lift doors open awaiting us and upon arrival in the Club Lounge a member of staff was ready to conduct the check in process. The club lounge manager greeted us and wished us a pleasant stay. Check in was very efficient, our passports were taken away and returned within a matter of minutes. Refreshments were offered. We opted for tea (loose leaf tea) and was poured in front of us in a pleasant manner.After the refreshments we were escorted to our room (club deluxe)Our bags were awaiting us upon arrival to our room.Now to our only complaint, upon arrival to the room we both noticed that the room reeked of strong cigarette smoke. A non smoking room was booked and confirmed. Due to my partner suffering from mild asthma we complained to the club lounge manager about this. The time was now 10pm and we had been travelling for 16 hours. Around 11pm, a member of staff came into the room and sprayed the room with some air freshener. Unfortunately this made the situation much worse as the smell was disgusting and over powering. Another telephone call to the club lounge manager was made. Around 1130pm a member of staff appeared with a machine to plus in to get rid of the odour. Fortunately this worked and we retired to bed. The bedroom consisted of two large beds, with plush pillows and crisp starched white linen. Other features of the room were a large sofa and coffee table (directly in front of the bed beside the windows with numerous western and Asian magazines and periodicals), a unit with fresh flowers and oriental ornaments, a large wardrobe with a good amount of hangers, a digital safe, an iron and ironing board. Between the beds was a bedside table with light, master switch for the lights, do not disturb button, white telephone and note pad with a pen. There was a desk and chair beside the sofa and next to the bathroom door.Onto the bathroom...White bath (located next to the window), sink, toilet, step in shower, a good amount of Bvlgari toiletries (Shampoo, Bath and Shower Gel, Soap, Conditioner and bath bag). In a drawer under the sink unit was a hair brush, comb, hair dryer and mouthwash.The bath which was perfectly maintained and lime scale and crack free was huge, water pressure was excellent and the bath filled up in minutes. You can lay in the bath and your feet touch the other end. The water pressure of the shower was also excellent.Curtains and blackout blinds offering complete blackout.The Club lounge which is on the 32nd floor features magnificent 360-degree views of the city skyline. Handsomely furnished interiors provide the perfect backdrop to enjoy the five culinary and beverage presentations daily. Breakfast consisted of an Asian selection as well as a western style breakfast consisting of Fresh fruit juices, cereals, selection of fresh (and I mean fresh) fruit, champagne, mineral water, pastries (fresh and very tasty), and a small cooked selection. Tea and coffee was poured at our table and Toast was offered. Due to being out of the hotel during the day, we did not sample the luncheon service however returned for afternoon tea. Afternoon tea is a huge affair, dainty sandwiches, scones with clotted cream and preserves, dainty cakes and gateaux. Tea and coffee is poured at your table. Champagne is also available. Club lounge staff remembered I like champagne with afternoon tea and a pre dinner drink. Without asking, I was presented with a glass without asking.Cold milk served every time with tea (without asking) normally they serve tea with hot milk (I have noticed this in many Asian hotels)Extra Bvlgari toiletries during turn down (without asking)Being addressed in perfect English our names and the only place in the world where my surname is perfectly pronounced.1. The buffet was perfectly maintained and replenished throughoutMy partner was still unhappy how the hotel dealt with the problem of the cigarette odour problem the previous night. The club lounge manager dealt with our complaint in an efficient and polite manner and took off the first accommodation to compensate us.Dinner and refreshments are provided in the Club lounge, which consisted of a selection of hot and cold items, both western and Asian. Alcoholic and no alcoholic drinks (including champagne) were also available.Internet is available in the club lounge and is complementary.The hotel has a gym, due to having a busy schedule, we use the gym or the spa but the gym had the latest equipment. We wish we used the gym now. Another reason to return to the hotel.Checkout was efficient and attentive. Our bags were taken off us and we were escorted to the car for the transfer to the airport.Overall a good Ritz Carlton but not as good as the RC Tokyo or RC Osaka. Disappointing problem over the Cigarette odour but this complaint was dealt with and we were compensated.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3bd8aa78fcc443d89d9ba0336589ec32" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect We have stayed twice this year at the RC Tokyo. Both visits were perfect.Our first visit to the RC Tokyo was also our first visit to Japan. We arrived at Narita Airport minus our baggage due to the incompetence of British Airways!After spending over an hour filling in lost luggage forms we finally made our way to the Arrival Concourse.We had thought about getting the Limousine Bus from the Airport to the Hotel as this seemed the easiest option without getting a taxi or hotel car service which were both very expensive.I have no problem paying good money for services when they represent good value but for a one way transfer from the airport to the hotel is not good value when you can get there via public transport for about approached the desk for the limousine bus and enquired about the journey to be told there another bus to our hotel for nearly 2 hours as they are timed to coincide with arrivals. Unfortunately they timed to coincide with British Airways losing your baggage and having to stay behind filling forms in.We therefore decided to make our way to the Narita Express Train. This is just one of a number of train services that operate from the airport to different parts of Tokyo.We approached one of the automated ticket machines and followed the instructions. Simple enough, or so we thought. We then approached the ticket inspection only to be stopped and told we had only purchased a reservation and not the actual ticket.We did read up about this before we left the UK but of course after a long flight and problems on arrival we had gone and forgotten. We went back and this time went to the staffed ticket desk, there we were greeted by the always fantastically pleasant member of staff who issued us an additional ticket and off we went.The Narita Express train station is directly under the terminal, there are two stations, one at each of the two terminals and it is just as easy as the Heathrow Express. The noticeable difference is that the staff are friendly, helpful and the trains are spotless and leave bang on time.Our journey into Tokyo was quite long, about 60 minutes, through typical industrial land until you reach the outskirts of Tokyo itself when you start to see the bright neon lights, even in the middle of the afternoon.On arrival at Tokyo Station we disembarked our train into a station that handles over 4,000 train journeys a day. If you think of the size of the new St Pancras, plus the size of Kings Cross, plus the size of Euston then you will be getting near to the size of Tokyo Station. The station is located in the Marunouchi business district near the Imperial Palace and the Ginza shopping area. The station handles most of the Shinkansen (Bullet) High Speed Trains, Local and Regional Commuter Trains as well as the Tokyo Metro (Underground) network.If you intend to use the train, then there is one piece of advice I would recommend before travelling to Japan and that is to get hold of a Map of Tokyo Station before you leave. You will defiantly need it otherwise you will never get out of the station.Thankfully the RC Tokyo were kind enough to post us in advance a copy of the map and with that in hand we tried to find our way to the Metro Station.Even with a map we had to ask several people before we finally ended up in the right location. (A big thank you to everyone that helped!).If you intend to get to the RC Tokyo by Metro then you need the Marunouchi Line (Red Colour) from Tokyo Station, one stop getting off at Ginza where you change to the Hibiya Line (Silver Colour) from Ginza to Roppongi (4 Stops).The next problem was getting a ticket. We were at the entrance to a long corridor leading down to the Marunouchi Metro Line from within the Station. There were ticket machines all around us and also ticket booths.We assumed we needed a ticket from one of these booths to be able to get on the train, wrong!, if you see the green machines with JR or Japan Rail on them then these are for the Commuter Trains not the Metro.Continue down the corridor and eventually you will reach the main Metro Station Concourse where there are a large number of automated ticket machine (they take coins and notes) where you can purchase a ticket.The first time you use the metro the best options is to purchase the cheapest ticket then when you arrive at your destination, just insert your ticket; it will tell you if there is an excess fare to pay. If there is just look for the machine marked similar. Just insert your ticket and it will tell you how much to pay.The good thing with the ticket machines is that you can put your ticket in any way you like and it always takes it and produces it at the top, perfectly pressed and facing the right way, go on try it (the simple things always amaze!).On arrival at Roppongi station you will be greeted with numerous exits. If you take any of them you will end up right in the middle of a busy street with your entire luggage, instead follow the signs for connections to the Odeo line. You will basically walk along nice wide underground walkways until you see the signs for the Midtown Shopping Complex, follow these signs and you will arrive into an upmarket shopping centre where you should start to pick up signs for the Ritz Carlton. Keep making your way to the outside plaza where you will find the Ritz Carlton entrance in the corner.This is a side entrance but it certainly beats walking all the way round the complex to get to the main car entrance.From the side entrance you follow the signs to the lift and make your way up to the 42 floor, this is where the main lobby and reception is located and where the Ritz Carlton Luxury begins.As soon as we walked out of the lifts we were greeted by members of staff and escorted to the reception desk. As you take the short walk to reception you start to notice something very special. Every member of staff in the lobby seems to stop and bow at you, a polite bow back is greeted with a second bow and a smile of appreciation.At reception the escorting member of staff introduced us to the reception team, all of which bowed again and we were then welcomed by Josephine the Rooms Division Manager (on secondment from the RC Hong Kong whilst it undergoes renovation).As soon as we gave our names we were immediately recognised as being resident on the Ritz Carlton Club Floor and we were escorted up to the Club Lounge (53rd Floor) by a member of staff who then introduced us to the Club Lounge staff who handled our check in.We were immediately offered a complimentary drink, we both chose their recommended Cherry Blossom Cocktail which was champagne with a delicate taste of cherry, very welcoming after the long journey. We were also given some hot towels to refresh ourselves.The check in process was perhaps not as quick as some of the more business orientated hotels but it was certainly more luxurious and relaxing with everything being handled for you whilst you enjoy your refreshments and a view of Mount Fuji from what is Japans tallest building.When we were ready we were escorted to our room. The member of staff introduced us to the facilities and checked to see if there was anything else we needed. They had already picked up on the fact we had only two small bags and asked if our luggage had been lost, from that moment they handled everything with British Airways, telephoning them constantly for the five days we were without luggage. They even communicated with our next hotel the Ritz Carlton in Osaka and made sure they were aware of the situation offering to transport the luggage on should it arrive.The room we had booked was a Club Deluxe Room, again located on the 53rd floor just round from the club lounge.The room itself was fantastic and very well furnished. The hotel was celebrating its first birthday whilst we were there and they provided us with a bottle of very nice Bordeaux together with a RC Tokyo 1st Birthday Corkscrew in a small presentation box and some delicious chocolate truffles.The room itself had two large double beds (American sized doubles), these were of the usual high RC quality, two large wardrobes one with a laptop safe the other with integral drawers and a valet box for your overnight shoe shine.In the entrance hallway there was a side unit containing not a mini bar like some 5 star hotel provide, the RC provides an honesty bar build into the unit with fridge containing everything from the finest Remy Cognac through to the classic Japanese Sake, next to the fridge were drawers full of fine red wine, a selection of different snacks together with the facilities to mix your own cocktail.On top of the unit was a traditional Japanese tea set, the rest of the equipment such as kettle and tea or coffee, were located inside the unit.There was an additional unit inside the bedroom which contained a Bravia LCD TV with the normal interactive functions such as internet access, movies, music, etc.The room also contained a decent sized desk together with two desk chairs, lamp, stationary, power outlets including international adaptors, etc.There was also a coffee table together with a selection of western and Japanese periodicals including a book (together with a detailed map) about the sculpture / public art around the Midtown area (worth a walk around to get your bearings).The bedside tables contain a good bedside lamp together with an electronic control panel; this controls the curtains, the blind and all of the room lighting including the bathroom. It also has a do not disturb button which puts a little red light on the door outside.The bathroom was huge, bigger than the whole room at a recent supposed five star hotel we stayed at in Manchester.You enter the bathroom through a pair of wooden double doors, inside there are two large vanity units each with its own wash basin and set of drawers containing towels, hair dryer, various toiletries such as toothbrush and paste, hair brush, mouthwash, body location, mending kit, etc.There is a large deep bath that has the perfect recline for enjoying a glass of wine whilst you relax watching the TV. Yes the bathroom has its own TV. Not only that but like all technology in Japan, it far exceeds our own in Britain because this TV just like the one in the bedroom can at the press of a button translate everything that is said into another language. I just mean subtitles, it mutes out the normal speech and replaces it with that of your chosen language. Fantastic. Of course there is the usual selection of international channels there as well, watching BBC world presenters talking Japanese is very strange, but not as good as watching Japanese presenters talking in English.The bath has a handheld shower should you wish to wash your hair in the bath. There is also a separate shower room with large rain shower head.The bathroom toiletries on the Club Floor are all Bvlgari The Blanc (45ml bottles) which we enjoy.You may be wondering where the toilet is (or maybe not!) well once again those technology experts of Japan just have toilets they have TOTO.TOTO is in its own little room. It has a heated seat, automatic flush and special Think bidet, upside garden sprinkler and blow dryer all in one! All controlled from your touch button control panel. (As I previously said with the ticket machine at the Metro Station, the simple things always impress!).The bedroom also contains a small table and two arm chairs or in some rooms there is a window seat. The view out of the window is amazing; we looked right down over the Imperial Palace and most of Tokyo.I am told that the rooms at the RC Tokyo are the largest in Tokyo, I know how true this is as we staid anywhere else in Tokyo but they certainly compare well with other 5 Star Deluxe Hotels we have stayed in.Back to the Club Lounge, this is open I believe from as early as 6am through to about 10pm, every day of the week.The lounge provides complimentary refreshments throughout the day including a breakfast buffet of western and Asian foods, mid morning cakes and coffee, a light buffet lunch selection, an excellent afternoon tea buffet, an evening pre dinner selection followed by late evening drinks and desserts.The buffet always contained a mixture of western and Asian foods and it was constantly restocked. If you are only a light eater then there is more than enough to provide for you throughout your stay. We did find that late evening we were wishing for something a little more substantial so we did use room service a couple of times.The food is all presented on a large central tables and a number of side tables. You are requested to help yourself from the buffet. Drink orders are taken from you by the Ladies and Gentlemen serving in the lounge and they are then brought to your table.Champagne (I am unsure of the vintage) is free flowing so feel free to ask for it. There is a selection of different loose leaf tea and coffee is also available at anytime and is served in the finest Wedgewood china.The lounge contains a selection of sofas, comfy chairs and tables together with a small library area with newspapers and magazines as well as coffee table books. A rare Wedgwood Portland vase is on the book case.The lounge staff will do anything for you and provide all of the normal concierge services you would expect.After your first introduction at check-in it appears that every member of staff remembers your name and always makes you feel welcome.The problem we had was we only had the clothes we had travelled in together with a pair of jeans each in our hand luggage. The staff were very understanding of this and mind us using the lounge for the time being in our jeans and trainers.I would say that I would not personally as a guest like people to use the hotel or the lounge with such clothes in an evening. Whilst T-Shirts and Jeans are fine for sightseeing they do lower the class of a hotel in an evening. With this in mind we set about finding some suitable clothes and went into the shopping centre next door. The problem we had was that Japanese clothing sizes quite accommodate our western physiques!We therefore went back into the hotel we were again immediately greeted by Josephine who instantly recognised us. We told her of our predicament and she immediately sprung into action by ringing round clothing stores for us. She then provided us with a clear map and directions together with opening times and escorted us down to the main entrance.Within a few hours we at least had a change of clothes we could use within the hotel without feeling too out of place. We just had to pray the holiday insurance would pay out as the Japanese prices for clothes were worse than Sloan Square!We enjoyed room service a number of times throughout our stay, on each occasion the food was delivered quickly and presented on a small dining table brought to our room all set up for dinner together with starched white table cloth, small square vase with an flower in, cut crystal glassware etc.The food was very fresh and of excellent quality and quantity, kept hot in special heated boxes so none of the problems of cold food like some hotels seem to be good at!It was also explained to us on each occasion to phone down and they will remove the table straight away as they knew they can sometimes get in the way. We tested it and within 3 minutes of the call it was gone!I did use the hotel gym during our stay; it certainly puts every UK gym I have ever been to shame. The gym is located on the 54th floor and has all the latest Life Style fitness equipment, together with a warming up area, smith machine, benches, free weights, barbells, dumbbells and a varied selection of resistance machines. The cardio machines overlook the City skyline and have televisions built into the machine showing the same channels as in the bedrooms together with various western and Asian music channels and radio stations. All the gym staff are friendly and approachable and welcome and greet you personally whilst you are in the gym (at shift changes new staff even greeted me)If you are in any difficulty whilst in the gym, there are discreet camera dotted around the suite, so if you are in any difficulty whatsoever, a member of staff will appear and help you; I was having difficulty in using the Smith machine and after several minutes on working how to screw more weights onto the machine, a member of staff appeared and helped me.Throughout our stay the hotel staff were fantastic, they anticipated our needs at all times such as providing double the amount of toiletries on the second day as they had found out our bags were still missing.Perfect. Harmony in a very busy City.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c406d5199f1cae83a559ec3d71188558" url=""><![CDATA[Better than the RC Powersocurt, not as good as the RC Osaka Last week I spent two nights in the Ritz Carlton in a Junior Suite ( 410 EUR per night, breakfast an extra of 28EUR). The hotel is part of the new Beisheim Center, built in elegant american architecture style and it includes the Ritz Carlton, office spaces, apartments and a Marriott Hotel as well. The Beisheim Center is owned by Otto Beisheim (80 years old German billionaire, founder of the Metro trade group) and located on the Potsdamer Platz, the former nomansland, where the Berlin Wall went through. I arrived at the hotel around 11:45am, albeit the early time, my suite was however ready. The problems started when I tried to enter my room - the keycard didn't work. So I asked somebody from the hotel staff, who was walking by, to open my room. I entered the room and had the intention to phone the reception desk to bring me a new card - unfortunately the phone didn't work. None of the 3 phones in my room. And 20 minutes already passed by and I was still waiting for my little piece of luggage to arrive in my room. So I went to the reception desk and asked for a replacement of my keycard and the whereabouts of my luggage and told them to get my phone working. After 10 more minutes my luggage arrived and I decided to try the spa and fitness facilites of the hotel. The swimming pool is rather small, just enough to refresh yourself. Two hours later I was back in my room and the phone still wasn't working. I got dressed and left the hotel, stopping by the reception desk, and told them again to fix the phone - which they did at an unknown time later that day.Some other annoyances: No LAN/Fax/phone/electric socket right on the writing desk in the room - it's all on the floor under the desk, so you have to crawl around. And no WiFi in the room. I think this is unacceptable for a brand new built 5*+ hotel.The suite itself is really nice. They did a great job in building this hotel but the service and some other details need improvement.FBWe ordered in Room Service for dinner as our dinner plans fell apart at the last minute. We ordered very simple food -- a cheeseburger with fries, french onion soup, a chicken panini, and caesar salad. The food was decent if not again aggressively salted. The meal was fairly timely (late by 7 minutes) but was not very hot by the time it arrived.Breakfast:The quality of the breakfast was decent but nothing mind-blowing. Service was awkward and not particularly attentive. Eggs were cooked to perfection and the coffee was excellent.ServiceI understand that we visited at a terribly busy time but fundamental service gaffes pervaded the hotel part of our stay. I think the hotel cannot handle the volume of business for its size and it most certainly did not handle the chaos very well.I had to prompt the hotel at almost every step -- the service was not effortless or intuitive; at best, it was reactive and only when prompted. We had requested turn down at a certain time, but housekeeping came at their convenience. When we asked her to return later, we were told that she could not come back.Such issues marred what could have been a wonderful stay and should not have happened at a hotel of supposed calibre as the Ritz Carlton.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>