<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="c27558ea6b1f2d68503353b64f0b4910" url=""><![CDATA[Not so good not so bad. I spent one night with my g-friend on 07/16 our second time in a year for weddings. The rate was great for the area but this property is old. I would say a great family value for those looking to stay on south beach without the high prices. They have a large pool with cabana rentals available. The food can be pricey and not so good. The breakfast buffet is good though. The rooms are spacious but the comforters and pillows need upgrading. They have been slowly updating the hotel but they should have sank more money into it and made it more contemporary. It has a well-kept older facility feel to it. Boring but not a rip off.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f5e661c6f5d69cae177e0057edf627ba" url=""><![CDATA[Service Service Service I spent a week with my g-friend over Labor Day for Bumbershoot. The Gray line airporter drops off around the corner from the hotel for about 10 per person, by cab 28 total but make sure they give you the flat rate or Town Car is 38. The location is central downtown across the street from W. a quick walk to most points of tourist or business interest. Yes the Space Needle is a bit far off but you can take the monorail at the Westlake Center, which is an easy walk away. For the tourist the Underground tour, Public Market, Space Needle and EMP are a must. Leave a bit of room in your luggage because the shopping is great. The neighborhood is very safe and clean. Room: The Mediterranean Suite is quite large, equipped with a two-person Jacuzzi tub and small stand up glass-enclosed shower. The room had no view but we did not care. The room was clean except for a small throw blanket that adorned the foot of the bed, which we took off. It was tastefully decorated and the walls were striped. Trust me you wont feel like you are in a stale hotel. Ask for a gold fish or bring your well-behaved dog for company.Service: All aspects are excellent. Front desk house keeping concierge room service bell desk are all ready to provide you with the warm and professional service. Test them they flinch.Gym: Open 24 hours with several newer cardio machines and a few dumbbells. The highest weight being 25. They have water towels and a TV. however is within walking distance.Gastronomy: Sazerac is worth a try if not impressive amusing.This was my third visit to Seattle first to Monaco. While I like the beds at Westin better I prefer Monaco at least until I can afford W. This being my g-friends first visit to both she wants to go back for Bumbershoot next year and stay at Hotel Monaco.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>