<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="f770daffae91a9f1fc2767b93d958584" url=""><![CDATA[Sparkling fresh and new. The view from our room.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="44a6eab9ce3e61ea6c0511558022b9e8" url=""><![CDATA[Downtown and up there with the best of them View of the Space Needle from our hotel room
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3754350d998dd2a512006dc286557413" url=""><![CDATA[Youthful and modern What a breath of fresh air. A unique experience....most of it delightful but one or two negative points.The positives (and there were many):1) Very helpful friendly staff2) Personal internet booking service- staff offered to arrange restaurant bookings and an airport pickup via email3)Central location just off La Ramblas but very quiet4) Relaxing rooftop terrace5) Free drinks and snacks available in the lobby 24 hours a day6) Free internet access (one terminal) in the lobbyThe negatives:1) Decor felt like a rather stark version of Habitat - funky but not comfy or homely. Lobby felt like a shop interior, not a hotel.2) Bedroom and lounge were dark and rather unwelcoming. The coolness might have been a relief in the heat of the summer but not at the end of March.Despite these gripes, the overall experience was very positive because the staff were all so kind.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="70232a12267b8a53d4cb7852b4cbcf58" url=""><![CDATA[Another bullseye for Tripadvisor! I picked this hotel out for our 4 night stay in Manhattan in July because of the rave reviews on Tripadvisor. I was not disappointed.Positive features: Great location in midtown Manhattan; very helpful staff; complimentary buffet breakfast with free newspapers; large bedrooms for New York; complimentary drinks and nibbles in the Club Room from 5pm to 8pm Monday to Friday; room rates very reasonably priced.Negative features:Only one rather slow elevator; bedrooms somewhat dark and dingy.These are minor gripes. I can highly recommend the place and would certainly stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>