<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="2c03beff71e3ba06e3ddfd6bda990aef" url=""><![CDATA[an overall great family holiday resort! We just arrived home on the 16th of February after spending a great week at the Melia Caribe Tropical resort. My husband and I travelled with our two daughters who are 3 and 5 years old. The resort grounds are large and extremely beautiful. There is a train that ran all day every 15 minutes or so and took you all over the grounds. We never had to wait long for the train and our children enjoyed the ride through the resort. Our hotel room was 43 and was situated close to the restaurants and a short 15 minute walk or short train ride to the beach and pools. We have travelled quite extensively and were very surprised after we arrived home to read some of the negative reviews. First of all the grounds were one of the nicest we have seen as is the beach! Beautiful white sand and turquoise waters. The rooms were nice and kept very clean. Our fridge was stocked with water and beer daily by the maid. The staff were extremely nice and accomodating and genuinely love children! It is hard travelling with children but we felt the staff bent over backwards and made our holiday a very enjoyable one. We did tip but did not feel pressured to as we have felt at some other resorts. The food was plentiful and there was a large variety. I can't understand people complaining about the food as there are 8 or 9 a la carte restaurants and three buffets offered at particular times of the day. The staff at the buffets will make you eggs etc anyway you like them at breakfast and fresh pasta of your choice at lunch and dinner. There were so much food to choose from I can't imagine anyone having a hard time finding SOMETHING that they would like!! You do have to call to make reservations for the a la carte restaurants the day before. If you call between 7-8 am you will be sure to get into the restaurants of your choice. Just be flexible with the hours of your reservations if you are able to. On a negative note, I did get sick from what I am not sure but just mildly and I recommend packing the necessary medication. The rest of my family was fine and you run the risk of that happening no matter where you go! The mosquitos were quite bad at night so pack some bug repellant as well.In closing I think your holiday is what you make it! If you are expecting a nice holiday I don't think you will be disappointed at this resort. We weren't! We met wonderful new friends and enjoyed our stay at the Melia Caribe Tropical Resort. We look forward to returning in the future.Burlington, OntarioCanada
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ca226e9bd384d3ed1bd626ee12904a8b" url=""><![CDATA[Can't go wrong with the Majestic! Just got back from a week at the Majestic Colonial in the Dominican Republic Punta Cana Feb 9th- 16th. To start I highly recommend the resort and leaving on a Friday to Friday. We traveled with our family of four and another family of four. We did not have to wait in line other than for 5 minutes at the Domincan airport. Everything just seemed to fall into place!The hotel was very good! The food was plentiful and delicious. The buffet that was offered at Valentine's day was the best I have ever seen not just in the presentation but also in the selection and taste. The best part of this resort other than the fact that it is not huge is that the restaurants did not require reservations other than for the Japenese restaurant and the Le Gourmet restaurant. Never had a problem getting in at the time you wanted. Service was very good!The staff were friendly and very accomodating! They genuinely love children! The kids club was excellent! Maggie and Maria who took care of the children were wonderful and made the children feel at ease which in turn made the parents feel comfortable. All four of our girls had a great time and enjoyed the mornings they spent at the club on the waterslides. and drawing pictures. The kids club facility was extremely clean. The resort offered entertainment both for the kids and the adults in the evening. We enjoyed the shows.The rooms were very nice ....huge showers and a bath in the rooms. The balconies were very large. The rooms overlooking the pool were nice. Spacious and very clean!We would highly recommend this resort to anyone considering the Dominican Republic. The beaches were gorgeous as was the pool that ran through the whole resort. Never had a problem finding a spot on the beach and pool provided you got out to reserve your spot by 9 am or so. A few of us had tummy problems temporarily but that is what happens when you go to a different country and indulge in a lot of different things. Although I am not a doctor I would highly recommend the Dukoral (travelers anti diaherea oral vacination) that can be prescribed by a physician. Worked for me! Just an extra percaution that could be and was worth the extra cost. Enjoy your vacation! Lay back and relax. Don't be in a hurray and you will get your monies worth and more from this resort!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>