<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="ec0d14860b62c4cb607cdf98108d6a7f" url=""><![CDATA[Great Room, good conf facilities This is an on airport property. The only bad thing I could name was that I couldn't take the train to my desired terminal because I had checked luggage and wasn't on american airlines.'As soon as I arrived via shuttle bus from my terminal, bell staff was there to take my bags. (golf bags get me automatic bell service, otherwise I haul them.) They were very responsive, timely, helpful, etc. The bell man even suggested restaurants (unsolicited) and other helpful info.My usual late arrival room service was very good, but pricey. The sunset over the runway/traffic control terminals was very cool. The full moon was equally good. Who could have imagined a room with a view at the airport. (No noise either!)The room was very modern, very clean, and well apportioned. Maid service was good.When I needed to catch the shuttle to terminal e, the bellman/limo driver was extremely helpful. (A cabbie didn't know where one of the better known golf courses or hotels was located the day before.)I'd stay there again!.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="01e9e7d49109e5745c5eb5b86da73b13" url=""><![CDATA[Great historic hotel with modern amenities I've stayed in many 'historic' hotels throughout the world. Historic at most just means old. At the Adolphus, it was a clean, restored, updated with modern amenities where necessary, and a great hotel. I had a red-eye flight into Dallas. I'd called two days before to see if I could check in early. A room was ready for me at 7:00 a.m. (without charge.) It was clean. Room service was fine (and seemed reasonably priced..)I'm a business traveler so I measure things by clean, fast internet, thick towels, good bed, and warm water. They passed on all. They shower head was adjustable and was actually unique. It sprayed directly down on top of you.I'd stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>