<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="2e95f9e3a92ed0efbd9e514eb04b01d0" url=""><![CDATA[Hilton Hawaiian Village, a great property The family and I just returned from a 7 day stay in the Hilton Hawaiian Village and we had a great time. The wife and I were celebrating our 10th wedding anniversary and decided to stay at the village because we were going to have over 12 people in total with 4 children under 11 and thought this would be a great place to spend our 7 days. While the Village is a great property there were a few proplems. We stayed in the newer Kalia tower the newest of the 4 towers on the property and we had an ocean view. The room was average size, a little small for the amount of money the hotel charges, but the view is probably the reason for the rate. A plus about the room is that there was a little mini fridge in the room which would play a major role in our stay. We had 2 doubles in the room which were very comfortable. There was a standard 32 inch TV in the room with many cable channels. But again for the money that was charged there should definately be a flat screen in the room. But that is a minor issue. In the room were also a wet bar, a safe (which you can use for a minor fee) a writing desk and a recliner. High speed internet was also available for a small fee. The bathroom was a good size with a bath and shower. In our tower itself there was a spa and pool on level 4 and a Starbucks and a store selling those miniture guitars that are so popluar in Hawaii in the lobby. The grounds at the Hawaiian Village were beautiful and big! To get from one part of the property to the other it took a little walking but at least you had a lot of eye candy to look at while you were walking. There were flamingos, penguins, parrots, many types of birds all walking around on the property. Also many different types of flowers, trees, and other plant life. I definately had the feel of being in Hawaii just by walking around the resort. My wife and mother loved the fact that there were over 90 different types of shops on the hotel grounds. So any time we had to walk across the grounds for any reason it gave them an excuss to just look. The only drawback with the grounds that I can think of is the traffic. Because there are a lot of people in the Village there are cars that constantly come and go out of the property. So you always have to be careful that you watch were you go when you cross the street within the property when you go to the other side of the Village. Within the property there are many different resturants serving a variety of foods. There was an Italian resturant, a Japanese steakhouse were they cook the food right in front of you, Bar and Grills, and even a Round Table Pizza. You could also find on the property an Ice Cream parlor, a Hot Dog place and a buffet resturant that was open to the outside private beach. If you decide to eat at the resturants, however, make sure that you bring plenty of cash because they are not cheap. Each resturant is at least 2 times as much as the same type of resturant would on the mainland. Even Round Table and the Ice Cream parlor were much higher then normal. But, I guess that is the price you pay for being in Hawaii. Many of our dinners were spent outside of the resort (luau, dinner cruise and others) so we didn't have to spend the high prices. When we did want lunch we went down to the ABC store right on the property and bought lunch meat, bread chips and sodas and used the fridge in our room. We saved a lot of money doing that. Not that we were being cheap, but i just couldn't see myself spending $30.00 for a kids lunch that they probably would even finish. On the property there were many places to swim. There was the swimming pool hot tub on the 4th floor of our tower. They were a little small so we were only there 1 time. We spent much more time at the Super Pool, private beach and lagoon on the property. Every time we went to the Super Pool we had a good time. We always had chairs to sit our stuff on, there never seemed to be a lot of people there, and the pool was so big we could splash around a little. The lagoon was lovely. Again not a lot of people when we went so we could spread our stuff out of the beach and have a good time. We rented a paddle boat and went around the lagoon which the kids loved. The only drawback with the lagoon and also the beach was you had to rent beach chairs. I felt for the amount you pay for everything they could at least let us use the beach chairs for no charge. Overall we had a great time at the Hilton Hawaiian Village. They have everything you can think of right on the property and the service was great as well. If a person wanted to they can stay right on the resort and never leave; I wouldn't recommend it because there is so much to do on the island, but you could. The only problems I had with the resort is the size of the room for the money, the price of the resturants and you get nickel and dimed for things that could've been included. But with that said, if your looking for a hotel for the family I would recommend the Hilton Hawaiian Resort.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>