<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="9dd25358fc0155a34291f5e47f308b76" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect hotel to start our honeymoon We had the pleasure of starting our honeymoon at the Chancellor Hotel as part of our three centre west coast US visit to San Francisco, Los Angeles and Las Vegas. I chose the hotel as it was recommended by Trailfinders who said their guests loved it, and despite extensive research on the net and Tripadvisor I could not see another hotel I would prefer.We arrived at the hotel at 1.30 am after a nightmare 24 hour, 3 flight due to plane delays, journey from the UK (7 hours late). After taking a minibus from the airport we checked in and were warmly welcomed, no queue due to lateness of the hour. I had emailed the manager in advance and he had allocated us a high floor (14th) room with a view of Union Square as requested. A bottle of wine on ice and a lovely giftwrapped photograph frame were waiting for us due to this being our honeymoon. I must be in the minority as I did not think our standard room was small at all, average and above average compared to many UK hotel rooms (it was half as big again as the room we spent our wedding night in, in Scotland, although I appreciate many US hotels have larger rooms) and, given the massive walk-in cupboard with two luggage holders for storing our suitcases and hand luggage, I found the room spacious and not cramped at all. Nice sized bathroom with toiletries and bath salts as well as the renowned rubber duck! I also chose from the pillow menu the next day. I knew there was no air conditioning as it is listed against all the information you read about this hotel, e.g brochures, Tripadvisor, net info and hotel website so It's really not a surprise. We found the ceiling fan to be sufficent in October. We never had to wait long for a lift/elevator and I never noticed any shabbiness in the bedroom or public areas which other guests have remarked upon (and our visit was some time ago before renovations). Maybe I am lax in choosing not to inspect every surface and drapery looking for minor flaws but I was on holiday and it all seemed ok to me.The location is spot on, right next to Union Square and 2 cable car routes. It's not far to walk to get onto the various bus routes either, Susan at the Tour Desk told us the buses we needed to get to Golden Gate Park for example. She also booked our return transport to the airport. We received two complimentary $5 cable car postcard passes on check in, but as we purchased the excellent value $18 3 day muni passes, we kept these as souvenirs. I loved riding the cable cars for fun as well as for getting places. We found the people very friendly and the city very cosmopolitan, I was surprised how much at home I felt. Had a lovely boat trip on the Bay under the Golden Gate Bridge and a separate ferry trip to Alcatraz which is unmissable - make sure you get the audioguide tour. An ex-inmate Darwin Coon was signing copies of his book on the day we visited Alcatraz and answering questions - an unexpected bonus.The hotel does a nice breakfast and we used our 10% discount coupon given at check in for this. We also had to visit Sears Fine Foods next door given the high recommendations it receives but I found little difference between the two. We also had a good value breakfast at Lefty O'Doul's two blocks away and enjoyed visiting this bar at night too. Met some very interesting people! Alicia at the bar at the Chancellor was attentive and my husband had a few drinks here through our visit whilst waiting for me to get ready oh and to watch the sports on TV. Various complimentary foodstuffs and tea/coffee are available in the lobby although we never took advantage of these due to eating so well. Location wise we much preferred the city centre location as compared to Fisherman's Wharf (an easy cable car ride away), plus you can walk lots of places, Chinatown is not far, and we used the buses, cable cars and streetcars to go further afield. I had added San Francisco to our trip after deciding against Hawaii and it went from being our third choice city to first place. I definitely left my heart in San Francisco and can't wait to go back. And we will be very disappointed if we don't get a room at the Chancellor.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>