<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="8877648de96741f0fb20db27a2ef2829" url=""><![CDATA[Negatives outweigh the positives My wife and I stayed at the Stanford Court with two other couples for three nights prior to a week's visit to the wine country in northern California. On balance, although the hotel does have some positive features, our collective opinion was that the negatives outweighed the positives.On the positive side: great location on Nob Hill just a half block from the intersection of three cable car lines. The staff is friendly, professional and helpful. The public areas and Fournou's Oven (the restaurant) are attractive and comfortable.The guest rooms were quiet during our stay,although the hotel appeared to be full. But the negatives: all three of our rooms were TINY with no views whatsoever. My wife and I were using Marriott rewards points for our stay, but the other two couples were paying regular non-discounted rates, yet all three of us commented on these being perhaps the smallest hotel rooms we have stayed in in many years.The entrance to the hotel is not on the street, but set back in an attractive courtyard. Traffic was frequently congested in the courtyard and there were sometimes long waits for taxis although there were numerous free taxis passing by on the street outside of the courtyard.TV reception was barely adequate on old TV sets in our rooms. There is no free internet connectivity, although there is an option to purchase a high speed (not really) connection through the iBahn system in the room for $9.95 per day. Like all Marriott properties, this is a totally non-smoking facility. One may view this as either a plus or a minus, but smokers are relegated to a dark corner of the courtyard where a few ashtrays and seats are provided.On balance, especially because of the tiny rooms, we would not stay here again on our future visits to the San Francisco area.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>