<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="8f65f6b7283fbac07fa72d931d201419" url=""><![CDATA[Good location and lovely rooms We only had one night sadly, but our room was lovely and the hotel was surprising easy to find. Even though we arrived at 11pm, we were offered a welcome drink, which sadly we had to decline as we were in a hurry to go out and have dinner. The location is good - about a 10 minute walk from the Born area and close to the Ramblas etc. Good shopping nearby if you like that sort of thing - including a large zara.Only thing not so good was the lack of breakfast. Confusingly, there was a menu in our room mentioning a terrace and breakfast, but when we left the next morning and asked at reception (I think it was a maid on duty) she just said 'no breakfast'. So we found a hotel cafe nearby. Was a shame to leave on a bit of a downer like that so for that reason I'm not giving it 5 marks.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="62aa44cad8e235682bd9a405d83a8cef" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel but location not so great The Mandarin is a great hotel but the location does let it down. Whilst for business guests I guess this is not so much of a problem, but for tourists who have a few days, I would not recommend this place so much unless they got to grips pretty quickly with the transport options.Hotel itself, cannot fault. We didn't get any Molton Brown toiletries that I read of in one review - maybe this is just for Club guests? Incidentally the hotel tried very hard to flog this option to us - it just didn't seem to make economic sense. The breakfast was wonderful but we found the restaurant prices obscenely expensive. Made the mistake of eating at Mortons one night (we'd left it very late to eat, our feet hurt too much to go out and it was the only place that would take us at 1030pm at night in the hotel) and I was shocked by the rip-off prices. S$ 20 for a Martini, when you can get a fabulous one with views to boot at New Asia Bar at the Swisshotel for S$12? S$35 for one tiny crab cake? I refused on principle to order a main course as I felt that to charge those sort of prices for something that would cost a quarter of the price outside was taking the michael. Service was annoyingly American, with waiters wanting to 'present' the menu to us instead of just letting us read the menu! Next thing they will be giving a slideshow. Plus they never let us alone for a minute. Not the place for a romantic dinner.The concierge was not well informed on bus routes - I guess he is more used to helping business guests and hailing cabs. We wanted a bus to the Orchid Gardens and was told that there was only 1 bus that didn't quite go as far - not true. Luckily the bus driver helped out and put us right. There's a bus that takes you right there BTW.This leads me to the location. Not great for tourists. Whilst you can walk, in the sapping heat that's not always an option. City Hall MTR is about 10 mins away and not much use if you want to go to Chinatown or the Quays as this involves a nightmare change at Doby Ghaut. My recommendation is to go across the road and get a bus from Esplanade Mall. The bus maps are easy to work out, they are cheap, and air conditioned! First 2 days we used taxi, then graduated to MTR, but finally worked out the buses were the best way to go. There are loads of buses that go direct to Orchard Road.Next time we visit Singapore, we'd choose the Fullerton. Great hotel in a very central location.Don't bother going to Raffles for the Singapore Sling - what a disappointment and waste of money! DO visit the Swisshotel on Stamford Road and head to New Asia Bar for great cocktails at sunset. We enjoyed Clarke Quay area very much at night, and had the most wonderful brunch at Marmalade Pantry in the Palace Renaissance mall on Orchard Road. Shops don't open until around 1030/11am, so it's great to go there for a late breakfast before the shops open.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4f5b1de2d1a1c4f64aa3f4611e4fbc19" url=""><![CDATA[From Hero to Zero ... terrible experience on my second visit. Never again! Having stayed here previously, and rated it a 5 out of 5, I was looking forward to my second visit. Unfortunately it was a disaster and I checked out this morning feeling angry, tired and ripped off. I have tried to be proactive by attempting via Hotels Catalonia's 'Contact Us' section of their website, to complain, but quel surprise it does not want to accept my message.I checked out of the Catalonia Avinyo this morning at 9am. The bill was some Euros 394 and I had a Euro 500 note which I wanted to pay the bill in cash with. The girl on duty said she only had 50 Euros in change and refused to get change from elsewhere to help me. I did not want to use my credit card, incurring extra FX and commission charges, when I had the cash. She claimed the barman had no money either - I do not believe this as I was kept awake by the noise from the bar. I cannot seriously believe that a hotel chain of their size would not keep an adequate sum of cash in the till. We reached a stalemate as she refused to contact anyone to help get change (when I asked to speak to the manager, she said she was on duty and therefore was the manager). She refused to deduct a small amount of Euros (I asked for a discount of 4 Euros) from my bill to compensation for the FX charges I would incur paying by Amex. She suggested I go out into the street and look for change! Knowing full well that banks were closed. I had to get a cab to the airport so unfortunately had to pay by credit card. I left feeling disgusted.I find it hard to believe this hotel would only have 50 Euros available in cash onsite, including bar takings. Is this a con to force us to use credit cards? So my first warning to travellers is to make sure if you pay in cash, you have the right change!The above changed my rating from the 3 stars I had planned to give, to 1 star (ideally I would give none).The room this time was awful. Room 101 (literally). The first floor is actually a mezzanine, so opens down below to the lobby and bar area. This means it's very noisy. There was no window, just a window that gave on to the corridor. Pointless, as to ensure privacy you had to pull those curtains to stop passers by looking in. For Euros 150 it was not worth it. The noise from the bar kept me awake most nights until around 1am. This morning however, I was woken at 430am this morning by loud talking, followed by screaming and shouting from the reception area. This continued until 6am. I was too frightened to go down and investigate/complain as the shouts were very threatening. When I raised this issue on checking out, the duty manager stated it was noisy people outside the hotel. I do not believe this as I clearly heard them in the reception area taking cans from the vending machine and in any case, should the external doors not have been be closed at that hour of the morning, to ensure the security of guests? Finally, 2 Euros for minibar - not used - was added to my bill and in my distress this morning (lack of sleep plus the discussion about the change) I did not spot this until I had left.This was my 2nd visit to the Avinyo, and my last. The location is great, but there are lots of hostels and pensiones in the same area that I am sure could offer a clean room at half the price.If you do stay here, avoid rooms on the 1st floor as there is no protection from the noise, both from the bar and lobby, and any users of the internet. Room 101 is actually the room closest to the outside area, so that in particular should be avoided.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="679c1d6501cf96df611b6931a2b05413" url=""><![CDATA[Superb location, smallish rooms but can't ask for more This misses out on full stars because our room/floor felt very smoky. From what I understand, you are asked to not smoke in bed but this doesn't mean you can't smoke, so try and ask for a n/s floor.That apart, the location cannot be faulted. Less than 5 mins walk from the west exit of Shinjuku and just across the road from Kabuchiko.Rooms were compact (hard work getting 2 suitcases in) but as always clean and comfortable. A good choice for Tokyo.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>