<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="a30e139bb5f2b4efb8644b49a41c9b9c" url=""><![CDATA[Decent hotel The Marriott is a good, decent choice in the Fisherman's Wharf area. The hotel is centrally located in the wharf, but away from the main street. Close enough to waterfront, but away from all of the noise. Also close to the cable car turnaround. The Fisherman's Wharf area is very touristy, with the atmosphere of a seaside town more than a big city. The hotel staff was friendly and helpful. The rooms are decent and clean, but, could definitely use some updating.While not the most luxurious hotel around, it is a solid choice and would recommend it if you get a reasonable price.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0d51f5583282414d0146750b7e0f3a30" url=""><![CDATA[Loved the Place I recently stayed at the Arizona Biltmore 12/4/04 - 12/8/08. This was the second time that I stayed at the Biltmore. This is one of my favorite resorts. I think that the hotel and the grounds are beautiful. I loved the Frank Lloyd Wright type architecture and the grounds were well-manicured. Yes, the grounds are a little confusing at first with the buildings sprawled around the property, but you get the hang of it really fast. The resort has a lot of comfortable areas where you can just sit and relax, maybe read a book of just people watch. The weather was lousy during this visit - 50 degrees and raining for four straight days - but the resort is comfortable enough so that you don't feel trapped in your room. They also run a shuttle to the Biltmore Fashion Park right outside of the hotel. Be warned that the shopping area is outdoors. The room was large and comfortable and nicely decorated. The bathroom had a double sink. The room may seem dated if you are not a fan of Frank Lloyd Wright, but the decor is appropriate to the theme. The pool area is great. The pools themselves are large and there is a water slide. Unfortunately, on this visit, the weather prevented anyone from using the pool. On my last visit, the pool area was quite crowded on the weekend when it was 100 degrees. However, there are othere pools around the resort that are not as crowded and much more quiet. I found the staff to be friendly and extremely helpful. The concierge was great with sightseeing suggestions and directions. I ate the cafe for lunch a couple of times and was able to order items that were not on the menu.Overall, I loved the resort and would definitely stay there again. A couple of minor negatives that I will mention. I thought that the spa area was small for a resort of that size. The locker room was small and the indoor whirlpool, sauna, and steam room all seemed cramped in too small of a space. Also, the resort will tack on several charges to your daily rate. There is an automatic $3.00 per day housekeeping charge and a one-time $10 bellman charge. Also, expect anything that you buy on the resort grounds to be twice the amount that you would pay outside.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="906ceec8ef9ab7310fbcf6b8126dd5cc" url=""><![CDATA[Enjoyed my stay at the Hotel Arts I stayed at the Hotel Arts for a business conference at the beginning of March 2005. The hotel is very nice. The decor of the public areas is modern looking - more like a W than a Ritz Carlton. The staff is very nice and helpful and just about everyone spoke English - particularly the front desk staff and concierge. The staff was helpful in giving directions, recommending activities, and they arranged an 5:00 A.M. taxi to the airport. The location of the hotel is away from the main tourist area, but only a short cab ride away. If you are in decent shape, you can walk to La Rambla in about 20 minutes. I would imagine that during the summer the location is very attractive, being right on the beach. Unfortuantely, it was very cold during my stay (it even snowed one day). The rooms were very nice. I stayed in a regular room which was extremely large by European standard. However, it did take me a while to figure out the light switches and, even with all of the room lights on, it seemed dark in the room. The rooms could use a little sprucing up. The rug looked like it was a bit ragged. However, all in all, I would say that the Hotel Arts is a wonderful hotel and would not hesitate to recommend staying here.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f29b2e2208aa3e8bf26ccae7222ae09c" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel I recently stayed at the Hyatt at Fisherman's Wharf. The hotel has recently been renovated and the room are very nice. Blues and browns with modern wood furniture. The bed was comfortable. The lobby was nice, but unimpressive. The hotel also has an outdoor pool and hot tub, but I did not get to use the facilities as it was too cold.The hotel's location is in the center of Fisherman's Wharf and convenient to the cable cars and other transportation to the business district of San Francisco. There is a supermarket and a drug store a block away from the hotel.The staff at the hotel was very nice. The front desk staff was very pleasant and welcoming. The bellmen were helpful, arranging transportation for me to a business meeting outside of the city. The hotel has a sports bar/restaurant - Knuckles. It is said to be a historical location. The food was good (although not great_ and the service was very good. Generally, its burgers, sandwiches, and the like, although there are some higher-end offerings.All in all, if you are looking for a nice hotel in the Wharf area of San Francisco, I would recommend this hotel. It is much nicer than other hotels that I have stayed at in the Wharf area. The only caveat I will mention is that the Wharf is very touristy and reminds me of being at the Jersey Shore (which I quite enjoy also). If you are looking for a more upscale area, stay in Nob Hill.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="338d9de0f17f785d35b0e61836bb34b7" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel I recently stayed at the W Seattle. I was hesitant at first to stay at this hotel as I am not fond of the trendy hotels. At this price point, I usually prefer hotels such as the Four Seasons. However, I needed to stay here to meet with business colleagues. I was very pleasantly surprised with my experience. I loved the hotel and would definitely stay here again when returning to Seattle.The hotel has a very modern, hip look and feel. The rooms were very nice and spacious. They had a very comfortable feel to them, especially the large sofas against the windows. The staff was very pleasant and accomodating. The front desk was very welcoming. The blow dryer in my room was not working. When I alerted the front desk, it was replaced immediately. I ordered room service the first night. The food was good, and was delivered promptly. I liked the extra touch of the candy Nerds that were included in the delivery. I also ate breakfast and lunch at the hotel's restaurant. Again, the staff was very nice and service was prompt and efficient. The location of the hotel was central to everything. It is a few blocks to the Seattle Art Museum and the marketplace. It was within walking distrance to the monorail to the space needle and also to Pioneer Square. If you are looking for something fun and unusual to do, there is a great underground tour in Pioneer Square. The only negative to the location is that the area is quite desolate at night and there really is not much nearby except other hotels and office buildings.All in all, I really enjoyed my stay at the W Seattle and would highly recommend staying there.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>