<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="62e13fb40f4c0fcaf319b9033bde056b" url=""><![CDATA[Just OK for the price My family and I stayed in a Mediterranean Suite for 3 nights, and to begin with the location of Le Meridien is truly excellent--close to sightseeing spots and metro stations!But other than that a few problems occured:The telephones in the room were out of services and were not fixed. The suite lacked a plasma tv--a very mediocre CRO TV with poor video quality. The furniture in the room was worn out!Concierge was not properly staffed.Fairly friendly staff thoughThe terrace of the suite is a big plus--especially nice with sunny conditions.When you are paying 500 Euro or so for a night, one would surely expect more from the hotel--probably the room amenities and decoration would be better in the renovated rooms--but still no excuse after the hotel has undergone a 30 million Euro revamp!Overall so so experience, might try H1898 just next to Le Meridien next time.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="47edbbebb37ad11209801c3d016e50be" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic stay! Having stayed at the rather pleasant Alfonso XIII in Seville two days ago, my family and I were equally happy during our stay here. We booked an Executive Suite--very spacious with--finally a plasma TV in the living room!! Quality bedding and excellent view!The only criticism of the room is the poor quality of woodwork--closets, door locks were poorly maintain and we all really struggled to get in and out of the bathroom every single time! Concierge was very helpful and always fully staffed.The restaurant--La Rotonda--simply fantastic! We had an Opera Brunch on Sunday, truly amazing experience!Overall a very nice stay here and will definitely stay here again!N.B. The room service menu is severely over priced---we were charged 30 euros just for a club sandwich!Also Westin charges 170 Euros for a 50 minute in-room spa--what a rip off!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>