<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="0016cab0c5460807a896ab15e42730d5" url=""><![CDATA[Miami Int'l Airport hotel Our flight into Miami was very late on 3/17, we had reservations at the Miami Int'l Airport Hotel. Check in was very quick (it was 2:00 am). The room was nicely decorated, but was very small. With two large suitcases and one carry on, we basically had to climb over them to get to the bathroom. There was also a running water noise all night long. When we opened the wooden shutters, the view was of the top of the buildings air conditioners. Check out was very quick, and easy to catch a cab. It was about a $24.00 taxi ride to the Port of Miami.This hotel is OK for a short layover, but for $157.00 I really expected a little more room. And the fact that some of the rooms had padlocks on the outside of the doors made it kind of creepy. I was wondering what I had gotten us into! They did have a security guard sitting in the hallway which also made me wonder...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e040d2d31b4616b2fd86089d9aa2bfac" url=""><![CDATA[Hyatt Regency Miami We stayed at Hyatt on 3/25 after a cruise on Carnival Valor. We had stayed here last year as well. Taxi fare from the Port of Miami to the Hyatt was about $27.00. We had early check in with no problem. We were in room 2230 which had a bay view. The first thing we noticed was there were no chairs on the balcony like last year. The sliding door was also stuck and we couldn't open it. We called the front desk to request both chairs for the balcony and for the door to be fixed, they sent some one up within an hour to fix the door. I also asked this person about the chairs. We spent the afternoon over at Bayside Marketplace, came back several hours later and still no chairs! There was also no ice bucket liner (there was a hair inside the bucket), and no ashtray (in a smoking room). I went to the front desk in person this time to ask for chairs, a liner and ashtry. In about 30 minutes the liner and ashtray arrived, and the guy said he was going to go get some chairs for the balcony. Well, we checked out at 6:00 am for our flight and we still hadn't received any chairs for the balcony, and the person at the front desk didn't bother to ask how our stay was. Luckily I had reserved this room at a discounted rate through Working Advantage for $135.00, but was still disappointed in the lack of service in comparison to last year. The room rate listed on the door was $559! They've got to be kidding!Don't get me wrong, the hotel is not horrible by any means, but I'm not so sure I will stay at the Hyatt on our future trips to Miami. They have put up three new condo's or hotels nearby since the last time I was there that you don't have a great view of the bay any more. And chairs for the balcony seem hard to come by ;)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eee97c66c0323278b12dff2bca45a827" url=""><![CDATA[Hyatt - Miami My daughter and I stayed at the Hyatt for one night before our cruise, we chose the location because it is very close to the cruise port (about $12.00 taxi ride). The hotel was very clean, with plenty of room. Ice and soda machines in the hallway. The pool is small but was nice and clean. This hotel is in the financial district, there are no stores / restaurants close by, lots of traffic since there is a convention center attached to the building. The hotel food was way too expensive for our budget (pancakes $14.00, orange juice $4.00, bacon and eggs $22.00). We got a reduced rate on the room (rack rate was $339.) through Working Advantage for $135.We would stay at this hotel again, but would have lunch before getting there and bring breakfast items for the next morning ;) I'm sure it would be perfect for the business traveler with an expense account.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>