<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="ff0551f1184f1fcfb08cae1bda2ed198" url=""><![CDATA[Great Rate off the beaten path. TV Tower
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3453cfb24b5f8877d9375da9fcd51bbd" url=""><![CDATA[Location is top notch This is truly a great hotel (and you pay for it). For travelers it is in an ideal location for NY. Right there at Times Square.Check-in:Quick and efficient (after we figured out my boss had all the rooms under his name).Room:I had a large king room (3628) that had a nice couch also. Everything worked fine and I was very happy. I didn't have a view but I did give up a room that had a view but was close to the elevator.Bathroom:No problems here either. Hot water right away everyday. Soap, shampoo and all the other stuff they give you.Price:Out the roof. This is one expensive hotel. Paid around $500 a night for a busy week in NY.Checkout:They screwed up here and charged me internet all 3 days. Easily fixed.Bars:They are all over. 2 on the 8th floor and the revolving on the top of the hotel which was cool for 1 night.Internet:16.95 a day with unlimited calling. There is no free internet anywhere in this hotel that I could find. Even the wireless you had to pay for in the lobby. The only free internet was to printout boarding passes.One strange thing are the elevators. You have to push you floor and it tells you what elevator to take. I guess it is quicker then just hitting up or down. Overall just a really good hotel. Yes you pay a lot to stay here but pretty much all the hotels in NY are just expensive. If it was on the company tab again I'd definitely stay here.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="04c590e632e571cd40c8431b0a937816" url=""><![CDATA[Horrid service. Bath
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="07991602efe91e61bb3fc8db42af2fb4" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel with good location Bed
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f739cece571ea48a475b474f01dcdf08" url=""><![CDATA[Great location but loud! Soaps
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>