<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="493b81483009b2ad4011f4a0398fc17a" url=""><![CDATA[stay here only for value and location, not looks or luxury Let's face it: Hawaii is expensive. With all the major hotels being in the several hundred $$$ per night, Waikiki Wave is only slightly over $100. However, despite the boutique hotel logo and website appearance and a renovation (which i would just call slight remodeling), the rooms/facilities not cool or hip, and are nothing more than a 3 star standard---only it benefits from a great location (in the heart of Waikiki, you can't get better than this), and a smiling staff.The rooms are spacious (2 queen size beds) but the decor is pretty pathetic. maroon printed carpeting, furniture that shows wear, dark bathroom, etc. The room is clean enough, but not 5-star pristine. Bathroom has yellow lighting, is cramped, and feels claustrophobic. Mirrors have some fingerprints if you look carefully. The one bonus is that the linens are extremely clean and there is no gross puffy bedspread that you fear will never be washed---instead there is a waffle weave blanket sandwiched between 2 flat sheets --- brilliant. There is NOTHING romantic about this room. I would not recommend this for couples looking for a fantasy getaway b/c you will be disappointed upon seeing this room. Instead, splurge the extra $$$ and go to the Halekulani Hotel which is just breathtaking.I would recommend this place to groups of budget-conscious friends (not couples) looking for an inexpensive place to stay---a clean bed and a place to crash. You cannot beat this location as it is close to everything--as i said, it's in the heart of this area and everything is within walking distance--shops, the beach, other hotels, etc.No need to visit the pathetic pool which is *shudder* out by the parking garage. it is a sad, wading-pool-like small triangle of water that hasn't been skimmed in weeks. The gym was being renovated at the time so the staff gave me access to a 24-hour fitness (which faces Waikiki beach), only a 10 minute walk from the Waikiki Wave. Staff is typical Hawaiian, accommodating and nice, pretty good service, no attitude.If looking for a nice beach restaurant, i recommend the Hula Grill which is above Duke's Restaurant. This restaurant overlooks the beach from the 2nd floor and at night is quite romantic. PROS:-budget friendly-awesome location: close to beach, food, shops, etc.-clean beds and linens-nice staffCONS-rest of the room is um...motel-ish but not overly gross-not romantic for a vacation getaway-feels cheap
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c75f0f61eb1cb4d26c89e0a5cd28f22a" url=""><![CDATA[Shameful, shady bribery racket going on despite wonderful rooms Despite a dreamy, marshmallow bed and room that meets all standards (you get what you pay for, this property aint' cheap!), I was truly disappointed with the shady operation that is blatantly going on with the employees that work there, and i want to bring this to your attention. Outside the hotel there is a taxi line for the airport. The valets will let you bypass the line and immediately you a taxi if you slip him $5 or $10. If you don't give him anything, he'll tell you to wait in line (which takes a long time). If this doesn't seem so bad yet, wait --- the TAXI DRIVER then has to surreptiously slip him $10 for the privilege of getting the long airport ride! These valets are raking in a cool $15-$20 per taxi customer, and given the high activity level of this Marriott, these guys are raking in $$$ per hour at while taking advantage of the customers and taxi drivers, all off the books.My colleague and I carefully watched this all unfold while we were outside: Valet in top hat greeting a customer, see him get a bill, and the valet pretends that this tipping customer has a reservation. A taxi will pull up, and the valet will say what's your name again? in front of all the poor people waiting in line, and then lead the customer into the taxi. The Valet leans into the Taxi driver's window to give directions and slyly gets his take. When we got in the taxi, the driver admitted that he paid the valet. We asked him why, and he said he had no choice. if I don't pay, they'll get the next taxi to pay up. We need the money and the long ride to the airport is important to our salary. The cops know about this bribery racket but haven't done anything about it. He also added that sometimes the price is $15 to get an airport ride.Now you may shrug at all this, but what does this have to do with your stay? Not much, maybe. But it says a lot about how this Marriott treats customers after they exit the property, after paying $350+ a night to stay there. It leaves a bad taste in my mouth.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>