<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="cf08859154052c3c8f8b1c7fa367c0dd" url=""><![CDATA[Overall nice resort... I went with my just the two of us for a relaxing vacation. Over all this resort was very nice. The grounds were kept very beautiful. The beach was well kept, although with some seaweed in the way. **The main issue we had was the time-share agents. I think they were being paid on commission; they simply would not leave us alone. This one guy would show up everywhere we went in the resort. Even the beach!! We found this to be the main issue, because we came there with the intentions of relaxation and unwinding from the stresses of NYC. I even had to call the guy a stalker because I felt he was. We tried to be nice at first and explain that we were not interested in buying or looking at the time-share properties. They made it seem like it was a necessity to set up this appointment to see it. Anyway, the resort restaurants where very good. The seafood dinner happened to be our favorite. We did find a restaurant called the Los Dos, which wasn't listed as a dinner restaurant. It is for couples only, a very nice outside area, close to the Dominican restaurant. They had a very good Lobster appetizer. The buffets were pretty good, variety. Lots of flies so I became picky about what I chose, they should have more nets or covers over the food because of this problem. I tried to get things as they were placing them out, to ensure the food was ok to eat. The set up with the three trains was a cute and good idea, however a couple of times we had to walk to our destination because of the trains breaking down. Hint sit in the back because of the smell of the train, really bad! Cute Flintstones characters, I got a pic with Fred! Cute for the kids. They staff was generally friendly and tried their best to speak English for us. The room was well kept, very pretty. You may want to bring your own pillow, the offer very little pillows for a king sized bed!We would go back to this resort, as long as the price was good, but it is not our first choice. We have been to D.R. once before, and the beaches are always nice and the grounds are always very well kept. They keep lots of landscapes and natural trees, which is nice for a resort.Contact me if you want pics or info. Thanks.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="216e1c6aa5879d8ccd7e34d77872b013" url=""><![CDATA[Never go back (My Fiance I stayed for 5 nights) They did not have our reservations, we had to buy a calling card, ended up not being able to use this card (only can use the cards in your room, not on the pay phones), used our credit card to call our travel agent to clear this matter up. Finally we got our room.The customer service was awful with this woman, and most of the other workers. I have never met a receptionist at a resort, that care about there guests. She obviously did not care if we stayed or left. Once getting to the room we noticed some problems with it. The remote for the TV was broken and two lights were out. We made many phone calls to fix these problems. We called three days in a row and kind of gave up. Each time they said they would come right away. They even had a card that hung on the door, for anything that needed repairs. We were to check off the problems and hang it on the outside of the door. That sign remained on our door all five nights we were there. They never came, and never fixed the problem. On the night before we left our building only, had lost all power from about 9:00pm-6:00am. So that night we could not leave our room because we had to use electronic keys and would be locked out, as well as being very hot in our room with no air conditioner. Finally on the day of check out, check out was noon, so we were there at 11:45 to check out and get a taxi to the airport. There were two people ahead of us. We waited in line until at least 12:30 to finally get waited on. I have never been anywhere that check out took at least 45 minutes. We simply get out of that resort fast enough. I ended up getting bites all over my legs, I thought it was mosquito bites, but later found it was more like bed bugs!! Gross, how dirty. Please protect yourself and do not stay here. We will not stay at the Barcelo ever again, and will not be back to D.R. any time soon!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>