<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="83f2a3fd217ce0caa94677631bf9dce1" url=""><![CDATA[loved EdenH edited review- Just returned on May 4th, we were there from April27th to May4th. This is about our 10th trip to Punta Cana. YES, we were very concerned about the previous reviews, Big Time. Yeah we got a good deal, so we went for the Paradise Club and hopefully in six months we can get the same deal - we will go back!Beach chairs - not any problems - they must have received the shipment.Just a note - we are not in our younger years (we both work full time, every day) and have a different agenda than a younger traveller (we used to be one). But just so you know, on our trip into the hotel we were with a young honeymoon couple that just loved it and had a great time!Problems with ala carte restaurant? - none- however we do not eat at 5:30 or 6:30, even at home we usually eat at 7:30 or 8:00, in fact I just cleaned up from our diner and it:s 9:35. Ala carte restaurants were perfect for us; first we didn't go until 8:30 or 9:00 and waited, at the most 15 or 20 minutes. No you are not in a smoke infested restaurant. I smoke, my husband doesn't, never has and in the ala carte restaurants there is no smoking. In the buffet they have a section for those nasty people.ALL of the staff spoke more English than any of the other resorts we have been to and worked extremely hard. They were more than happy to acommadate you and were very friendly.We enjoyed the casino, it's only $5 at the black jack tables and they serve drinks. The poor serve has to go outside to another building to fill her orders, they should have a service bar in the casino. We played every night, in fact closed it some nights. In the end my husband won a couple of hundred and I lost $55 - horrors!Our room was in building 1 and our room was 1272, second floor, with view of ocean and in front of pool. We were very near the beach, which is near the restaurant on the beach. You can sit and have a drink and eat, enjoy the scenery or be at the beach and come and eat :something. I can truthfully say that the food there was just okay, not great and the same all the time, but, hey, the surroundings were awesome and serene.The buffet has a different theme every night and just so you know - you will not starve.We did have one mosquito in our room at check-in and I made that little sucker disappear real quick. After about our 3rd day a can of bug spray appeared in our room, maybe we got someone else's, so I did spray the balcony, as not to waste it.They have a beach party on Saturday nights and boy-o-boy do they try
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>