<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="6321ea6c0d5e8444f1e460cc64f04d63" url=""><![CDATA[Less Than Impressed Stayed at the W Honolulu Diamond Head for one night in December 2008.Before I get to the meat of the review, I do want to say that the staff was friendly and outgoing. They seemed genuinely interested in helping and being pleasant.Despite that, I did experience a number of problems during my stay and even the friendly staff seemed to overlook things now and then.- On-demand TV quit on me. 30mins in to a movie I was watching, the on-demand stopped working. Just went to a black screen. Could not get it to work again during the rest of the evening or next day.- Room service item I ordered was uncooked (frozen, even!). I guess the soup I ordered is prepped and then put in the freezer, to be thrown in the oven when someone orders it. Seems someone forgot to throw it in the oven, though, and it arrived totally frozen. Not sure how that was overlooked. They replaced it, but offered nothing in return but the replacement (no extra entree or beverage or even credit on my folio).- The chair located at the desk in the room was disturbingly dirty. Maybe it was just the white upholstery that made it stand out that much more, but it was unappealing to the eye, to say the least.- TV picture quality was below average. Most channels were a bit grainy.- There were some errors at check-out with my folio (I am a Starwood Preferred Guest member and so earn points on stays at W hotels, and I was credited with an incorrect number of points and so had to follow up with SPG later on to get my missing credits).The above all left me feeling less than impressed, especially after having stayed at some incredible W properties in other cities. The physical property itself also feels fairly dated, and even ocean-view rooms are actually partially-obstructed ocean-view rooms, given other, taller, high-rise properties sit between the W and the water. So long as you're expecting that, there are still some decent views to be had (of Diamond Head itself, especially), it is close to the water and has a nice park in front as well, but you're not quite waking to the sound of crashing waves and a view of the blue ocean.Again, staff was very friendly and so I never got too frustrated during my stay. Only being there a single night, I just figured I'd be gone soon enough and so it wasn't too much of a bother. But had I stayed more than one night and continued to experience issues, it would have gotten old quickly. Further, the W is not priced in a way or located in a spot, in my option, that makes the occasional mishap worth dealing with on account of savings.With plenty of other options in Honolulu, I'll be passing on the W next time around.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f6796b8039b035c66298cfe6387076aa" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Stay At the Gateway Usually I'd not stay at an airport hotel unless airport access was key (such as an overnight layover or a quick business trip in and out of town) but some family matters had me traveling to Los Angeles and having to make last-minute plans not only for a room for myself but also for a couple of relatives for an extended (4+ days) stay. I chose the Sheraton Gateway because LAX would be an easy landmark for my relatives to find and LAX is somewhat central to the entire L.A. area (and I'd be driving all over, from Orange County to the Valley to the High Desert, Santa Monica and everywhere in between during my time in town).Check-In was a breeze, and I was upgraded to a suite (thanks to SPG status) that was extremely spacious. The entire hotel has received a rather recent upgrade, and the rooms are tastefully and quite well decorated with a modern feel. It had a large desk/workspace, sitting area with couch and two lounge chairs, king bed. Only aspect of the new, updated rooms that I found lacking were the bathrooms. They're nice and all, but pretty small. Your standard, hotel/motel-sized bathrooms. Closet was also small, but there was plenty of dresser space so that wasn't an issue for me.Wired and wirless highspeed for about $10/day. 24hr Room Service and just about everything I ordered while there was really good.The Starbucks in the lobby was extremely convenient and great to have handy when heading out for long drives to various relatives' homes every morning. It closes pretty early though so it's no evening hangout place.24hr Valet came in handy. The lobby bar was a relaxing place to hangout at night. Maid service was attentive (I don't morning maid service and told them my first day there that 3pm was a good time for them to come clean, and they showed up at or shortly after 3pm every day while I was there!) and thorough.I never once heard a plane take off or land while there, though my room faced the airport. So either I got lucky or things were insulated quite well. Proximity to the airport actually made for some real convenience, as freeways are very close (405 and 105). All in all, was quite pleased with the stay and the relatives I'd arranged a room for also were very pleased with the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="02f91fbf1d3ae5487da2972a62d1cf39" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, nice hotel Just wrapping up a stay at the W Hotel in San Francisco. It's been an extremely nice stay and I quite enjoyed the room.The W's location is great - very close to all the shopping, dining, etc on Market St. (if you're an SPG member and location is key to you, SPG has several properties all within a few blocks of one another around Market St. including Westin St. Francis, Westin Market St, St. Regis, W, and Palace Hotel and so you have a lot of really great options). I stayed in a high-floor Fabulous room which had ample space and a nice, large bathroom. As with some of the other Ws I've stayed it, some of the furniture was more stylish than functional/comfortable (such as the desk chair) but the bed and pillows were fantastic. Always tend to find great beds/pillows at Ws. Work space was very well done, with plenty of outlets and internet hookups conveniently located (I hate having to dig around a room looking for a place to plug your cell phone charger or laptop in to). The view from many of the higher floors is great, as well. I had a wonderful view of the surrounding city scape and bay.Depending on the time of night, things can get pretty crazy at the entrance to the hotel. Cars were backed up well down the street trying to pull in to the hotel's driveway as valet attendants scrambled around, but quite frankly as I walked around the neighborhood I saw the exact same thing happening at other hotels in and around 3rd St. and Market St. so I think that's just more of a San Francisco/Market St/Union Sq. issue than it is a W issue. Despite that, everytime I got my car out of valet it didn't take long at all (even if I didn't call down ahead of time).Room service was good. Didn't blow me away, but didn't disappoint, either. It was delivered in a timely fashion, though. I'd suggest requesting a table with your room service as most rooms don't have much of a seating area fit for dining. Lobby (Living Room) scene wasn't as wild and crazy as some of the other Ws I've stayed at (at the W San Diego there was a line down the street of people waiting to get inside to hang out at the lobby bar!), where it's like going through a nightclub on your way between the street and elevators but it was lively and obviously a popular place to hangout in nonethelessAll in all, a comfortable stay with helpful staff (all friendly and ready and able to give directions and advice on what to do and see whenever I asked for it).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bec1a9a49339da0bc9cd03a88a931b31" url=""><![CDATA[Great blend of classic and modern My overall impression of the hotel is no doubt influenced a great deal by the room I had during my stay there. I booked what was essentially a standard room for a recent business trip to Berlin but, upon check-in, was upgraded (thanks to Starwood Preferred Guest status) to a 1-bedroom suite, which was one of their themed suites (themed suites are individually appointed and decorated according to who they are named after, such as Bach or Goethe or other historical and artistic notables). The suite was large, wonderfully appointed, had a great deal of character and charm, and was ideally situated (fourth floor, right at the front of the building with a large balcony). Tons of closet space, wood paneling in certain areas, a huge bathroom (with dual sinks, walk-in shower, seperate bathtub, lots of counterspace, and a separate toilet area also with its own sink and a bidet), work desk, sitting area, yet more and more closet space, flatscreen TVs, minibar, and so on. Like the hotel itself, I found the room a great blend of charming and modern. They didn't sacrifice character for their recent renovations, clearly.Service throughout my stay was also very nice. Everyone spoke excellent English - likely better than my own, really - and requests were handled quickly, competently, and with a smile. The location of the hotel couldn't be better, either. It's just a block off of Unter den Linden, and just a short walk to the Brandenburg Gate, Museum Island, the Tiergarten, the Holocaust memorial, and other sites. There's plenty of shopping and dining nearby, as well as plenty of public transport options right outside the door.Dining in the hotel was quite good, and their breakfast was fantastic. Restaurant on the ground level was very nice also, and the lobby/foyer area at the base of the grand staircase was a nice place to hang out and relax, as well as meet up, with afternoon tea and snacks as well as a full bar.Given the experience we had here and the overall feel and service at the hotel, I found it to be quite well priced, as well. Would highly recommend the Westin Grand Berlin!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>