<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="d247c61765ce397b3e30f69a52007418" url=""><![CDATA[Great location for aquarium My daughter and I had the Hilton FAMILY PACKAGE which was a real deal! We got tickets to the aquarium, breakfast buffet, an in-room movie, snack bags of popcorn and little soda bottles. It also comes with a Discovery Kids backpack filled with a digicam and other little things. We had a great time!The walk to the aquarium and whale watching is super easy and then also a quick hop to Quincy Market. This hotel is excellently located for that part of town. (A cab to Copley Plaza was $8)Our corner room (1216) was a suite with living room, dining table with 4 chairs plus a king bedroom. We had some very nice harbor and surrounding views. The bed was plush and comfortable with lots of pillows. The bathroom was marble and excellent. I am now a big fan of the Crabtree and Evelyn La Source products that the hotel provided.We had room service for dinner and the table was perfect for that purpose. The margarita pizza was very tasty and the kid's pasta was hearty. The room has a wet bar which we didn't use.The breakfast buffet at Caliterra was perfect....lots of choices both healthy and decadent.I followed a GREAT tip from another tripadvisor post and parked around the corner at ONE and TWO INTERNATIONAL PLACE for $7 on the weekends. I was in at noon and out at 3pm the next day for $7.00. This was a huge savings and literally is a few minutes walk to the hotel.My only complaint is that the ventilation does let smoke smells come through. It was awful at times.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7e7da776c81306c3078c84cf6c71950b" url=""><![CDATA[Good, but not amazing. We chose the Westin Times Square specifically based on the good reviews here at Trip Advisor. We stayed for 2 nights in a Club level room (1424) which was a larger corner room. It does not have amazing views being relatively low on the 14th floor. As for city noises, it was quiet enough. We heard sirens every now and then but not regular traffic noise. The Club lounge (on 8th floor) is not extraordinary.......it offers a continental breakfast (only warm item was oatmeal) and then an evening hors d'oeuvres offering, which was much better. Free teas, coffees and soft drinks are available all day long. The location of the hotel is excellent........it really is in the thick of it, and maybe even too much for our tastes. Times Square was crazy crowded even just to cross through to get to other midtown locations. There are lots of dining choices, movie theatres and subway stations just out the hotel doors. We normally would stay at the Rihga but it is now The London and not family friendly any longer. We had 2 kids and this room had plenty of roll-around floor space for them. Each window had a window seat for looking out and they liked that. There is also one club chair and one desk chair. We ordered dinner room service and used the beds for seating purposes.Hotel parking = $45 per day......the steepest we have ever paid in NYC.My only real complaint is that the bathroom door is glass and anytime someone turned on the light during the night or early morning, the room was lit up as a result. I called for a night light but there were none. A night light would easily fix the problem. The double roller blinds do an excellent job of making the room dark.Enjoy your stay.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>