<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="41c193e46a2681977f0e79abfa203eda" url=""><![CDATA[Mixed feeling!! A group of 7 of us stayed in the radisson for a weekend recently. The hotel had many different advantages and disadvantages. The hotel itself is beautiful with great, friendly staff who are always willing to help. Beautiful rooms and bathrooms and the lobby is great. The location of the hotel is quite good. It is about 3 minutes from the red light district but far enough to be out of the way if you don't want to go near it. It is also about a five minute walk from Rokin/Damrak. Overall the hotel was quite disappointing. It was simply too expensive for what you got. The rooms were nice, yes, but for half the price you could still get a lovely room in any adjacent hotel. We had a drink at the bar one night and a double southern comfort and lime cost me 15 euros! Unbelieve considering it comes from the same factory as the southern comfort I would pay for at home....!! Proceed if you have a fortune to spend...!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1a3d01db62e9379b3e82e6be0c70081e" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic Hotel Overall I recently spent a week at the New York Helmsley Hotel and had a fantastic time in the hotel and in New York.On arrival to the hotel the staff were very helpful and friendly. There's always someone around to give you some help and advice at all times of the day/night. Every member of staff we met were very friendly towards us.We stayed in a twin room on the 31st floor with a fantastic view over 42nd street and buildings beyond (see my photos). The room was well equipped with flat-screen TV, comfortable beds, clean linen and a fantastic en-suite bathroom with plenty of towels, etc every day.Security at the hotel is fantastic with extra-safe security at night. Mindy's restaurant has excellent staff but the food is slight pricey for what you get. Harry's bar has a nice friendly feel and is not too expensive compared to other bars/pubs in New York. But obviously there's plenty of alternatives near the hotel instead if you wish!Location-wise the hotel wins me over again. Fantastic shops such as Gap are literally a minute away. Times Square is about a 10 minute walk and everything else is nearby. The Crysler building is literally opposite the hotel and The Empire State building is quite close too. We also walked from the hotel to 5th avenue to do a bit of shopping. It was about a 20 minute walk but there's plenty to keep you occupied on the way. The subway is very close to the hotel too so basically every area in New York is close to you!Overall I would rate this hotel 9.5/10 - it really was a great stay. The only downside would be Mindy's restaurant, although we only had breakfast in there. If you're planning a stay at the New York Helmsley Hotel, you won't be disappointed!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>