<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="b5a740fd13c84e3b318ba293238cdfcf" url=""><![CDATA[nice hotel We stayed for 2 nights as an extended family and had 2 rooms, on the 41st and 43rd floors. The rooms were nice, very large, although our agent had not requested non-smoking rooms and the 43rd floor was a little smokey (but my husband couldn't tell!). The pool is lovely, and there is a good choice of restaurants. We had breakfast in the hotel, which was very nice, and we ate in the asian restaurant there too, which was excellent. The hotel was incredibly busy when we were there (it was a national holiday), so the lifts were a nightmare - twice we took the stairs to the 39th floor and took the separate lift there after waiting for ages. However, in spite of this they sat us down at breakfast very quickly. The concierge staff were excellent, very helpful, and there was nothing wrong with reception either. We would stay there again definitely, and the location is perfect.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="16914a2edf1f22dff0754c0510ebcd2f" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect Location We stayed in a family room on the royal floor, which was perfect for 4 of us. The room was lovely, and very clean. Incidentally, no security problems as there was a safe in the room which we used at all times. The breakfast was not very good - only used for convenience! Not cheap, but not many places with family rooms in Barcelona.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="11c0c835d0b07605d25b8e57b7f7031f" url=""><![CDATA[lovely hotel We stayed in this hotel for 4 nights in August. We had no problems with the elevators at all - even though work was supposedly going on. We had paid extra for an opera house view - the weather wasn't great, so on balance I didn't think this worth the extra money. The rooms are great, and the breakfast was very nice! The hotel bar was fine - although it closed at 11pm which was a little strange (although it is in the lobby, so you can still sit there). The best thing about the hotel is it's location - you can walk to the opera house, the Rocks and lots of restaurants in about 5 minutes. Also the ferries, trains and buses are only 2 minutes away as well.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c1da14c05b8053fcc45cb8f019ce5661" url=""><![CDATA[great hotel The best things about this hotel are the location, the view and the rooms! All are perfect. We didn't eat in the hotel, but had a cheap and cheerful breakfast in a diner a few doors down. The rooms were well equipped and quiet, and the views from the 39th floor really good. The service was very good. The best thing is the location, walking distance to everywhere.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>