<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="423b2bea305d885cb092c66fdf989729" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Stay We (2 adults 2 kids) stayed at the Pacifica Beach for 10 days March 20 -30. I was somewhat afraid after reading the reviews here but we loved it and would stay again. We were in the Beach Tower (the tower closest to the beach) on the 10th floor with a partial ocean view. We really liked it. The view was excellent. The staff was excellent and very nice. The room was average with 2 beds. Carpet was dirty but that is to be expected with a light carpet and sandy feet. Other wise nice room with coffee maker and refrigerator. Water pressure in the shower was excellent. Water was always hot even when I was the 4th in a row to shower. Bedding, pillow, mattress were all good. Each room has a balcony so it was nice to drink coffee in the morning and watch the tourists take surfing lessons. Once you get out of the elevator, it literally is 45 seconds to the beach. The beach in front of the hotel is a nice swimming area. The area next to it is great for boogie boards since more waves. We had breakfast included with our room packagage and it is a great buffet with seating next to the HUGE aquarium which is cool. The in-room safe had a sticker indicating a $3 per day charge but we were not charged at all for 10 days of use. My only complaint is the parking is expensive--- $15 per day so $150 for the trip...almost as much as the rental car. Overall, a very nice stay and I would recommend it and I will stay here again. The front desk said that next month (April) they start a remodel. There is an ABC store right off the elevator in the beach tower and there is an ABC store on every block. This store has everything you need from snacks to alcohol to sandals and it is fairly priced....they could hose you but they don't for some reason. If you need a rental car for only a day or two, there is a Dollar Car Rental right in the lobby so convenient. Next time instead of renting a car for the whole stay and pay parking, I would only rent it as needed from the lobby since some days we didn't use it.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>