<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="54cae20e139f8a435828645c9c731ea2" url=""><![CDATA[still a pretty good value in New Orleans The Hilton Rvierside is a bit dated but still has all the comforts and amenities of a top business hotel. HIlton Honors (Silver and above) have free access to an excellent full service gym onsite including indoor tennis and volleyball. The location is wonderful, with easy walking distance to the French Quarter, The Arts (Warehouse) District, and the Convention Center. New Orleans has completely bounced back, at least in these areas and the financial district, and in fact, I found them even nicer than they were immediately prior to Katrina.The sports bar at the Hilton lacks local cuisine, on the menu, which was surprising. Drago's, the onsite Seaood Restaurant is excellent, much above the standard fare at normal hotels (though this should be an expectation in New Orleans).The staff was friendy and welcoming across the board. From check-in, to the fitness staff, to the restaurant staff, they made a long stay extremely pleasant.One minor thing to consider is the proximity to the train tracks and the river, which each bring a certain brief amount of noise (even on the 23rd floor) but this was not really a problem for me.This is my 5th stay at this hotel, and it remains my hotel of choice in New Orleans.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0e9960e0b93df888527b1671339de1ae" url=""><![CDATA[There is nothing not to like Although I typically stay at the Tokyo Prince, I stayed this time at the sister hotel, the Prince Park Tower. What a difference! I have an executive room with a beautiful view overlooking Tokyo Ginza. The food choices are superb. Executive floors have a dedicated set of elevators accessed by key card. The staff is friendly and attentive. The fitness facility is outstanding, albeit quite a walk. Be cautioned: Unlike American hotels, people typically dress in street clothes to the fitness center and change there. They look a bit askance if you wear your workout clothes in. They do have new clean clothes for you to wear while working out. They also have a full length lap pool (indoor and immaculate) and a wonderful natural hot spring. Internet connection is via LAN and no charge. The cable is in the room, thus avoiding those annying trips to the front desk (why some hotels do this is beyond comprehenshion). There are a number of wonderful sites within 15 minutes walk, including lovely shrines in Roppongi Hills and the Zojoji temple.The Dutch Embassy is very nearby. Tokyo Station is a 10 minute (1500 Yen) taxi ride. The bus from Narita takes appx 1.25 hours and costs 3000 Yen. Akihabara (electonics) district and Roppongi (party) district are both within 15 minutes public transit. Nearby shopping is high end, so with the state of the dollar, be forewarned.This will be my hotel of choice for all future business trips to Japan.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="332d05602d6ff1f3a41f80a4c9aba00a" url=""><![CDATA[Bed was worse than slow painful death In the interest of trying to save my company a couple of bucks, and because I am in A'dam all the time (working for a Dutch company), I tried the Botel. I cannot even describe the torture of this accomodation. First, they have you pay for the entire stay in advance (understandable after the fact). The room itself was adequate, though if you stay on the side facing into the city, plan on getting no sleep until at least 3:30 when the last drunken revellers make their way in. The shower barely fit me, and I am pretty small. And then there was the bed. I did not think it was possible to have a bed that uncomfortable. I booked 3 nights, and can honestly say that my last night, I did not even bother going back to the room. I had an early flight home and just spent the whole night walking around A'dam. I was tempted to check the rates in the Red Light district for just an hour's nap. The bed on the botel was torture. Worse than a Tijuana prison holding cell floor (further to which, I will not comment on my familiarity). In the interest of fairness, while the check-in was laboriously slow, the people were friendly enough. And it was fairly cheap. But I would never go back.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d4a3125cc36986e6dfe0b8195ecc8e96" url=""><![CDATA[A pleasant hotel with a few issues I have stayed a few times at the Victoria for work meetings, most recently last week. It is an older hotel and an Amsterdam staple. The staff is courteous and helpful. A couple of downsides: - The cleaning staff failed to remove empty bottles and cans on 2 different occassions from the room. If you don't put them in the trash can, they don't clear them. - The bathroom had a strong sewage smell every day. Not overpowering, but clearly noticeable. - The hotel restaurant food was not very good (at lunch and dinner). I spend a lot of time in Amsterdam and typically go to a select group of restaurants and avoid hotel food in general. This hotel reminded me why I do that. We had 2 lunches and a dinner at the hotel and all were sub-par.My room faced Centraal Station and was a bit noisy, but that is to be expected. If you want a quiet room, you should request that and get something facing away from the station. To rooms and common areas have WiFi and the connection is average. The price is a bit steep (I think about 15 Euro 24 hours). Eventually, hotels will have to recognize that free WiFi should be a requirement for business travellers.The fitness center is there, but is nothing special (and confusing to get to if you just try to follow the signs). The pool is so small as to not be worth getting in. I am not sure if there is an extra charge for use, as my company is Dutch and provides access to all amenities as part of our staying there. Better to get your excercise walking around Amsterdam if you have the time.On the plus side is the location. It is a 3 minute walk from Centraal. Can't beat that, particularly after a redeye flight. Note that there is a LOT of construction going on near the station, so that should be a consideration if noise is a factor. That said, it is no louder than a typical day in New York.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b3691e63fc6dd01b5074ffe20bbdca81" url=""><![CDATA[A wonderful hotel at a reasonable price I just left the Monaco and would say that this hotel has absolutely everything for the business traveller. Firstly, in all my years of travel, I have never come across such a friendly, welcoming, and inviting staff outside of Asia. That alone makes this hotel stand out from most US hotels. But there is much more to recommend it. The location is good for anyone staying in Seattle for a conference, or with a need to be downtown. The convention center is appx 10 miute walk, but conversely, it is closer to the waterfront and Pikes Place. The room was outstanding. The bed was large and luxurious, Internet (both wired and WIFI) available at no charge to guests and with a very good signal. The desk was adequate size for working and the room itself was not cramped. Paper at your door every morning. Good coffee (but then again, it is Seattle...).The gym left a bit to be desired, but it was adequate and what was there was new, clean and in great working order,and it was available 24 hours. And they did have a reciprocal agreement with a full health club nearby.The hotel has a bit of a funky vibe (complete with faux leopard-skin robes in the closet), but not so much as to turn off even the most conservative business traveller. In summary, I would recommend the hotel to anyone heading into downtown Seattle for any reason.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>