<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="0d7a914b0d9090fa07897bb6a642ce28" url=""><![CDATA[lovely hotel Just returned from a 10 day stay at the Bali Hyatt. We've had a wonderful stay there. The rooms are a little dated, but are still very comfortabel and clean. Our balcony had a great view over the hotel garden, which is magnificent. Breakfast is very good. The level of service is excellent and everyone is so friendly. I miss the Bali Hyatt already and would return in a heartbeat.Anouk
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0b8da2ce756d5c345e5c7f8febd22b34" url=""><![CDATA[great place We had booked for a beach room, which was a bit of a dissapointment. Very dark and with a bathroom that was not that clean. So we upgraded to a clubroom. This room was absolutely perfect and we highly recommened it to everyone. A great bed, perfect bathroom and a very nice terrace. Another plus was the beautiful clubpool. Overall this is a very nice hotel. Good breakfast, nice pools and a nice garden. Sanur has a few good restaurants (we loved Ming and Donald's) and bars .
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d1d8993d528d8db26cc63b3b7f7764ba" url=""><![CDATA[quite average Just returned from one week at the Legian Beach Hotel. Although we had a pleasant week, we'll probably never return to this hotel again. In Bali you can get much better value for the same (or even less) money. We had booked a superior cottage with a double bed, which in our opinion was awful. Because the room was situated in the middle part of the cottage it was very dark inside. The room was also very, very small and there was absolutely no privacy in the part of the hotelgarden we were in. We therefore decided to upgrade to a deluxe bungalow, which cost us 25 USD per night extra. Although the room was much more spacious and private (and very clean), it wasn't worth 25 dollar because of the fact that it was an exact copy of the superior cottage. No extra's at all, not in terms of amenities, nor in terms of service. The two pools are not very big, but quite pleasant. Breakfast was good. We had lunch in the hotel once (the pizzeria), and although the food was good, the service was very slow and not very friendly. There seems to be a lack of interest by many of the staffmembers, and that was what bothered me the most. We've been to Bali for 4 years in a row now, and stayed at many hotels, but have never encountered people who were unfriendly and not interested, until now. Better luck next time, but not at the Legian Beach Hotel.Anouk
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="20d1975710553ba0a395acebfda27e84" url=""><![CDATA[very nice hotel The NBH is an excellent hotel in balinese style. We had a superior room, which was nice and spacious enough. It had a very good kingsize bed and a nice balcony. The pools are great and so is the garden. We loved the spa pool. It was very peaceful there and very quiet. Breakfast was excellent. Although the restaurants are a bit expensive, the food is great. Overall just a great place to stay!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>