<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="51d2df42fc800b4983aac7d062d0b7c6" url=""><![CDATA[High in the Sky An interesting thing about the Conrad in Miami is that the lobby is on the 25th floor, and the concierge is on the ground lobby. Weird, I thought at first. But when you think about it, Miami is a high crime city, and I think by having you walk past the concierge and all the ground floor emplyees, and taking one of two elevators to the 25th floor, and then having to walk past the front desk and lounge to get to the only two elevators to get to the guest rooms; it is probably about security and quiet.The smallish bar on the lobby level was great, cool sophisticated and outdoor tables where you can look at the water while you have a cocktail. Great martinis.The continental breakfast in the restaurant was also very good. At lunch or dinner DO NOT order the Kobe hamburger. I have had real Kobe beef in Japan (which is why I ordered it) and this was not it. Maybe they meant Kobe like. It was also overpriced.The rooms was very nice, but a little smaller than I am accustomed to, but I guess it has to do with the high price of real estate in Miami. Hip modern decor, reminded me of the decor of the Beverly Hilton, but not nearly as fine, and the room is smaller. Good bedding with high count sheets, bathroom all granite and marble, very nice. I had a nice water view from (I think!) my room 1917.The exercise lockers were OK, not fabulous ,as was the pool. That whole area needs updating.The staff were very gracious and helpful. EXCEPT the concierge who was not dependable. I ordered a town car to take me back to the airport, and when I arrived downstairs at the appointment time, they were like who did you talk to? We don't know anything about this.Tip: free wifi, but ONLY in the lobby. They charge you for it in your room.Tip: ask for a waterview room, rather than a city view. Worth it.Tip: if you do anything with the concierge, write down his/her name and the date and time you talked so you won't have to be on the defensive if they do not deliver.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>