<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="b4117fe303aa2ff1f443ea516c528eb6" url=""><![CDATA[Riu Bambu Hotel (February 9 to February 23, 2008) My wife and I travel to a Riu hotel every year. We have stayed at Riu hotels in Mexico (Cancun, Mayan Riviera, Puerto Vallarta (2), Cabo San Lucas), Jamaica (Ocho Rios, Negril) and Punta Cana. Our first Riu hotel was the Riu Bambu about 8 years ago and we liked the beach and palm trees so much we decided to return.The weather was very good while we were there. It must have been around 90 degrees most days. We got rain on 2 mornings which lasted about an hour but it was sunny by 11:00 AM. It also rained on 3 nights (once during the night and twice around 9:00 PM which we solved by staying at the bar).I will rank the positives and negatives of the Riu Bambu versus some of the other Riu hotels we have stayed at.POSITIVES:1) One of the better beaches for sand and lots of palm trees2) We didn't have to wear a wrist band. Only the people at the palaces had to wear a wrist band. We were able to spend time at the Riu Tiano and Riu Naiboa at any time for drinks and eating.3) Entertainment was very good here although the Riu hotels need to change it up because we have seen most of these shows at other hotels. If you like to dance, this is the place to go. The entertainment staff have dance lessons at 11:00 AM and 4:00 PM every day (salsa, merengue and buchata). My wife was dancing at most of the classes. The Bambu is the most active of all of the 5 Riu hotels in Punta Cana. We saw many wrist bands from the 'palace people' at our patio bar at night as well as the dance classes and afternoon pool activities. We actually did an 'egg toss' on the beach one afternoon. The enterainment staff refer to the 2 palace hotels as cemetaries because they are so much quieter. 4) The hotel consists of 2 storey units with 6 units on each floor which may force you to walk a bit more but the grounds are very nicely kept up and it is enjoyable to walk around.5) Price. For the money, I don't think you can find a Riu where the prices are as good (except for Puerta Plata, but the beach won't be as nice)6) International flavor. There is a nice mixture of tourists here that you will not see anywhere else (Germany, France, Argentina, Hungary, Italy, Spain, Russia, USA and Canadians). This makes it alot a fun at night and around the pool area when they run the entertainment.7) Bar Service. They always had at least 6-7 bartenders at the bar each night. You didn't have to wait at all for a drink.NEGATIVES:1) Riu Bambu is an older Riu and the pool is nothing compared to the pools in the newer hotels (especially when compared to the new palace next door)2) I noticed that some of the food stations were not as efficient as other Riu hotels. I would go to get friut (melon or water melon) and there wasn't any there. I would go back later and it would be restocked. I noticed this at the beach restaurant for hamburgers and pizza.Deciding on which Riu to go to?If you are debating on which Riu to go to in Punta Cana, this might help. If you like a nice quiet vacation, go one of the Palaces. If you like to go to the specialty restaurants, go to the new palace, it has 5. If you like to be active, the Bambu is best choice. If you are under 30, the Tiano is the best choice and we found the Naiboa to be really quiet for the entertainment at night.Excursions:We have done most tours over the course of our travels so we decided to do the Altos de Chavon trip. We left at 7:20 AM and got back around 6:20 PM. The caves were really cool to see. We also went to a cigar shop and had lunch on a boat where Rambo was filmed. Altos de Chavon was a small village that was nice to walk around. I wouldn't rated this a my favorite excursion but the guide on the bus was great and we got to see some of the country side and the city of Hiquey.OTHER Travel tips:1) Always secure your table first when eating at the buffet. We saw lots of people walking around with a full plate of food, looking for a place to sit.2) Learn some Spanish, bring a book. We know enough Spanish to ask for things like utensils, a table and directions.3) Bring lots of $1 bills for tipping. These people work really hard and don't make alot of money. I was giving tips to our waiters so we had no problem getting a table at night and getting prompt service.4) Be prepared for your room to have 2 double beds.Overall, the trip was very good until we got to the Punta Cana airport on the way back. I can only describe it as 'utter chaos'. There was people everywhere lined up for all destinations on the Saturday night. The security for baggage check was almost none existant. The security person wasn't even looking at the monitor when our bags went through.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>