<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="94eb1403b5197cb51bb918de2a45237a" url=""><![CDATA[Definitely not 4* and really pushing 3* When we arrived our friends card key did not work and had no electricity due to this so they changed the room. The rooms were so HOT that although we live in Spain we found it unbearable and had to open the window and sleep all night everynight (four nights) like this even though it is November and the temperature outside was cold.. The noise was LOUD outside. We asked for the heating to be lowered but although they attempted it, it did not happen. Then we found our door didnot lock. We just pushed it and it opened! we spent ages each time we left the room trying to get it to stay shut - my husband went to the reception and the gentle man said 'this is Spain - things get broken ' my husband said 'could he arrange to have it repaired 'the reception said ' what was the point it would only be broken again!.The conversation went on in vain for at least another five minutes and never was repaired..Also the toilet syphon plunger didn't work we had to keep repairing it after use. Also the shower curtain rail came off the wall. Also the key to the mini bar lock wouldn't lock.Also the sink plug did not work so we had a dirty sink at all times. Also when the people upstairs had a shower - so did our bathroom and next doors! According to the concierge 'this is normal as it is Spain' We pointed out that we live in Spain and had never experienced this before in ten years of residence and he just smiled and shrugged. The bar was never open and a snack bar was not in existence - we could find no instructions as to the whereabouts of the breakfast room and just followed our noses. A dreadful experience all round not to be recommended.The only help we received was when we were leaving and an elderly gentleman on the desk assisted us with directions.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>