<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="17acbb7ddb30e5dcfd029cb39bae8ef5" url=""><![CDATA[Think twice before booking at Caribe Hilton My husband and I stayed at the Caribe Hilton from 8/15/08 to 8/21/08 and we were very disappointed. I had called the hotel 5 days prior to arriving, just in case, to confirm our reservation and let them know we would be arriving late (11:00 pm) and to request one king size bed instead of two queen size beds. They confirmed us for a late arrival and one king size bed. So naturally, when we entered our room (right by the elevators) we found we had two double/full size beds. Not king size, and even smaller than queen size! So my husband headed downstairs, spoke to the manager on duty and was told there were no other rooms, but that the next day they should have rooms become available and we would be switched to another room. He also said to just leave all our bags packed the next morning and staff would move our suitcases to our new room. So that night we slept in kid-sized beds, as best we could with the constant noise of the elevator all night long! It literally sounded like a roller coaster! The room itself was seriously out dated and abused. We weren't expecting luxury here, just a certain standard of cleanliness and care in the room. Very disappointed. The next morning we headed out and, just in case, stopped at the front desk to remind someone about our room change. No one knew a thing about it. No notes were left by the manager for anyone to follow up on. But they did change our room to one in the Hilton Honors tower. We thought that sounded great, but it still turned out to be less than what you would expect of a Hilton Hotel anywhere else. Again they put us right next to the elevators, but at least in this building you couldn't hear it. The room was......okay. Nothing great, just okay. There were stains on sofa and carpet, a hole punched in at the base of bathroom entryway (odd) and a leak in the bathroom ceiling that landed on the bathroom counter. (I had noticed a stinky wet towel on the counter when we arrived and figured the maid had left a dirty cleaning towel there by accident. No, the maid had left a towel there on purpose to sop up all the dirty water that leaked through the ceiling! I had to keep doing the same every day to keep my personal items from being soaked!) We didn't bother to change rooms again as I can't imagine that any of the other rooms in the BEST tower would be any different. Also, the parking is atrocious. Seems like the Normandie Hotel next door is quite the hot spot on Friday and Saturday nights, and they all park at the Hilton! So you can forget about parking on the street and or even in the hotel parking! Everyone parks there, hotel guest or not! We had no choice but to go with valet parking, and even still our car stayed exactly where we left in front of the lobby for about 2 hours because even the valets had nowhere to park it or even move it.The food and drinks at the hotel are overpriced, as expected. The pool definitely didn't look clean. The beach is okay, definitely not a Caribbean white sand and blue water beach....far from it!We really only picked this hotel because the location was convenient for our needs on this trip and because we figured (wrongly) that we could count on Hilton quality. If you require a clean hotel room with few visible signs of wear and tear, do not stay here. The lobby area is very nice, and deceiving if you think the rooms will be similar in quality. But the rooms are what matter to me, so I would definitely not recommend this hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>