<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="da510a30085c925f27e497e85a5234ec" url=""><![CDATA[Average Stay at the Helmsley Our arrival at the Helmsley was at about midnight and after 8hrs on a plane, were looking forward to getting to the hotel and grabbing a coffee or a bite. From outside it looks like something out of a film, very bling, if not a bit seventies.Arriving at the hotel: the doorman let us struggle through the door with our own bags, not a great start, and the woman behind the desk acted most upset that she had to deal with some customers. Her manner was poor, bordering on rude, when she laid down the law about how she would charge my credit card for potential damage to the room which, she was eluding to, was the 'approval' to see if the credit on the card was good. My faith in the hotel was falling.We asked if we could get a drink.... No was the answer. The bar was shut, room service was closed too and she didn't know of anywhere nearby to get a drink at that hour. By the way, we'd visited NYC before and knew that there would be somewhere - we just didnt know where in that neighbourhood and found somewhere a few days later.Our first room on the 19th floor, was cold, had broken heat, an even more broken door lock that took many to open (we went down to reception and it took 15min for anyone to show). The room was okay - broken hairdrier, good view, nice TV, great bed, though it was a little shabby. A call down to reception about the heat was ignored.Next morning we showered, in the cold (it was 13F outside so the room wasn't much more) and headed down to reception. We complained and was told that these issues would be resolved immediately. They weren't. Most of the reception staff didn't care and had to look up simple info like when the bar was supposed to be open etc.It took several more calls and a final visit to reception when the issue was finally escalated and we were moved to the 31st floor to a better (less broken) but smaller room with a better view.The new room solved most of the issues, though the doorlock was still intermittently faulty - a fault most of the other guests we spoke to seemed to agree with. The director also kindly sent a bottle of bubbly to try make it right which we appreciated and went some way to salvaging our trip.To be honest, we were so tired of complaining that we left the remaining issues outstanding as it was really spoiling our trip.Room service was dire at all times. Always at least 35+ minutes if you wanted just a coffee (no facilities in the room) and the bar regularly didnt have coffee (this is NYC for Christ's sake!). Lucky there were 2 starbucks within a block or two though it was very dissapointing not to be able to have breakfast in bed a couple of times or at least a drink before setting out.If you have to stay here, I'd recommend the mini market on 2nd ave (right out of the hotel, right again onto second and it's on the right). And for breakfast - also on Second Ave - the Townhouse Cafe had the NICEST staff and the food was great value. On the left hand side, a couple of blocks down on the left hand side of second.Conclusion. Wouldn't stay here. The Helmsley wasn't cheap and last year we paid a little more for the Hilton Times Square which was light years better in terms of facilities and service. Unless there's big improvements, I won't be staying here again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>