<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="531234747b4331e3c7e3c7ad89c56aa3" url=""><![CDATA[Be prepared to share your room with tiny strangers We have recently returned from Holiday Inn Walk of Fame, on Highland Avenue, Hollywood, LA. The best feature about the hotel is the convenient location a 5 minute walk from Hollywood Boulevard, where find such attractions like the Chinese Theatre, Walk of Fame, Hollywood Highland Shopping Mall, Wax Museum, Believe it or Not and Guinness Museums, and many souvenir shops and Capitol Records Building to name a few. The Hollywood Bowl is within easy driving distance, as is the Universal Studios Theme Park (about 10 mins drive).The room was very clean and tidy with just one very tiny exception not sure if this problem is common throughout the entire hotel but we definitely had literally hundreds of these crawling all over the bedside areas (including some which managed to find their way onto the duvet) and the window area was all full of them (room 609). Apart from this, the actual hotel itself was clean and tidy, and staff were also friendly. They do a free transfer to and from Universal Studios with the own Minibus, which is very handy. We found the hotel reception to be very average; not going to say they were rude like some other reviewers, because that was definitely not the case with us. The concierge is very friendly and approachable, the one to call if you want to book a tour/limo, want info on attractions, etc. He was actually more helpful than the reception. The other staff are also extremely helpful; they are very quick to bring you fresh towels or razors, etc, etc. There is public internet access downstairs, but you have to use a credit card for this, otherwise there are modems in each room for laptops. There is a gym which is nothing to get too excited about (a treadmill and a weight machine to be exact). The hot tub and pool are nice although it is only 4ft deep, meaning its child friendly. There is also a restaurant located downstairs but we use it bother when you have so many Italian pizza/pasta shops, Subway, McDonalds and Burger King within 5 mins!If you are arriving at LAX airport, then the best way to this hotel is by Airport Shuttle Bus, which costs around $11 pp, you can also book this method to return to the airport via the concierge. I noticed that a lot of the previous reviews mention that the lifts were faulty, but I can report that this problem is sorted now may be slow, but definitely safe and not noisy.I would recommend the Stars Homes Tour (Beverly Hills, Rodeo Drive and Bel Air), which lasts 2 hours and is definitely worth the money and of course, Universal Studios both of which are great fun for the full family.So, the best advice I can give if you are choosing this hotel is ask to see the room they give you BEFORE moving all your stuff in to avoid any unwelcome guests.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="326c07b92e60156d285bc318a36d8c28" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent location; decent hotel We chose the Metro Hotel on 35th Street street, as it was recommended by our Tavel Agent for it's excellent Manahattan location. The location is ideal - about 10 mins away from Time Square, literally round the corner from the Empire State Building and with the nearest subway only a couple of minutes away.Room were very tidy, air conditioned and are cleaned daily. The rooms include a TV and a safe. My complaint about the room is that we had a brick wall in our direct view from the window. Although the bathroom was well maintained, it is really small.The hotel has a nice 30s art-deco theme throughout. The restaurant is overpriced and it is better to eat from outside the hotel, as it is better value for money. The free daily breakfast is nice, and a good mix of cakes, breads, fruit, cereals and drinks are available. Reception staff can be approachable at times, but rude at other times, depending on how busy they are. Ideal only for it's location, but would consider trying out another hotel within the same area when i return to NYC.Approx times from hotel to:Empire State Building - few minutes walkTime Square - 10 minute walkGroundZero - 10 mins (subway)Madison Square Garden - 10 minute walkFifth Avenue - 15 minute walk
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>