<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="a1f8b495fc30ae6af22b30cc842b2f2d" url=""><![CDATA[Mezza Mezza I've stayed here several times and find the quality slipping from past visits. My room was very small and barely had room for 2 double beds. The furniture was cheap and damaged. The cleanliness here is definately lacking. I am a stickler for a clean room, and noted stains on the rug and mold on the bathroom tiles. My shower didn't drain properly to top off my overall dissatisfaction. I think there are many better choices in the neighborhood, including the Marriott Copley and Hilton Back Bay, which is across the street.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f7d45fc91ebe78a40781b67edfdc9ed5" url=""><![CDATA[Best Beach in Waikiki I just returned from an 8 night family vacation at the Hawaiian Village, including taking 2 teenage girls. The HHV is a very nice resort that exceeded my expectations.The HHV happens to be on the widest and best part of Waikiki beach. In fact, only a select few hotels have actual beach (usable) frontage. Hotels like the Sheraton Waikiki and Halekulani are impressive, but do not have a beach you can enjoy. Other hotels on the beach have only a sliver of sand and are crowded (Outrigger, Royal Hawaiian). If being at a full-service RESORT with all the bells and whistles and directly on the beach, then you can't go wrong by staying at the HHV.We stayed in the Kalia tower 10th floor, which was nice with confortable beds and a good-sized bathroom. Since we booked with Hotwire, we had no choice in room options, and could have been located at the discretion of the resort. However, we asked the front desk for room with a good view, and were happy with the selection. Our room was clean, and the housekeeper worked hard despite the best efforts of the girls to leave their belongings where-ever. Although we could see the constuction of the new Waikiki tower off to the right, it was never a bother. There was very little construction noise that we could hear..The hotel grounds, shopping an restaurant choices were all excellent. Food was available at all price ranges. We ate at Bennihana (food good, prices moderate), Golden Dragon (great food, but the staff rushed us), CJ's (nice breakfast), Roundtable pizza (teen best, pretty good pizza) and Tropics which sits on the beach (nice view, good music, lunch, strong drinks). The grounds also included an ABC convenience store where everything was plentiful and, yes, cheap. Lastly, the Wianna restaurant located across the street from the hotel offered a huge breakfast (good) at low prices.We loved everything about the HHV. The grounds were beautiful, the staff was pleasant and helpful. The choices of things to do were nearly endless. The girls especially loved taking surfing lessons offered through the hotel. We thought the Friday night Hawaiian show, including fireworks outstanding even at $12 pp. The Kalia tower also has a private pool that was away from the crowds. This was a better option for us vs. the super pool, which was busy.Sure you pay more staying here, but everything is expensive in Hawaii. Go the the Hilton. Be impressed. Make family memories that last a life-time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>