<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="81970fc0f164992b25af99f212fecba7" url=""><![CDATA[Dependable offering - close to airport - will stay again I travel to Phoenix for business about once a quarter for business and have stayed at this property twice now. Both times I have found that: -- The room was clean, and the photos on Travelocity etc are a true representation of what you get -- Rooms are a suite that I expect from Doubletree including separate sleeping area and microwave and small fridge -- The front desk staff is above average especially for an airport location -- The breakfast buffet was free and not very crowded (I only stay mid-week when families etc are not around like weekends)-- Parking was available and freeThe complaints on noise likely come from this location having open common courtyards - not a closed box design. I have really not had an issue though with noise. In my view this property is a safe bet for Phoenix airport stays - and I will use it again in the future for my business trips.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="71ab550f883834bb5e9320652006356b" url=""><![CDATA[Strong positive - a few tips Based on the reviews from others on this site we stayed here in early June (07) - and were not disappointed. Not much to add that has not already been said - so I will offer some local pointers for those that would like to stay here: 1. The Limousine Bus from the airport stops and picks up at this hotel which is great. This bus is an excellent way to get to and from the airport - as cabs are very very expensive, and if you have a lot of bags, using the subway can be a challenge. You can easily find the ticket counters @ the airport when you arrive and the hotel will sell you a ticket at the front desk when you depart. 2. This hotel is two quick subway stops from the Tokyo (Tsukiji) Fish Market that is in many guide books. You need to get there very early but it is worth the trip in my mind. Unique and fun. But wear shoes that you are OK getting wet and mucking around in (It is an active fish market - not a tourist attraction). 3. For great sushi try Midori-zushi - remarkably reasonable prices given the quality. Note the sign is not in English but it we found it. It is in Ginza and very close to the Imperial Hotel. Address: Ginza 7-108, Ginza Korida-dori 1F. Open 11am-2, 5-9:30pm dailyWe would stay @ this hotel again on future trips.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>