<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="8d5eef9b6e4d1cb3629d40df90a2d165" url=""><![CDATA[Glad we gave it a 2nd chance This was our second trip to Barcelona and we tried to stay here previously, but it was full. We are glad we gave it a second chance. Went with our daughter and son-in-law; who arrived before we did. They had a nice chat with the front desk and had us moved from a back room to a room facing the plaza/cathedral. The staff also sent them a bottle of bubbly to help them enjoy their stay. This was a nice touch. There can be some noise in the plaza, but the back rooms are not necessarily quieter. Hotel has a nice lobby and a good location. The rooms are typically small, but fine for sleeping. The bathroom area was OK with no difficulties.We did not have any meals at the hotel, but found nice spots for breakfast nearby and good dining in the area.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cf3f1c4a139b0b3f28d2f58a132156d2" url=""><![CDATA[The Orchard met our expectations The Orchard is a charming small hotel in an excellent central location. Although I would not go so far as to qualify it as romantic (it's on a most romantic hotels list), there were many nice touches in the Art Deco design of both the Lobby and our room. We had a suite on the fifth floor which was nicely furnished. The huge bathroom included a separate tub and shower stall. The bed was comfortable and the robes and slippers were a nice touch. The minibar was well stocked, including a respectable bottle of wine. We were on the fifth floor but still had a lot of noise from the traffic. What we appreciated most was the location. From the hotel we were able to walk to Fisherman's Wharf, Union Square, Chinatown, and North Beach as well as two high end restaurants.. It's about 6 blocks from buses and trolleys that get you to most parts of the city. The staff was very friendly and if the desk clerk didn't have information we needed, the doorman did. On the one occasion that we needed a taxi, the doorman arranged for a private car that charged taxi prices. In the hotel restaurant, the cold buffet breakfast (only option) was pricey at $14. but the small plates dinner menu is worth having if you don't want to go out. We travel a lot and prefer to stay in small, interesting hotels. The orchard was not our most memorable but was quite satisfactory.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>