<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="d421504f057145cccd33188e5b6ca5f0" url=""><![CDATA[2nd stay here - loved it! View of winds raging onto beach from balcony of room 610
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0bb30a83641888d2cc02850ebf986add" url=""><![CDATA[Expectations far exceeded! Loved it! We stayed at this hotel for 5 days (joining my wife who had already been there for 3 days). The hotel is very conveniently located for travelers, about half a mile from the airport. It includes free transportation from/to the airport to/from the hotel. Be prepared to pay for parking - about $10 per day. The valet parking is definitely not worth it - unless you like to be pampered. I didn't even check the price.The location of the hotel was surprisingly good. The airport's proximity had to be seen to be believed - the planes could not be heard at all. The check-in process was smooth. We had arrived by a late night flight that turned into a very early morning flight - around 2 AM. The staff were courteous, helped get the luggage to our room and we settled in.The room itself was spacious. It was *not* the suite and yet we could place a rollaway bed in the room and have space left for walking around. The rollaway beds were nice too - not the folfing variety, but a stand-on-end variety that meant that the mattress was no too soft or springy. The bed itself (important for people with delicate backs) was not the best. I have slept on better beds. The bed (King size) was too springy. I would (almost) gladly have slept on the floor. The rooms were surprisingly well sound proofed.My wife liked the 2nd floor exercise space - I myself worked out in the room itself (5BX requires surprisingly less space - look it up on Wikipedia), and my kids liked the swimming pool which they used once and even then it was too cold.On the whole, we had a great time and liked the hotel as a place to access the best things in LA.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>