<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="ef2e25091bcd1b4e7a020509997cc2e6" url=""><![CDATA[Luxury with a capital L Eiffel Tower from Balcony
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1177b2c796172c3f56c8ccd4e9976a40" url=""><![CDATA[Heavenly........ We stayed at Raffles in June 2006, when attending a conference at the Suntec Centre, which is very close by. We fell in love with it and have been looking for any excuse to return ever since. We finally made it in late February 2008 and nostalgia had not distorted our memories. From the moment you step from the car you feel welcome. No need to scrabble around in your pockets for passports etc.; check-in is in your suite; once that's done, your luggage will have rejoined you and it's time to relax. As many reviews have already said, there is a feeling of history and timeless elegance about the place; and despite being in the middle of a busy part of town, within the hotel grounds there is a feeling of tranquility. Although it is a prominent landmark in the city, they have been very careful to strictly limit non-resident access to the majority of the grounds and we were surprised how few other guests we encountered when not in the restaurants or bar area, despite the hotel being quite full. The staff are incredibly attentive, helpful and polite; nothing is too much trouble. There is a rooftop pool and an adjacent gym (small) and spa. The pool and gym are open 24 hours. The spa is not state of the art; but it would be incongruous if it was. Instead the therapists rely on their skills which are superb.The Raffles Hotel Plaza is also worth a look around. We had suits made at Coloc on the 2nd floor (=1st floor UK) and highly recommend it for service, price and quality. If I really had to nit pick, these are my criticisms1) the Tiffin Indian restaurant (which we visited last time) was disappointing. The food is buffet style, in rich sauces, and was not as tasty as the smells eminating from the restaurant would suggest2) The Courtyard restaurant is lovely (particularly recommended is the Singapore chilli crab) but in the evening there is a singer crooning Sinatra-esque ballads. Unfortunately the PA system is poor, and set too loud, leading to a distorted and overpowering racket which ruins the atmosphere.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>