<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="43637bdc68fad772c0bffceed909558b" url=""><![CDATA[Really pleased with chose the Metro I stayed at the Metro in New York last October and afraid taken me all this time to do this review. However, I did particularly want to do this review as my husband and I were so pleased that we chose the Metro. We know where to stay but our friends from Washington recommended the Metro. We were particularly pleased with location, being very central, surrounded by lots of shops, within a few yards of the metro station and within walking distance of Penn Railway Station, which we needed as we were travelling onwards to Washington. The one down point was the lack of medium range restaurants in locality. We arrived in the evening and wanted to have a meal but all the restaurants nearby were fast food, serving mainly pizzas, hamburgers, hot dogs etc. We find a decent reasonably priced restaurant in the area at all. Maybe someone else will be able to recommend one but we walked around for at least an hour and could find nothing. We ended up eating at the Metro Hotel restaurant which was good but it would have been nice to have a choice. We did find in most areas of the City that there were plenty of cheap fast food restaurants and also very expensive restaurants but a lack of medium range restaurants. sure they are there tucked away in side streets but we walked a lot and see many. We stayed in a basic room with no upgrade and were really pleased with it. It was a little on the small size but what you would expect for the price we were paying in a major city. Everything was very clean, the bed was comfortable and the bathroom had a bath as well as a shower. The free Broadband was good and really fast. It saved us a lot on phone calls as we could E Mail our friends in Washington when to expect us etc. However, the biggest bonus was the breakfast. Our room price included Continental breakfast and we were expecting just tea/coffee and pastries but there was a really good selection, including large selection of bread/bagels, cereals, boiled eggs, cheeses, yogurts, muffins, selection of teas, coffee, hot chocolate. I have probably left things out as hard to remember everything. There may have been cold meats but I have noticed, being a vegetarian. My only complaint would be that it was served with the usual plastic cutlery and paper plates that we found in many establishments in New York, however, probably just being fussy, being used to standards in the UK. As it was winter we could not use the rooftop bar but sure that would be really nice in the summer. So all in all, I would thoroughly recommend the Metro for a short city break in a central location.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>