<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="7">
		<document id="c473b2a70b1abd6493c3e177b756e0ff" url=""><![CDATA[Very nice The hotel is in a nice area of Tokyo. The lobby and public areas are nice, staff is very friendly. Rooms are small, clean and comfortable. The TV is limited to two English speaking stations, CNN and BBC news. There is pay TV if one wants movies. Good views are afforded from the higher floors of this 24 storey hotel. I did not eat at the hotel, as I found the prices to be somewhat high. Breakfast buffet was about $25.00 U.S, there are other places to eat in the area.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c8d0fca073012e7dda96576b21397976" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Hotel Nice hotel. Friendly check-in, very clean and well maintained rooms. Rooms are small, hotel is located in an old building which is nicely maintained. There is complimentary business center, also a bar and restaurant.Complimentary refershments are located in the lobby in the afternoon. Location is excellent for touring the city.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2fad2b7a212329b7e0fe2e38d71e872b" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel Nice hotel located near the gay area of the city. Within walking distance to good shopping, transportation very close by. Nice clean rooms, except for the large metal garbage cans located in the bathroom, the type one would find under a kitchen sink. Room overlooked the very nice swimming pool. Check-in quick and friendly, restaurant and internet also available.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eb752d4ca139fe9e1a0abde5265633eb" url=""><![CDATA[Good value I stay at the BW Executel numerous times thoughout the year. I have just returned from my last visit. I find the hotel to be clean, yes there is the faint oder of smoke in the hallways from the smoking rooms, but I always have a non smoking room and it is fine. The hotel is laid out in a T pattern and yes just like any large hotel there is some walking to the rooms, there is an elevator that services the floors.The room is large, clean and comfortable. The staff friendly and helpful. There is a business center with free internet 24 hrs. The shuttle sometimes runs late, especially in the morning so book one that is a little earlier than you need. There is a continental breakfast which is ok, nothing great to it, there is a Ihop about a 10 minute walk away from the hotel. Also if you need a grocery store, a large Safeway is located about one half mile south of the hotel. There is a local bus stop across from the hotel, service is every 30 minutes, the bus will take you to the airport, Seattle, or south to Federal Way, I use the service all the time. I would recommend this hotel for value, and cleanliness.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e5e3d2d248854049dd3ddcc1fcd3f904" url=""><![CDATA[A pleasant stay Very nice property, quick and friendly check-in. Nice spacious lobby and very nice comfortable breakfast room. The rooms themselves were spacious, with a living room, bathroom, kitchen and bedroom. A TV in the living room and bedroom. Rooms are modern and extremely clean. Free wifi is also offerred in the rooms. There is also a fitness center for guests. Breakfast was excellent and was included in the room rate. Eggs, french toast, cereal, juices, saussages, fruit, coffee, plus many others goodies. Plenty of food to start the day right. In the evening there is also food offerring, but not on the weekend when I was there. The hotel is a few minutes away from downtown, public transportation is across the street.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f0fdf5c256fdab6e59749c5f17f67b47" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel with one draw back I recently stayed at the Holdiay Inn Zocalo, located in the historic zone of the city. It is located just of the historic square, two blocks from the subway and near many fine restauruants and shops. The rooms, at least the one I had was small and compact, nice TV, large bed, shower in the bathroom. The room was immaculant, extremely clean, and well kept. My room looked out onto the street, 5 Cinco de Mayo. The lobby was nice, with a small bar, and internet service, free, limited to 30 minutes a day, after that it is 50 pesos, you can find much cheaper internet locations throughout the city. The staff was friendly. Two blocks up the street on 5 Cinco de Mayo and on the same side of the street was a great restaurant, La Capilla, I really suggest this restaurant. The hotel has a restaurant on the 6th floor, buffet for breakfast but a bit pricey for my liking, around $12.00USD, there is a Mac Donalds around the corner if your so inclined. Now for the one draw back of this hotel. During the day, and in the evening, into the late evening, 11pm or later, the Aztecs perform on the square and the sound of the drums beating constantly can be heard in the hotel rooms. If your a light sleeper, you are going to have a problem, no doubt about it, so take ear plugs with you, or you will not sleep. Other than that, this hotel is one that I can suggest, saying that, I would probably not stay at this property again due to noise from the drums at night.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="392016ede9bde32b2756acad2c7b026f" url=""><![CDATA[Very nice hotel Spent three nights at the Ambassador. It is in a prime locaton for shopping. It is an older hotel, so don't expect a fancy 21st century property. You get a clean nice room, good TV, nice bath. The hotel has double doors leading into the room, so you get less noise from the hallway, saying that however, I heard no noise from the hallway at anytime. The lobby is very nice, and the staff helpful and friendly. The buffet breakfast in the morning is fantastic, one of the best I have seen. Large breakfast room looking out on the passing street scene. If I go back to Berlin I would certainly stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>