<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="758d4b6d8886ce9ab46a5d743ffb9ff0" url=""><![CDATA[A Very Nice Surprise! What a view! Stayed 3 nights in an executive suite on the 15th floor with amazing views of the Hollywood hills/sign. The room was large with expansive windows. Overall service in the hotel was exceptional as well. Don't worry about the spa renovation warning on the hotel's website. This in no way interferes with the hotel overall and noise was not a problem. Location, location, location....a walkway leads to the very nice shopping center connecting all the major Hollywood tourist sites for great pictures. This is an above-average property. One suggestion: go early if you plan to have the breakfast buffet. The line/layout of the buffet gets long due to the setup. I would stay here again without hesitation. I have stayed at numerous hotels in the area including some very expensive 5-star properties in Beverly Hills, and the Renassance Hollywood ranks at the top of my list.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1c6c187f4a7b4760ab64d9a81a9611cb" url=""><![CDATA[Very luxurious, Service Without Exeption was Perfect!!! Overall a fantastic property with incredible levels of service. The only downside is no beach - but, took the shuttle/option of using Casa Casuarina (former Versace mansion) on South Beach one day and it was such a nice change of pace. Pricey but worth it - you don't mind paying premium prices when you get what you pay for. Just be aware the hotel is NOT on the beach and in fact has very little beach/swimming compared to actually being on South Beach. On the other hand, it is more relaxing and not as hectic as the overall South Beach experience. Rooms are perfect - no problems - great bed and great bathroom. I have stayed in two room types and any room at this property from a furnishings/functionality perspective is very nice. No request went ignored and overall staff training/experience level is second to none.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c6fca3c0f6573ed69240b289d7b4b7ec" url=""><![CDATA[Disgusting service - No comparison to other Intercontinental's This hotel is in no way up to par with other Intercontinental's in Latin America/worldwide. Service in EVERY respect is terrible, from the housekeeping that does not show up until 5:00 PM despite repeated requests for service to the absolute zero service in the casino. I was playing $25 blackjack tables for HOURS and not one drink order. Finally complained to management and even the blackjack dealer was literally screaming for a waiter to take orders wihtout success. The bathroom is tiny, the shampoo/amenities sorely lacking and the bed is worn out. Nasty hot tub with brown water and absolute dirty bed linens/bedspread shows this property in desperate need of repair. For $300 a night, stay elsewhere. Never again will I stay here. Nasty nasty nasty is all I can say about this hotel. Oh, the Ruth's Chris restaurant/service is excellent, but stay elsewhere and go there to eat. The Intercontinental is nothing more than a rundown Holiday Inn. I agree with the previous post...this place is dangerous for familie and children as well. The bathroom at the beach was used by non-guests and very dirty. I had my towel actually stolen at the beach when I went to the room for 30 mins. to check email! Not safe and dirty in general!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d06ac4c2018aac34e82e74ba90ba2afa" url=""><![CDATA[Serivce Awful. Internet Down 1/2 of the Time This place may have been renovated, but service levels are awful. Booded 2 oceanfront corner pool/ocean rooms @ 280 per night + 10% resort fee. Internet was down most of the time and wireless-only service is non-reliable and fails constantly. All guests in the hotel who had computers were complaining. Hotel staff clueless as to what to do. They would transfer me to a toll-free 800 number that went to India only to be put on hold for 20 mins before I was told an storm in Atlanta had caused global outages for the StayOnline (ironic name, right?) service. My comapny headquaters are in Atlanta and when I called the office, we were up and no major thuderstorms in the area. The hotel was just using this as an excuse. No major hotel, and especially one that caters to convention/business travelors should have such poor technical services in a newly renovated room. Drinks in the executive lounge are $8.50+ for serve-yourself bar. Security at the hotel is terrible. Anyone from the street can access the elevators and there were two security situations that had to be addressed on my floor during my 5-night stay. Sign-in within the executive club is also very unsecure and receptionists regularly would repeat guests name and room number when they walked in.....not a good idea in today's environment! In addiition, sign-in book is left laying out for all guest coming in to see. Hotel operators are responsible for handling calls to all areas of the hotel (ex. no front desk button on the ohones) and they often will disconnect or put you on hold forever before coming back to explain that no one is available. This Marriott has a great location but service it terrible. Rooms are nice now, but AC is either too cold/too hot 24 hrs a day. This hotel has had a facelift but nothing major. Business people will be majorly disappointed and families will be turned off by the price. All will be disappointed at the level of general service and staff competence. SJU needs a true 5-star property with consistent, reliable services. I have stayed at this Marriott many times over the years and sadly nothing has changed other than a badly needed room renovation. Guests paying these prices expect to receive more. Having to beg someone to setup an umbrella on the beach was also frustrating. Unfortnately, this is about the norm in SJU. Oh well, I tried it....again. Management has major issues to overcome at this property.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cd4d44b248b1d7a744f10876b43a20b6" url=""><![CDATA[Terrible Service and Very Bad Experience Overall Contacted the hotel a couple of weeks before arrival to inquire about any presidential suite type room with an adjoining extra room. Spoke directly and in detail with the hotel reservations manager. The hotel offered me a good rate so I decided to check out the property even though there have been mixed reviews on travel websites, including TripAdvisor. The hotel has undergone a beautiful renovation somewhat similar to what hotels in Miami Beach went through 15 or so years ago - very Delano/National type feel, especially at night. The views from the room and potential for this property is incredible - but note I say POTENTIAL. Service levels, especially for upscale type standards is horrible. There are glitches everywhere - for example, the room (presidential suite) had no air conditioning upon my arrival and there is no individual thermostat in this spacious room. The phone in the main living area was not working. No hairdryer in the bathroom. No safe/secure way of storing valuables in the suite. The toilet would not flush in the guest powder room. Water pressure in the very nice marble shower is poor and the water ran out of the shower all over the bathroom and into the adjoining toilet/bedroom area. While sitting in a room over 100 degrees for 2 hours (no air conditioning as previously mentioned) the front desk told me to keep the doors to the balconies shut because opening them would not allow the air conditioning to come on. After 2 hours of sitting in a room I called down again and was irate when I found out notihng was being done to turn the air conditioning on! I was put through to a manager who said), I understand you are having problems with your air conditioning - how can I help. Was it too much to expect for the air conditioning to be on upon my arrival given there was no way to control the temperature in the room myself? Other problems are pervasive - never enough towels both at the pool/beach (people were complaining and I even heard staff say where are the towels in this place). Turndown at night removed towels but never replaced them - on two nights I had only 1 towel left in the bathroom after turndown service! The concierge is nonexistent - I called several times during my 4-day stay and there was never any answer at the concierge desk - the phone rang and rang and no answer. Ordered room service and two times the orders were wrong - no orange juice, no cream for the coffee, etc. - order went to wrong room and overall very slow - 45 minutes for them to bring up breakfast and still had the order wrong. The final straw was after I had ordered hotel room service each day (breakfast and lunch) and wanted to order a pizza for lunch (not on the room service menu) they would not allow the pizza delivery guy up to my room. They called from the bellstand and I told them it was o.k. and I could not go down to the lobby because I was on a work conference call but a very rude bellstand manager told me I would have to go down to the lobby myself. When the front desk gave me the pizza delivery number, they failed to tell me it would not be possible for it to be delivered to the room!!! The bellstand guy (after arguing with me about hotel policy and how they did not allow delivery/outsiders onto the room floor) begrudgingly offered to bring it up himself - mind you this is to someone paying a substantial amount of money for the presidential suite and adjoining room - they acted like they were doing me a huge favor by bringing up a pizza. Oh, and should the hotel be so concerned about security, then why are the exterior room balcony floors crowded with teenage locals who just get into the elevators (they are not keyed/secure) and hang out on the balconies at midnight partying? It seemed obvious to me the hotel is concerned more about lack of revenue from a guest ordering a pizza than actual security. What could have been a relaxing vacation turned out to be a stressful situation at the property because of poor training and employees who did not have a clue about dealing with guests in an upscale establishment. I complained to management who was understanding of my complaints but of course not much could change during my stay. Bottom line- this place is new with much potential - the renovation is mostly very nice/beautiful but there is a lack of substance when it comes to actual levels of service. I agree 100% with a previous post - the service is terrible - I'm sorry, but no other way to say it. What a shame because I'm sure the owners and developers have great expectations for the property - but until there is better training and experience from a guest level of service perspective, they will continue to get mixed reviews - some nice/some terrible as is evident on Tripadvisor. I spent over $6,000 for a 4-day stay at the La Concha and experienced nothing but stress and problems every day and every time I tried to get any service at this place. Buyer beware - experienced travelors who appreciate upscale amenities and levels of service will be disappointed.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>