<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="6f2ce61af1ca4697fabc5be1334e16ec" url=""><![CDATA[amazing I was at PPR in November 2007 for a wedding. It was truly a beautiful and amazing resort. I have traveled to Curacao; Mexico; Jamaica; Costa Rica; etc. and this was one of the nicest resorts I have stayed at. We were given an ocean view room at check in without paying for an upgrade and this was just the beginning of a wonderful stay. Our room was immaculately clean - no smell at all - and was truly beautiful - bed and bathroom gorgeous - the minibar was stocked daily with alcohol and water and beginning on second day it was stocked with the alcohol we requested as well as extra bottles of water. We had beer/alcohol delivered to our room at night at no extra charge - the food was really good with the exception of the dinner buffet - we only ate there the first night because we arrived too late to get a reservation at the other restarants and it was typical buffet food which I do not care for - all other food; including breakfast buffets (made to order omelets) and lunch (made to order steaks/fish) homemade guacamole, etc. were awesome! We had lobster 2 different nites at 2 different restarants and it was delicious - we had no problems getting dinner reservations - you make them either day of , or the evening before - all staff were very friendly and drinks are made with top shelf liquor if you request - I read reviews before we went and can't imagine what some of the posters complained about - HOWEVER- there was a family from New Jersay we heard and saw while there and they complained about sevral things and were the same people that ate pizza and left plates, ect. around pool where it specifically says no food in/around pool - so I guess there will always be someone complaining about something - even while breaking rules....! I ate at all restarants available and all were good - my favorite was the lobster at the outdoor restarant on the beach and passions restarant (no children allowed) very romantic and good food and the italian was my least fave but still pretty good. If you have specific questions feel to contact me - the wedding was beautiful and went off without a hitch! They seem to have a great wedding organizer/planner. I think the beds around the pool were called palapa's but whatever they were called - they all had a towel on them by the time we got down to breakfast each day but we wanted to be in the sun anyway so we did not mind. Overall - a fabulous experience.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>