<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="69d5b9d04eb33eed9532764e93900908" url=""><![CDATA[Imperial it is The Imperial Hotel was selected for me by my colleagues in Japan, because it was within walking distance of their offices. I was completely impressed with the hotel in every respect. The service was consistently excellent. I read in my guide book not to tip people, but I tried anyway, and the bellman absolutely refused. As an aside, the hotel is very sensitive to the needs of a novice like myself. The bellman always asked me where I was going, and told the cab driver in Japanese for me. That was immensely helpful. My room was on the tenth floor. It was large, modern and comfortable. The bathroom was particularly nice, with a shower with excellent water pressure, and a modern tub with jets. The toilet had a heated seat and bidet, the soaps smelled lovely, and the hairdryer was strong and hot. The room is equipped with sensors that detect your presence, and light up when you approach (for example, a panel next to the bed that controls opening the curtains, the sound in the room, etc.). My PDA was not working in Japan, so I could not use my phone or email. The hotel phone charges were very modest, and the business center has free internet access. They actually opened early for me one day (usually opens at 8). I ordered room service for breakfast, and it was prompt and very good. On my departure day, I went down to the cafe (which opens at 6am) and asked if I could possibly have a quick breakfast in 15 minutes. I had my food within 3 minutes, and had time to spare! Every person I encountered was professional, friendly and fluent in English. My feable attempts at Japanese were warmly acknowledged. I will absolutely stay here again the next time I am in Tokyo.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4ecce9f0c7b8db562f17877ff0c2f2c1" url=""><![CDATA[Functional, not fancy I stayed at the Hampton Inn Seaport on business, because it was the closest hotel to the financial district I could get...with 2 month's notice! I had no trouble catching a cab in the morning. Including taxes, I paid over $500 for one night, and that was the AAA rate. This is supply and demand at work, I suppose. I gave it 3 stars because it was no way worth $500 a night. I was a little afraid when I saw the front of the building--completely nondescript. Having said that, I arrived late at night, and my room was ready and the front desk was very efficient. My bed was very comfortable, the flatscreen tv was great, and the bathroom was spotless and well stocked. The free breakfast was absolutely fine for me--great coffee, cold cereal, baked goods, yogurts, fresh fruit. SO, if you can get a good rate (which, based on the other reviews, seems to be available on the weekends and during nonpeak times), I wouldn't hesitate to stay here, if you don't mind having downtown as your home base.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>