<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="9e93686b690406fd83b0af2bb65158ad" url=""><![CDATA[A great stay We stayed here as part of a conference deal and really enjoyed our visit. The shuttle from the airport was prompt and easy to find. We arrived before midday after a very long and tiring flight from Sydney and were afraid we'd have to wait for our room. Check in was quick and staff were very couteous. The room was ready straight away. We had a lovely room over looking the pool area and the airport runways. There was very little noise for a hotel so close to such a busy airport. The room was very tastefully furnished and very clean.The Concierge(s) was very helpful and would go out of his way to give good advice. He even advised us that we could buy tickets to the Dodgers' game on the internet far cheaper than he could get them for us. The hotel shop had a good range of essentials and some of their souveniers were cheaper than in the downtown stores. My son and husband spent a lot of time at the pool area. The pool was clean and the hot tub was also well maintained. There were always staff on hand to replenish towels and generally keep an eye on everything. The towels were large grey and white striped beach towels which was a very nice touch. We did not eat at Shulas but did use the bar menu to eat by the pool. The menu was limited but the food was good as was the food ordered from room service. The room service staff were delightful. We did not eat at the Sushi Bar either as we are not huge fans but it seemed popular. Breakfast from the buffet was good and plentiful and we felt it was very reasonably priced.This hotel is located a long way from anywhere except the airport which is a disadvantage for a long stay as cab fares are horrendous - $45 one way to Dodgers' Stadium. A car would have been helpful and we would rent one if we were staying for the same period of time next time. However, bus fares are cheap and a ride to Santa Monica or Long Beach is $1.50 round trip. A trip to Downtown LA will cost $3.00 for an all day pass. The bus station is 5 minutes walk behind the hotel. Make sure you have the exact money.We also found that it was easy to walk up Sepulveda Ave to the shops - about 20 minutes walk - or the bus will take you there also. There are quite a few cafes, department stores and supermarkets there.We also got wise and checked out the neighbouring hotels for more food choices. If you are desperate, there is a Subway outlet next door and other fast food outlets close by.My only gripe with this fine hotel was that when I ordered a cup of tea by the pool, I was charged $4.00 for a very small pot of semi boiling water and a tea bag!We stayed at a neighbouring hotel on our night before returning to Australia, and believe me, the Sheraton wins hands down. Everything at the Sheraton is professional and we were always treated with the utmost respect.A tip:If you are clastophobic as I am, elevators are always a bother. The elevator doors at the Sheraton Gateway are slow at opening, so don't panic!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="49993e3cd0d162f3fd46974ae594e31a" url=""><![CDATA[Absolute Class We stayed here for a romantic night away from home. We had a spa suite in the front apex of the hotel. This hotel is high class from the minute you pull up outside the building until your car is returned to you at the end of the stay. Professional staff, clean, beatifully appointed room and a gorgeous bed all add up to the perfect stay. The attention to detail is fabulous. We will be staying again soon.If you are looking for a place to eat away from the hotel, try the Masuya Japanese restaurant just meters from the hotel. Fantastic and very well priced.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ed2f7e8acad98f8f93f6523bed412630" url=""><![CDATA[Could be better We stayed here again enroute to the US mainly because of proximity to the airport and it was pretty good when we stayed here last year. We booked a suite for $20 more so we had more room. It is not a cheap hotel in our view so look for good deals. The king bed was very comfortable but there was no bed for the two teenagers. The queen bed advertised turned out to be a sofa bed which we had to ask to be made up. Quite frankly, if I were the hotel manager I would have been embarrassed by the dilapidated state of the sofa bed. The matress was literally undulating! It was falling to bits. They left only one pillow so we had to ring again and ask for more which were delivered promptly. The towels left for the kids were thin and fraying. The location is great and the pool and garden area are very nice. There is a walkway to the beach. The room had views of the garden area, the bay and the airport. Next time, I think we'll look around for something else.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>