<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="56ea656efc54322e36ea3e92b38d5c6c" url=""><![CDATA[Relaxed elegance, quiet comfort Difficult to fault the surroundings or service at the Camino Real; I got our room at a modest discount via Expedia and was very pleased with what we found.It's a very different sort of hotel to the usual vertical filing system for business travellers -- the low-rise Camino Real, with architecture inspired by local tradition and the air of a museum or campus, all long corridors, modern art and arranged around gardens, is a very pleasant place to spend some time in Mexico City. It feels spacious and restful, unlike many similarly-sized hotels that are just a conventional highrise.We had an 'executive club' room on the top floor; basically the same sort of room as the rest of the hotel but with dedicated checkin, access to a lounge, complimentary breakfast, lunchtime drinks, and a cocktail hour - all very much appreciated and the service was always very courteous and accurate.The room itself was large with a very good 'wet room' shower in a brown marble bathroom. No problems with the kingsize bed, and there was a decent-sized working/dining table and a very comfortable armchair too. Decor was fairly neutral, most of the hotel being a mix of white, solid summer colours (beware of the VERY BRIGHT yellow wall by the fountain on your way out in the morning -- you'll need your sunglasses!) and dark woods. Cable TV provided a reasonable selection of local and US channels, although (as a British visitor) BBC World would've been nice ;)The pool and surroundings were up to standard.The Camino has four restaurants (Mexican, Chinese, French, and Italian) and several bars - the 'Blue Bar' being particularly interesting as it's essentially built on a perspex floor over a shallow pool - rather like a glass-bottomed boat. There were a couple of niggling little things - I'm sure the smoke alarm in our room was doing odd things with blinking lights, and we seemed to be sharing control of the aircon with a mostly-benevolent spirit at times (although the temperature settled down correctly!) but on the whole - an excellent experience. A stylish, laid-back and refined hotel conveniently located for Chapultepec, the Paseo Reforma and the Metro.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>