<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f330020101ba90bd7feda8c3f866f824" url=""><![CDATA[The Ritz Carlton --- Over Rated My girlfriend and I went to the Ritz for six nights over the New Years holiday. Ive stayed in Ritz-Carltons many times...mostly on business trips to Atlanta and many many times in New Orleans, where I travel for work all the time. The best: The pool is beautiful. The gym and the spa are also very nice. The beachside restaurant was delicious, and the bar was very nice as well. As far as amenities, this hotel is typical RC. Everything is beuatiful and very organized, the service is, in my opinion, just as it should be for 6+ bills/night for a room near the airport with a view of the ugly hotel next door.The worst: The main problem with this hotel is the constant nickel and diming and the crime situation in Puerto Rico. I felt like every time I turned around, there was another bill to sign. On our third night we took a cab to Old San Juan to check out some of the clubs, listen to some music, and feel some of the local flavor that everyone raves so much about. Very very shady. I live in freaking Jackson, MS and work in New Orleans, the street violence capital of the US. I even felt uneasy. On our cab ride back to the ritz. the taxi we rode in had a bullet hole in the front windshield (NO JOKE) It was nuts.The New Year's party at the Ritz was pathetic. Not fun at all. After paying the price for entrance to the party, we had one glass of champagne and bolted to the Hilton, which had a waaaaaaay better party, including people actually smiling, plenty of free drinks, and music that didn't sound like a broken Harry Bellafonte record.THE ABSOLUTE WORST: On our second to last day, my girlfriends diamond stud earrings and two bottles of cologne were stolen from our room. The earrings and one of the bottles of cologne were gifts that we had exchanged on our arrival. We filed a police report and a report with the hotel security. The earrings, which were $4000, were supposed to be replaced by the RC's insurance company (I had receipts). It's been months, and I haven't even been able to talk to anyone about this. They just blow me off and say that it is still Under Investigation. The Bottom Line: PR is a hell hole of crime. Go somewhere else. For the same price as the RC in San Juan you can go to Caneel Bay or Nevis. Im so pissed off by this earring/eau de toilet heist that I now stay at Le Pavillon when I go to New Orleans, even though I always had great experiences at the RC.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>