<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="2fda52f606838a21483a194956f9375f" url=""><![CDATA[1st Class All The Way My partner and I stayed at the Grand Marina the night before we left for a cruise. We had booked the Celebration Package about 3 months out.When we arrived at the hotel to check in, I was very impressed with the location, the staff and the over all look and feel of the hotel.The hotel was located directly on the harbor about 5 mis from the cruise port. We were watching the ships come in from our room. The only bad thing is that we did not have a balcony.The staff was over the top friendly and making sure that every need was met to our expectations. Thier serivce level was right in line with that of the Ritz Carlton. I have to also say that I did not see one bad looking person in that hotel. Where do these people come from. Just sitting in the lobby for a little people watching was the best free enjoyment that I had.However, the most important thing that totally won me over took place at check in. When I booked the Celebration Package it was 3 months out. However by the time I checked in the price of the package was reduced by 50 Euro's however I was not aware of it. When I presented my credit card to check in, the staff person told me that I am getting a credit since the price was reduced. How many US businesses would ever do that!! We were very impressed and would suggest this hotel to anyone.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="506a2a58e5d12818a33a99cc72a7cf97" url=""><![CDATA[You have got to visit this hotel property We went to San Fran for the 2008 Labor Day Weekend. We stayed for 4 nights and wish we would could have stayed for 4 more.If you remember the 80's TV Show called Hotel, this was the hotel it was filmed in and modeled after. This hotel lobby will take your breath away. I have stayed in many 5 star and 4 Diamond level properties and this one is right up there.The stay was great, the chamber maids were extremely pleasant, the concierge knew everything about the hotel and the surrondings and the drinks at the bar were out of this world.The hotel is so beautiful that over the 4 nights we were thier they had 2 weddings a day. The hotel is located directly at the top of Knob Hill which is between the Union Square area and Fisherman's warf.You can walk to Union Square but not to the warf due to the hills and the grade.I can go on and on with my bits to make you feel comfortable about this hotel but I do not have the time. I can tell you that I we have booked this hotel again for our trip back to San Fran over Christmas.PS - I did forget one thing. The hotel has two areas for rooms. You can stay in the original side or on the new tower side. Here are the differences:Original Side - These rooms are larger, have 12 ft ceilings, all the old wonderful crown modeling, victorian type look and feel and all the charm. The only draw back is you do not have a view. You only look out over the garden area or onto the street.The Tower side - These rooms are not as large (they are approx 450 - 500sq ft not including the very large bathroom) The views are either of downtown looking onto Union Square OR directly facing the bay. We were on the 20th floor and looked direclty at the bay, golden gate bridge, alcatrez and China Town. The view was worth every dollar spent.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>