<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="56b1a74a191a06afefda8c98a0cb2f03" url=""><![CDATA[Loved, Loved, Loved Sofitel St. James!!! My husband and I stayed at the Sofitel St. James 05/17-05/21.The minute we arrived... we were greeted by a friendly doorman who took our luggage while we handled the check-in process.We arrived to the hotel an hour before the check-in time, this was not a problem as our room was readily available. The check-in lasted all of 5 minutes before we were off to our room.Our room was very clean and nicely decorated. As soon as we were in the room I had to lay on the bed and rest a little while as the jetlag was setting in. As others have mentioned here on tripadvisor...the bed was soooo comfortable!!! This was just what we needed after sitting in an airplane for 11 hours. 2 out of our 4 night stay at the Sofitel St. James, we had drinks at the hotel bar. The hotel bar was not very big...but very nice and comfortable with great service and great martinis. The location of the hotel could not get any better. Sofitel St. James is a few blocks away from the Piccadilly Circus, and Trafalgar Square. It is also a short 10-15 minute walk to Buckingham Palace and to Covent garden. If you are looking for a great hotel in a great location...look no more and stay at the Sofitel St.James.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1666d131a5af613cdb5bc428f2063406" url=""><![CDATA[Hilton Hawaiian Village is great!!! My husband and I just returned from a 9 night stay at the HHV. We were there 9/9/-9/18. We had no problems with check-in, Alii tower has its own front desk. We stayed in an ocean view room in the Alii' Tower. The room was great, and it had a great lanai. There is maid service 3 times a day, and the Alii tower has its own pool for Alii guests only. The private pool was the best part, the super pool is too crowded. In regards to the food, there is many restaraunts to choose from on the property. My husband and I are picky eaters, and didn't care for some of the restaraunts. A few of the restaraunts we tried were: The Golden Dragon-Chinese,Sergios-Italian, and Hatsuhana-Japanese. They were all ok, I was just not impressed. There's the Wailana coffee shop across the street, this no frills restaraunt is great for good tasting breakfast at a cheap price. Lunch we had by the pool, RoundTable Pizza, Hamburgers etc...We usually ventured outside of the hotel for dinner. 3660 on the rise is an excellent restaraunt, the concierge can make the reservations. Also, the Cheesecake Factory on Kalakaua St. is good. The weather in Honolulu was wonderful, occasional showers but that's normal in Hawaii. Overall, the Hilton Hawaiian Village is a great place to stay when in Honolulu.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>