<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="8e184f6462d6915449b28ee3c6c03b29" url=""><![CDATA[A good choice for central london Our experience reflects that of other positive reports. This is a very nice, well-run hotel. Yes, an attempt was made to up-sell upon check-in but that can be good if they are offering good value, the money they don't earn tonight will be gone forever. We chose not to upgrade and the room was fine, well furnished but in line with London hotels it large. The location is very convenient to Trafalgar Square, The Mall and Piccadilly. While the hotel is tucked out of the way taxis were easy and the surroundings pleasant; this is a great place for a hotel. Housekeeping was good the staff acknowledged us when we entered the hotel each time and the concierge cheerfully provided the services we asked for. These people know their business and we will return on future occasions.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8fb4991b446f176ac0cef5d743c03e3f" url=""><![CDATA[Very nice hotel, good service and attentive staff This is a very good hotel run by people who know their business and what their guests want. The rooms are nice, well furnished and everything works. The staff is tuned in and attentive. The concierge was first class apart from the cost of Internet connectivity there really isn't anything negative to report. It is only when one sees a good concierge that one is reminded how important they are.It's an interesting local for a hotel but it's great only a short walk to everything in the centre of the city, right by the theatre district, a short walk to Oxford Street, Piccadilly and Leicester Square. Soho is full of interesting restaurants, clubs (Ronnie Scots) and traditional pubs.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e39f51208f640d1deca1e145a41e23c2" url=""><![CDATA[Genuine good service and an overall nice hotel I have stayed at this hotel for few nights three of four times a year for over a decade. I am motivated to leave this review to recognise that it isn't easy to delivery the same level of service over such a long period of time, This can't be any individual, it has to be the result of the hotel's culture. The breakfast is good, the wine and cheese in the evening generous and enjoyable. There are a range of room types but all with the same style of elegant, albeit a little faded decor. While my friends stay at more well known hotels in the area and I have tried them too, I return to The Elysee and am never disappointed.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>