<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="6c650633dffe70b8f6892514bacf3a73" url=""><![CDATA[Should be demolished We stayed in an oceanfron jr. suite. The view was beautiful...the room was vile. The sink was outside the bathroom, in a corner of the bedroom. The bathroom door was not solid...it was a louver door...the shower was army camp quality...the wallpaper was peeling and the tile grout looked filthy.The hotel location is private and it is nice to be away from, but within walking distance of, Waikiki. There is no pool and no place to just sit around and read a book. There is no hotel presence on the beach. If you want a chair, rent it from the concierge and carry it to the beach! This is not luxury by my terms.The restaurant is nicely situated, but they take reservations for Breakfast tables with a good view.....so you can arrive and see an empty table with a nice view and then be seated at the table next to the dirty dishes.We walked by some rooms and saw that they were literally 3 feet wider than the bed...........Do yourself a favor and go somewhere else! As for the reviewer who never stayed at a better hotel, my deepest sympathy!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7425f7ffe15c5555d2c67d34c27b6dc3" url=""><![CDATA[Almost good We stayed in a club room on the 39th floor..the view was beautiful. The service was abominable. We tried changing the turndown time to a later hour so we could shower for dinner first, but in 8 days we only could manage it once!The concierge was disorganized and fairly useless.The buffet dining room (not club level) was always overcrowded...it was adeqate for 20% of the capacity of the hotel.We found the rooms nicely furnished. The plumbing almost worked.....if you don't mind a tub stopper that failed to open).The food prices were absurdly high for Mexico City....and the cover charges were outrageous. We ate at the best restaurant in the city and only rarely paid a cover charge (much less, and usually for music).The botted water in the room was imported and was $8..the local water in the gift shop was $1.50 for a litre and a half.We paid a daily hotel fee and have no idea what it covered...wish we had disputed it!There was no comment form, and the tv based comment screen was not functioning for 8 days.We were happy with the location and wish someone competent would take over the hotel.Sorry, amigos!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>