<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="4385a801f6dc2d995f4e528236f9019b" url=""><![CDATA[One Great Vacation We just returned from our 1 week stay at the San Juan Marriott. Our room was very good and my wife loved the plush pillows. The staff was great from check-in to check-out. The entertainment every night was super (everyone was up and dancing till all hours). Some complaints that we read prior go leaving just wasn't there. The beach was clean and yes the neighboring buildings are being worked on so don't look at them, keep your eyes on the ocean and you will have a great time as well. We took a tour through the hotel for the rain forest. Our guide (Gus) was great and well worth the expense. We bought a bottle of rum at the walgreens to cut down on the cost of drinking at the bars all night (saved a bunch). We went to Old San Juan several nights (we recommend the Barrachina - dance show and dinner good and reasonable).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fe9e99cf15a59c70b76f7dac10e2b1a9" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Vacation Location We just returned from Iberostar Punta Cana, and it was a wonderful vacation. This was our second time to visit this location and all the reviews that said the food did not change are so very wrong. Every day my wife and I had something different at the buffet. Our room was great and for $20 extra at arrival we were upgraded to a ocean view room. Our 3 specialty dinners were also excellent. We did Mexican, Chinese, and the Steak ones and the service and food was great. Our room was perfect, the beach and pool were great. We also enjoyed the shows at night. The dancing was so very good. I don't know what other people expect from an all inclusive resort. Most of all the staff was all friendly and efficient. They had a Christmas Gala buffet that could not be out done, with lobster and so many other choices made to perfection. Trust us, we would not go back to a location if it were sub par. We intend to return again in the near future.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>