<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="72b2d3a03d87414ae8f4c1fbb4805e83" url=""><![CDATA[Good conference venue I stayed at this hotel for a conference. When I got the conference details and looked at the room rate, I began looking for a different hotel! But the others in the vicinity seemed even more expensive.The Park Plaza has a certain slightly old-world charm: it is an older building, and they play that up a little. It is, however, well-appointed, clean and well-maintained. (The heater/cooler in my room was making a loud noise when I arrived, but they quickly sent a technician to silence it).The fitness room is barely adequate - much better than some hotels, but not satisfactory for anyone who wants to do serious resistance training. In-room internet access is not cheap ($11 basic; $13 for VPN-capable service. There's no explanation of what the full extent of the difference is). Breakfast was not included in the rate. The Hotel breakfast is not cheap, but there is a cafe outside, on the same block, which does all kinds of stuff. Similarly, for dining, there are several restaurants and a pub on the same block, and several other restaurants (for various budgets) within a block or so. Provided someone else is paying the bill, or you are reconciled to paying good money for a hotel - as you will need to in this part of Boston - the Park Plaza offers a comfortable place to stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0e44d173fe805c4aee1407ee46c3c624" url=""><![CDATA[Modern German Chic, at a price I stayed at this hotel for three nights, for a conference. On the day I arrived, Germany was playing in the finals of the Euro2008 football competition - so the streets were full of noisy fans. The hotel arranged for me to have an inside-facing room, to avoid the noise: full marks for customer service!The whole place is very stylish and efficient; clean and well-maintained. The reception staff were exceptionally helpful (in English or German!). As a business hotel, it would be hard to beat: the location is also great for West Berlin, and there's a U-bahn station right outside if you want to travel around the city. The bedrooms was well-appointed, and comfortable, with a fairly firm bed. The espresso coffee machine was a nice touch. The gym facilities are a little basic - some cardio machines, but almost nothing for resistance. The sauna, however, was very fine (do remember to take a euro coin for the locker).Breakfast was pretty good, with a wide variety including big jugs of freshly-squeezed juice. The conference meals were in private dining places in the hotel, and were also superb. All this comes at a price:the conference rate was EUR 150, including breakfast. Some people said you can get a better price than that on the web: even so, it's certainly not cheap! The only other downside was that, with all the conference delegates wanting to be fed half an hour before the conference started, there was sometimes a queue for breakfast. That smacks of bad planning.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>