<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="46261fc076d6583f6a50ac48dda45c8d" url=""><![CDATA[OK stay at the Washington The positives-The room was beautiful and very large. It had a balcony, beautiful windows and a chandelier, nice sitting area and a desk. The beds were 2 twins pushed together and were comfy enough. Good heat as well which was needed b/c it was quite cold out. The hotel is in a quiet area.The negatives-The location wasn't great for us. It is good if you want to spend your time there near the museums but we found it annoying to travel all the way to the center or from the center back to the hotel. For this reason alone we would not stay here again. It would have been nice to have tea/coffee facilities in the room....we tried to bring up juice/coffee one morning at breakfast and were told we were not allowed, so b/c of this we did not eat breakfast although it looked standard anyway (cereal/cheese/meats).The last thing I want to mention is that I would have hoped the staff would have been more friendly....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2a9e41559ade8a4163f7772645414e92" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent Value for the Money Got an excellent deal for 5 nights at this hotel. We paid with credit card when we arrived at no extra charge. We were first given a double room which was VERY small. I was not very happy with this room. Since we were staying 4 more nights, I waited until the next afternoon and asked to be moved to a bigger room. They said no problem but I had to wait until the next morning. The next day we were moved to a very large room(twin) with 3 windows, table and chairs, desk and lots of room. So be aware the rooms here vary. The beds were not the best but not the worst. The bathroom was a decent size and the water pressure was good. I found the staff to be attentive and friendly and always around. You had to leave your key when you left each time but it wasn't a problem and I liked the safety feature. At night we never waited more than a min. or 2 to be buzzed in. We had breakfast most mornings, which consisted on coffee, juices, lots of breads, cheese, spreads, cereal and yogurt. Plenty to start your day. Location of hotel was great as well, right next to the Mariott in a quiet neighborhood. Overall at the price we paid we would stay here again as long as we got the bigger room.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b188b0749d34341a593cc2ce26c88d26" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel..... Nice, clean room. I choose this place for the free parking. I would stay again if I got a good deal. Far away from the action so I would only stay here if you had a car. Got an upgrade one stay and had a very nice room but don't know if that would happen at a busy time. Front desk staff was nice. Not much food in the area.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cd544b58e2c913c0df0202dd65e90797" url=""><![CDATA[We will be back..... We will definitely be back. The location of this hotel was perfect for us(not in the center) but then again we are walkers. The room was very nice, double bed, chairs with table, desk ect.(as pictures on the website). The room had an entire wall of windows (don't worry there are blackout curtains) that overlooked the street/canal-just beautiful. The room had coffee/tea making facilities which was nice b/c I could have coffee whenever I wanted-and it was really good! The bathroom was a good size with a tub and good hot water and toiletries. The breakfast was more than standard which included coffee/tea/juices/granola and cereal/cold cheese and meats/breads with so many spreads to choose from/yogurt and fruit. It was more than enough to start the day and served in a very nice room.You had to leave your key when you came and went but it wasn't a problem at all, it's a small hotel and we never had to wait to do this-and the staff was very pleasant.The only negative I can say about this hotel is that the bed was very hard and uncomfortable but this is just preference (it didn't stop us from sleeping though). Also if you are a light sleeper you want to request a room in the back. The hotel is in a busy area and there is street noise until late-this didn't bother us though-again-just preference.All in all we will definitely be staying here next visit.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>