<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="4304784feabc5c352ec7985503beaddf" url=""><![CDATA[Brilliant Hotel, would highly recommend We choose this hotel mainly on the strength of the great reviews left by trip adviser users and disappointed. This hotel is excellent, all the staff were extremely helpful and friendly, when we arrived at the hotel four hours before the given check-in time they were very accommodating and made sure we were in our room within 30 minutes.The rooms are lovely, we were on the 7th floor at our request after we read on this website the problems with noise on some of the lower floors and we disturbed by it at all. The room itself did face a busy road but the windows shut out any road noise so that wasn't a problem. The rooms were extremely clean, plenty of space and very modern with flat screen TV, radio etc and decorated with lovely finishing touches. The bathroom wouldn't have looked out of place at a 5star hotel, it was extremely high quality with a great bath and powerful shower. The toiletries in the bathroom were much more than the standard, with razors, make-up removers, shoe shine etc, etc in additional to all the usual things, this coupled with the free safe, well stocked mini bar etc made this hotel a little extra special. The hotel and the rooms are exactly as they look in the pictures, if not better.The hotel the bar was nice, we had a few drinks in there, bar staff were friendly. We didn't eat in the restaurant but it looked very nice. The free internet access was also an added bonus as was the roof terrace pool. It was small but at the end of the day you are in the centre of Barcelona so any pool is a bonus. The Location of the hotel couldn't have been better, a couple of minutes walk from Playa de Catalunya, which is one of Barcelona main square's at the top of Las Ramblas. Perfect position for sight seeing.Las Ramblas is great, take time to have a drink there and watching the people go by and the mime artists - how those people stand so still is beyond me! Barcelona is a brilliant city with so many things to see an do - the Casades (get there early it gets so busy), marina, zoo, Gaudi Cathedral were all brilliant places to go and we tried to walk to most places to see all we could of Barcelona, which was tiring but worth it. Lots of lovely places to eat and drink, and the shops go on for ever.I would highly recommend both this hotel and Barcelona itself, we will defintely be going back again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="56c9a2f6d375c91d8db99f6a05775b14" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel in a perfect location We stayed at the Donatello for the first two nights out our holiday inCalifornia. The location was great; a two minute walk from Union Square. We were on the fifth floor, our room was clean, comfortable and very large. The little kitchen and sitting area was a nice touch.All was well until we tried to get to sleep, the constant noise from the car rental company next door was unbearable, they were shouting and banging all night, with no regard for anyone trying to sleep! It was so bad that my partner went down to reception to ask that we be moved, they do anything immediately but they promised to moveus in the morning, which was they did. This was a real shame and not exactly the hotels fault as it is out oftheir control, but still very frustrating when you have just had a 10 hour flight from the UK. The staff were all really helpful and friendly and we would definitelystop at the hotel again, with a request to not overlook the car rentalplace of course!San Francisco itself is wonderful and we would definitely want to return in the future.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="699b62921121749a98d2f24b31653126" url=""><![CDATA[Loved this Hotel Room
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>