<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="ed4013e230a9e81c6f60f977480ef6b2" url=""><![CDATA[Quirky and fun! This is certainly not a hotel for a romantic break away but great for a group of people visiting Amsterdam. Just been on a hen party and stayed there and really enjoyed it. The rooms were fairly basic but quirky and the bed was one of the most comfy I have slept in! The bathroom was roomy, but bit wierd no shower curtain meaning it got soaked! The staff were really friendly - very helpful and spoke perfect English. The hotel is only a mnute from the nearest tram stop and then 5/10 minutes into Centraal, really handy for the centre. I wouldnt come here with my husband but for a fun trip with lots of mates where you need somewhere functional but nice to sleep, this is it!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e7524e9f02c68dc3a3681901c600afeb" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic capital hotel We stayed recently at this hotel for 2 nights on a Friday and Saturday.We arrived late on the Friday night but still received a very warm welcome and even a free upgrade! We felt the commual areas of the hotel were modern, clean and welcoming.The room itself was great. Good bed, lovely seating area, good size bathroom with great shower. This was really just a stop over for us but would have been equally as nice as a romantic weekend away.The area was quiet as a business area, so really peaceful. There is a Wagamamas, Pizza Express, Chez Gerard , All Bar One - all nearby, although closed at weekends. But its really near the tube and easy to get a cab into the centre.All the staff we encountered were incredibly friendly and helpful. When we left, we needed a taxi. They booked us one and when it arrived, came out the hotel to the cab to make sure everything was OK and to help us with our bags. Not many hotels I have stayed with bother to do that.The breakfast was fairly good but pretty expensive but then I find all hotel breakfast are like this.Bearing in mind we paid for 2 nights on a weekend, we thought this was an incredible find. Friendly, nice rooms, nice commual area, near enough the centre but away so quiet and all for in one of the most expensive cities in the world. Would thoroughly recommend. Wished I knew of this before!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>