<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="8c0cc441edfb7f69224aee4d984803d0" url=""><![CDATA[Don't miss dinner We stayed in the Wentworth for one night in February 2008. The staff are friendly and helpful even if they greet you in French, I suppose to accentuate the French Accor Group ownership of the chain. The room was clean and modern but we felt small for this level and price of hotel. The bathroom was very small and did not have a bath only a shower. When I mentioned the size of the room it was explained as being a which restricted alterations that could be made.The buffet breakfast in the Garden Court Restaurant was underwhelming and the impression we got was that they just could not cope.In the evening dinner at the same restaurant was sublime, such a change from breakfast time. The service was impeccable, the knowledgeable and friendly staff always seemed to be there when you wanted them. The food was some of the best that we have eaten in Sydney. We especially recommend the scallops, had to ask for extra bread so we did not miss a drop of the delicious sauce. The meal was finished with crepe suzette at the table, a treat not offered in many restaurants these days.So to sum up the Sofitel Wentworth in Sydney, small rooms, give the breakfast buffet a miss but even if you are not staying there go for dinner.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="46db849d012f6e9491387a88b5611578" url=""><![CDATA[Beware of al la cart meals in the restaurant We stayed in the Sheraton on the park for three nights in March 2008. The entrance and lobby area are impressive, the staff friendly and helpful. Our room was large with a good size bathroom which had a bath as well as a shower. The room had all the amenities you would expect from a hotel of this level and price. Our room was at the back of the hotel but the rooms at the front have views over the park, but at an additional cost. For all services such as housekeeping, maintenance, room service etc there is only one number dial. I think all hotels should have this feature, no dialing one number for one thing and another number for something else. Another feature we liked about the room was the electrically operated blackout curtains, nothing worse than having light leaking into a room at night.Unfortunately the Botanica Restaurant was another story. It is basically set up as a buffet restaurant. The buffet breakfast was great with a large choice of food. We did not sample the dinner buffet but it looked very good with a seafood bias. Unfortunately we dined al la carte. Once for dinner where the food was just OK but for the price not up to expectations, and once for a light lunch where the food was terrible. We both had a burger but could not finish them as they were burnt and dry. The waitress handled the situation very well and took it back to the kitchen and offered complimentary desserts and coffee. I filled out one of the was your which I always assumed went straight into the bin but to the Sheratons credit the food and beverage Manager contacted us and wanted details of why we were dissatisfied. To sum up the Sheraton on the Park in Sydney, good rooms and good guest services. On the downside eat at the Botanica Restaurant if you are into buffets but eat elsewhere if you want al la cart service.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>