<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="724dfd1c5f08952a7af7c53a2fb5aeb6" url=""><![CDATA[A rip-off, though I do heart the comfy beds. After several nights of inns and motels on my road trip, I was so ready to sleep on a nice fluffy bed with equally fluffy pillows and duvet. Hotel 480 did not disappoint. Check-in was a breeze, and the staff was extremely courteous. The location made it easy to walk almost everywhere we wanted to go, which was great, because who wants to drive in SF? I have no complaints about my experience here; in fact, I would whole-heartedly recommend it to anyone...that is, anyone with deep pockets. Internet access was $10 per day, and parking was approximately $50 a day after taxes. Now, I'm from LA so I'm used to paying premium prices for parking and mandatory valet, but $50 was a sticker shock, even for me. In the end, everything added up to almost $300 a night for a room in a three-star hotel. We had a good experience here, but not THAT good.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c170eed866eb0980a0f442f3a9a49160" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect view of Union Square! My stay here was nothing short of perfect. I was here for a business trip, and the company sprang for a corner room on one of the upper floors, giving me a gorgeous view of Union Square and the rest of San Francisco. The bed was the perfect blend of firm mattress and soft sheets, the bathroom was huge, and I got a copy of the San Francisco Chronicle every morning. The staff here is amazing...everyone always has a smile on, and there's always at least five people waiting to help you with your bags, opening the door, or getting you transportation. This place even has a gym, so I didn't have to hike to the nearest 24-hour Fitness on Montgomery. Only thing was that the internet was $10 a day, but I found that having to pay for internet is the norm among SF hotels. If I could afford this place, I'd definitely stay here when I'm in town for fun.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>