<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="290b59363eed3d844b73068e4554e252" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel in good location This hotel was in a great location for one that is not on Las Ramblas. A 5 minute walk took you to the Port area or Las Ramblas but for travel round the city the underground train station is at the front door of the hotel- you couldn't get any closer. The rooms were well appointed- nothing luxurious but pleasant if slighly small. The breakfast was very good- I would recommend you book this at time of booking hotel room as works out cheaper and it was a cooked breakfast with eggs, bacon, cereal, fruit, fruit juice, toast, tea, coffee, buns etc. Small pool on roof- more of a plunge pool but sunbathing area as well with small gym- I loved it as you had great views over city and nice to relax and cool down - no its not big but ideal for a city hotel. Lots of nice restaurants in Barcelona- I recommend going just of Las Ramblas for great value and go to the Fairy Bar at the bottom of Las Ramblas beside the wax museum just for the novelty factor. We took the tourist bus round the city and although I would never normally do anything so tacky it was a great idea as limited walking- we got to see al the sights and you can hop on and off as you want- top tip don't board in Place Catalyna as its so busy- we boarded at the Port area- means you get to sit upstairs which is a must. I would definately stay in this hotel again as its a great location and good value for money in Barcelona where many hotels are overpriced and not great.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bdb1fe9abd1856994be40e38ebe37c0b" url=""><![CDATA[Do not stay here its terrible Hated this hotel- their website makes it look really nice but when you arrive it is grotty and smelly. We had to change room 3 times and we had booked a family room with 2 adults, 2 children and we ended up in a room with 3 of us in 1 double bed. We had no coffee maker in the room and when I queried this at reception was told that guests steal stuff from the room all the time and the hotel can't afford to replace them. Bathroom so small that the door skimmed along the toilet when you opened it and you had hardly enough room to sit down. Air conditioning unit attached over the window so you had no daylight and it was extremely noisy all night.Didn't sleep under the blankets as the bed was dirty and the room really cold and heating not working properly. Felt quite unsafe as hobos hanging around the entrance shouting abuse at us everytime we left the hotel. This was quite expensive for what you got as the standard was terrible - a youth hostel would have been better!!! One of the worst hotels I have ever stayed in.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>