<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="56836f9b86c4c9269170b414f31bcd75" url=""><![CDATA[Truly a good, reasonable hotel in London My teenage daughter and I have just returned yesterday from a one night's trip to London. I chose the hotel purely on the reviews given on this site.This hotel was an excellent choice. As said by other reviewers, the Luna Simone does not have big rooms - but who cares - as you only sleep there after a day doing the sights. The main thing, as far as I am concerned, is the cleanliness. This hotel is really clean and fresh - from the moment you step through the front door. We had room 10 on the front and even had the window open at night. We don't mind traffic noise and had a good night's sleep.We had a nice breakfast in one of the very clean and stylish basement breakfast rooms. It was not the most interesting breakfast we've ever had, but very nicely cooked egg, beans and bacon, having first had cornflakes and toast.This hotel is close to Victoria and Pimlico underground stations and is in a very select area of London. I would recommend it to anyone looking for a clean, friendly, budget hotel in a nice part of the city.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bedce0d98c134bed82834bb67379b507" url=""><![CDATA[Average Comfort I stayed here with my husband and teenage daughter at the end of July for 3 nights as the first stop on our around the world tour.The hotel is convenient for viewing Fishermans' Wharf, the crooked road and to get to trams.The room we were given had a wonderful view of the Golden Gate Bridge and we had no complaints regarding the size or cleanliness.The biggest problem was breakfast time! This only ran until 9.30 and so everyone headed down at 9am arrving at the same time. The breakfast room was just not large enough to hold everyone so there was an overflow into the reception area. One morning we ended up eating out there on sofas, hoping that a table would turn up eventually. The breakfast buffet was pleasant enough, but it was a bit of a scramble amongst all the other guests (who'd arrived at the same time!!)Comfort Inn - you need to sort this out with an extension!Anyway, a nice hotel for the price, but head down early for breakfast!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>