<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="af2b0e80133b0c829761c1eefcffe609" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful stay Another picture of my room
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0d159bd29974b6b843098e097c8f8ec2" url=""><![CDATA[It's a Royal Palace What an incredible spectacular palace in the middle of an otherwise modest city. All advance arrangements via e-mail were promptly responded to, and were faithfully done. Upon arrival you are greeted as royalty, and it just keeps getting better. Every last detail is spectacular. Outstanding breakfast, bar, terrace, dining. Rooms, lobby, gym, pool are all out of this world. Rock star spotted at poolside (Iggy Pop). Staff at all levels treats you with the utmost courtesy and respect. No ripoffs or jacked up prices for tickets, reservations or taxis/limos. Complementary goodies galore upon arrival. It's on a quiet side of town, near a tram stop, easy walk to start shopping or dining. Fantastic and plentiful amenities by L'Occitane. Prices are appropriate for a 5-star hotel, and it's worth it here.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1ff50f4e245bcf64278ab31702a2a276" url=""><![CDATA[Pleasant Stay in S.F. Perfect location on the northeastern side of Union Square, very safe, convenient to everything, near all the best shopping and close to Chinatown Gate. Everyone who worked there was most pleasant, friendly, and helpful.Rooms were very nice. The fitness center is one of the best I've ever seen at a hotel. My only complaint is that the breakfast room is much too small, resulting in waiting times of up to an hour for a table. This really threw off our plans every morning. They need to serve breakfast in a much larger room. The breakfast buffet itself is excellent, and the staff there are very very kind and friendly. The elevators also required quite a wait sometimes, as this is a very large hotel for only 5 or 6 elevators.Overall, we really enjoyed staying here, but don't pay extra for the breakfast- you'll waste a lot of time in the morning waiting for a table; just eat at any of the coffee shops or diners surrounding the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>