<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="be5fd1d02026231d30ccb0cde5a13901" url=""><![CDATA[clean hotel, great price Seattle was sold out, and this place got good enough reviews on tripadvisor, so I chose it. Good price, nice to be in the center of town. Pros: inexpensive and cleanCons: no A/C, small TV, small bathroom, no internet accessBasically, a room, clean sheets, good location. No regrets... I got what I paid for and was not disappointed.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="271aa145de9af93cec262b5fa82251e8" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel. I'd return in a heartbeat. Fantastic hotel. Wonderful service.Plus:* Great location* I arrived early, and while my room was not ready, they were very accommodating regarding my desire to change and freshen up.* I had a corner room, and while other corners would have a view of the water, my room was great. Lots of room, big TV with art/music channels, very very comfortable.* Very comfortable bed. Prompt room service.* Nice area for breakfast and drinks* free high speed internet, wired and wireless.Cons:* Parking was pricey* None that I can think of. For any business/pleasure downtown, this is a great place to stay. Highly recommended.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b397766786aafd6aad71cef18d5e548e" url=""><![CDATA[clean, but issues with service I understand it is always hard to meet expectations in a service industry, but too many strikes against the marriott on this visit.I reserved 3 rooms. After being told that they could all be on the same floor, only two were on the same floor. Having arrived at 3pm, I could only get into one room.They messed up one of my relatives reservations, and would not honor the original room rate (only a small nightly difference).I called for my car, which was valet parked ($45/day), and it took 35 minutes to get it, even though it was 6 in the morning. I went downstairs to get a luggage cart to get my suitcases out of our rooms when leaving. When I got back downstairs, I was instructed that I wasn't allowed to take the carts. Other items to note: No lobby to speak of. No food other than breakfast. room service is delivery from a nearby restaurant. As you can read, none of these were serious offenses. The rooms were clean. Shower had plenty of hot water. Rooms were a perfectly reasonable size. Breakfast buffet was fine.I'll stay elsewhere the next time I am in NYC. At $200/night, this would have been fine. At $375, I expected more.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>