<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="9631021d0c3132a4ec06d0511281873e" url=""><![CDATA[Hmmm I was in Singapore for a conference and this was the conference hotel. I had come from Bangkok where I was in the delightful Swiss Lodge--a small boutique hotel--and this was just way over the top. It is huge and the lobby was always crowded. I am not a fan of big chain hotels so that was an immediate demerit for me. The location was great and the staff was nice but it was too big, too expensive, and offered no more than the Swiss Lodge at a fraction of the cost. On my own, I would never choose this hotel but as a predetermined base, it was ok.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ca27e368fa6f9c33278bc5b263c84a88" url=""><![CDATA[Try Anothr I spent four nights at the hotel for a conference and was not impressed. The conference rate seemed to be quite high and was more likely a function of supply/demand than a reflection of value. The staff was pleasant and the meals prepared for the group ranged from acceptble to wonderful. However, the room was dowdy and there were some odd quirks. My message light stayed on all the time--despite no messages and repeated promises to fix it. The shower only pointed straight out, rather than down, which was very odd. My main complaint was the nickel and diming that was everywhere. They offered one free pack of in-room coffee with others available at a modest price. The bottled water could be taken for $4.25!! and there was no mileage credit given because of our group rate. I would neither go back nor recommend it based on my experience.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8a3aa66e3ab0b19fdb3f7826710083b9" url=""><![CDATA[Just what I needed I needed a handy airport hotel for an overnight. Last time I stayed at one of the NH hotels and found it very far away and too much money for such a brief stay. The Intercity measured much better on the overall scale. It was more convenient and had everything I needed for my purpose--which was a place to sleep. The room was clean, well appointed and left me completely satisfied. The bus was rather crowded and probably should run every 20 minutes.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6bac3beb64d03dec3d79b732a7b4501a" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Place I satyed four nights at the hotel for a conference and found it to be a fine establishment. I was in a distant section that made access to the lobby and conference section quite a hike but was near to the spa and pool which proved to be an advantage. The pool is immense and, as a swimmer, was most welcome.The food was tasty and well presented and the location was very convenient for access to lots of transportation and local activities.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>