<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a0fa762603304e1ab340eb51ead5c056" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic hotel...Fantastic City I have just returned from spending 7 nights at this fabulous hotel. Being English and on holiday I didn't know what to expect of a city hotel but I was impressed and highly delighted by our choice. The staff were always friendly and extremely helpful and knowledgeable. The hotel room was large, well appointed and very clean and maid serviced daily. We were on the 8th floor directly below the pool and exercise room and had a great view of the southern edge of the city. The lobby provided a relaxing place to sit while enjoying a coffee. There is a computer suite with 2 internet PC's and printers for checking e-mail and researching the days activities. There is also a pay phone and ATM machine for those last minute cash withdrawals. The breakfast was very good with a great choice of pastries, fresh fruit, yoghurt and cooked sausage and eggs even up to 10.00am when they stopped serving, with coffee / tea available all day. The location although not in the centre of Boston was only a few minutes away from downtown by silver line bus (the stop 2 blocks away) or the number 1 bus, giving access to the T stations and a direct route to Harvard (the stop being just across the street outside the hospital). The location of the hotel is on the edge of a residential area and industrial estate at a major intersection. Some people may be threatened by this type of neighborhood but we walked every where and never at any time felt under threat.Although there is no restaurant on site there is a McDonalds and a bar/diner across the street and 5 minutes walk away down Mass Ave is the quaintest diner you ever would like to eat in Victoria's was the best ever.We only used the hotel shuttle once and that was to return to the airport. It runs on the hour and takes about 10-15 minutes to make its way over to the drop. At 4.00pm we were the only passengers .The driver was prompt, extremely helpful and very courteous and his demeanor epitomized everyone we encountered at this hotel. All in all you get what you pay for and more....go on give it a try...you won't be disappointed !!!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>