<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="94fc59220c2cd297f4970bd8d46c83b6" url=""><![CDATA[What a DIVE! The best thing I can say about this hotel is that it was pretty centrally located. Reading the other descriptions, I wonder how this could be the same hotel we stayed in. There were six of us at this hotel for four nights. We had three separate rooms. The first day we watched a roach walk along the hallway to our rooms. The beds were NOT good (as someone mentioned). They squeaked, and were thin, and soft. The rooms were exceedingly small, and the bathrooms even smaller. Only one person could fit in our bathroom at one time. The shower was so small that there was no way to even bendover in it. The bathroom was very simply remodeled with tile and a new sink..But the faucet was so close to the back of the sink, that it was hard to wash one's hands. The noise level from the restaurant next door..or whatever that was..kept us up at night. In one of the other rooms that two of our group was staying in, they could hear cats crying outside. at night. There is one very, very small elevator that sometimes didn't work. The staff working there seemed nice. That was a plus. tHowever, we all couldn't get over just how cheap the rooms were. Even the towels were small and rough. The outside of the hotel looks fine, and the lobby is okay too, but the rooms are the worst we've ever stayed in. This should not be rated as a three star. If this is what three stars are like in Miami Beach, , I hate to see what a two star would be like! As to the hotel being called a Suite Hotel, none of us could figure how they can get away with that title. The rooms were way to small to fit anything but a bed and a very small table. There was a decent closet in the room. I usually do not write reviews, but I just felt I had to let people know about this one! If you don't care about anything but just having a place to sleep, this hotel would be okay..But the rooms are really not up to what one would expect in a three star hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>