<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="3339634aef06d95be860000ef03feada" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, good hotel - but avoid first floor until building work ends First off, at the time of writing (Aug '06) this hotel is adding a floor and there's a lot of building work going on - but don't let that put you off. We liked the location (thirty steps from the beach) and the local vibe so much we (two adults and three teenage children) extended our stay and wished we'd checked in earlier.We had a suite with a partial sea view - very spacious with a sofa bed and a rollaway, plus a king size double in an adjacent room. The suite also had a kitchenette with a big fridge, microwave and cooker, although we never used it because there are so many good places to eat at all prices within walking distance.Reception staff were very helpful and they provide free cookies each day, the breakfast is self-service and a bit basic, but it is FREE and you can top up further nearby.We would recommend avoiding the third (really the first if you're from the UK, and second if you're from the US) floor on the side of the hotel where all the building materials are kept - I had concerns that the pile of wood allowed someone walking along the street to climb onto our balcony if they desired. I mentioned this to the very helpful receptionist who immediately found us another room on the 4th floor (with less clanking air conditioning) and told the builders to move the timber away from the building.You can hire surf boards at the back of the hotel and get a discount if you mention where you're staying too. The pedestrian boulevard at the back is fantastic for people watching - all human life is there with a great spectrum of characters going for a stroll, literally hundreds of them - but amazingly they're gone by 9pm.The beach is brilliant with life guards evenly spaced along the sand and the surf was amazing.When the fifth floor is finished they're probably put the rates up - so get in now and get a bargain.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>