<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="8f675557f0fdb956488d7c4e7bf1e5b6" url=""><![CDATA[Drowing in its own hype Just returned from the NYE bash at the Gansevoort South, and I must say that I was terribly disappointed with some aspects of this hotel. Their NYC reputation has extended among the South Beach regulars, and the place is awash is hype. Hottest Spot nonsense that will probably not last the quarter. This hotel occupies the former Roney Palace property, and they have surely invested a huge sum into its renovation. To this effect, they have succeeded; and the sleek, colorful, and sophisticated design of this hotel is spot on South Beach. But this is where the magic stops. For their New Years' bash, we paid nearly $300 per ticket, on the understanding that this price included open bar, food, and perfomances by hip hop artist T.I. The open bar was a singular unit, thus it took nearly 45 minutes to get a drink. They oversold their tickets, so food was only provided to the tables, which cost $5000 each...A clear case of tolerated false advertising. The bar was only pre-stocked.expecting to see T.I. perform on stage, but instead I saw him being beamed in on a flat screen from Times Square. Really, this party was a joke. The door staff was quick to turn their back on you, which is a common and annoying gesture in SoBe. However, if you're paying the massive amount that will inevitably greet you upon checking in, the last thing you want is to be ignored when you need help. For this reason, I do not recommend this hotel. Like most hotels in South Beach, this hotel is stupidly expensive...but unlike the rest, it reeks annoyingly of pretention. For the price, you can book a room at The Tides, Shore Club, or The Delano, all much better hotels that have made their mark in South Beach, and surely will not treat you like you are a bother. P.S. They valet parked my Porsche GT, and still treated me like I wasn't rich enough to step inside.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>