<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="fda8f50c7ac57b8ccc13b1eb89cfd743" url=""><![CDATA[Highly recommended We stayed at the Argonaut in August 2004. The hotel was beautiful - enormous room, fabulously comfy bed, all fixtures and fitting seemed brand new. It is perfectly sited for Fishermans Wharf and it really felt like a luxurious hotel including complimentary wine around 5pm each evening. We arrived from our long haul flight quite late in the evening, our first visit ever to the west coast and we got a really warm reception that set our holiday off on the right note. Only downside for us was that our deal booked over the internet did not included breakfast... the Argonaut have a restaurant - the blue mermaid - where you buy breakfast and this worked out quite expensive for us. Would strongly advise you book a rate with breakfast included. That aside, we would definitely stay there again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6f1071e01de5be9f2b9e61e0ec7df175" url=""><![CDATA[A magical experience We very recently had a weekend break at Casa Camper with some good friends to celebrate a birthday. It was the best hotel experience any of us have ever had. I had asked for a bottle of Cava to be waiting in our friends room and not only had they remembered to do this (chilling in an ice bucket, ofcourse) but they had also made a small birthday cake with candle and left a lovely note for her. The hotel is ultra modern and very stylish - but somehow manages to have a real warmth about it. The 24/7 food was fantastic (the cooked breakfast was superb) and because all the food is included in the price, it really made it very good value. It is exceptionally child friendly yet child-free couples would love it also. I can't imagine staying anywhere else if we visit Barcelona again. At one point, sitting on their roof terrace with a view of the rooftops of the city, sipping chilled wine and tasting their delicious snacks we tried to invent a new holiday game - If you could improve one thing about this hotel... what would it be? and we were all lost for ideas. It is as if the owners have brain stormed everything people look for in a hotel and then gone on to make it happen. The only suggestion I can think of is... we need one in every city!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7594be0cb2ad4e17d29369b353d0d52d" url=""><![CDATA[An underwhelming experience We originally booked into the Hotel New Amsterdam (having found it on Tripadvisor) but received an email a few months later apologising that they were being refurbished and explaining that they had moved our booking to the Times Hotel instead.The Hotel is in an excellent location - on one of Amsterdams three main canals - Herengracht. It is within easy walking distance of the grand central station where you can pick up the canal bus and tour the city by water and also within walking distance of various museums. Or you can just meander along the canal and simply enjoy the beautiful architecture. So... location great.The hotel was clearly recently refurbished - a nice clean interior. The reception is very modern - bright red furnishing and white walls. It also houses the breakfast area, which is fairly small and very open plan. So open plan that if, like us, you are seated near the front door, it can get very draughty with people coming and going, and you do feel a bit on display whilst you eat. Breakfast was disappointing - the croissant were clearly a few days old, the choice of bread and jams limited, the choice of cereal also very limited. There was ham and hard boiled eggs but, all in all, had breakfast not been included in our room rate, we would definitely have eaten out at a cafe on the 2nd morning.Our twin room was very small indeed. It had two single beds pushed right next to each other (not enough room to leave a space in between) and a wardrobe. That was all the room could take - the TV was a slimline version mounted on the wall (absolutely no room for it to have been on the floor). You could just about walk around the two beds. It felt even smaller because the facing wall was covered in a massive mural of an enlarged van gogh painting. Very bright and innovative but somewhat overpowering in a tiny room. The bathroom, however, was spotless with a very effective shower. The service was not brilliant - I asked for advice on restaurants and was underwhelmed with the response. When I tried again and asked for the best area to walk to for a selection of restaurants I got a disinterested you will find restaurants anywhere type of response. So, it was clean and well finished and the location was great. But I would definitely try somewhere else if I return to Amsterdam because for the price we had a very average hotel experience.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>