<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="cc96895100c3a2b122225cb7bec7cfb6" url=""><![CDATA[Outstanding location Just got back from a week in Florence (Firenza), staying at Westin Excelsior, with my wife on a vacation. First of all, let me say that this is probably the BEST location in Florence, with the best views, right on the Arno river. We looked around alot for other hotels we might want to stay at for our next visit and came to the conclusion that this is the best place in town (our guides told us the same thing) Across the square is the sister hotel, the Grand Hotel, which is equally as nice. You can walk to virtually everything within 10-15 minutes, straight down the sidewalk by the river Arno. It is worth the money to get a room with a view of the Arno, and balcony (they are really tiny balconies, but at least you can open the doors and gaze out). If you stay at an in town hotel, be prepared for alot of noise on the streets.Rooms are small, but nicely decorated, and our bathroom was actually bigger than many American hotels, with double sinks, separate toilet area and excellent shower/tub-great shower water pressure! I might advise to avoid stepping up to the suites, since they are really not much larger than a regular river view room (the pictures are misleading). English television selections are BBC and CNBC or else movies, but you probably won't watch TV anyway. The hotel employees are really, really helpful, and very nice and speak English quite well, so that is not a problem. The prices of food and drinks are quite high, but there is never a need to eat at the hotel, because Florence has so many excellent Trattorias, Cafes and Restaurants, all within a couple of minutes of the hotel, that are 1/2 or even 1/3 the price.Our room was around $500 Euro per night and I think we would pay that again and stay here if we go back. Walking guides of the Duomo and Ufizzi are avaliable thru the concierge, and they can get you into these places without lines, but they are quite expensive if booked thru the condierge--$80 Euro per hour, plus the cost of the entry to the museums. A guide is worth it, but maybe they can be found at half the price by not going thru your concierge.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>