<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="91b9ca38cbd4bb6bf5430012bd71db73" url=""><![CDATA[Jury's is simply fantastic My husband and I actually got married at Jury's Boston Hotel, and it couldn't have been a more perfect experience! I found this hotel during Boston's restaurant week, and enjoyed dining at the Stanhope Grill (which is incredibly good.) After seeing how kind and accomplished the staff was, and how consistent they were at being so great, we booked the restaurant and 10 rooms for our big day. It couldn't have been a better experience, both the wedding and the hotel stay. All of our parents and family who stayed in the hotel had a fantastic time with great service and comfortable rooms. The larger two-double-bed rooms had a gorgeous bathroom, and our single-king was nice too. The room was spotless, and all the staff was super kind. If you want easy, friendly, elegant service that is better than the supposed-best hotels, than Jury's is the place. There's no finer property in town when you consider the whole package, and the location is superb. Considering I paid way over $10K for my wedding to be held here, I think every cent was well worth it!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="045161445c4bfffbfd0e34675f25d7ee" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect Stay Except for One Annoyance My husband and I stayed here for our last night in Sydney, as part of our honeymoon. I must say I have never seen a more beautiful and luxurious hotel, in all of my travels. The location is to die for, and the staff are incredibly nice and attentive. I almost fell over when the reception agent walked us to our room, and made sure everything was to our liking. An incredible hotel, a gorgeous room, and a stunning bathroom without a doubt. And, the automatic shades were cool, but didn't close 100% (and you can't move them by hand.) BUT, there was one REALLY annoying thing, that totally knocked one owl face off of my rating. They charged us $11 to make a 1.2 minute call to a local number. HELLO!? If people are paying over $500 a night for a hotel room, do you charge them to pick up the phone for 1.2 minutes, to call a friend in the same city? I was amazed at something so thoughtless/greedy/silly. So, I hope your stay is as great as ours, but stay away from the phones! Don't even look at 'em, or you may get some obnoxious charge! And, uh, the breakfast is $45 each. I don't know what they was serving, but it couldn't have been that delicious. The view, though, is unbelievable, with the sound of waves under the restaurant when the windows are open...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e537f4ff74f49450c939bcf60bda62da" url=""><![CDATA[Good but too expensive, esp with extras I've stayed at the Sydney Sheraton Four Points previously, and it's a good hotel, and this time was a good experience. BUT, they annoyed the heck out of us with their many fees. It costs money to use the office center, the breakfast was good but hugely expensive, and then the rooms aren't cheap either. The hotel is nicely located in Darling Harbour, but there's lots more of Sydney that's worth exploring beyond this area. If you want a great hotel that's spotless and easy, and close to tourist interests, this is a fantastic choice. Just be ready for lots of fees!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>