<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="5c56c57a210b222eebf1588fd26c2ed6" url=""><![CDATA[Spectacular My Minneapolis flight came in very late and I booked a stay instead of driving over an hour home at midnight.What a beautiful hotel. It is easy to find through a catwalk at the airport. They also provde a shuttle if you dont want to walk.In the lobby there is a nice pub and all business amenities.The room is absolutely beautiful, new furniture, updated, with a pretty view of the airport and water.In the morning, I went to the health club. There are towels, a locker room, a lap pool and updated equipment. TV's were everywhere to offer distraction and individual TV's on each machine.I am a Silver Hilton member and I was immediately offered services of the members lounge, even though its usually for Gold or Platinum members. there was complimentary breakfast, newspapers, magazines, concierge and another business center. Beautiful setting.The staff were all excellent and to be commended for their attention to detail.I have been in many Hiltons due to business and this was absolutely the best. I will definitely go back, and my thanks for a wonderful stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="59b880193bb84ed1f828bf664211c49d" url=""><![CDATA[Not impressed I attended a 5 day conference onsite sponsored by an employer. I travel quite a bit on business so I can compare offerings and expectations. There is no complimentary transportation from the airport, so prepare to pay either a towncar or Super shuttle both ways. Expensive and not expected for a large resort hosting business conventions on a regular basis. Internet is not free either and charged daily, whether you need basic or VPN. It was an extra $75 charge for me. Although the resort adverstises many restaurants, only two were open. There was nothing inexpensive and I paid $17 for a cheeseburger. The resort is not within walking distance of anything, so I paid a hotel employee through the conceirge service to take me to the closest supermarket and pharmacy. He was very nice and waited for me so I could get reasonably priced snacks and drinks for the week. The rooms were fabulous with terraces, nice two room suites and plenty of room. There was a mini bar in my suite with typical minibar prices.The elegant restaurant at the top of the hill was wonderful, attentive staff, nice food and a shuttle to your room. Beautiful view. That was a bonus. Another interesting point, I had a very early departure one morning so I went to the desk and settled my bill the night before. When I pulled up my bill a week later, there was an additonal minibar charge of over $50------ If I had not called, my employer would have paid for that or given me a lot of grief about some thing I didnt do. To their credit, there was no argument and I was told the charge would come off right away.So, it was a 50/50 kind of trip. All right but not great. Really too bad.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>