<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="8a737c0267b963697dab209927c16c54" url=""><![CDATA[Stress Free Vacation We stayed at Excellence May28Th till June 3rd.Being self employed its hard getting away from more then a long 3 or 4 day weekend. So being able to spend 6 nights at EPC was a nice treat. First thing I wanna say which has no barring on EPC itself is if you can book your flight and not have to use Miami as a stop do it. It is the worst airport I have ever been in. It wasn't bad on the way to Punta Cana but Customs was a mad house. There was so much confusion on where to go and how to get there and with it being a major international airport the customs lines are long. Airport was beautiful never been to a port where its all open air and thatched roofs. We were in and out of the airport in 30 minutes tops. We booked out transfer with Mikes Taxi's. IBK They were right there as you walk out of the airport. The driver was nice he spoke little english and we spoke little spanish so we didn't communicate with each other very well. LOL The ride was fine wasn't horrible but I can see where some people complain about it being rough or dangerous at times. Its long if you get caught behind some of the large construction trucks if you get lucky and have a semi clear ride it could be under an hour if not expect 75 minutes or so. Pulling up to the lobby is much like any other resort you get the customary champagne and wet towel. We were escorted to the Excellence Club for check in by my man Antonio who we would see all week. He remember our names all week and is an asset to this resort. Which may seem strange since he was a bellboy but he really has great customer service skills. We meet Roberto he runs the Excellence Club and is the best. Was willing to do anything he could to make sure we had the best time while we were there. Throughout the week as we walked by the would get a wave or an hola or asked if we needed anything to make our stay even better. Took a few minutes for check in and chatted for a few then they took us to our room. We stayed in swim up room 10004.It was nice it was clean and there was a flat screen TV. All a man needs right? We had a nice bar filled with different hard liquors that we actually never used. Only thing we did was asked for a bottle of wine each day and they brought it by in the afternoon each day. They had 3 choices of beer Presidante Bohemia and Bud. Ended up changing the Bud for Number 1, which is a Dominican beer, which ended up being our favorite. They also had a few snacks including Kit Kats Oreo's and crackers. Which we found came in handy each day.The room was one of the few that have lounge chairs right in front of the room or a hammock right outside your door. Neither was a big deal since we asked for a room that was closed to the water. We did have 2 chairs and a table outside our door though.Drinks were good I will say I hear a lot of people complain about the drinks not being strong and this has a lot to do with the type of drink you order. If you are ordering Sammy daiquiris etc this will more then likely be the case because they are premixed and in a machine just waiting to be poured out. You can go anywhere and the drink will be weak from these machines. All you need to do is ask for a little extra run or tequila when you order it and they will put it in. Any of the other drinks that they pour and pre made you wont have a problem with.Food was good we ate at every restaurant except for Barcelona the Mediterranean. I was a little worried about the lobster since I have read in numerous reviews was not good. It was my favorite meal .I got the cajun spiced grilled lobster and it was delicious.The grill was pretty good as well. And then portions at the grill were large. Actually too larger for us we had a ton of food we even finish. The beef was a little overcooked then what I asked for but it was still easily cut with a butter knife so it dry at all just not quite how I asked for it. Not a biggie.Spice was a good meal also the Asian restaurant and the sushi was pretty good as was the duck I got.After all the raving about the french restaurant here on T/A and from talking to other guests at the resort we were really looking forward to our meal and ended up disappointed. Not because it was bad, it was good just not great. The service was the best we had all week for dinner. I think it had to do with higher expectations. The meal was good nothing blew us away.Then Toscana was the Italian restaurant its lacking in atmosphere but this is just due to it being a multi purpose restaurant. Its connected to Barcelona and kinda has a school cafeteria feel to it. This is because it also serves the buffet for breakfast and lunch. Food was good here though.For lunch our favorite place was the Grill. It has a couple of lighter options for lunch when its hot and you what heavy foods like burgers etc. And the big reason we went there a lot was because of the service we got from Ricky. He was great, always attentive and would chat with those that were interested in having a conversation and would leave you alone if you were having a private conversation with each other. Never an empty glass I normally had wine with lunch and I walked out each afternoon a little buzzed because he always had my glass filled. I actually had to ask him to slow down. LOLI will say we had no wait times at any meal We showed up to meals between 6:45 and 7:30 each evening and the restaurants were near empty so it looks like most people eat late. We were actually disappointed a little since we like to have a few drinks and chat before dinner. The meals also only took 30 minutes tops which seemed strange to us if they are trying to have upscale meals. We were also a little disappointed with this since we got all dressed up for a meal and it was so short. I am sure most will like this but we were never in a hurry so this our preference.Beach and pools were nice. The beach was clean no trash or rocks and we had plenty of room to pick a chair all day long. The water was black or red flagged each day but it have any problems out in the water you can get out there chest high without being worried about the rip current. Any deeper and you need to use caution.Pool was good we woke up the first morning early fully expecting the chair wars to begin. So I got up at 6:30 looked out our sliding glass door and not a person in site. Took a shower etc watched some TV looked out again around 7:45 right before we went to breakfast and there were only 2 spots taken so we went and saved a spot thinking we would be outta luck if we waited till after breakfast.We ate and went back to the room to change headed out to the pool around 9:30 and there were atleast half of the lounges still open but most of the shaded lounges were taken by this time. This was how it was everyday of our stay. Not sure if this is just because we were in the Excellence Club part of the resort. The main pool area where all the games happen was full each morning by 8 AM so if you wanna be there show up early but if you are not into that then I think you need to play the chair wars at all.We really do any excursions since we were there to relax only thing we did was the horseback riding which is offered for free. Make sure to book this the first day you arrive it books up fast.It last about 45-60 minutes you go through a path through palm trees and come out to the beach take pictures which they will try and sell to you later and then walk along the beach back to the resort. Its nice nothing spectacular the horses are not well taken care of the look very malnutrition which is kinda sad.The only show we went to the Michael Jackson show which was pretty neat. The rest of the shows are the typical shows all resorts have. We go to any of the others did kinda watch from a far from the Kafe Nothing made us get up to go watch.I used the gym a few times and was very clean and well taken care of. I workout 5 days a week with weights and while it was limited with free weights it had plenty of machines and cardio equipment. Was the best gym I have seen in an all inclusive resort.One of the major pluses we noticed were the covered walkways. This was a nice touch. It really was nice if it was raining or if it would be really hot and you wanna walk without getting beaten by the sun.We never had any issue with water be it hot cold or the pressure and we had no power issues. We kinda expect it to happen but never had these problems.Had one bug problem the entire time and it was in the bathroom and it was just one bug but it was huge. LOL Again the nature of the area and we kinda expected it being on the bottom floor.There are tons of birds fish turtles all over the resort along with a few small lizards and they have boxes set out with food to feed all of them. It was nice to walk by and feed them throughout the day and take pictures.Overall we enjoyed our stay here a lot and would recommend this resort to friends and family. Its nice to know we now have a place we can go next time we vacation in the Dominican.If you have any questions feel free to contact me.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>