<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="067ad50a34cf7a51c50c8862efe6b33c" url=""><![CDATA[EXCELLENT! Just returned from this hotel a couple hours ago and just wanted to come on here and say all the bad reviews must be for a different hotel as myself and the rest of my party found absolutely nothing to complain about during our two week stay.We stayed in block 5 on the ground floor which had a perfect location - in the centre of everything, but far enough away from Sneakers disco so we couldn't hear it at night. The rooms themselves could do with a lick of paint here and there but overall they do the job for the amount of time you spend in the room. Maid service everyday, fresh towels everyday, bed linen changed every couple days. We had 4 cockroaches in the room over the course of two weeks which is nothing really. Bathroom is simple and could do with updating, but our shower worked and was nice and hot so no complaints. The food in the resort was extremely varied and all very high quality. Windows the main buffet restaurant has a different theme night every night (Spanish, Dominican, Italian, Gala, Beach Party, Mexican and International) and the food within each theme is so varied - how anyone can not find something they like is beyond me. Every night there is a pasta station with various types of pasta and sauces - all delicious and freshly cooked in front of you. Breakfast is again a buffet, containing various breads and cold meats, cereals, hot items such as eggs, bacon, sausage as well as cakes, muffins, doughnuts etc. You can also create your own omlette which is made to your liking - very tasty!Beach restaurant offered more of a snack based service - rice, salads, cold pasta, chips etc. With a snack bar just outside cooking fresh burgers and hot dogs - just be careful to check your burger is cooked thoroughly before you eat it.We visited 4 of the 5 a la carte restaurants and enjoyed them all.Aqua (the main restaurant for the Bavaro Suites) is amazing! I swear that my meal there was the nicest meal I've ever had, not just on the holiday but in my whole life!D'Mario's Italians was really nice too, good range of pastas and pizzas as well as several types of meat. We visited there twice as we enjoyed it so much. On our second visit we found the service quite slow but not slow enough to make a complaint.The Tex-Mex American Grill was also an enjoyable night however the service in there was extremely slow, it took us over two hours to eat our 3 courses. The food however was very enjoyable, with a wide variety of choice.The fish restaurant on the beach side was also enjoyable, they have a great range of fish available but also a non-fish meat for those who don't enjoy seafod. Yes you do have to pay extra for lobster but there is so many other choices to select from that there is no reason to bring this up as an issue.The bars are scattered right through the resort, you're never too far away from the rum and cocktails. We spent most of our nights either at the beach side bar or the backstage bar, where they have quite an extensive cocktail menu that they can customise for you (change Rum for Vodka etc.). Every night there is a different show in the theatre, we only saw one (The Micheal Jackson show) which was really good and entertaining. We used two of the resort's pools - the main one and the adult pool. We found the main pool extremely loud and busy so we found the adult pool a fantasic haven - this is not a negative of the main pool it simply wasn't what we were looking for, but it would be great for fun loving families and children. The adult pool was perfect for us, we were able to lounge by the pool on sunbeds which were always readily available as the area was so quiet. There was often some kids who invaded the pool but staff were quick to remove them. The adult pool bar is where we found our favourite staff member Nicholas - he is amazing and deserves a pay rise! He brought us drinks in and around the pool without even having to be asked, we just kept tipping him a few dollars every day and we seemed to become his favourite customers!As for excursions I highly recommend every trip we went on; Tropical Sunset, Reef Explorer (it's about 30ft away from the hotel, not travel necessary!), Saona Island and the Monster Truck Safari. If you do go on the Monster Trucks take some gifts for the children of the DR and Haiti as they come up to the truck and you visit a school. Many people on our trip simply took the hotel's toiletries and the children loved it - it's a very eye opening trip! A few times a week some vendors come into the resort and set up stalls throughout the site. It is a little annoying but it's also quite fun and interesting. They sell all DR produce - Rum, Cigars, paintings, jewellery, clothes, ornaments etc. and and definitely flexible on their prices so always haggle! Some give you free gifts just for looking. It's good to compare rock bottom prices with the stall vendors and the shops within the resort as there is often a severe price difference.One tip I would give for anyone visiting this hotel would be to take effective insect repellent. I came away from the resort with a very high number of mosquito bites, mostly on my ankles and feet. We were told when we arrived that you can purchase insect repellent patches (similar to a nicotine patch) that I would definitely buy if I returned to the DR.Overall I highly recommend this hotel to anyone, we had an amazing holiday and I'm sure you would to if you went.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>