<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="1fe1d66cd7de1cc48a51e6bd70beeec0" url=""><![CDATA[P-E-R-F-E-C-T Vacation First of all, my Husband and I are in our early 60s and this was our first trip to Punta Cana, as well as our first time at an all-inclusive resort. We booked our trip (8/13 through Liberty Travel (Kimberly Scharf) in St. James, NY. We had direct non-stop flights on American Airlines from JFK.ARRIVAL: We arrived at the Majestic at approximately 4:00PM and were personally greeted with an icy cold Majestic and welcomed by Annemarie (who is a very sweet and lovely young lady) at the check-in counter. She made sure we made our dinner reservations at LeGourmet (French) and Matsuri (Teppanyaki) before she personally escorted us to our room (#2127) was one of the four room choices we had originally requested). Upon entering our room, we found a Welcome Platter and a Bottle of Champagne on the table to welcome us. That personal touch made us feel special right from the start.ROOM: We were in a Majestic Junior Suite (which is a Ground Floor Swim-Out Suite) in Building #2 along the Swimming Pool, directly across the Pool from the Spa. Our room was in the middle of the resort (between the Lobby and the Beach) where it is quieter. This room category is Adults Only. Our room had a slightly musty odor (which is common in the Caribbean), but Lysol Spray took care of that in a very short time. The room was large and very clean. The air conditioning was very comfortable and the ceiling fan circulated the cool air throughout the room. We took the advice from prior TA Reports and brought two of our own flat rubber stoppers (for the jacuzzis) and an automatic night light (which we placed in the outlet by the sink). We also brought RAID Flying Insect Spray with us to spray our room each day for any mosquitoes that may have gotten into the room, but we never had a problem.ROOM SERVICE: They have a very limited menu, but on several occasions we found the Club Sandwiches for lunch while relaxing on our private terrace to be very good, along with a bottle of Presidente from our mini-bar, which was fully stocked daily.TAP WATER: Do NOT drink or use tap water to brush your teeth or to rinse your mouth or toothbrush. We used only Bottled Water and had NO problems. Be sure to keep your mouth closed and be careful not to swallow any water while showering.SUNSCREEN: We brought SPF-60, 45, 30 and 15 along with us. We both started with SPF-60 on the first day and got very little color. My husband (who is obviously smarter than me) continued to use SPF-60 throughout our entire stay and came home with a nice golden tan. I, on the other hand, thought I knew better, and decided to step down to SPF-45 on the second day and ended up burning rather badly on my chest and arms blisters and all. Only you know how badly you will burn in a very strong sun VERY CAREFUL.BEACH OCEAN: The beach is absolutely gorgeous with soft white powdery sand. There were always plenty of palapas and lounges on the beach to relax in the shade. The ocean was always calm and crystal clear during our entire stay. The water temperature was very warm (at least 85 degrees).SWIMMING POOL: There were also plenty of palapas and lounges in the various areas around the Pool. The Pool was always very clean and warm (sometimes actually too warm and more like a bath). Be sure to bring your own Pool Float(s) with you to float around on as the resort does NOT provide them.BARSWET BAR (Swim-Up Bar): This bar is located near the Beach end of the Swimming Pool. They serve drinks on the Pool side (as a Swim-Up Bar) as well as on the Land side where they have several tables chairs. Be sure to say Maximo at the Wet Bar (on the Swim-Up side). He is the one who is always smiling and saying Everyone seems to love him and when you meet him, you will definitely know why.BEACH BAR: This bar is located in the center of La Hispaniola which is located in the Palapa Hut on the Beach.LOBBY BAR: This bar is located in the lower Lobby and is a gathering place from 5:00PM Whether it be a cocktail before dinner or a night cap after dinner, be sure to say Pedro and Alejandro, who are both a lot of fun and make great Dirty Monkeys and Mojitos.PIANO BAR: This bar is located in the upper Lobby. They have live piano music in the evening. Be sure to say Roberto. He is also a great guy.PLAZA BAR: This bar is located outside in front of the Buffet Supreme. They have live music in the evening with plenty of tables to sit at while relaxing with your favorite beverage.CASINO: The casino is small, but not too small to have a little fun in after dinner. There are 3 or 4 tables and about 20 slot machines ($.01 - $.05 - $.25). The casino also has a small bar to the left as you enter.RESTAURANTSBUFFET SUPREME: This restaurant is located adjacent to the lower Lobby. The only meal we ate at the Buffet was a huge breakfast each morning, which is my favorite meal and which we both enjoyed very much. They had several different food stations: Omelettes Eggs Toast Fruit Fruit Smoothies They also had a buffet table with bacon (the best I ever had), ham, sausage, etc. You will find practically anything you could possibly want at this buffet. The Chocolate Croissants are to die for.LA HISPANIOLA: This restaurant is located in the Palapa Hut on the Beach. It serves a continental breakfast in the late morning and lunch and afternoon snacks during the day. (In the evening, this restaurant becomes the Steak/Seafood Restaurant, which is separated by the Beach Bar, for dinner.) We ate lunch here a few times and found the Pasta Station to be the best choice. They had several different kinds of freshly cooked Pasta (cooked in front of you) along with 3 different Sauces (Tomato Sauce Sauce Sauce). I tried all 3 Sauces and they were all very good. My husband also had a Panini Sandwich one day for lunch and he liked it very much.LE GOURMET (French): This restaurant is located in the lower Lobby and is Adults Only. The food and service were both excellent. choices: Filet of Beef Snapper We both had the Filet of Beef which was very tender and very good. The only thing we did not care for was the spice used in the gravy served on top of the filet. It was a rather strong-tasting spice that was unfamiliar to us.MATSURI (Teppanyaki): This restaurant is located in the lower Lobby and has two separate rooms (each room seats 12 people) around a Teppanyaki grill. choices: Filet Mignon Each person is allowed to choose 2 out of 4 choices. Since there were 2 of us, we ordered all 4 choices to share between us and each of us got to taste a little of everything. Our was served with Fried Rice. Everything was superb and we also enjoyed the Teppanyaki unique presentation.TRES CARABELAS (Seafood): This restaurant is located in the Palapa Hut on the Beach. A few small tables overlook the pool. choices: Grilled Lobster Snapper Shrimp. We ate dinner here 3 times. We had Grilled Lobster 2 or 3 times and each time it was cooked to perfection tender and very tasty. My husband also had the Garlic Shrimp and he enjoyed that very much as well.RODEO STEAK HOUSE (Steak): This restaurant is also located in the Palapa Hut on the Beach. It is separated from Tres Carabelas (Seafood) by the Beach Bar. choices: Chateaubriand Chops We ate dinner here 2 times and each time we enjoyed the Chateaubriand with Bearnaise Sauce served on the side. Both times the Filet was very tender and juicy and cooked exactly the way we ordered it RARE.LA BODEGUITA DEL MAJESTIC: This is a late-night Snack Bar and is open from 11:00PM It is located on Caribbean Street near the Casino and Sports Bar. My husband had the Deep Fried Hot Wings and Nachos with Cheese several times and he enjoyed them both.CONCLUSION: We both had a wonderful and memorable vacation in Punta Cana and look forward to returning to the Majestic in the very near future. We found the resort to be very clean and beautiful, our accommodations to be very comfortable, the dining choices to be numerous and the food quality to be far more than acceptable (based on US (Northeast) standards). The Dominican people are extremely hard-working. Most of them work 16-hour days and as many as 12 consecutive days (or even more) before getting 2 or 3 days off. Some of them actually live at the resort and away from their families because it is too long a distance for them to commute on a daily basis. We found the Dominican people to be some of the friendliest and nicest class of people we have ever had the privilege or pleasure of meeting while on vacation. Instead of feeling like strangers in a foreign country (which is what we really were) always felt welcome and like we belonged because of the way the Dominican people reached out to us and welcomed us into their Country. Even though we did not speak their native (Spanish) language fluently am sure they knew that we were at least trying to communicate with them in their native language. I would highly recommend this resort to friends and family everywhere.Liked: EverythingDisliked: Nothing
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>