<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="1b076a066159e42f510330984e510e49" url=""><![CDATA[Okay Hotel The hotel rooms are much too small. There was only about two feet of space when you walked into the room. There was no room to put suitcases. We cleared off the space above the TV for my husbands and put mine on the floor under the TV. I don't think I'd ever stayed in a room so small.The A/C either makes the room too hot or too cold. We were constantly making adjustments (even in the middle of the night). The air also seemed to blow directly down. We couldn't find a way to adjust it.We found the bar prices to be a bit high. We had a Mai Tai at Duke's for $7, and they were $9 at the hotel bar, and it was made with lesser quality ingredients (in my opinion). The restaurant prices seemed high, so we never ate there, so I can't give a review on that.The beach was almost a private beach for the hotel. It was quiet and peaceful. (Compared to Waikiki) The hotel lent us mats and towels to use. This was very nice.The bellman is also the valet, towel lender, direction-giver, luggage checker, etc. They need another person to assist with this job. We had to wait frequently, because we couldn't find the bellman, because he was outside somewhere or giving directions.Also, we had a later flight, so we asked if we could leave the bags while we walked around a bit, since checkout was at noon. They said it was fine. They had a room to put them in. We waited for the bellman, and he gave us a tag for our luggage. When we returned, we found our luggage still stacked in the lobby next to the desk. We were able to just take our luggage and walk out. No one ever questioned if it was our luggage or verified we had the tag for it. Not very secure.The walk to Waikiki was about 15 minutes. Not bad, but if I had to do it again, I would stay closer to the main beach for activities and a larger room and walk down to the beach by this hotel. Also, the buses no longer run on the road by the hotel, so you need to walk over to the zoo to catch the bus (not a bad walk 5-10 minutes), but not as convenient as described in another review).
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>