<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="13f0a70b05836ff4507770ea9dfb5039" url=""><![CDATA[Don't stay here unless you're a tourist, or a Gold HH Member I just want to comment on this hotel based on the other reviews. This is a nice hotel if you get a room on the Executive Floor. If you're not a Gold Member, and you're here for business longer than two nights, then you'll start to miss the typical business amenities.I stayed here for a week, and had a single bed. I complained because quite frankly, I couldn't sleep in it without feeling like I was going to fall out of bed. I'd never been offered a single bed for business travel in my entire career, so I never expected to see one on my first trip to Tokyo.I also think that in general, if you are female, and in my case, I am also Asian, I am occasionally subjected to second-class service. I think this is a common complaint by most female executive travelers. But that's a whole other traveling issue. Long story short, I am spoiled by American hotels and big comfy beds. Since I travel mostly for work, the bed is the most important part of the room. I don't fault this hotel entirely, but the truth is, I was judged as someone who could tolerate inferior accommodations as compared to my six-foot non-Asian colleague who would have been given the double bed without hesitation.If you don't fit my profile, you'll probably do fine at this hotel. If you are a Hilton Honors Gold member then you will score high with all the proper business amenities. I am terribly disappointed because I have no safe in my room to lock up my electronic gadgets and computer when I'm out at customer meetings. I am disappointed about my bed of course. I am disappointed that there is no complimentary coffee in the room (there is coffee you can buy through mini bar for about $6 US, my company doesn't reimburse mini-bar charges either.) I am also disappointed that access to the gym will cost me $20 US dollars per use. My company doesn't reimburse for gym fees, so I'd have to shell out $140 of my own money (weeks stay) in order to keep myself in shape for these long haul flights into Asia. The food is outrageously expensive. I couldn't get a bowl of fruit for less than $10 us dollars, and it was canned fruit! There isn't anything to like about this hotel, and it rates very low compared to US Hilton Hotels for business travel. I have to give it a low score just so other business travelers will be cautious in case they can't get an upgrade to the Executive Floor. The non-Executive floors have very tiny bathrooms, meant for small-framed people. Frankly, this hotel should just charge more money and give me what I need rather than nickeling and diming us to death.What's good about the hotel? The airport shuttleIt's cleanThe service is decentIt's centrally locatedGood luck!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bc0be35ce504410b0d20e6ceee3ef94d" url=""><![CDATA[Luner New Year at the Langham Place This is an excellent hotel with excellent service in one of the most historic parts of Kowloon. It's going to be my home away from home whenever I visit or work in Hong Kong. The MTR is right downstairs, there's plenty of outside restaurants and shopping inside the connected mall, and even a theater next door if you've got time for a movie.PROS: Convenient to everythingBeautiful rooms, small but efficientFlat screen TVComplimentary tea, coffee, and daily bottled waterRoom serviceWonderful bed and linensInteresting glass bathroomDirect shuttle to and from the airportGreat serviceImmaculateNear all sorts of transportationCONS:The restaurant is okay, and pretty expensiveI did not experience any cranky concierge...rather the opposite. Efficient and attentive. I like that kind of service. For the price, I paid a little of $200 US per day, I felt like I got my money's worth.I recommend this place to anyone who is adventurous and wants to really taste Hong Kong.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>