<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="44acf09fa64c3d5d908e48303e9431b6" url=""><![CDATA[Hooray for Hollywood ... Renaissance!!! What a great hotel! From the early check-in, to the clean, stylish and QUIET room. Great city and Hollywood Hills views and the best location ever. The room rate included a full breakfast at their restaurant Twist and free admission to Universal Studios. Also the restaurants in the complex (Vert and Trastevere) were excellant.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b5134b5a138850e21adff762a05a33a9" url=""><![CDATA[Disappointing! The pluses, the Stanford Court has a great location, we had a wonderful city view from our room, and the mattress and linens were top notch. Unfortunately it went down from there. The rooms are tired looking, even though they have recently been re-painted and wallpapered, along with new rugs and drapes. The furnishings are old and tired, a cane and rattan headboard just doesn't cut it in a luxury hotel. Some basics like an in-room safe and mini-bar are nowhere to be found. Coke and Ice Machines are located on the 2nd floor, not very convenient. A circa 1980's TV took up half the bathroom counterspace. Bathroom and dressing areas are tired and worn. Breakfast at the restaurant is top dollar, in the $30 (with tax and tip) per person range. I guess the room rates are reasonable for San Francisco, but the hotel is need of renovation. Even the lobby and lobby bar are tired and seem like they haven't been renovated in years.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="df03b4597967edc8aabac127044c20c9" url=""><![CDATA[3 Star Hotel At 5 Star Prices Can't believe the rates at El Convento!!We stayed one night pre-cruise at nearly $500 per night. Definitely overpriced for the product being offered. 3PM check-in turned into 3:45PM due to the very pleasant staff being over worked due to understaffing. We were offered a rather unpleasant room, which we rejected and ultimately were offered a bay view room after another 30 minute wait at the front desk.All metal surfaces in our room and in the public areas are showing signs of rust. All plastered surfaces are either cracked or mottled. Any repairs that have been made, such as painting, plastering, etc. have been performed substandard.Rooms are small and dark. Bathrooms are smaller yet and in need of renovation.Tenament views on the first 3 floors just add to the disappointment.The Taxes and Hotel Tariff of over $90 per night are ridiculous.The hotel does have its' charm, very atmospheric including all of the restaurants. Of course all venues are high priced. $25 for breakfast, $35 for tapas lunch.Wine and cheese on the deck is nice touch.At $250 per night (tax and tariff included) it's a very acceptable experience.Think Doubletree not the Ritz Carlton.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2690c08d9e632f330bbe97ff86fed52d" url=""><![CDATA[Can't get excited! After reading the reviews on this website my expectations were high. The hotel didn't strike me as very architecturally interesting either inside or out. Surely not in the league of the Plaza in New York, or the Palace in San Francisco. Front desk didn't have a non-smoking room in our room category so we were downgrade to a regular room. The room was large but plain, with not much of a view.Hotel is not very user friendly, newspaper delivered on Saturday but not Sunday, no coffeemaker in the room, not much of a selection in the mini-bar. The most attractive public space, the Terrace Room is not available to guests, only private functions. The breakfast restaurant was empty, I guess the prices keep non expense account guests far away.As I said, can't get excited!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>