<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="9e70356ab141c93d6d2e2ba4b0fd1583" url=""><![CDATA[Not my favorite Sheraton Usually Starwood is my favorite chain, but this Sheraton is a dud. Hotel staff were average... we had to ask several times for housekeeping to put a sheet on the bed (for some reason, all they kept putting on was a comforter and it wasn't always clean, and we had to call four times for our mini-bar to be cleared out so we could use the fridge. The concierges were sometimes ok, but many times they kept telling us to ask one of the others that would be on site the next day (why hire concierges that don't know where things are?) and there was on that was less than competant. (Very disappointing.) The location was good... near Darling Harbor, so that was nice. The room was clean-ish, but I just didn't get the feeling that it was well-kept. If you stay here, stay on the Harbor side, the view is worth it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="480f8d74d85f15f3fccdc4b5be761664" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel / great service! Stayed at the St. Regis for work. What a great place. It's rated 4 stars, but I'd say it's a 5 star. Great pool, great gym, great hotel room, superior service. Everything was super comfortable and I really loved having a tv built into the wall in the bathroom by the bathtub. I really loved this place...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8a6ca47a44f74f1871831a2d64e7bc9d" url=""><![CDATA[A taste of Berlin (old and new) This is a pretty intersting place. Great views -- right outside of the hotel is the Brandenburg Gate (and a Starbucks across the street -- old meet new!) The rooms are pretty comfortable and the beds are decent. The wireless connections are speedy (although expensive). If you're a vegetarian, you won't find anything to eat at the hotel, but there is quite a bit in walking distance. (We took a Hop On, Hop Off tour where the bus picked us up on the other side of the gate.) The gym is small, but has decent machines and free weights (and free bottles of water.) We ran a business event at the hotel, and everything went very smoothly. Great service.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>