<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="971877d8a4d3b1f886f249ed1cb2e938" url=""><![CDATA[Awesome for early AM flight Wow! what a suprise. We stayed at the this property for one night (July 3) with my wife and two children (4 and 18 months). Check in was faster than I have ever experienced and had a newly renovated room on the 7th floor overlooking the airport (the parking garage actually). Room was larger than I expected (two double beds) and had plenty of room for the porta crib. The bellmen were very helpful with bags and even set the crib up for us. My Son and I went swimming and a had a great time. The beds were super comfortable and we slept well (very quiet). The hotel was not busy (very slow) but I don't think that would change if it was busy.Check out was very efficient. The shuttle comes every 15 minutes, and is less than five minutes from the airport.We will definatly stay here again if we have an early AM flight.Great job on this property Marriott. I'm a big fan.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="03f0c30ac734ff44f6eb6872428c72c3" url=""><![CDATA[Not a 3* property (anymore that is) Stayed at this property for one night (2/21) with my wife, prior to an early AM departure.Parked my car off site, as I didn't want to pay $12.00 a night for parking. Shuttle picked us up at the airport within five minutes. Quick trip to hotel (Driver was friendly and helpful).Check in was very convenient and quick. Front desk folks were very nice. Lobby looked nice with good looking lounge/bar downstairs. This is about the end of anything good at this property.We were assigned a room on the 8th floor (a smaller king room, according to the nice guy at the front desk). He was right. very small King room, with a bathroom that looked like the size of a broom closet. No way two people could fit in that bathroom at one time.The room had a work station, king bed, small chair in the corner and an older 27 inch tube tv. The bed was uncomfortable and the pillows were not very nice...really could not find a combination that worked for us. The outside room noise related to airport traffic and plane take off and landing is pretty significant. I think only slept well between 2-4 am, when I was not hearing plane noise.The room was old and needed updating. Old linens, furnature, etc...what I would expect at a 2* property.The check out was easy, and shuttle ride to the aiport was quick and less than 5 minutes.If you want a hotel that is great for location, nice people and prompt shuttle service this would be the place...but if you are looking for a good night sleep, nice rooms....look someplace else.This place had be a good 3* at one point. But now, I could only give it 2.5 due to the amenities it offers.We had a great rate through priceline, so maybe that's why we got shafted in a small gross room, but I can't imagine any other room on the 8th floor being much better.Good luck!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="87cf16e1c76e1c00e61a08174797b532" url=""><![CDATA[Another Great Stay-Trip # 3 for us at the VP My wife and I stayed at the VP for one night. This was our third time staying at the property. The first time was on a Priceline Bid, and fell in love with it. We booked a package deal that included a bottle of wine upon check in and free parking. (parking is expensive at all Seattle DT hotels, usually $25-30 per night).We booked a King Premier room. It is a bit more expensive, but worth it to have some extra room. If you book this room, ask for a room that ends with 02 (7002, 8002, etc,)..These rooms are bit lager than the others. We stayed in room 1010 this time, and found out the hard way the 02 rooms are a bit roomier.As usual the staff was friendy and cooperative. Check in and out was extremely swift, and our car was retrieved in less than five minutes.The evening wine tasting from 5-6 is always a bonus. Good wine, nice atmosphere and very relaxing. Only complaint was some late arriving folks at around 3 am next door that were very loud in the hallway. Other than that, our stay was exactly what we were looking for.if you are looking for some personal attention, less crowds and fantastic accomodations stay the VP. This property does not have a pool, and is not ideal for kids..but for adults staying on business or leisure get-a-ways it's fantastic. It is close to all downtown shopping and sites. Again, I highly endorse the VP and will stay here again in the future!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c9f630d606c71c242d95b2a24c0e447d" url=""><![CDATA[Good Option Downtown, Nice new tower! Stayed at the Seattle Sheraton for one night in December before the Holidays. Have stayed here in the past, and enjoyed returning to the remodeled lobby and new tower. Stayed in the new tower in a corner King (very nice room). Booked the Macy's gift card special, 212, for room and a 100 gift card to Macy's. Not a bad deal for the room at 112.Check in was very fast. The new tower is a bit of walk to the elevators, so if that is an issue, I would ask for the old tower. As others have said the pool and gym are not in the new tower, so getting to the pool/gym, you must walk through the main lobby and go up to the 35th floor of the old tower.Room was fantastic, with a good view of Puget Sound (in between other buildings of course). This property is very close to all major shopping, dining, etct in DT Seattle. The Market is three blocks down the street (tough neighborhood, so be aware on your walk).Parking is brutal, but it is brutal everyplace downtown. Valet is the only option and is 27 a night. We used the Valet due to convenience. They were fast and efficient, unlike other posts have mentioned. I did call in advance to the Valet and ask if my car could be brought up. Both times it was waiting when I arrived 10 minutes later. If you don't need your car, park down by the Seattle Center (much cheaper) and take the monorail to Westlake Center. Hotel is only a few blocks from the Westlake Center. You can also park on the weekends in parking structures around the area for much cheaper, but during the business week it is a wash (five bucks less, and much more of a hassle). Again the new wing is very modern and nice. Typical 4* starwood property. Nothing wrong with the old wing, just a little more worn out and needs some TLC. Did not use room service this time, but in the past it was pretty good. No complaints.I would recommend this property.I have also noted that it is frequently bid on through priceline for 99 a night. That would be well worth it for either wing.Have fun in Seattle. We are local and love going downtown for a night here and then. Would gladly stay at the Sheraton again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>