<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="16ab1ce03c7b8810ceabc60f695b89bf" url=""><![CDATA[Decent place to stay, great value My wife and I stayed there about a year ago when the Ramada on Bourbon was full. The price for this hotel was right, and I left fairly pleased.The rooms were a little small and a bit outdated, but they were clean and functional. The staff was helpful enough, if unexceptional, and there were no major issues during our stay.Location - for many people going to New Orleans, location can make or break the trip. Even though the French Quarter is not geographically large, there is quite a difference in the areas you can visit. I would recommend this hotel for families who want to visit New Orleans and get a clean room for a great price in a fairly quiet location. The area is perfectly safe, and it is fairly removed from the Bourbon St scene. However, if you are looking for a quick walk back to your hotel after a night on Bourbon, you may want to look somewhere else. It is a bit of a hike, but not too far as long as you aren't falling over inebriated.All in all, it was a suitable replacement for my normal New Orleans hotel. Price was great, hotel was clean, and I was happy. Families should definitely check this place out.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b56c222c75e40bd779179e6f2b208d36" url=""><![CDATA[Decent choice for first time visitor to Amsterdam My wife and I stayed at the Victoria for 6 nights, and had a pretty good experience in all areas. I would definitely recommend this to anyone who is visiting Amsterdam for the first time.I booked this hotel as part of a travel package on Priceline, which gave an amazing rate for this hotel. I read some of the earlier reviews and was hopeful our experience would be better than some of the reviews I read. It was!We arrived at Schipol at about 1030 AM after an all night flight from Houston. Jumped on the train to Centraal Station, and 20 minutes later we were in the center of town. Walk just across the road (You can't miss the hotel) and we were attempting to check in at about 1115. The room was not ready yet but an extremely helpful bellman offered to take our luggage for us, which allowed us to go explore for a couple hours. The room was nice, clean, and fairly large by European standards. While it is certainly not a 4 star hotel, everything was in good working order and the mini-bar, safe, and bathroom were all working well and in good shape. There have been some renovations over the past two years, and I understand that some of the rooms need a little work, but everything I saw was clean, neat, and tidy. Breakfast I would not do unless it is included in your rate. They want 20 Euros pp and that is a little pricey for breakfast when you can get better and more food for a lot less. The bar and restaurant are nice enough, but a tad pricey considering what you can get 5 minutes away. Go to Barney's on Haarlemmerstraat and have fun for half the price!Throughout our 6 nights, we did not experience one problem. The room was cleaned every day, the front desk was always very busy but extremely friendly, and the concierge was the best part of the stay. Granted, they are going to want a few Euros thrown at them, but they are the best I have seen anywhere in the world. For a 5 Euro note each day, they will make reservations and tour bookings for you, give you inside info on where to shop, eat, drink, etc. Again, it may cost you 30-50 Euros throughout your trip, but they can make your vacation a little more pleasant and a little less difficult.Now, would I stay there again and would I recommend others to stay there? Depends on what you are looking for and what you want to do in Amsterdam. For a first timer, I would say yes. The reason being is that for many first timers, it can be a difficult city to navigate due to the concentric nature of the layout. This hotel eliminates your need for a taxi from the airport (50 Euro each way!), it eliminates a need for a Taxi once you get to Central Station (just walk across the street), and it is right at the main Tram lines which are easy to use and will take you literally anywhere in the city you can think of. No walking long distances back to your hotel late at night, everything right there for you. No carrying your luggage throughout the city upon arrival and check out (you would be amazed how many people have to do that). It's just easy, simply put. You are about 3-5 minutes walk from the Red-Light District to your east, and about 2 minutes walk to Voorburgwal on yoru right, which is a big time touristy street with shops and clubs. The hotel is certainly not in an unsafe area, but keep in mind that being sandwiched in between 2 big tourist areas means that it is in an area of a lot of tacky souvenier stores and people wanting to sell you things.In terms of being close to other places, everything is easy on the tram, which is right outside Centraal Station. Walk to Anne Frank Huis about 10 minutes, Leidesplein is about 25 minutes or 10 minute tram ride. Dam Square 5-10 minute walk, and Rijksmuseum/Van Gogh/Heineken Museums all about 30 minute walk or 10 minute tram ride.The next time my wife and I visit, I would probably look for something in Jordaan or down near De Pijp, which are both close to the center but a little quieter and a few less tourists. But if I couldn't get something in those areas for a good price and had to stay there again, I certainly would. Think of it like going to NYC and staying in Times Square. Kind of tacky, but safe, clean, and close to a LOT.That being said, nothing wrong with this particular place. Great location, nice people, convenient, and clean.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>