<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="6e0ce58c8b03f32e973b18ff61dd0c3a" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel The hotel was under renovation when I visited, so I had to use a side door, but when my cab arrived there were doormen on the sidewalk to direct me to the right place. It's apparent Sheraton has taken steps to minimize inconvenience during the construction. The construction wasn't a problem when I got to my room though. It was on a high floor as I requested and was located well away from the construction. I only wish the Club Lounge was open all day like those at Ritz-Carlton. I tend to sleep late and always miss out on the continental breakfast!The 35th floor pool and jacuzzi had excellent views. The jacuzzi didn't work, but it was nice to sit in anyway. I think they overcholorinate the pool though. It was nice to have changing rooms at the hotel pool; I don't like to wander through a grand hotel in my swimsuit on my way to/from the pool!Pike's Place Cafe used to have such wonderful regional cuisine; they've since replaced the menu there and for room service with the new Sheraton standard. I like to experience regional cuisine when I travel, but I must admit, the carrot cake on Sheraton's menu is to die for!Guest service at this property is intuitive. When I asked the front desk for the location of the nearest cellular telephone store so I could buy a new charger for my cell phone, the clerk produced a box of them from housekeeping. Apparently a lot of guests leave cell phone chargers in their rooms and he allowed me to pick out the one that matched from the box!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3b7f5379876c8ede7dd7a17562c00bfc" url=""><![CDATA[Very Enjoyable! Upon first impression the Westin New York at Times Square is lovely; it's nice to have an entrance lobby at street level, and a quiet, removed lobby on another level. Definitely appreciated. The hotel decor is modern and tasteful. There are many check-in desks with a well marked area for Starwood Preferred Guest Gold and Platinum members. There was not a wait at check-in for any agent. I'm always pleased when a hotel has my room ready before the stated check-in time. The rooms are excellent! I admit the television was a flat screen which was particularly subject to light from the window, but that was easily fixed. The rooms are very well decorated and have that squeaky clean feel I expect from large chain hotels, but manage also to be comfortable and homey at the same time. The only problem with my stay was inattentive service at breakfast. The service staff didn't offer any beverage refills, and the staff was rather mechanical. Take order, bring order, bring check. I understand breakfast service isn't incredibly complex, but a little intuition on the part of guest needs would be appreciated. I mentioned my displeasure with the service to a front desk agent, who apologized, but made no other gesture. At Sheraton, any complaint is usually handled with some form of compensation. I was not *completely* satisfied due to the situation of service in the restaurant, but I'm sure it was a fluke. Westin at least has their concepts down right, and the facilities are wonderful.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="382e835b522db06e845703bb8bc5ca2a" url=""><![CDATA[Hyatt Century Plaza top-notch Century Plaza was wonderful. I arrived late and asked to have a colleague able to check into my room for me. WhenI spoke to the front desk to follow up, as soon as I gave my name, without looking at my record, the front desk agent said Oh, your colleague has just checked in. That is some good service. Throughout my short stay, the front desk offered amazing service. However, the hotel restaurant falls short of expectation. The food alternated between high quality and mediocre, but the service was slow and the staff seemed confused.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="602114103c6699757e47d86ceb33357d" url=""><![CDATA[Seattle's Best! Arrived very late in the evening for a one night stay. Staff were very solicitous, and on par with the hotel's service standards, each request was met with of course. All staff were pleasant, rooms were comfortably furnished with the latest innovations in guest room design, baths were wonderful. Even for a one night stay, this property was the best I've experienced in Seattle. Special kudos to the Pan Pacific for staff training; this is the best formal service I've received in a long time!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>