<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="e18503baf8192890467ddc4c54fd4c52" url=""><![CDATA[Loved the Spa, hated the hotel Dallas is definitely not the LA of the South, no matter what other reviewers may have said. I've lived here for 5 years and trust me, Dallas is just another big suburban city in the mid-west that now has a fancy hotel to flaunt. Having said that, don't stay here. Here's why:1) You HAVE to valet your car, and for those of you who might not realize how horribly inconvenient this is, I'll explain: every time you park your car you have to pay 5 dollars plus tip for the valet service. And once you get there, you'd better not need your car again until you're going somewhere important because the line to get your car back in the evenings is HORRENDOUS. I came just to use the spa once, and after my treatment waited no less than 20 minutes in a line full of drunks just to pay $5 to drive my car home. The couple behind me had to wait in the line too, and all they needed was to get something out of their car that they'd left when they checked in (the Valets can't tell you where your car is for some reason, so you won't be able to run to your car to get something by yourself).2) The staff was nice enough to me (though not as nice as at the Crescent), but the other guests were just awful. Basically, the W is the type of place to stay if your self-esteem is based on the cost of your clothes. I am by no means poor, but walking through that lobby in my casual wear I was looked at like a leper. The crowd at this hotel is basically the nouveu-riche set of Dallas.3) The bar scene in Dallas is nothing too special. Ghost Bar stays true to that. While the scenery may be pretty neat, the crowd is the same as I described above. If you're a young woman like me, you will be dealing with a bunch of 50 year old men who think they can buy you, and a bunch of highly metrosexual young men who will try to impress you with their $300 t-shirts. For dance music I suggest Lizard Lounge (where Fatboy Slim and Paul Oakenfold go to play when they tour here), Club One, Zubar, Minc Lounge, among others, where the people are friendly, the drinks are cheap, and the music is much cooler. Don't go to Ghost Bar where you'll pay $12 a drink just to wait in line 30 minutes and be treated by the club staff like you're a nobody.Basically, the other reviewer was right, this place is very see and be seen. However, if you are the type of person who couldn't give a flying explitive about being seen by whoever might see you at this hotel it's not worth it.If you're looking for a real unique Dallas experience stay at ZaZa (the Dragonfly is great), the Adolphus downtown, or Crescent Court (the staff there is AMAZING and the rooms are fantastic, there are also some great restaurants there you will be talking about long after you leave). All those hotels are the same price or cheaper than the W, the people are nicer, and you get much more for what you pay. They are also in better neighborhoods. You can actually walk to bars and clubs from the Crescent and ZaZa, whereas at the W, since the Victory Plaza isn't completed, you're going to have to drive or get cabs everywhere (especially because Dallas is a very dangerous city - DON'T walk from the W anywhere unless you know where you're going, ZaZa and Crescent are in the middle of everything, though, so it's pretty safe to walk from them).Having said all that I will say that Bliss Spa is GREAT and you should definitely make time to go there no matter where you stay. The only drawback is that it's in the W and if you go after 5 you will have to deal with drunks wandering around and being loud (I swear the W hosts huge private parties every night, the elevators are usually pretty full of rediculous people!). Bliss is expensive, but worth every penny.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>