<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="fef7296dfa0d25e98a2aefcd6786ecad" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent, Splendid, Superb Hotel My favorite hotel chain is the Mandarin Oriental. And this one is a perfect example why. It made our Tokyo visit just marvelous. Service is top-notch. Terrific room with stunning views. Quality, first-rate furnishings and beddings. Heated toilet seat! Spa was magnificent. Over-all first class.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="61a41dd10c8c08b4a4a8d7435b5dab74" url=""><![CDATA[Disappointed I always check the tripadvisor website for hotel reviews before I decide which hotel to book and so far it has never failed me till I stayed here. 1. Someone from their management cancelled my reservation, good thing I had the confirmation letter they sent by email printed out with me. I arrived late that night and was really tired. The guy at the front apologized and instead of giving me a better room for the inconvenience tried to downgrade me because of the unavailability of the room I originally booked.There was a girl who happen to just wander by from management as well who had to help him get me a better room ( hellooo !!!- this is what youre supposed to do).2. The one bedroom suite was ok. There is no TV in the living room area. Bed was comfortable.3. Hotel close to a sketchy area.4. They did not clean my room one of the nights.5. Camus restaurant was fabulous however.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a14b9433fc26eb40cb92e186713aa0ab" url=""><![CDATA[Will stay there again, maybe Just ended my four night spirit of lifepackage with them. I was greeted by the butler on arrival who led me to my room which I thought was great because it was personal. I stayed in a one bedroom casita with a balcony that overlooked the ocean. This was wonderful. However, the room is not quite 5-star. It was old and needs to be refurbished. The bathroom also looked pretty used. It was clean however. The service was wonderful. They catered to my every need. Food was just ok. The spa was fabulous. The housestaff were all friendly and courteous. Great tennis lessons from Juan. I will stay there again maybe if they put me up in the new area that they are currently building.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>