<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="3ae9abdb2f33e634a9b8af5bb397e753" url=""><![CDATA[impeccable Lovely hotel in the heart of Barcelona. We stayed at Hotel 1898 in June 2008 for 2 nights. We really enjoyed our stay at the hotel but the rooms are a little small, especially at a night. We had a terrace so that helped, otherwise we would have felt too squashed in. We stayed in room 526, which was on the 5th floor, facing the back of the building. The rooms were extremely clean and always had fresh towels and bed linen. The bathroom was lovely and with me being 6'2 the bath was ample. As for the rest of the hotel, the spa in the basement was nice, but the water in the pool was extremely cold. Almost to the point of shivering, the steam room was not working either! We found that it would have been nicer if someone from the hotel had shown us around first as it was a little off putting just walking round free roam. The roof top bar/pool was ok. The bar is extremely expensive, for a gin and tonic. The pool on the roof is very small, the photos on the hotel website make the pool out to be bigger than it actually is, also there is no where to change on the roof so if you are wanting a quick dip in the pool, forget about it. You would have to walk back through the hotel dripping wet. Also we couldn't find any dry towels on the roof on 2 occasions. We didn't have breakfast in the hotel as for it seemed expensive. Plus the hotel has a door into the Starbucks next door so we just went there {be warned though that in Barcelona none of the Starbucks Menus had a translation so unless you are fluent in spanish/catalan you might just have to guess}.We had drinks in the reception area of the hotel, but again very expensive and the quality was nothing special. They had very little choice if you didn't drink alcohol, which is the norm in Barcelona from what we found. We found that the hotel staff didn't really speak to us much, even though they had door staff and reception staff. This was a little off putting. We were able to check in at 12 o'clock which was nice. The music system in the room didn't work at all and the TV was almost unwatchable, very fuzzy! for a night you would expect these things to work. The pillows and bed were lovely though. Very gay friendly in the hotel, we had no issues with that. If anyone has any questions feel free to contact me x
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>