<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="ddc88c1e17eee0c472c0ce379dcf0488" url=""><![CDATA[On-site at FRA but feels like a million miles away Super convenient access from the terminals makes this a #1 choice in my book. After picking up your baggage, you can literally walk up/down/left/right, depending on your origination point and within 5 minutes you're at check-in. Signage is at a minimum, look outside for the big Sheraton sign on the left, or head up to Departures area C and you'll see the hotel crosswalk. Service was surprisingly slow. I booked a Club Level room which was spacious and clean, however, I didn't see the snack area other reviewers have mentioned. Room service was efficient and tasty. If you need an iron, you must request one! The gym spa are new and lightly used... not to mention an awesome way to blow off steam.If you're willing to experiment, try the Oxygen Bar, where they serve pure O2 to refresh weary travelers.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="764bca5cb59001ab0f9a297dcb161ca8" url=""><![CDATA[Nice but not worth the price As many other reviewers have commented, my wife and I felt the MO was nice - but not worth the price. We stayed in a Premier Park View Room, on the 46th floor for 3 nights over New Year's Eve. Upon walking in the room, the first thing you notice is the gigantic, black Trump Tower that filled 30-40% of the park view! The bellman dropped that when the MO opened, Trump hung a banner on his hotel goading guests with a better view -- not surprising.The room was spacious and well equipped. The bed was super comfortable, in the same class as the Heavenly bed at the Westin and W hotels. The electronics (TV, stereo, etc.) were mediocre and had to be rebooted several times during our stay when the TV wouldn't turn on, change channels, etc. A modern Tivo and other components would do a much better job. The bathroom was large and very nice, but only had one sink. Although we were offered tea at check-in, we ordered coffee when we got into the room. The bill was $26 for a small pot!We spent a half-day in the MO Spa, which was fantastic. The VIP room has a private shower, soaking tub, bathroom, day bed and massage tables. The spa service was second to none, and like the hotel, expensive.On NYE, we enjoyed dinner at Asiate, the hotel's restaurant. The initial service was a little slow but picked up through the meal. The food itself was good, not spectacular. The hotel's lounge offers great views of the park and Columbus Circle (they also suffer from being blocked by Trump Tower).Overall, the MO New York doesn't compare well to other 5-star hotels I've been fortunate enough to stay at. They need to sort out the in room electronics and come back down to reality on food and room pricing (to be fair, compared to other NYC hotels we ate at, they are close). The hotel staff from the bellman, to the front desk, to the concierge were courteous throughout our entire stay.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>