<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="ce8ea0bc8e229a27f8a464dd64377e2a" url=""><![CDATA[Good value stay We stayed at the Diamant in late August 2008 in a Deluxe Room. Our experience was in line with other positive reviews on TripAdvisor, with a couple of similar gripes. The staff was all-smiles and most helpful. When we arrived early in the morning to a full house, the girl at the front desk offered to call my mobile when a room was cleaned, which she promised to expedite. It took a bit longer than expected, so she set us up with complimentary wireless access in the lobby.I wouldn't describe the hotel as luxurious by any stretch of the imagination, but it was clean and well above average. The location outside the CBD was great, with close proximity to the Kings Cross City Rail station, as well as a Coles supermarket and numerous eateries. My gripes were in regards to the bathroom, the charging of incidentals to my credit card, and wireless signal in the room, none of which were a huge deal or reason to avoid the hotel. The bathroom was more form than function, with a shower that had only a tiny barrier between shower floor and bathroom floor. Make sure you position the floor mat well to avoid water around the toilet! There was no towel rack, which essentially prevented the environmentally-friendly practice of re-using towels. Upon check-out, when charging for internet services, the hotel used Travelex services for currency exchange and processing. Travelex does their own conversion estimate on the spot, and the slip you sign at the hotel declares you are foregoing conversion by your credit card, in favor of the rate given by Travelex. At the time of our visit, the USD was trading between $0.83 and $0.86 to the AUD. The conversion rate from Travelex was $0.90. If we weren't rushed to catch a shuttle to the airport, I would've insisted that charges be converted by MasterCard directly.As for the wireless signal in the room, it was sporadic. It was generally very slow, with times of no connection at all. If you find this to be the case, there was also an ethernet connection on the desk, which was quite reliable.One very positive bit of kudos was related to the mini-bar. Upon request, the hotel staff emptied it, quickly and free of charge. Most hotels charge for this service.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>