<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="f9c1067bf7273e41217cad0956e52eb1" url=""><![CDATA[Good Place for the Price We stayed here for one night which concluded our 2 week vacation to the bay area. We took BART from the city to the airport and then caught the free shuttle to the hotel. Kind of a round-about way but it saved a lot of money. The shuttle was a little slow after a couple of calls but it is understandable because the airport was almost deserted when we were there. The hotel was well priced for what we got it at, $75 on Hotwire. I mentioned that to friends in the elevator and another hotel guest seemed astonished that we got such a low price. (He probably paid about $110+). The room was fine and the hotels service was good. The fitness center and pool downstairs was a little dated but not too bad. We arrived late and have a car so we go anywhere for dinner except Windows on the Bay, the hotel restaurant. The regular menu is quite expensive and kind of insulting for a place like that. I would spend $20+ for an entree in the city at a nice restaurant but not here! Fortunately they had a cheaper bar menu with still disappointing food. The service was good but it was about 11:30pm at night so I would expect good service! It was my birthday so I had a Brule but it was not very good. Our bill for food was almost as much as the room rate. There is a walking path in from of the hotel that we regretted not using the next morning. It looks out on the San Francisco Bay and has a nice view.Bottom line: stay here if you have a good rate and eat at the restaurant unless you HAVE TO.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8a84433a091768ceac84f603c8aa684d" url=""><![CDATA[OK hotel, theres probably better. We stayed here on the Forth of July after making a reservation with our Hyatt Points months in advance. I heard that the rate was up to $200+ for the night we stayed. We arrived way before the check in time but they had a room for us. When we first checked in for our non-smoking room, we were unpleased to find that the room they had given us was smelling of stale smoke. I went down and they changed our room to one without the smell of smoke. I didn't like the fact that getting to the elevator from our room seemed like a 5-minute walk through confusing corridors. The rooms are not all that big and ours had a view of the roof. We did check out and use the outdoor pool and whirlpool which was nice before we went to go see the fireworks. The fitness room was average but had a sauna which was a plus. The location is mostly up to your preference. We didn't find Fisherman's Warf to be all that great because it was mostly full of tourist traps and was a little creepy at night. The location is about 2-3 blocks in from the Warf. We stayed here on our last night in the city, but the other 2 nights were spent at the Hyatt Regency down at the Embarcado. We found this a less tacky, less crowded place to spend our time. If you do stay Fishermans Warf, check out the Argonaut Hotel or even the Best Western (dont knock it just because it's a BW, because it looked quite nice). If youve got any questions, dont hesitate to email me.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="deed4056afa5a5e2de98496bfe884ab8" url=""><![CDATA[good hotel but nothing unique A nice hotel in a great city. Nice location. I read a review from someone else here describing the lobby as a lot of dusty, fake greenery. I do agree, the lobby is big, but not bright and cheery. It's you typical large city convention hotel, not too much character. I have come to the conclusion that longtime business travelers have know for a long time: it matter what the brand of hotel is, they are all the same in a city. Please please please don't pay more just because this is a Hyatt because it could easily be any other hotel. The name means nothing in a city. When visiting San Francisco, have a car unless you need it. This hotel is located with public transit right outside your door. The California line for trolley cars is just feet from the door, BART and the MUNI metro are across the street. The F-Line streetcars run right by the hotel and go to Warf and Union Square. The ferry building is located in the back of the hotel and will take you to Sausalito. We even got to Muir Woods without a car by using the very comfortable and efficient Golden Gate Transit Buses. The embarcadero and ferry building is fun to hang out at on an afternoon for a long lunch and lazy day of shopping. There was an art festival with vendors and such on the weekend when we were there. The hotel rooms are about the normal size for a city hotel. The bathroom is quite small and not all that luxiourus. The Mini-bar is computerized so think your storing anything of yours in there. It's overpriced as usual ($3.50 for a can of soda) but once in a while its fun to empty it out when your business is paying. Otherwise, there is a 7-11 and Starbucks located across the street for more reasonable snacking. The fitness center is small and there is no pool. We did not see the revolving restaurant. I will warn you that we ate at the breakfast buffet in the morning for free but if your paying it's an outrageous $20 per person! Its good food but not worth that much!If you have ever been to NYC you will appreciate this comparison. If you love time square and all of its tackiness, stay at Warf. If you enjoy the more laid back areas that are not as touristy then stay out of the Warf area. If you have any questions about the transit in the area of the hotel hesitate to email me.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>