<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="400ac770e994738ab36561c4f577d570" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel! First time in Paris, only there for 2 nights and 3 days. I was looking for a nice place to stay that was convenient. I decided to use Hilton HHonors Points and book a reward stay and I was not dissapointed at all with this hotel. First, as far as getting to the hotel from CDG airport, the best thing to do is to take the Air France bus for 20euros round trip and take it to the Arc de Triomphe stop. From there it's about a 15 minute walk at most to the hotel. Very safe. As far as proximity to other things, it's about a 10 minute walk to the Champs Elysees, which wasn't bad at all. Grand and welcoming lobby. The hotel is very nicely decorated in a art deco style. The statt at the hotel was very friendly and eager to help (also spoke good English!). I checked it at 8am in the morning and was able to get my hotel room immediately.The room was very comfortable, nice size for Europe standards.Shower and tub in the bathroom in all nicely done in marble. Large towels. The bed and furniture were in good condition. Satelite t.v. with several stations in English. All and all, a very pleasant room.I'm not sure if it was because I was a Diamond Hilton HHonors member, but on the first night I received a nice note from the General Manager and a box of chocolates. On the second night I received a very nice bottle of wine again with a note from the manager thanking me for my stay and wishing me a happy new year. Wow, was I surprised.I was able to get the buffet breakfast included and was very surprised with how good the food was. A lot of choices, made to order eggs. Again, very nice spread for Europe standards.Again, can't say enough great things about this hotel. I would gladly stay hear again when I return to Paris!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="45b427403cf75d46bb581969f746d442" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic Hotel! We had a great experience staying at this hotel. My partner and I were on a 2 week Italy vacation staying in four different cities.From the moment we checked in, I knew this was going to be a great experience. The staff was superb! I asked for assistance in changing a train ticket and they took care of it for me without any hesitation. They even remembered my name each morning when I came down for breakfast. (That was impressive!!) We had a very nice sized room with GREAT AC! A yummy buffet was also included in our room rate. This hotel is about a 5-7 minute walk from Plazzo Vecchio and the Uffizi Gallery. I would highly recommend you take the CitySightseeing Firenze Bus (About 18euros per person) and take both line A B tours. You can hop on or off the bus at any stop and it's a great way to see the city and get yourself oriented. Make some time to stop in Fiesole too, it's a beautiful town about 20 minutes outside of Florence!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>