<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="0b0de3028115d52edd34353b5414730c" url=""><![CDATA[Great location The Belvedere was perfect for our three day stay. With three of us (two women, and one son) the corridor into the room offered a private nook for quick fchanges and the kitchenette area gave an extra sink for teeth brushing etc. .5 minutes walk to Times Square and all that surrounds it and a subway station 3 minutes walk. The Olympic Diner just round the corner on 8th was simple but really good for a quick relatively cheap breakfast. The smear of cream cheese on the bagel was so thick my son took a photo of it!My son used the gym at the Belvedere, and while it was modest it certainly had all that he needed. The staff were polite if not friendly.My only complaint was the elevators! Slow beyond belief!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="60cacbb875404dec4acbd0b85b9ff43d" url=""><![CDATA[Just lovely After a long trip staying in several hotels, this was such a pleasant surprise. We arrived very late (1am), and were greeted warmly and without fuss. All the desk staff were lovely and helpful. Our room (two queen size beds) was incredibly spacious, clean and very comfortable. We're not talking fancy, but there were lovely details - beautiful lamp shades, good closet space, lovely bathroom products, and attention to details like how towels were folded.Everythin was really clean and fresh, and maintenance was obviously a priority.Our room was right on Washington, which is quite busy. It didn't really matter. Despite some demolition work across the road, the room still felt quiet.It was quite chilly while we were there and had rained so everyone ate breakfast in the breakfast room itself rather than the pretty courtyard. While this space is modest, there was a lovely feeling of shared holidays. The breakfast is simple and generous and made a pleasant change from paying through the nose at a restaurant. The courtyard is as pretty as the picture suggests, and before the rain was a pleasant place to sit and read the paper for a little while.The hotel is located two small blocks from the beach - less than 5 minutes walk (and I'm not big on walking) and you're on the beach without the hassle of taking any transport. There were plenty of really welcoming and afforable places to eat. We made use of the local Big Blue Bus to get to Santa Monica, which meant a bit of walking, and taxis. Word of warning - the Santa Monica taxi dirvers like to take Lincoln Blvd back to Venice Beach. If you're on the 3rd St Blvd (a lot of fun on a sunday aft.), this takes you out of the way at both ends of the trip and costs up to $9.00 more (in peak hour). Ask them to take Ocean (VB taxis did this without being asked).I would recommend Inn at Venice Beach without hesitation.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>