<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="446a6663a48cfe80e9445ea16233cdad" url=""><![CDATA[Sour Singapore The Elizabeth Hotel failed to provide the room we had booked. I must state that my wife and myself were happy with the transfers to and from the airport as well as the breakfast provided by the Hotel, however the rooms that we had booked and paid for (to the travel agent) at the end of May 2006 did not align with the room we were given. When we arrived at the hotel we were directed to our room however when we entered the room we discovered that the room had not been serviced after the previous guests had left - there were towels strewn around the room and the bed sheets had not been replaced. We immediately went to the foyer and informed staff of the condition of the room. I also mentioned that we required a non smoking room and were informed that one was not available. After checking their available rooms, my wife and I were offered a non smoking room with three single beds with the promise that a room with a queen size bed would be available the following day. I reluctantly agreed to this as we had just flown from Paris via Heathrow and was extremely tired. The following day after sightseeing and shopping we returned to the Hotel (around 6.00pm) expecting to have been transferred to a non smoking room with a queen size bed as promised. However, we were only offered a non smoking room with two single beds and were required to wait for over an hour for this room to be serviced (with the compensation of a soft drink). We found during the night that the adjacent room (there was a locked door between our room and the adjacent room) was occupied by smokers and the strong smell of cigarette smoke was coming under the door into the room thus compounding our problems. Our treatment by the Hotel in Singapore has left us with feelings of discontent and we would not consider staying at the Elizabeth Hotel in the future.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>