<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="97af2fea2b765883a417df5bb7d4f8fc" url=""><![CDATA[Stylish Modern Art Deco hotel -- but bathrooms are small The very stylish art deco decor begins in the 2 story lobby. There's a gas fire place surrounded by bright, stylish furniture, dark book shelves and terrazzo floors. The blue violet velvet panel behind the front desk is repeated in elevators that have aluminum walls and black trim. There are 3 sizes of rooms; I stayed in the middle size($109 per night) with 1 bed and it would have been cramped for 2 people. Floor plans vary from room to room but all rooms have large windows and views. Room decor is also art deco: windows have floor length black gold striped drapes, beds have shams and bolster; tables and nightstands are light maple finish.My bathroom had a toilet in one corner with pedestal sink next to it and tub on other side of sink. There was no space between these items and the towel rack was almost over the toilet. There was only 1 glass shelf just big enough to hold a tissue box and a spare roll of toilet paper. I had to put my curling iron on the toilet tank. The toilet paper holder was under the pedestal sink's water shut off - and about a foot above the floor. If you want a spacious bathroom or a room with 2 sinks, you won't find it here. Towels were larger and softer than usual; room was equipped with microwave, refrigerator, blow drier, iron ironing board. The room was very clean. I stayed 2 nights and didn't hear any noise from other rooms. The entire property is non-smoking. Front desk staff was courteous and helpful. There's a complimentary continental breakfast in the basement and a Tully's coffee shop off the lobby.It's easy to find from the freeway and in the midst of restaurants and shops in the University district.I would stay here again. If you're in the area, stop in just to see the lobby decor (see their web site).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ca1be33bdcd39ee8c250bd13898a0ea5" url=""><![CDATA[Go for the tower rooms! I stayed here on November 7-8, 2004. When I read the previous reviews, I asked if my reservation was for a wing or a tower room. It was for a wing room but the reservation staff courteously changed it to a tower room. Access to the tower is by external glass elevators. My room was large, quiet and had a small balcony. There was a stain on the carpet but otherwise it was clean and well maintained. The room was equipped with a coffee maker, iron ironing board and blow dryer and there were 2 sinks - one inside the bathroom and one outside. The room did not have a refrigerator or microwave; the high speed internet connection in the room cost about $10. There is no complimentary breakfast; there is a coffee shop and an espresso bar that also sells yogurt, bagels and pastries. The hotel has a complimentary airport shuttle that runs every 15 minutes, 24 hours a day. I was attending a large conference held at the hotel. My co-workers with wing rooms said they were 'okay' and they heard some noise from neighboring rooms. The wing hallways had a damp smell. One wing building was closed for renovation.All staff were very courteous and helpful. For me the location worked well since I was attending events at the hotel and didn't have to rent a car to get there. If I had transportation and didn't have events at the hotel, I would look a few miles away for a better buy for the money.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>