<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="d86e709f970ca6a631a80b37cd4ae7cd" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Historic Hotel! Incredible Location! The Wyndham Bourbon Orleans is a nice historic hotel, right in the heart of the French Quarter. While not a five-star hotel, its location makes up for it. The hotel occupies a city block between Bourbon Street (where the bar is located) and St. Louis Cathedral. The hotel is built around the New Orleans auditorium, which dates to 1817. Most of the building is newer than that, however, and the hotel has distinctly New Orleans architecture. The hotel is nicely maintained and gradually getting back on its feet post-Katrina. My room overlooked the swimming pool, with a big comfy bed and marble bathroom. Nice! I don't believe the courtyard rooms have balconies, but they do have balcony rooms that overlook Bourbon Street. It's probably noisy on that side, as Bourbon Street is unbelievably loud. From my room, however, there was total silence.Room service is minimal at the moment and limited to po' boys and burgers. Hours are 5p-10p only. However, they'll deliver snacks and drinks to your room 24/7. One reviewer said the bar was closed, but it has since re-opened. The restaurant is open, as well. There's also a nifty little wine bar and bistro across the street that's worth a stop.The staff was great --- friendly and helpful all around, as is common in the Big Easy!There are great advantages to being a Wyndham ByRequest member. I booked my room at Bourbon Orleans for $89 plus tax, and that included free parking -- something they're offering through the end of August '06. What a deal! Parking usually costs at least $25 in the French Quarter. ByRequest members also get in-room snacks and beverages upon arrival, and 500 frequent flier miles. I booked here for the rate, and I'd definitely choose to stay again at normal rates. I love the authentic architechure of the hotel, and the location cannot be beat!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fee6c0245232ef65c7a306c8dce60050" url=""><![CDATA[Terrific Staff We stayed here for a week with a relatively large group of people, as a friend of mine was getting married. Overall, I was quite pleased with the all-inclusive experience. The staff was probably the best part of it! They were terrific, helpful, and friendly. The brochures say gratuities are included, but they don't make a lot, so tips are important and appreciated. Make a special effort at the swim-up bar, where tourists understandably go without money. The rooms were sub-par. The beds weren't all that comfortable; and in every room that I saw, the idea of a king bed was really just a couple of smaller beds pushed together. Worst of all, the pillows were very thin. If you can pack your own, do so! We ate very well. Nothing stood out, but there was a wide selection at all the meals. Trying to figure out a seating time is about the most complicated thing; but once you've done that (first day), the rest will go smoothly. At breakfast, there are both European-style and American-style breakfasts. The real issue is reservations for the restaurants. Most people want to go to the steakhouse at one time or another, so you've gotta get your reservation in early in the morning. (It's been awhile, but 7AM is the time I remember). We were usually out fairly late the night before, so that was problematic. On the third attempt, we got a table. The beach is spectacular. With so many Europeans, it was also topless to a large extent. I wouldn't say clothing-optional, although I saw one woman fully nude. She was the only person in a week, so I wouldn't recommend it. The Dominican Republic is a conservative country. Watch what you wear off the resort. But if you're getting some rays, nobody will bat an eye if you're topless. DO get a massage while you're there! I got one on the beach and was happily talked into several more. Every other day, it was wonderful... and much cheaper than in the United States. In a package of three, I believe I paid $135 ($45/per).There's a town close by. It's a short cab ride away and a good opportunity to look for some good Dominican cigars. Bargain for them! The asking price is not the price you should pay. Dominican cigars, by the way, are among the best. If you enjoy a smoke now and then, it's worth making the trip to town. Buy a lighter in town, as well, since everything is very expensive at the resort's little souvenir store. You do NOT want to buy anything at the store if you can help it.Finally, if you need cash, there is no ATM in the guest areas of the resort. Do not believe, however, that there is no ATM. Some employees will say they don't have one. But there is a big building where employees from all the Riu resorts gather. There's an ATM right outside. You have to walk about 10 minutes, but it beats cab fare to town. Ask for directions... it's not hard to find.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9cde4faeaf267272fb70ec5774c40df8" url=""><![CDATA[Nice Views... OVERVIEW: The Hilton is a big hotel! So when we needed a room during Jazzfest, it wasn't hard to find one here. The Hilton is close to Harrah's Casino and about three blocks to Canal Street and the entrance to the French Quarter. Its location means you can get a nice room with a relatively close-up view of the Mississippi River. It's one of the most interesting views in the city. Overall, the hotel is very nice -- about what you'd expect from a big, full service convention hotel. No surprises and completely comfortable.EXECUTIVE FLOOR REVIEW: As a Hilton Honors member, I was given an upgrade to one of the executive floors, which also give access to the 29th floor lounge. The lounge is a comfortable place to simply kick back and take in the view. It's also where the hotel serves a complimentary continental breakfast. But by the time we arrived, the food was pretty well picked over. It was also packed with people, with no immediate place to sit. Part of this could have been remedied by stretching out breakfast hours past 10AM (on a Sunday!!). The rooms are on higher floors, which mean better views, and there are nice bathrobes in these rooms. But I'd suggest you take the executive room only if offered, and not pay for an upgrade yourself. It isn't worth the price.SAVE MONEY: We booked on the hotel's website and paid dearly for our room during Jazzfest --- about $220. Our friends booked through Priceline, would up at the same hotel on the same night, and only paid $65. Sure, they were on a lower floor and missed the free breakfast... but they saved over $150. Of course, this isn't an option if your heart is set on the Hilton (you don't know where you'll stay on Priceline).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="71bb3f5be0f28467f15eca5d353e481a" url=""><![CDATA[Good Hotel, Fantastic Restaurant The St. James Hotel is a nice hotel. It's comfortable and we had no problems. If you can, get a room on the top floor... our room had a raised beam ceiling. It adds a lot of character to the room. On the ground floor, the St. James has one of the best restaurants in the city. Even if you don't stay here, eat at Cuvee! Impressive wine list, great food, and a casual upscale dining experience. The Trip Advisor reviews speak for themselves.The St. James is by no means one of the best hotels in the city, nor would I call it a full-service hotel. But you'll be within easy walking distance of the French Quarter and the best of the city, and you'll sleep well. I read an earlier review that claimed Hotwire called it a 4-star hotel. It's a 3-star by most accounts, and it's perfectly nice.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>