<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="0809c9a03209adf2c86cd21d6bea6c07" url=""><![CDATA[I enjoyed my stay here Stayed here for just one night, but enjoyed it. Check in staff very nice, rooms basic but comfortable, no views to speak of but oh well. Right next to the metro station at Kings Cross, but the neighborhood is nothing exciting. The restaurant at the hotel is good and has a nice wine list, there are also a couple bars across the street if you want a nice cold beer at a good, non-hotel price. I would stay here again for sure, but there are still other places (and areas) I would prefer.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="59a8242d707ebbe774710646fb7e8a11" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel in a Great Area Took a few days off after work in Dublin to come to my favorite city, London. Originally planned to stay in a hostel to have some fun, but since I was feeling under the weather, after one night in the hostel, I decided to use some Hilton HHonors points and stay here. It was an absolutely fantastic experience. The hotel is so easy to get to either by DLR (South Quay) or Tube (Canary Wharf and a 2 minute walk), and in an area often overlooked by tourists, but includes nice restaurants, shops, and the 3 tallest buildings in the UK (one of which, the Citigroup HQ, I had a view of from my room). Check in staff extremely nice, room very VERY large with lots of open space, bathroom very clean and comfortable, and bed quite comfy. Breakfast was a little dissapointing, and had I actually paid for it (they gave it to me for free since the hotel was full and they could not give me a room upgrade) I would have been darn right angry. Health club quite good, and concierge fantastically helpful recommending a good Indian restaurant (Mem Saheb, try it out), finding me a post office, and other odds and ends. I would certainly stay here again without a second thought...it's almost nice to take a break from the busy areas like Knightsbridge, Bayswater, etc. while still actually being in London
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e82e4d3658b6b50750b546ab4f202a74" url=""><![CDATA[A great experience in a great city Stayed here on a reward for three nights after working in Mascot. This hotel was great - excellent service, comfortable room (mine was on the 29th floor with a nice view of the Opera House), good bar and restaurant with typical hotel prices (but the bar wasn't bad in that respect - get a Bondi Beauty, especially if Annica (sp?) is making it!). It's so easy to get here and to get around - CityRail and Sydney Ferry both operate a block away. I would love to stay here again next time I am in this great city.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="783d1bac1210c02dccd8fccede212fd7" url=""><![CDATA[Really enjoyed the Park Plaza I'm in the middle of a stay here and really enjoy it. Staff is excellent, English is pretty good, location fantastic - right next to the Regent hotel but cheaper and set back from Jinbao Street so it's a bit quieter too. Being set back can be a bit difficult for a taxi driver but it's not too hard. Subway station just down the block (at the base of the Regent), Starbucks next door for a taste of home if, like me, you've been gone a while. Lei Garden on the 3rd floor of the Jinabo Tower is a good choice for food, and there are ATMs at the front of Jinbao Tower from several bank chains. Walking distance to Forbidden City and Tiananmen Square is a nice perk.Beijing is a nice city, but not my favorite. If I come back, though, I will certainly stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>