<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="35e07f91b9f21056d8b8a8f35535e752" url=""><![CDATA[hip and fun hotel - we're anxious to return! What a refreshing blast from the past. My husband and I stayed at the Belmont during the Texas/Oklahoma game weekend, on October 11th. The hotel was booked to capacity (note to self: book early for next year's game). This was our first stay at the Belmont, and we loved the hotel. Because of events related to the State Fair and the football game (Texas Longhorns now ranked #1!), we didn't spend a lot of time at the hotel, but we did walk the grounds and ate at the Cliff Restaurant next door.In short, we had a wonderful experience. Despite the hotel being fully booked, or perhaps because they had planned for it, the staff was available and responsive, and we felt well attended, from the valet staff, to the staff members who drove the shuttle that took us to the bus station to catch a bus to the Fair, to the front desk and housekeeping staff. Mandy was especially considerate and helpful. Nice to see someone who keeps their cool on a what was almost certainly a demanding weekend, and seems to actually enjoy her job.Our room was basic, a room outside the main building in the old motor court area. The room was fresh and clean, and quiet (as we had requested). The bathroom was older with updates and sparkling clean, with large fluffy towels. We added the romance package to our stay, which included a nice French Brut champagne and chocolate-covered strawberries. The menu at the Cliff Restaurant was varied (light eating to full dinners), and our dinners and desserts were delicious, with super-attentive and friendly waitstaff. Room service is available from the Cliff. Valet parking is (or was, on this weekend anyway) $15.00 per night, and not free as we had expected, although the in-and-out was free. We used the valet since the parking was more secure, although there is a self-park lot next door to the Cliff Restaurant.We're already talking about returning to this charming restored hotel. If you like a hip, retro hotel (with a few key modern conveniences), and with staff that actually seem to enjoy working there, check out the Belmont. We predict you'll arrive and leave with a smile on your face. We did.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="500f84cd8c158bce290eddda7cf6daa9" url=""><![CDATA[clean, comfortable, affordable Traveling to Madrid as a solo female, I felt safe in this very clean and well-located hotel (just steps from the Plaza del Sol and the Plaza Mayor). From my initial experience booking on the Internet, to checking in and out, I found the employees of the Hotel Plaza Mayor to be muy amable...very kind and helpful. English spoken here, though all tolerated my sincere attempts to speak Spanish. I stayed in room 504, a small room with a twin bed, for 60 euros per night. The bathroom (toilet, sink, shower) was spotless, and yes, small again. But who spends much time in their room in Madrid? I was very happy with the room, for the price. The room also had a safe (1.2 Euros per day), a TV, and a desk. Pequeno, si, but functional. My room overlooked a small, charming Plaza, which was busy for much of the day and into the night, but on the 5th floor, I heard very little with windows closed. No sounds from other rooms either, though the hotel was almost full during the time I was there.The Hotel offers breakfast for an additional fee. I recommend trying the small cafe directly across the plaza (to the left) in front of the Hotel, for a cafe con leche and pastry (2.10 Euros).Also - Consider having dinner with steak (solomillo) at Casa Paco's, a few minutes' walk from the Hotel (Puerta Cerrada 11, just off the Plaza Mayor), with salad and Valdepenas red wine. This will set you back a few Euros, but worth every penny. Enjoy.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="886015d2deaf38b483b08998e9beed2b" url=""><![CDATA[comfy bed, good value for money I just returned from a 2-night stay in Honolulu, at the Aqua Palms. I booked this hotel based on generally good ratings on Tripadvisor. Overall, for a base cost of $90.00 per night (AARP or AAA rate on the hotel's website), the hotel was a good deal for Honolulu. Add $18.00 per day for secure parking under the hotel (still a good deal for Honolulu). I liked the parking, and didn't mind paying, in order to have a car available. Unless you plan on staying/walking around only in crowded, hectic Waikiki (and you really shouldn't), a car is a good investment on the Island.The room was really clean, with a unique, colorful Island decor. Not fancy, but it made me smile. The pillow top bed was made for getting a good night's sleep - very nice. I also thought my room, at the end of a hall (no balcony/lanai, though many rooms have them) was quiet; I heard nothing that kept me awake from any direction. One welcome source of music from outside my room was the chirping of a friendly mynah bird that came back often during my stay, perching on the adjacent balcony (did I mention that I didn't have a balcony? --- and wished I did! --- next time).I was told on booking that with an AARP rate, I was eligible for an upgrade, based on availability. When I arrived at the hotel, the clerk seemed surprised to hear about this (I had it in writing, as part of my reservation confirmation). She told me no upgrade was available, unfortunately. A box of macadamia candy was given to soothe my distress. Ah, well. Overall, the hotel was a good deal for the price, a tradeoff for being on or closer to the beach. I felt safe and welcomed generally by the hotel staff. If you want a fancy pool or other facilities, be prepared to spend more money...quite a bit more, probably. If you want a clean, quiet place to sleep in between exploring the amazing sights, smells, and sounds of Oahu, this should more than fit the bill.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>