<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="b918710e335cd26f35864d25f927f94b" url=""><![CDATA[Exactly what you need in Waikiki! First let me say that I have stayed at the Four Seasons in the US and abroad as well as at $10/night hotels in SE Asia and this really met all of my expectations. Not super fancy, not a dive, good value for my dollar. This is Waikiki after all so yes, it's noisy at night, yes, there are expensive restaurants and lots of people. If you want a different experience, stay at Turtle Bay on the North Shore or head to another island.I got a $192/night rate on Orbitz for an Ocean Front Deluxe and ended up in room 2761 in the Diamond Head tower. Tried to check in at 1pm, but the room was not ready. Came back at 3pm as advised and we were set. They did try to put us in an Ocean VIEW (rather than Ocean Front which is a nicer category) room, but when I pointed it out, they made a speedy change.The hotel is in a great location 20 steps from the beach and our room was nice and large with a spectacular view. It had a large side chair/ottoman, desk and chair, flat screen, dresser, separate dressing bathroom area. The pool is tiny, but the lounge chairs are very comfy and if you want to be in the water, the beach is 20 steps away. Service was excellent and for the price we paid, it was a bargain.I also really liked that when you called or spoke to the concierge about doing an activity, they gave you all the options including how to take a bus ($2) to get somewhere vs. pushing you into one of the tours.PROS: Big room, great view, good price, they loan you sand chairs and beach towels to take to the beach for free, car rental on site, laundry on site if you need it, live music at the pool/bar in the evening, and right in the heart of everything WaikikiCONS: Restaurants in the hotel are only so so and kind of pricey (but lots of things in walking difference that are better/cheaper), the door has a big gap underneath so lets in light from the hall, the non-smoking rooms allow smoking on the decks so if you have your door open or are outside it smells when others smoke. The bed is not super comfy, but the linens are great.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>