<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="0cdeb393df17538aa56c3b6d20edbc53" url=""><![CDATA[high class on a budget My husband and I are both in graduate school, while working full time, and decided that after finals we would take a weekend to get away. I bought tickets to the Blue Man Group at the Charles Playhouse, and found a deal to the Park Plaza (nearly next door) for $99 per night. We booked a Saturday night in December. The hotel is VERY regal, full of history, as can be seen in the chandeliers and mouldings, and original tile in the bathroom. The room we booked was, understandably, very small, but completely sufficient. It needs a little updating, but it was more than sufficient for our needs. We didn't utilize the restaurants, shops, or room service, so I can't speak to those aspects of the hotel. Check in was easy, no problem. We found our room with little difficulty. Bed was VERY comfortable, and there was a plethora of pillow choices. Cable was great, nice deep tub in the bathroom, everyone was pretty friendly.The one main downside of this hotel was that the walls were VERY thin. We could hear arguments going on down the hall, and we could hear EVERY word. I've never come upon this problem before, and was a bit confused as to what to do. Eventually it just stopped and everyone, presumably, went back to sleep. Other guests were stomping their feet on the floor and banging on the walls to get them to stop, but they were obviously intoxicated and oblivious. It was 2 AM. We could also hear other guests down the hall having a completely different and seemingly more pleasant interaction. Very clearly. I'm not sure if it was the clientelle was that there that weekend of if the walls are particularly thing, or a combination. I like to go away and be alone, but this aspect made it difficult to feel like you're alone. You were aware of everyone all of the time. It might be different in the upgraded tower rooms, but certainly not in the cheap seats.Otherwise, we really love Boston, and love to visit, just not sure we would go to the Park Plaza again. We went for a little of Old Boston on the cheap, which we were able to achieve.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>