<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="4c0ecc90d72bfb0918f704d81eb2b175" url=""><![CDATA[Absolutely Spectacular! No question that this is one of the best hotels I have ever stayed at. BUT, there is a caveat. YOU MUST STAY IN THE NEWLY REMODELED ROOMS!!! These are on the 39th floor which means they are Executive Level rooms. It is worth the extra money (probably about $40USD per night). The Executive Level means you have access to the Exec. Check in on the 40th floor along with the Executive lounge which serves free breakfast and night cocktails. The rooms on the 39th are BRAND new so much so that the one I was in actually smelled new (you know that construction smell!). The room decor on these new rooms is very akin to the W Hotels (I shouldn't say this too loud since the W is just down the street from the Nikko). The view is phenomenal and the service is 5****. They go above and beyond the call to make things right. On the executive floor you also have access to a butler service that will press your clothes and shine your shoes. In the morning, my wake up call was followed by fresh coffee moments later -- with warm milk for the coffee! The hotel has a gym and spa area on the 4th floor. For hotel gyms it actually has a lot of equipment. I am a gym freak so I found a Gold's Gym within walking distance (15 minutes). There are a bunch of hotels right in this area (the InterContinental, W Hotel, Marriott, etc)... so location wise there isn't much difference. The W looked to be quite happening at night as the lobby bar was PACKED. BUT, if you want a nice luxury hotel, the Nikko is the place to be. Again, I take no responsibility if you do not stay in the renovated rooms.As far as the neighbourhood, Polanco is one of the safest and wealthiest neighbourhoods in Mexico City. No problem walking around during the day or night. There are plenty of police around too. Shopping in this area is for the wealthy too. With Hugo Boss, Armani, Canali, etc. the shops are exclusive designer shops. There is also a tour bus that stops near this hotel and it will take you around the city in about 3 hours if you don't get off the bus.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>