<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="2d8ceb7606d26d40bfffa77d1219ab38" url=""><![CDATA[Great base Stayed here from 6th to 9th February and found it to be an excellent base from which to explore the area.The accommodation was in a room with twin beds, TV, minibar, desk and a large spacious and spotless marble tiled en-suite. The beds and towels were changed daily. The room was not very large but adequate enough for a short stay. A longer stay would warrant asking for a larger room. Storage space was limited, a chest of drawers would have addressed the shortfall.The hotel is just two minutes from the Placa Catalunya which is at the top of the Rambla. There are great shops between the hotel and the Placa and El Corte Ingles store is in the square. We only ate in the hotel once as we found a great restaurant on the left of the Rambla, near the hotel, called Attic. This had great food and evener better prices. We ate breakfast in two places, Viena, a cafe next door to the hotel (freshly squeezed orange juice, croissants and coffee), this cost 9.50 euro for two of us. We also had the same in Cafe Zurich on the Placa and it was 12.50 euro there but we did not mind as the cafe is steeped in history, worth a visit. To see the city and outskirts the best way is the hop on, hop off bus which leaves Placa Catalunya very regularly. There are two routes, the North and South and these join up for ease of transfer. We were a bit anxious, having read previous reviews that the staff might not be welcoming but we did not have that experience, quite the reverse, in fact. I fell on the afternoon before leaving and broke my wrist and sprained my foot. The staff were great getting me ice and ice packs plus sympathy and advice re contacting medical assistance, if wished. I could not fault them and found them very warm and welcoming.TIP - if ordering a taxi do it from reception, the receptionist will have the taxi driver call into the lobby and she confirms his booking, this way you are secure in the knowledge that you have got a proper taxi. I would recommend this hotel to couples, older people, smaller families, business visitors and single persons. As it is a quiet select type hotel it might not appeal to younger groups. It is very quiet and peaceful there. I cannot wait to return.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fea3e7ede400e92113e6a9b844568d4c" url=""><![CDATA[jewel in the latin quartier Booked this hotel on the internet having sought location advice from Trip Advisor. When travelling in France we always book Logis De France hotels as these have never disappointed. They are always lovely warm and friendly stopovers. This hotel is small but really comfortable with quite big rooms for Paris and a great en-suite. The staff are really friendly and will make calls for you and arrange trips. The hotel is close to a really exciting daily market and about 10/15 mins. walk of Notre Dame and the right bank. Breakfasts are great with croissants,chocolate croissants, yoghurts, cereal, cheese and crusty bread. Tea, coffee, water and pure orange juice are available along with jams.Be sure to go to Shakespeare and Co book shop on the bank of the Seine, a great experience.My children booked us a treat ride from the airport with ------------ and two lovely men, Vincent and Jimmy made our Paris experience with a night drive through Paris past all the sights. Magic.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>