<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="96d03c4411c1de1ef6c08267149dc13d" url=""><![CDATA[Overpriced and in bad need of a remodel I'm a mid-30's professional that travels often. I live about 4 hours away from New Orleans and have visited several times a year for the past fifteen years. I have tried all types of accommodations in and around the French Quarter from hotels to private homes. On our last visit to New Orleans (New Year's Eve), my wife and I strolled by the DuPuy and looked inside the lobby. We decided we would try this hotel when we returned in April for the first weekend of Jazz Fest with my in-laws. By making a few phone calls, we were able to secure two non-smoking king rooms with balconies overlooking the courtyard at a rate of $289 per night thanks to Pat in reservations. (These types of rooms are scarce during big events).Check-in was great. Our car was parked and our bags were promptly brought up to the room. The front-desk staff was helpful and check-in was immediate. The room, however, left a lot to be desired. The french doors to the balcony did not shut or lock properly. Everything was tired and dated. The very tiny bathroom had several bulbs that were burned out over the vanity and the tub was dirty. There is no in-room high speed internet service and the dial-up will cost you 75 cents a call. The only high point to the room was that it faced out over an interior courtyard that cut down the noise level as compared to a room that faces out over the streets (if you have ever stayed in a balcony room on Bourbon you will appreciate that).The level of service greatly deteriorated after check-in. In the four nights that we stayed there, the maids never cleaned our coffee pot or placed out new coffee (horrible coffee- btw). No one ever replaced the burned-out bulbs over the vanity in the bathroom. The convenience bar in the room had orange juice in it that had expired over two months ago. The breakfast buffet consisted of powdered eggs and fruit that was left sitting in the sun. Service was downright rude at breakfast and the employees could have cared less if anyone was there. When we, and other guests, inquired about items that were getting low, we were shrugged off. On the day of check-out, the bellboy/valet was very rude to us and other guests. In the lobby, after a guest a complained of being awakened by loud noises, a hotel employee loudly proclaimed, if I had to be up at 6 this morning, so should he!At $289 per night plus tax and $24 nightly parking fee, you definitely do not get the service and room you are paying for. There are much nicer, and newer, hotels to choose from in this area.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>