<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="12dc14ff0ffdcbd41dd03d6d53e6daad" url=""><![CDATA[Affordable Paradise We read at least 50 reviews before we booked our trip for May 19 -26 so here goes. Please read princessbubbles77 trip report of May 21 because she stayed in the same room as we did (3333) and had a similar good experience. Her TR was very thorough.The beach is awesome: Turquoise water and powdery white sand. Supposedly, even the beaches at the resorts on either side of Barcelo Premium are not as nice. The two pools are lovely and kept up nicely. The beach and these two pools are so nice, that I would have given this resort an Excellent even if there weren't other good things about it. I think there is discussion about whether this is a 3 or a 4 star resort because all the rooms aren't renovated yet. If we had been given an old room that was musty we wouldn't have been happy. As it was, we were given a newly renovated room which included a flat screen TV, pillow top mattress and no musty smell. The shower needs some kind of shower curtain because the 3x5 plexiglass shield does not keep water from going all over the bathroom. The minibar is stocked with water bottles, soda and Brama beer (not as good as Presidente but it will do). Being able to get water bottles all over the resort really keeps you hydrated and healthy. The food is just okay but I don't eat meat and the fish that I wasn't familiar with didn't appeal to me. I don't expect the food in the Caribbean to be good, but compared to other places that I stayed at, the food at Barcelo was the best. We liked the Tokio Hibachi restaurant and went there two times, although the grills make it hot in there. Roma, the Italian restaurant was quite good and air conditioned. I had a dessert there that was incredible. There were also gourmet desserts put out at the buffet that were quite delicious too. I liked the seafood restaurant El Marlin more than my boyfriend did, but I had lobster kabobs, even though I know the lobster in the Caribbean is chewy. With it out of the shell I could enjoy it more. The buffet changes a bit in the evening and on some nights it was better than others. There was a nice selection at the buffet in the morning, but it was kind of a pain getting your plate together. If you wanted toast you had to wait for it to go through the toasting machine and you had to get it before you got your eggs or else everything would be cold. I liked the cocktails. I couldn't tell that the beer in the tap wasn't Presidente but I drank mostly Pina Coladas and Strawberry Daquaris. They use just white rum for the pina coladas and the strawberry daquaris have a nice hint of lime and I liked them. I only tried Mamajuana on the last night but wished I had tasted it before that because I quite liked it. It tasted like grog to me and you can drink it without getting full. I thought the service was pretty darn quick, though I don't speak Spanish and that causes some delays and miscommunication. The entertainment in the evening was fine, though I wish they would cut out the lip synching and just stick with the dancing, which is quite good. The bonfire night was fun with the activities people playing funny group games and then lighting the bonfire and throwing fuel on it a few times. The disco did have a funny musty smell and I could have told my BF beforehand that he wouldn't like the music, which was dominican, some top 40 and some oldies. I'm a gambler and I play video poker in Atlantic City, so of course we hit the casino. They were handing out match play coupons for blackjack but I don't play table games. They have a table to play live poker but I never saw anyone playing. If you're familiar with video poker pay tables, it was funny to me that it's the same at the Barcelo Premium as it is in AC -- only one of the (7) machines had decent pay tables. We both played 9/7 DB for a small profit each. I would have played through my profit but my BF kept me in check. :-) The machines were from the Bellagio - they had plastic plates that listed them as such. You could put US bills into the machine but pay outs were in tokens to be redeemed at the cashier. A $100 pay out was a hand pay and the machine starts a-ringing. I too thought that Rahinel in activities was especially nice. He made a point to try to impart as much Spanish knowledge at the lesson in the pool bar at 10am as he could. Later he offered to sell us a CD of the Dominican music that they played, including the resort theme song that they do their little dance to for $10 and we're enjoying it now at home.Overall, this was the nicest Caribbean vacation I've ever been on, and beach vacations are not my preference to begin with. I hope that we won't be priced out of Barcelo Premium once the renovations are done and they work on more upgrades. We never left the resort and there was plenty for us to do. I'm looking forward to going back again. One note: Don't forget that the liquid restrictions on the plane are the same going into the DR as they are leaving it. I remembered to jam my hand cream into my checked luggage before we went through security, but completely forgot.... DOH!... that we were hand carrying bottles of alcohol that we had bought in the hotel as souvenirs. We were furious that they wouldn't let us back to check them but what were we thinking? No liquids over 3 ounces! After we calmed down we re-bought Rum and Mamajuana (not as good as the homemade stuff in the hotel) at the airport.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>