<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="2c92a376e459943b7015ef0570f20955" url=""><![CDATA[Sick from Breezes We stayed at the Breezes Resort in Punta Cana from June 14th - June 21st. I read the reviews on this resort weekly to get a heads up as to what to expect. The reviews were very helpful as I did take precautions while visiting this resort. Rooms: The rooms were ok and were your typical hotel room. We stayed in building 7 which overlooks the pool/beach area. The view from our room was excellent!Service: We found the service in the restaurants to be good. The bars at night got pretty overcrowded and you had to wait a few minutes to get a drink. Maid service was a little iffy. We had three days in which our room was not cleaned and were not given clean towels. We had to call the front desk those days to have new towels delivered. The people we went with had an incident of some stuff being taken out of their room (two bottles of rum). Food: The food was not the best! The reservation system for the restaurants is ridiculous! You have to get in line between 5:00 - 5:30 to assure a reseveration at the Italian or Japanese restaurants. Out of all of the sit-down-dinners, we tried everyone except the French restaurnant. Our favorites were the Japanese, Italian, and Dominican Restaurants. The food in these restaurants were excellent! The Mexican food was not good and the food at the buffets got a little bland after a while. However, the desserts in the restaurants were incredible!Pool/Ocean: The pool and the ocean are beautiful! If you try to reserve an umbrella by the pool too early in the morning, it will get taken away by the workers and given to somebody else if you are not sitting under it.Night-Life: Not too much to do at night. The shows were pretty boring so we sat around the lobby and played cards (make sure you bring your own). The casino was very small...don't waste your time or money!We did a few excursions while on the trip. We took a shopping tour, went snorkeling (Marinarium - you swim with nurse sharks and sting rays) and did the Outback Safari. All of these trips were well worth it. Our favorite was the Outback Safari as you got to see a lot of the country!Now that we are home, 3 out of 4 of us are sick. My husband came back with a 104 degree fever last night. He just got back from the doctor and has a severe bacterial infection and has to be treated with Cipro. He has to miss work the next 3 days. The doctor says it was caused by unclean eating conditions (food not prepared properly, eating off an unclean plate, food not cooked or kept at the proper temperature). The other two are also extremely ill. They both have severe vomiting and diaherra. I am not going to tell anyone not to go to this resort as it is not my place to do so, just take precautions before you go and make sure to pack plenty of imodium, pepto, etc. If you have any questions please feel free to email me at:good_deal37@yahoo.com
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>