<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="781ec7837ee3ab3e5c207957b80aab0e" url=""><![CDATA[Not a 4* but a good 3*... still a great holiday We were worried about staying at the Grand Paradise after reading some of the reviews but I have to say that generally we were pleasantly surprised. Both my boyfriend and I aren't complaining types so I'd like to think that you could take this review as you read it. 1. Check in : Absolutely fine. The flight was fine, the transfer to the hotel was fine. We waited about 10 minutes to check in and we had a drink provided for us. The check in staff were very friendly, professional and helpful. Alex, who checked us in, spoke very good English. We were given a remote for the TV and we paid $20 for the safe for 2 weeks. We were only given one room key but we didn't ask for 2 so no complaints there.The bellboy took our luggage and we were given a ride on one of the golf buggies to our room straight away. We tipped the bellboy $1 but he didn't seem to be waiting for a tip and he was grateful. 2. The room : Very nice. We were staying in block 9 which seemed pretty new. The room had 2 king size beds, both of which had decent mattresses (although one was slightly better than the other). There was a flat screen TV which worked perfectly, could receive all the channels. The bathroom was spotless, shower bath and wc. We had complimentary soaps and shampoos left although we didn't use them. 3. The maid service : Good. We agreed we would tip the maid $1 a day. The first day we left the dollar we came back to a towel folded into a heart shape with flowers on the top, an extra room key (so the air con would stay on all the time), as well as all new towels plus 2 extra ones. We felt slightly guilty that we'd only left a dollar but we were on a tight budget and only tipped $1 again the next day. When we came back to our room it was cleaned well but the extra room key had gone and there were no towels folded into pretty shapes. The air con was efficient enough to cool the room down within about 10 minutes when it was on anyway so we didn't require an extra room key. I guess if we'd tipped $5 the next day we would've kept the key but it wasn't really important to us. 4. The mini bar: EXPENSIVE. Within the all inclusive package you get a gallon of water (replenished whenever you finish it - every day if you drink it all) and 4 bottles of pop, which I think is plenty. We did eat quite a few snacks from the mini bar on a couple of days when I was unwell and we couldn't face walking to the buffet for breakfast or lunch. The price list is provided and it is expensive but we thought we knew what we were letting ourselves in for. I put aside money each time we ate something from the mini bar (and I was rounding up as well e.g. we had 2 chocolate bars totalling $7, so I put away $10. The following day a bill for what you've consumed is put in your room with the service charge added on and the total in dollars. Be prepared though when you check out they give you the bill for anything charged to the room and from the mini bar in pesos. They can only provide a breakdown in pesos. But when you pay for anything in cash at the resort they prefer dollars. If you want to settle in dollars (as we did) they then convert the pesos to dollars at their exchange rate and you end up getting fleeced. It is also impossible to tell if you've been correctly billed unless you want to ask for a breakdown, go and sit down and convert pesos to dollars for each day and then attribute it to what you ate. Also - one day we were charged for some peanuts ($11) but I am seriously allergic to peanuts and there is no way I had eaten them. We spoke to the rep about it and when we checked out they did take it off the bill. My advice - just stay within your all inclusive allowance. The mini bar is my major gripe by the way :)5. The beach: Gorgeous. The beach is beautiful. White sand, crystal clear waters. The beach is always very clean too. There is a lovely old guy who goes around collecting the glasses and he always smiles at you. I did feel a bit sorry for him but he was always smiling. The water can be a bit choppy, probably too much for young children but fine for adults. The sea is clean and there's no debris. The beach isn't stoney either which is nice. While we were there it was low season so there was no problem getting a sun lounger, even in the shade (as long as you don't mind sitting under a tree if all the umbrella things are taken - which we didn't). I can imagine it's hard to find somewhere in high season though.6. The pools: Very good. Both pools are very clean and nice. No problems with either. The swim up bar at one of the pools is great and Luis the barman was lovely. 7. The service: Okay. The service could be a little hit and miss but I cannot fault the staff. They were tirelessly, you never see anyone standing around. They always seem cheery and smile at you and remember you although sometimes you can be waiting a while for a drink. I think it's because the place is so big and could probably do with some more staff. At the buffet if both of you get up to get food at the same time and take a while you will probably find your table gone by the time you get back. We just took it in turns though so it wasn't a problem. Again I wouldn't like to go during high season as I imagine it's baaaaad. 8. The staff: Wonderful. They are brilliant. Some of the waiters really are funny and / or very attentive. Nestor who works in the La Palma buffet was an excellent waiter and he was gorgeous too haha. Kelvin who we saw working in the Italian was very funny - a real character. The animation team work very hard and are genuinely lovely. I went with my boyfriend but I still got a lot of attention from the male workers and I'm not anything special but they do like blonde women. I imagine single ladies would get aboslutely hounded, it was just a laugh cos I was there with my other half. 9. The food: Okay. I'm not a fussy eater but I did get bored of the food. Even though they have themed nights the stuff always seemed to be the same. Most of the food is okay although some of the stuff tasted funny. I didn't eat any seafood cos I was worried about getting food poisoning. We did have dodgy stomachs on 2 occasions but I do have a weak stomach. There are a lot of flies in the buffet but they can't do anything about that. We only tried the Italian la carte but it was very nice. Sadly one of the dodgy stomach incidents came after eating a not very hot lasagne there but I would still thoroughly recommend it. I expected at least one dodgy stomach whilst going to the DR though!10. The drinks: Good. The cocktails are nice if a bit of on the sweet side. You do only get a small plastic cup so take a travel mug if that bothers you. The beer is really nice and I don't like beer (I only like bud anyway). The measures are big and I can't say I thought anything was watered down. Mama Juana is very nice - you must try it!11. The disco: Awful - but bearable if you get drunk. You can request music but we didn't bother. There were a group of young Canadians staying there and when they were at the disco the music was good. The toilets were awful but no worse than a bar in Liverpool city centre so who cares?12. The other guests: Not overly friendly. I'm English and we only met one other English couple there. There were a lot of Canadians and lot of Europeans. I'd like to go to a resort where more people from the UK go to next time.13. The Entertainment: Good. The shows are good, the dance troupe are really good. It sometimes gets a bit tedious when the compere of the evening announced everything in 3 different languages but it is an international place and they make everything accesible to everyone. A few other things: I didn't experience anywhere near as many problems as some people seem to have. I've been totally honest and moaned about anything worth moaning about. The DR is a 3rd world country, the hotels are paradise compared to how the Domincans live so don't expect everything to be perfect. The staff are lovely and I had no problem with their English. They really appreciate any attempt at you speaking Spanish but they can all speak most languages. We didn't pay a lot for our holiday so we didn't go expecting the world. I wouldn't say the hotel is a 4* but it is a good 3*. If you want excellent service then you have to pay higher prices. I would love to go back to the DR but I'd probably stay at a different resort. I chose the Grand Paradise because we were on a budget. If you've booked here don't be frightened off by bad reviews, go with an open mind and an open heart and you'll have a wonderful time.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>