<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="044c35550a152cf31d933bbab6e669d6" url=""><![CDATA[The Majestic Colonial - Worth every penny! We spent 5 days at the Majestic Colonial in the Dominican Republic. And, what a wonderful 5 days it was!First and foremost, I need to preface the review simply by stating the obvious, which most travelers from the U.S. seem to forget. When you travel outside of the United States, you have traveled OUTSIDE of the United States. Things are going to be different than what you might be accustomed to. This is NOT a bad thing! Open your mind a little... you just might enjoy yourself!I could spend the entire review just talking about how beautiful the resort and the accomodations are. But, like many others before me, what really made this trip was the staff. Even late at night, you could find staff members cleaning around the resort. The wait staff at the various restaurants and bars were very friendly.Our staffer highlight though, was Nelson. Whenever we were down by the beach, Nelson was there to take care of us. He went above and beyond anything I could have imagined, coming around literally every 5 minutes to see if we needed anything! One of our friends on the trip with us asked Nelson, Where can we get fresh coconuts? They didn't have these at the resort, but Nelson wouldn't hear of us going out on our own in search... so he had a family member get us 4 coconuts (we had a group of 4 couples on the trip). He had them ready for us on our final full day at the resort!Nelson - you are awesome! The trip would have been great all on its own, but you made staying at the Majestic Colonial awesome! We WILL see you again!Other HighlightsWe typically spent our mornings at the beach, and our afternoons at the pool. Both settings are very inviting! The animation team at the Majestic are really fun. How on earth they are able to maintain the level of energy that they do is beyond me!I was actually pretty impressed by the food, to be honest! I wasn't expecting much only because it was an all-inclusive resort, but in the end I was very pleased with the meals. The buffet breakfast in the mornings really set up the day nicely. The steakhouse at night near the beach had excellent meats. All in all, it was a very good experience.As far as not feeling well during the trip, this wasn't an issue. Just make sure to stick to bottled water and bring along some Pepto (just in case). A little planning goes a long way!My one and only complaint - the ATM machine in the lobby wasn't working, so mid-way through the trip we didn't have money left. We ended up stopping at another resort and using THEIR ATM to be able to get some cash for tipping (remember, the staff don't make a ton of money, so tips are nice).To have an ATM machine be the only complaint (and in reality, that is the fault of the bank responsible for that ATM, not the resort), I'd say the trip was beyond a success. I look forward to visitng them again one day.I would highly recommend this resort to anyone looking to have a good time!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>