<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="fa89296b002ce76d46221aa3123e71e0" url=""><![CDATA[Hostel on steroids...has definite potential Location is great - essence of decor in lobby and main areas is decent and interesting. Room was....like my title says hostel on steroids...beds consisted of one untucked sheet on top...no blanket...no comforter...nothing...just a plain ol' white sheet. Now, this was not a total surprise to me because I did read the other reviews so I was prepared and did request extra blankets...which were in the closet when we arrived...two different ones...one was a nasty old polyester one that looked like the one I had on my bed in the 70's and it had a visible stain...the other was a white cotton one...which I used out of desperation. I slept with my shirt on the pillow to get my mind off the stained pillow under the pillow case. I was traveling for business and needed to keep the $ in check. If I were with my husband I would have changed hotels in a heartbeat if I could have found something reasonable. This is not a place you want to spend much time hanging out.Location - great...near convention center, Delano and Lincoln Street Mall. I'm all about fashion but...make sure your fashionable shoes are comfortable too.Staff - When we arrived, there was one young man working the desk who looked a bit like he picked up his logo golf shirt off the floor and came in from a late night out. He was nice enough but for first impression...made me a little uneasy. He left us at the counter at least 3 times going upstairs....we joked whether he was installing the camera in our room ;-) . Housekeeping - Well...they don't really replenish toiletries and even though there were 2 of us in the room, they only had 1 face cloth and none after the 2nd day. One towel for each of us and terrible tissues. Cleanliness...it was okay...glad I had my slippers. I was suspect the entire time I was there.I'm accustomed to staying in pretty decent hotels and inns and I really would probably not ever stay here again and I would only recommend it for young single people who just want to party and have a place to lay their heads down late night!As far as potential - they are missing the boat - this COULD be a great place. They need to stop cutting corners...simply a decorative throw or blanket on the end of the bed would be an improvement. Someone who has attention to detail needs to get involved. I truly believe there could be a balance of affordability and attention to detail to easily bump this hotel up a star or two.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>