<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="e5eacd093ab180b313344424ec83b426" url=""><![CDATA[Pleasantly surprised Booked two nights in Frankfurt through Hotwire without knowing which hotel wind up with until after my booking. Was pretty comfortable with it being the InterContinental as the price was ridiculously low and it being a 5star. Friendly doorman parked our rent-a-car just outside the hotel (saved us a bunch in parking fee) and a friendly gentleman at reception let us upgrade from the Hotwire room with a city view to a lovely room with a beautiful river view, for about 20 Euros. Location was great, we had warm, sunny weather and enjoyed walking along the river and into the old part of town. Also across the river is a lovely museum worth visiting.Can highly recommend the Signature restaurant on the ground floor, great food and top notch service.Just really happy with this deal from Hotwire.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="aad2aeac266adf378a2a9024ea413c66" url=""><![CDATA[Great value for money Spent the last (extended) weekend of May in Berlin at the Hotel Park Inn Alexanderplatz and was quite pleased. Everything as I had expected according to reviews from TripAdvisor and even better. The room was nice/modern with a great view and everything very clean. Excellent breakfast buffet (incl in our price) served 10:30 (make sure finished eating by then, the lady with the vacuum cleaner comes marching in and starts vacuuming on the dot, wont find any crumbs on her floor... ). Though the hotel is big there is no lack of good service. Enjoyed eating at fancy Spagos on the ground floor, good food and service. Went to check on the view from the sun deck on the 37th floor, but they were closed due to strong winds, maybe next time.Found location to be good for different walking ventures; the river Spree with boat cruises, Berlin Dom and Museum Insel, Nikolaiviertel, Hackisher Markt (beware of pick pockets) and Oranienburgstrasse where we had a great 3 course dinner at the lovely restaurant Kadima (Jewish/Russian, non kosher) for 30 Euros pr person, excluding wine. Also recommend a good restaurant downtown on a sidestreet from Sachs at Knesebeckstrasse, definately the best dinner of our five day city-break.All in all, a good hotel which I can recommend and would consider staying at again, great value for money.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>