<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="3528c4b391626e0f1b70f5f98723a684" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel, but the farewell could have been fonder. My boyfriend and I decided to splurge on a really swanky hotel for a couple nights as we were on a combination romantic getaway / Berlin extravaganza for about a week. When we finally found the entrance to the Swissotel (which is located above the C A department store on a side street) we were pretty damn pleased with the service. We arrived 4 hours early but were given our room anyway, our baggage was taken up to our room for us, and we were even escorted to the elevators by the gentleman at the desk. Not to mention we received free drink vouchers for a drink they make at the bar out of a variety of juices and special grouse. When we got into the room we were still impressed- HUGE bathtub (you can easily slip two people in there) and really comfortable bed. I was in love after having stayed at the Lindner for a few nights (which is no comparison, seriously). We enjoyed our stay there very much, our only problem came when it was time to check out. We were hastily offered our bags back to us even though check out at our next hotel wasn't for several hours. After some discussion, they agreed to hold on to our bags for us. We spent 1 hour trying to check out because they had to send someone up to our room to validate the minibar charges (which I believe were all of 4 Euro) and there was a HUGE problem with the laundry bill. My boyfriend who had decided to stay an extra four days needed to do laundry and so we were told by the front desk that it could be left out in front of the door and taken care of. We assumed there would be a charge for this, however we were never at any point told that it would be 49 Euro to wash 4 cotton t-shirts and a couple pairs of jeans. We argued with the front desk that we were never informed of the costs associated and that their policy was lunacy. Eventually we realized there was no reasoning with them and paid the bill. We later collected our bags, had them call us a taxi, and the doorman explained to the taxi where we were going after we showed him on paper the address of our next hotel. Turns out the doorman told the taxi driver the wrong thing and we ended up going to a different hotel. After trying to explain this to the driver he insisted that the hotel he had taken us to was what he was told by the doorman. After an arguement, we were finally taken to the correct hotel. So to sum up, here's my advice: Stay at the swissotel if you want a luxury experience- use their free drink vouchers- don't use the minibar- don't do laundry- and don't expect a welcome goodbye.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4c7a9f12946c03b423ebad240ee363d4" url=""><![CDATA[Literally In The Airport a little bit outdated, but very mod looking green chair.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>