<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="1603bb71fd76e600bf170951e9723d9f" url=""><![CDATA[Very enjoyable vacation The Reviewers: Bob, 58, and Sharon, 48, American, well traveled in the Caribbean, Mexico, Costa Rica, Asia-PAC. Adventurous souls interested in new experiences, cultures, food, fishing, boating. Appreciate the lap of luxury, but equally excited roughing it in fly-in camps in northern Ontario or tiny fishing villages on Pacific coast. Extremely limited grasp of the Spanish language, but willing to make an effort.Arrival, departure, and transfers, Punta Cana airport / Excellence: Among the easiest ever experienced. Breezed through customs on arrival, $10 visa fee apiece, porters aggressive but manageable. Contacted the resort in advance to arrange a taxi, driver was waiting with a sign. Seventy five minutes, sixty bucks and a ten dollar tip later arrived at Excellence. The drive nothing to worry about, slaloming through the potholes, application of the horn as an occasional navigational aid, all fairly standard in our experience. You never really get going all that fast. Certainly less of an adventure than using a twenty to motivate a NYC cabbie to get you to JFK in time for your flight . Departure at the airport was similar, waved right on through. No requests for any sort of exit fee. Got to the PC airport two hours early to allow for whatever we figured we had to allow for, sat at the gate and cooled our heels for an hour and a half before boarding for home. Way easier than the typical confusion in, for example, Mexico City.First impressions and check in: The initial impression of the place suggests me. Not a lot of screaming opulence or showy heel-clicking, but the large, open lobby and manicured grounds clearly exude quality and the staff appear committed to customer service. The guy who unloaded our duffels find our name on his list of the (I had confirmed our room a couple weeks earlier), but left us with the impression that it a problem. And yes, they give you a little flute of champagne. At the front desk, we produced our credentials and the staffer disappeared momentarily, then reappeared, saying, step into my we slid down to a more private area of the front desk. We were then informed that the staffer was hoping to us to a higher quality and hinted that, if we were so inclined, he might be able to us this I replied that I was sure we could work something out. He disappeared again. Not being we had booked the el cheapo garden view room, and at this point it was obvious to me that given all of those away. We were going to be upgraded, and our friend at the desk was hoping to make something off the deal. He returned, saying, am going to do something nice for you, and perhaps you can do something nice for went on to explain that we would be in one of the walk-out pool-front rooms. I appreciated the entrepreneurial spirit, and had anticipated it, folding a twenty into my hand. I smiled, palmed him the bill, and everyone was happy. No one explained the Excellence Club program or tried to encourage us to sign up, fine because decided that for us. We fell in behind the bellman and headed for our casa. The room: We landed in 6001, which turned out to be the closest walk-out to the swim-up bar, an obvious advantage. The bellman gave us the rundown, explained how to use the safe, graciously accepted his tip. The room and its furnishings looked recently updated, and indeed during the course of the week we saw new cabinetry that matched ours being moved into several rooms. We checked out all the equipment to make sure everything was working, the only flaw being that the screen on the sliding door was too short for the opening and would fall off unless closed all the way. No problem, we unpacked. Everything was clean and in order, the room spacious, the shower had great pressure and volume, two-person jetted tub separating bed and vanity area. Vanity had a single sink, a double would have been more convenient, but since we were never in a hurry no big deal. The bed was about what we have come to expect in Mexico, meaning beyond firm to hard, but manageable. Being off of a corner of the pool, the room had a slightly larger than average grassy area beyond the small patio, which included two comfortable chairs and a table. Like other pool-fronts, we had a hammock. Despite proximity to the swim-up bar, the room was not noisy at the times we were there, and since that bar closes at 6 p.m., no problems in the evening. The location is close to the central hub of activity surrounding the lobby, so very convenient. A bit of a walk to the beach, but nothing important.The grounds: Beautifully landscaped, impeccably maintained. The larger pool meanders over most of the length of the resort, between the buildings and the beach, unique and beautiful. There are only a couple places where bridges cross, so it takes a bit of orientation to figure out your shortest route to get from point A to B. Pool and ocean water temperature seem pretty similar, guess around 80. Lots of lounges, beds, and floats, all in good condition. Never had a problem establishing a beach head. Other than the swim up bar after finished up at the beach, we use the pool. Adjacent to the drive coming in there is a small ecological park with gardens and a jogging track. This is worth a walk through, as the gardens are quite nice and you will find peacocks, wild turkeys, chickens, parrots, and all manor of bird life hanging out there. During our entire stay, we saw but a single mosquito.The beach: The beach is long, wide, and you find a scrap of trash. Numerous palapas to duck under during the one or two minute sprinkles that occurred on a few days. Lots of beds and lounge chairs. Some have described the sand as darker than the whiter Caribbean beaches. Yes, it is slightly darker, but pure and without rocks, shells, or other debris, a joy to walk in. Because of the remote location, you can trek as far as you wish in either direction without encountering another resort. There were significant breakers each day, fun to swim in if you like that sort of thing, which I do. In addition to the tidal surf, the wind was up each day, so there was a lot of wind-driven waves as well. I find any rocks or debris in the water, just a nice sandy bottom. The best rips for body surfing or boarding were at the right edge of the property (as you are facing the ocean). I did not find the water threatening, and there were always a couple guards on duty, whistling in those who were thought to be too far out. The low-rise architecture of the resort, together with the palms in front, makes the resort almost non-existent when you are on the beach, adding to the beach experience. Exiting the property on the beach, both right and left, you will find a few vendors who will try to hawk you into there little shacks, but certainly no more aggressive than Mexico, they will take no for an answer. For those to whom such things matter, topless women were frequently in evidence.The facilities, activities and entertainment: Other than excursions, we spent most of our days on the beach, thus did not do things like tennis, horseback riding, pool games, etc. Saw some of that going on, and the staff appeared to work hard to encourage participation and make sure those engaged were having fun. The bars we frequented were Kafe (at the pool), Martini (off the lobby), swim up, and the long bar which runs adjacent to the theater area. The theater area, where the evening shows take place, is pretty neat, with comfortable couches provided to watch the entertainment. All the bars had a nice ambience, and were good places to chat up other guests or the bartenders. Service was prompt and selection was very good. No, you find single malt scotch, but the Johnnie Walker, Bombay Sapphire, Jack Daniels, Absolut, several cognacs, etc. are there for the asking. Sharon had the Excellence Massage at the spa, and spoke highly of the facility and service. The spa runs daily specials, so make sure you check that out prior to scheduling, you can save yourself a few bucks. We paid $98 for a 50 minute massage, tip not included. There are several shops on the property, and local vendors are invited in a couple of times a week to set up in the commons area. We see anything we wanted to buy. As has been said in other reviews, Domingo on sax is a genuine talent, worthy of any club in Chicago or New Orleans. He played before and after shows on several evenings, and we could have listened to him indefinitely. Absolutely top shelf. A rock / salsa quartet played one evening prior to the show, they were forgettable. The two shows we saw were Michael Jackson and the circus. We were entertained and enjoyed both. We both really enjoyed the adults only aspect of the place.Restaurants and food: Let me start by saying that Sharon and I do a fair amount of scratch cooking and know good food, however, we are in no way food snobs and can enjoy a meal at Also, this was our first experience with an all-inclusive, so we really have no basis for comparison. With that qualifier, I will start by saying that we did not care for most of the dinners we ate. First night was the French place, I had rack of lamb and she scallops. The scallops were pretty good, the lamb, although prepared to my liking, was about the toughest ever had. I had a quality piece of beef (fillet) at Barcelona, but it had simply been fried, and tasted mostly of the oil it was fried in. Sharon had chicken breast which was so so. The shrimp fajitas at Agave were served with just the shrimp with onion and a few green peppers, and the tortillas, no guacamole, shredded lettuce, salsa, etc. No Mexican spices and way over salted, as was most of the shrimp we had at the resort. The grilled lobster at the Lobster House was decent, but the salad was bland, and what was billed as lobster and shrimp chowder tasted like beef broth mixed with Thai fish sauce. Sides in most places were a few alongside instant mashed potatoes, which do nothing for me. I had mahi mahi at the Grill, fresh but again pan fried with no imaginative spices or sauce. The buffet out on the patio Friday night was pretty decent, and a great atmosphere, with Domingo serenading us through the meal. The house wines served with dinner were passable, and we never went for any of the premium priced stuff. For desserts, which neither of us eat much of, the coconut pie at Barcelona was good, the brulee at the French place not good. Usually split a plate of fresh fruit for dessert, which was available in some of the restaurants buffet style. The building that houses the French place and Agave has no real atmosphere to speak of, too brightly lit and aging infrastructure. The Grill and adjacent Lobster House are outside, and these were charming, candles and towering thatched roofs. Barcelona and Tuscany share one large room with a divider, but the layout and lighting are ok. The breakfast buffet at Tuscany is very good, eggs or omelets to order, bacon and sausages, lots of fresh fruit, great selection of baked goods, we ate there most days. We ordered room service the two mornings we had early excursions, it came at the appointed time, the breakfasts were good, and hot. In summary, it struck me that the kitchen really have a feel for how food should taste. Presentations were nice, which told me they cared, but there was no real character to most of it. Also, there was no evidence of any sort of local cuisine, something of a disappointment since we go for that.Service and staff: Our experience echoed all the good reviews you have read. We never waited for a seat at any meal, meals were delivered courteously and in a reasonable amount of time, bartenders were attentive and engaging, concierge helpful and thorough. Our room was made up and turned down each day by a lovely lady whose name I unfortunately catch. I started out leaving her two bucks a day, but after the third day, when we came home in the evening to a hot bubble bath drawn in the tub and flower petals around the sink, I upped it to three. From that point we got twin kissing swan towels rather than the single sculpture, and lots of flower petals. Mini bar was refreshed daily. On the beach, our man Felix was always available, friendly, courteous, and engaging. He seemed to magically appear just at the time you were thinking about another Bombay and tonic. For a large resort, this is unquestionably the best service we have received, rivaling small boutique places we have stayed. The staff was as willing to chat and socialize as you wanted them to be, and really seemed to enjoy that aspect of their jobs. All understood English well enough to do their jobs effectively, and they seemed to appreciate our bumbling attempts at Spanish. We tipped freely but not more than a couple bucks at a time. We see many others doing this so never felt obligated. It was simply our way of saying thanks for excellent service.In summary, this is a fine resort where you really have no excuse for having a bad time. Despite the less-than-stellar food, we would not hesitate booking with Excellence again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>