<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="199e14a6e26a26d61bd7db1599fd98dd" url=""><![CDATA[Outstanding in all respects Over the past couple of years, aging parent issues have taken me to Phoenix frequently, so I've had the opportunity to try several hotels in the metro area. After my most recent two-night stay, the Pointe Hilton Squaw Peak Resort is my new favorite. an with lots to recommend it.Our plane landed just before noon and, after a couple of grueling flights, my wife and I wanted to freshen up and eat a decent meal before seeing my folks. When I called the hotel, the front desk clerk was very helpful and confirmed that the suite they'd set aside for us was indeed ready, so we headed straight for the resort.Upon check-in, which was handled very smoothly, we were informed of the resort option package, which provides a number of amenities (including fitness center access, spa discounts, and local phone calls) for $2.25 a day. As Hilton HHonors members, we were also given two complimentary bottles of water.After freshening up, we headed to the Hole in the Wall Restaurant for lunch. This was a bit nostalgic for me, as I grew up in Phoenix and friends and I had frequented the Hole in the Wall at its original location in its early days. The food was (and still is) basic burgers, sandwiches, and quesadillas, but well prepared and reasonably-priced (especially considering in a resort). The service was also excellent.Thus fortified, we set off to see The Parents.Over the next several days, our two-room suite became our sanctuary. It included a separate living room and bed room, robes (without having to ask), a very comfy bed, the fluffiest towels I have used in a long time (at home or away), a balcony, a well-stocked mini-bar, and some of the best in-room coffee I've in a long time. While our room was in one of two multi-story buildings, the resort also offers casitas - single story structures away from the larger buildings and adjacent conference center.While the property has four restaurants, we only ate at the Hole in the Wall. However, we did use room service, which was also prompt, polite, and provided well-prepared fare.There are several pools available, including a small water park adjacent to the Hole in the Wall. And even though a fair number of kids were present at the hotel, it was overall very quiet.Plenty of free parking and easy access to the rest of Phoenix make this a winner in my book. Without a doubt, we will be back.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="345efd6ae6107577b3c7b13ceb38485a" url=""><![CDATA[Decent place, close to airport I stayed one night while in town for a couple of quick business meetings. As my schedule was pretty full, I didn't get back to the hotel in time for the manager's reception, but I did pop into the bar for a bite. I recall it as being busy and loud (typical of a hotel bar). The food was OK, but the house wines left a bit to be desired. My flight out left early, so I didn't get to experience breakfast the next morning.The room itself was nice: large, clean and well-kept. The staff seemed pleasant and helpful enough.One oddity: the shared computer -- the closest thing to a business center -- is right in the lobby. That's not bad unless you have e-mail you really don't want people seeing over your shoulder. The other facet of that arrangement is that the computer is accessible to kids who tie it up for long periods either gaming or IM-ing their friends. And the hotel staff doesn't seem inclined to enforce the age restrictions too tightly.Generally, a decent business hotel for value-oriented travelers.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7640d9534e197da528c8e4858c5c4dca" url=""><![CDATA[Decent hotel for the money I've stayed at this hotel three times in the last month. The people at the front desk were generally attentive and helpful, though the male bartender wasn't the friendliest guy I've ever had serve me a drink. The lady was quite nice.Overall, the hotel needs some sprucing up, as it's showing signs of wear. However, the rooms were generally clean with only modest wear showing. But be sure to ask for a room that doesn't face the atrium (where the pool is located) if you're concerned about noise.If you're a Priority Club member, the hotel provides coupons for a couple of drinks per night in the bar (99 Degrees), a coupon for a continental breakfast the next morning (add eggs and meat for a modest charge), and a cup of Starbucks joe.Be sure to get the AAA rate. The difference between the AAA rate and the standard rate is the biggest savings I've seen in some time.Convenient to I-17 and MetroCenter.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c8cd5e5007abe5a6781dd0c80a0d4f4c" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel, convenient location The front entrace from the sidewalk on Canal Street
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c31db7e115343a65bed4f3d424dcaba4" url=""><![CDATA[Would stay again My wife and I stayed here while visitng my elderly parents for Thanksgiving. On check-in, I asked about an upgrade as they had said they were pretty empty for the holiday. The room they gave us was larger, but it was more for business entertaining. It had an odd Murphy bed, the TV didn't face either a chair (there was no couch) or the bed, and it wasn't at all inviting. We went back to their standard room, which turned out to be just fine. As usual, the hotel gift shop items were overpriced ($3 for a bottle of OJ) but that's the price of convenience. And altough the CyberCenter off the lobby says Compliments of the Sheraton Crescent, the Internet services are not free as the word implies; they come with the usual charge, whether you're using your own laptop or their desktops.On the very positive side, all staff members were courteous and helpful, one problem with a slow-running drain was quickly attended to, the hotel was close to I-17 and MetroCenter (big shopping mall) and generally well-kept. Next time we're in Phoenix, we'll definitely look into the Crescent again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>