<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="83720bade12e6f72ed3386edc4e76172" url=""><![CDATA[Unbelievable Lack of Customer Care When we checked in on July 26, we gave them our keys for valet parking since this is downtown. On the 28th the staff brought our van to us with the back window totally burst out. They proceeded to tell us that this was our problem and between us and the parking garage. They did not even apologize. After the garage employee came he told us that if we didn't pitch a fit nothing would get done. I had a pretty big rant on the garage manager who told us it would take 2-3 weeks to get approval to fix. At that time we learned that the hotel had known that our car had sustained damage, but they had chosen to fail to tell us about it. We only saw the damage at check-out. I demanded to know why they had chosen to not disclose this to us so that we could get it fixed. They at first lied that they didn't know, but after the garage person said they had been notified, the desk lady changed her mind. When the front desk manager arrived, I asked him to refund us our stay because of the hassle this was causing us. It took me over 2 hours of arguing with him to even agree to refund one day. I am still in the process of getting the 2nd day refunded. The desk clerk reminded us that she had offered us a solution. The only solution she offered was to bring our vehicle with a broken window. It took them 5 hours to get our van fixed while my family waited in the lobby. They never once apologized until I told them that they had not apologized. I also said they could at least offer my children a drink. They never did. The parking garage manager actually wound up buying lunch for my family while the hotel only proceeded to make excuses and blame and deny that they did anything wrong. The bellman was the only one from the hotel that from the beginning said he was sorry, and he was yelled at by the manager to stay out of the matter. We were appalled at their lack of care or concern for our family. A minor fact...the continental breakfast consisted of only bananas, muffins, and pastry.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>