<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a32025ad7f70a3837f20854a631e3a62" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful facilities, inconsistent food/service My wife and I stayed at the IB four nights during our friends' wedding weekend. Our visit started great with very prompt shuttle service (through a private tour company) and a warm welcome to the resort by reception staff. We received an informative overview of the resort, a tropical beverage, and were invited to our room (1161) while our bags were handled by the bell staff. The facilities here are beautiful -- peacocks roam the grounds (more on them later), flamingos wade in ponds, the gardens are perfectly maintained, and the rooms are spacious and well-appointed. The fantastic pool is the focal point of the resort, but we spent most of our time on the beautiful beach with powder soft sand and crystal clear waters.Our only issues with the resort stem from our interactions with the staff and the food. First, reservations are required for the specialty restaurants at the resort (reservations are not required for the buffet restaurant). The guest services staff are unfriendly at best. They keep irregular hours and are very unaccommodating to large groups and changes to reservations. When attempting to make a reservation at the French restaurant, the staff person thought I said the Fish restaurant and gave me a reservation at the Mediterranean restaurant by mistake. When I went back to resolve the issue he refused to believe I said French and not Fish and by that time reservations at the French restaurant were not available. Of course, we found out later that the restaurant was in fact half-empty because so many people make reservations and then don't keep them. Thankfully, the Mediterranean restaurant was very good. The Japanese restaurant was not good. The buffet is expansive and caters to several nationalities' tastes, but overall quality was poor.Service at the restaurants was also spotty. Although the resort is all-inclusive, they don't make it easy to get what you want. Ordering anything other than the house wine requires a negotiation and at least a few requests.Other than our restaurant-related issues, most of the staff are energetic and friendly. The guys advertising resort activities on the beach can get a little too persistent and the impromptu performance art (for lack of a better term) are a little odd. For instance, out of no where one day a guy dressed as a peacock comes running down the beach chased by a guy dressed as a chef wielding a knife. The peacock grabbed my wife and hid behind her as the chef approached. Then they ran off to annoy other guests. Speaking of peacocks, they are beautiful and exotic, but they crow like roosters on steroids at daybreak.Bottom line, IB is a beautiful place. I recommend the specialty restaurants over the buffet, but make your reservations early in the day and avoid interactions with the staff for the sake of your blood pressure.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>