<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="4b44e6a8cf5e07001578b5929c19c4a2" url=""><![CDATA[Loved the Hoxton We had already booked the Hoxton Hotel for our annual week in London, for August of 2007, however, we found an absolute bargain and decided to stay for two nights in July, prior to our main stay.Having stayed in many decent four and five-star London hotels I was a little concerned with the Hoxton being a mere three-star establishment, but my fears didn't last long. We arrived by the nearest tube (Old Street), practically the heart of the City of London and enjoyed a leisurely stroll to the hotel, taking about five or six minutes.The area surrounding the Hoxton could be said to be a little run-down, however we found the area to be relatively safe and otherwise nothing of great concern. As we approached the hotel it looked rather modern and to quote others, 'trendy'. We approached the check-in desk in the main lobby passing the bar and lounge areas. We were very efficiently checked-in and dispatched to our room. On the day that we stayed there had been a problem with the computer that controls the access cards and so we were personally led to our room by a member of staff. This problem didn't last and within an hour or so the cards were activated.As we entered our room from the ultra-modern hallway we found, what on first inspection appeared to be, a small room. However the use of space was excellent and we didn't struggle for room at all. The cleanliness, decor and quality of the room and fittings was of the highest order. The adjustable LCD television above the desk made viewing from the bed a delight. Inside the fridge we found a complimentary quarter pint of fresh semi-skimmed milk and two bottles of mineral water. None of those awful UHT thimbles here! The bed was pure heaven, the heavy and plump pillows were dressed in the same crisp white, and rather expensive, linen as the rest of the bed and the whole sleeping experience was divine. The en-suite shower-room was tiled from floor to ceiling and the shower itself was one of the most pleasant in the whole of London. The strong shower never struggled for either power or heat and made cooling-off on a warm July day excellent. Unlike many London hotels, the cleanliness couldn't be faulted. The towels are extra-large and very soft; we also found extra towels and two extra pillows in the wardrobe.The extras in this hotel were very important to us; the free Wi-Fi internet access was easy, nothing to set-up and it worked instantly and was much quicker than our home broadband connection. The complimnetary breakfast of a banana, orange juice and yoghut (all Pret Manger) was always delivered at the time selected by us. The fruit was very fresh and the yoghurt excellent.There is a sense of down-to-earth honesty here that I have never experienced in any of the many pretentious hotels that I have stayed in. The telephone calls are charged at 3p per minute for national rate calls, instead of the usual pounds-per-unit price that other hotels charge. There is also a shop in the hotel selling chocolate, crisps, nuts and drinks and all at newsagent prices. A can of Coca-Cola cost just 50p.We did not use the restuarant on this visit so we therefore cannot pass comment, we'll save that for our August review.In conclusion, we would now always consider this hotel as our first choice in London. It's excellence is beyond comparison with similar hotels.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>