<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="b2f9e08505023c6fa3d73db53fc94984" url=""><![CDATA[An "Experience" Alright, this hotel was very good in some ways, but bad in others. Lets start with the bad. The hotel is extremely large and seems to be an epicentre for what is going on in Times Square. If you like to be in the middle of things, this hotel is fantastic, but if not, it is very crowded. It can be near impossible to get a lift up to your room from the street level because of the hundreds of people trying to get to the times square shows under the hotel. With it being a large hotel, I was suprised to discover the lack of restauraunts. There was one marriott cafe that closed at 8:30 (NOT HELPFUL, especially after wanting as much time out in NY as possible) and an extremely over priced show case restauraunt on top of the hotel, that revolved around in useless circles so that you could see NY, but really you could see nothing. The food served there was probably worth a quarter of the price charged, and had EXTREMELY slow service, which the waiter gave me attitude about and blamed in on another large group. Needless to say, I am an Australian and am not used to leaving tips at the best of times, so this guy was not going well. After that experience I left a very small tip and never went back. Be careful as they try to pull the trick of putting an AUTOMATIC 18%!!!!!!! surcharge on the bill if u have more than 4 people. We had 5, so the $500 bill for the trash we ate went up t0 590. Rediculous! Moving on. Being a large hotel, service was lacking slightly, and it took a long time to get anything. Putting that aside, it was a top quality Marriott. The room I stayed in was newly furnished, with new TV and had a fantastic view over times square. Saying that, LOCATION LOCATION BABY!!!! This hotel is fantastc. Right in the middle of everything, walk out the door and Times Square just hits you. A great place. So, to wrap it up. A busy hotel, but to expected in Times Square, bad food in typical marriott fashion, but a irreplacable location and a great room. It definately was an experience I will never forget.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>