<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="5d1be2c1c2f9f926bca94d3889aedf8e" url=""><![CDATA[Lovely hotel -- if only the standard rooms weren't so small I have only one less-than-positive thing to say about the Hotel de which is that the standard rooms are, as other reviewers have mentioned, very small. I stayed by myself in a standard double (Room 31), and, while it was adequate as a single, I have wanted to stay there with another person. On the plus side, the room was quiet and dark at night, the bed was comfortable, there was ample light for reading in bed (which was a good thing, since there was really nowhere else in the room to sit and read), and the bathroom was spotlessly clean, modern, and a decent size.Apart from the room size, I loved everything about the The public areas are beautiful. Even though it was too cold when I was there to eat breakfast in the garden, the glassed-in breakfast area that looks out on the garden is lovely (and several copies of the International Herald Tribune are provided every morning, so I was always able to snag a copy, no matter how many other American guests were eating breakfast at the same time). The wood-burning fire in the lobby looked so welcoming when I came back to the hotel late one afternoon, chilled after a long day of sightseeing in the Parisian drizzle, that I brought my travel journal down to the lobby and wrote up my notes on the day while sitting in front of the fireplace.I found the staff at the to be uniformly helpful and fluent in English. When I arrived, at 11 a.m., my room ready yet, so the desk clerk suggested that I wait in the breakfast room (where breakfast was still being served to late risers) and order breakfast if I wanted to, which I gratefully did. (Breakfast was included in my room rate and, even though breakfast on the day of arrival was, in effect, a bonus breakfast, no extra charge was made.) And when I asked another desk clerk to find a street address for me one day (having misplaced the address of a store I wanted to visit), he not only found it immediately but printed out an internet map of the neighborhood for me.Bottom line: if your budget runs to one of the larger rooms at the Hotel de hesitate to book a room there. If you can only swing one of the standard rooms, then whether the hotel is a good fit for you depends on how important the size of the room is to you, and whether willing to put up with tight quarters in exchange for all the other good qualities mentioned.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>