<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="eb2d456b63c2b524e57bc172ac03a060" url=""><![CDATA[opulent comfort My family including 2 very small children stayed at the hotel during evacuation for Hurricane Ike and were on the property for about a week.It is located near uptown and its sister property the Crescent but is secluded on Turtle Creek. It is also not very well marked which, in this case, increases the feeling of being hidden in nature while still in the heart of Dallas. Other nearby features include a running trail and Love Field (5 min drive). One can easily walk to the tram and take it downtown to the museums and aquarium (which we did with our kids). The service was warm and polite. People were treated the same whether they were formally or informally dressed. The lobby always had fruit and refreshments or coffee out for guests passing through. The staff consistently expressed genuine concern for our well-being and ease.The rooms are going to be upgraded by 2009 so, if like one of the other reviewers, you like the patina of older rooms you'd best visit soon. I'd be excited to see the renovation, though, because some of the furnishings are showing a little wear. The rooms are not particularly large or small but well appointed and the bathrooms were handsomely done in stone and mirror with fine fixtures. Our room had a live plant and there were always fresh flowers in the public areas.The hotel is built onto an existing mansion providing a sense of history and authenticity. Great just to explore and walk through, it gives character other hotels will have trouble capturing. The dining room was superb with locally sourced Texas ingredients served in a french style. Every plate came out meticulously prepared with perfect temperature and doneness. The wine list has a wine spectator award which is definitely deserved, though there were few bargains on it. The waiters and sommeliers were patient and affable.The cocktail bar has an avant garde mixologist who prepares old school items like homemade tonic water for gin and tonic (highly recommended) and new school molecular gastronomy cocktails. The bar itself is a dark and cozy space with jazz music in the mansion area.The hotel's workout room was well-equipped with dumbbells, weight machines and several types of commercial grade cardio machines.One would not usually think of such a place as good for children and indeed the pool area is not large but our children were very happy with the amenities available and the old mansion to explore. There is no formal children's program but the concierge can easily get babysitters. Our children were quite welcome in the hotel. I would not hesitate to recommend the hotel to travels of any type because it can suit anyone.We were checked on in the dining room daily by the hotel manager, Duncan Graham. It's great to see a hotel being successful one relationship at a time. His presence was a difference from most hotels where the responsible parties usually hide behind the staff. We felt no concern was too big or small to discuss with him and he always seemed to have time to chat.Overall, we loved the hotel and recommend it highly.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>