<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="bded01e237a66e94d5ee7d3cefc9af4d" url=""><![CDATA[Great Value, Great Location My husband and I have been to New York several times over the past few years and stay at a different place each time. We've stayed at the W, the Doubletree Times Square, the Warwick, etc. This time we stayed at Hotel Mela the week before Christmas. We just happened to find it online for a fantastic price compared to the other hotels during the holidays. We took a chance and were very please with it. The rooms are extremely small (what you would expect in a European hotel) but very clean, modern, and comfortable. If you want to be in the middle of the city, close to times square, and within walking distance to basically everything else (theater district, park, museums, etc) it is the perfect location for you. Although we didn't eat at the hotel, the restaurant looked very good. It was a nice surprise for us and overall we were very happy.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4ec31b3721bd30b08fbc99e377e97556" url=""><![CDATA[Believe the Reviews! I booked the Beijing Sihe Hotel based on these fantastic reviews. I was very excited, but a little concerned that my mother and I would be disappointed. We were thrilled with everything about the hotel! The staff was friendly and helpful through our entire stay. We left our luggage with the front desk 2 days before we checked in (because we could not take more than one bag on the train) and when we arrived our bags were in our room. The staff went out of their way to make our stay outstanding from finding a restaurant that delivered late at night to arranging a taxi to take us to the airport at 5:00am.The breakfast at the hotel restaurant was wonderful! The Chinese Dumpling Breakfast was one of the best things we ate during our stay in China. A great way to start our day before climbing the great wall. The reviews stated that taxi drivers had difficulty finding the hotel. We had the address written in Chinese characters, and did not have any problem. At the train station, we went through 3 taxi drivers before one knew where it was, but it was quick and the driver who took us easily made it to the entrance to the hutong. Taxis have difficulty fitting down the small alley, so we walked from the entrance to the hotel each time. It was a short walk, and well worth it! Overall, this hotel was fantastic! I will stay here again next time I visit and cannot wait to stay here with my husband. My mother and I loved every minute of it! Believe everything you've read! Stay at the Sihe!!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>