<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="8bc66fd55232715c396bfe3201d6c2a2" url=""><![CDATA[Airport Hotel with more! This is a great hotel for an overnight stop but also offers more if you want to stay a few days away from the noise and bustle of Victoria Island or Kowloon. The Novotel Citygate is five minutes from the airport on Lantau Island by free minibus which runs every 30 minutes. Check at desks A16 or B16 in the airport arrival halls. The hotel is new with very modern good sized rooms well fitted out with bar fridge, widescreen TV and tea and coffee making facilities. There is also a safe, iron and board and a hair dryer. They also supply a neat power plug adaptor kit - you can buy one for youself at the front desk. Rooms are very quiet and have nice views. There are two resturants, but can't comment on these as I only had breakfast which was very good. An out-door pool and gym are also available. The hotel joins the Citygate shopping mall which is full of factory outlet shops.Thru the mall is the cable car to Ngong Ping village and the Po Lin Monastary with a huge mountaintop bronze Buddha. Well worth the ride. Also in the mall is the Tung Chung MTR station. The ride into central Hong Kong takes 30 minutes. You can also take the MTR to nearby Disneyland.There is a bus station at the end of the mall near the cable car terminal where bus tours are available to the quiet beaches and small fishing villages around the island.Modern and well appointed at a good price, with more to offer than the average airport hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="115396d4e251a59bdab5d2af1c7672c3" url=""><![CDATA[Great value,good position Just back from 12 days in HK staying at the Kimberley. All the public areas of the hotel have been renovated, the rooms have been repainted and wall papered and the bathrooms have had a make-over. However the room furniture looks tired and the carpets need replacement, but everything works and the place is clean. Service is fine, the desk staff helpful and no supprises on the bill.Room sizes are on the small side but this is HK. Bed was hard but housekeeping supplied a soft overlay which improved things.When booking, include the breakfast option. The full buffet breakfast is great value. They also have an evening buffet dinner which is good and includes wine and beer.Position is handy in Kimberly Rd off Nathan Rd and a short walk to the MTR. We were on the 12th floor at the front and the room was very quiet. There is a 7/11 store across the road and a Welcome Supermarket down the street on the opposite side. Many small resturants nearby. Try the Nomad mongolian bbq.A good value mid-range hotel with no problems.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e21ca529ffe761186ecb69ab1c7149e6" url=""><![CDATA[Check you bill and don't use the phone! For a five star hotel this is good value. We had a great room on the 16th floor overlooking the harbour. The room was a good size with comfortable beds and all the usual fittings - bar fridge, safe, iron, hairdryer etc. The general tone of the hotel was high class with lots of marble and gold chandeliers. \The buffet breakfast is good but get there early as not much is left by the 10 o'clock closing time. The Promenade Resturant buffet dinner is great value with unlimited softdrink, wine and beer for an extra $HK68. Book early as it is very popular with the locals.Check your bill carefully when departing as we were charged twice for breakfast. Also beware of the hotel telephone system. In Hong Kong local calls are free but this hotel charges $HK6 per call from your room. Also do not use a phone card with an 800 freecall number as they charge $HK30 per call onto your bill. Go down to the lobby and use the public phones for $HK1 a call. Fair value, nice decor, great views but check your bill and don't use the phones.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>