<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="15f7e291d2cb2c646965dab6d1c9e7b3" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Hotel! My daughter and I came to NYC in May and stayed at the Belvedere. I stayed there 7 years ago and was impressed. We were there for 3 nights and had a great time.We arrived a couple of hours before check in and our room was ready, we requested a non smoking room and received one. Everyone at the front desk was helpful. One negative thing I can say is that the concierge was not very pleasant and seemed over worked. Just did not take the time that I thought he should have. He was busy answering phones, putting away mail talking to people who went by, etc.Our room was clean, the bathroom was tiny but OK, I loved the coffee pot and refrigerator. We did not eat at the hotel at all, I thought the food there was pricey. One thing I liked is the location. It is so central to everything, it is only a few blocks walk to the Today Show, you are right around the corner from Times Square where you can catch the red double decker buses (they were great - I would highly recommend them), it is an easy walk to the theatre and to the United Nations. Plus restaurant row is only 1 block away, I would recommend the Olympus Diner, right around the corner from the hotel - they were very friendly and the food was resonably priced.We really enjoyed our trip and would not hesitate to stay at the Belevedere again. The hotel was as great as I remember it 7 years ago.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f3cddc5c1a814f82869c3ef5c5575285" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Hotel! My husband and I stayed at the hotel October 29th to November 2nd, 2004. I booked the hotel because it was recommended by Frommer's travel guide. I also looked at the reviews on tripadvisor and that also helped me make my final decision.Our room was average sized, I especially liked the fact that it had a couple of chairs and a table. I hate watching TV in bed (it is tough with bifocals). The beds were the most comfortable beds I think I have ever slept in, I don't know if the mattresses were new, but they were great. They also have these down comforters on the bed and several down pillows per bed, it was so hard to get up in the morning. I actually looked forward to getting back in the bed.The room had everything we needed, bar, refrigerator, big TV, shampoo and supplies, hair dryer, ironing board and iron, an umbrella and extra pillows. It also has a keyboard for wireless internet (extra fee). I also requested a courtyard view room and that kept down the noise (although we were up early everyday anyway). In the lobby they have free coffee, tea and biscotti everyday and have wine and snacks from 5 p to 6 p daily. There are newspapers at the desk for everyone. We ate at the adjoining restaurant once - I was not impressed.The hotel was centrally located to all the attractions, only 2 blocks from the wharf. That was so nice. And there were a lot of restaurants around, and a lot of souvenier shops. Pier 39 is there and we spent a lot of time watching the sea lions (so did everyone else).All in all we enjoyed our stay and would not hesitate to recommend it to anyone and we would certainly stay there again. The staff was very nice.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>