<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="7">
		<document id="2a6d33860976302d1ec288a56976dac5" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful!!!! My husband and I spent 3 nights here recently. We were pleasantly surprised with our standard room. It was nicely decorated, clean and quite spacious. The location is excellent- just one block from Bourbon Street, and an easy walk to some great restaurants and Riverwalk. Be sure to have a drink at the Carousel bar located in the lobby.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d4dea9670c765992069bd29b7aeb4d70" url=""><![CDATA[Definitely 4 star +++++ My husband and I spent 6 nights here in mid June and enjoyed it immensely. The location is suburb;just minutes from Las Ramblas and Placa Calalunya. The hotel is just 2 years old, very modern with all the comforts of home. We had a 7th floor room with a balcony and we had no problem with noise. A nice plus is the free internet service next to the bar. If you like to shop, be sure to visit Corte Ingles at Pl. Catalunya. A great place for tapas is CAL PEP near the Picasso museum. But be sure to go early...theres no reservations and there are long lines.If you choose Hotel Jazz, you certainly will not be disappointed.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="42c1e91aa01387f461d54d6637a2fd0f" url=""><![CDATA[What A Gem!! Our 7 night stay at the Vitale was wonderful from start to finish. We had a deluxe bay front room on the 7th floor which was lovely. The view from the wall-to-wall window of the bay bridge was awesome. All off the staff were wonderful and accommodating, including the front desk, the concierge, bellmen and especially housekeeping. Our rooms were always cleaned as soon as we left in the morning. We ate breakfast in the hotel restaurant twice which we enjoyed. Boulettes Larder in the Ferry Building across the street served a great breakfast. (don't miss it) The hotel's lounge and outdoor bar/patio was open late and got very crowded. Despite this we never had any problem with noise. The hotel was in a great location away from all the hustle and bustle of Fisherman's Wharf. If we were to return to SF, we would definitely stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0a5627d863d89cf8fd332a1b8afed4fa" url=""><![CDATA[Definitely 4 star +++++ My husband and I spent 5 nights here and enjoyed it immensely. It is centrally located within walking distance to everything. The street to the side of the hotel (Montero) caters to the ladies of the night, but we found it to be more entertaining than dangerous. The hotel is equipped with all the necessities plus some. The refrigerator with water, beer, soda is a real plus and is stocked daily. Request a top floor, corner room if possible. Our corner room had 3 balconies and overlooked the Gran Via. If you like to shop, be sure to go to Corte Ingles on the Gran Via. We splurged and hired a private guide to take us to Toledo for the day. We loved this unique city. Transportation from the airport by taxi cost us about $30. If you're traveling on a weekday, allow for extra time; traffic is awful! If you choose this hotel, you won't be disappointed.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ee3c595de516870407d24296ed2c8212" url=""><![CDATA[Lovely Hotel but........ My husband and just returned from spending a week in Florence. The Astoria is in a wonderful location, just minutes from the train station, San Lorenzo market, the Duomo, and a 10 min. walk to the Ponte Vecchio. The lobby is very impressive with a large sitting area and a very relaxing bar/lounge ( however, it was not open in the evenings during our stay). The beautiful roof top bar is open at night til the wee hours of the morning. The views are breathtaking!! Our room was a Jr. Suite( a 2 story unit with a living room downstairs and a winding staircase leading to an upstairs bedroom.) The BR upstairs was spacious and modern. One unusual aspect of the room was that there were no closets upstairs- you kept your clothes downstairs. Quite getting used to! Breakfast consisted of cereals, fruits, juices , meats, cheeses, breads and muffins. Everyone at the hotel was very helpful. The hotel was in need of a few repairs, however. The rugs were very dirty and the walls could use a paint job or the wallpaper repaired.......All in all it was a pleasant stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ad0fc3df8fee108f208fac301c2f00ec" url=""><![CDATA[Still Wonderful! My husband and I along with another couple spent a wonderful weekend here at The Michaelangelo. This was our second visit here and everything was still wonderful. When we arrived early, our room was ready and we even received an upgrade to a junior suite. It was a very spacious living room/bedroom combination. One surprising observation upon unpacking was the lack of drawer space. There was also no safe in the room, no ironing board and iron, and no coffee pot. Continental breakfast is served in the lounge until 10:30 on weekends. The hotel is in a great location just minutes from the theatres. We come to Manhattan often and we would definitely stay here again!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6db28110422a17e96c98dcca6f604060" url=""><![CDATA[Typical European Hotel My husband and I just returned from a weekend in NY . Even though we requested an early check-in, our room was not ready til after 2. Except for Charles the doorman who was extremely courteous and helpful, we were not impressed with the hotel staff. Rooms were very reminiscent of a small European hotel. Our King room was very clean but small. The bathroom was even smaller!. To get to the sink, you needed to close the door. There was a small dressing room where you could store toiletries and put on makeup. For those ladies with long hair, bring your own hairdryer. The one in the bathroom has little power. The airconditioning was difficult to operate. It was either too cold or very stuffy. Rooms were not cleaned till mid to late afternoon. There is only one elevator, so be prepared to wait. Be sure to try the Monkey bar for drinks. It's a fun place. All in all , the hotel was just average. I would probably stay elsewhere on my next visit.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>