<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="e69eb10cc074d4fa2eb79bd8e5ca7a0c" url=""><![CDATA[Keio Plaza - Location, location, location We chose the Keio Plaza for its location and once there felt we had made an excellent choice. We wanted to be completely independent and by being right near Shinjuku Station we had ready access to anywhere we wanted to go. Hotel itself was also excellent - definitely 4 star plus, even though we only had a standard room. The room was spacious, the bathroom one of the best we''ve ever had, and our view was directly looking at the Metropolitan Govt. Office building - a landmark in its own right and quite spectacular, especially at night. Also in that particular building they offer free tours, and have a free observation platform on the 45th floor that overlooks the whole of Tokyo - open night and day. The nearby streets of Shinjuku seemed to be wall to wall restaurants and we had a great meal every night - the dearest being only $50 Australian, including beer. There were also department stores nearby which had food halls to die for - we were literally gobsmacked at the quantity, quality and presentation and packaging. ATM's were scarce on the ground but fortunately there was a post office a block away with oodles of ATM's and which was open 24 hours a day.The train system was most probably the thing we were most impressed by, and our one ride in a bullet train could only be described as wow. Shinjuku is the busiest station in Tokyo and caters for 4 million travellers a week, yet even in peak times we found it worked like clockwork - and the Japanese then, as we found them everywhere else, handled everything in such a polite and courteous manner. We had no trouble buying train tickets from vending machines - and followed the good advice we had been given, that if unsure what price ticket to buy, buy the cheapest ticket and then fix it up at the other end in one of the ticket adjustment machines. How civilised can you get! The behaviour on the transport system was always impeccable - signs requesting people not to use their mobile phones, not to eat or drink on the trains, etc., and then thanking them for the consideration, worked like a charm. Once again, how civilised!We did 3 day trips from Shinjuku - to Mt. Takao (just sublime), Kamakura and Mt. Fuji region. Also caught a train to Tokyo Station a few times and walked around Ginza (a bit akin to 5th Avenue, NY), to the Hama-rikyu Gardens on Tokyo Bay, to the Fish Markets and nearby local markets, and to a performance at the Kabuki-Za Theatre, where you can buy tickets to individual acts. Quite an experience and it exceeded our expectations.Also visited the 5 Museums area at Euno - caught a taxi there from Tokyo Station and found it quite reasonable. Noticed taxis all seemed to have white lace covers over the backs of their seats,and white damask covers on the seats themselves. They were just immaculate.After pounding the pavements day after day, or doing day trips, it was always great to get back to the Keio Plaza. It may have had over 1400 rooms and sound impersonal, but we found the rooms, service, and atmosphere excellent. Possibly our only ciriticism would be that we thought all their restaurants were pricey but with endless restaurants nearby that was the least of our worries. The fact that it's less than a 9 hour flight from Australia, only 1 hour time difference, you can drink the water anywhere, so many signs are in both English and Japanese, the people are helpful and courteous, plus the countryside is so interesting, has made us hope we can go back again for a more extensive trip.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>