<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="2b546e4e798e8f472c70fcb0130edd62" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent location and great staff - highly recommended We booked this hotel based on the reviews at Tripadvisor. The number and caliber of most reviews were amazing.First impressions count. My flight was scheduled for late evening, but it was badly delayed. I called the hotel before boarding. Their attitude made the first good impression. Receiving a warm welcome in the middle of the night healed most of the pain of a very delayed arrival. Gassim and Miriam are wonderful hosts.The location is perfect. Like many guests, I had an amazing view of the Duomo from my window. The rooms are spacious, comfortable, clean and very well maintained. The bathrooms are well furnished and very clean as well.Florence is a big open air museum and cultural centre. It is plenty of top fashion brands for serious shoppers.The overall stay and the outstanding service from the hotel exceeded all my expectations. Highly recommended!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1cf79858dc3a320fd046d601f1f80b8b" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel, excellent location December 2007 was my second time at Hyatt Regency San Francisco. The location is perfect to explore most attractions. There is a metro station and a cable car stop within a walking distance. The Port of San Francisco is across the road. It is one of the best views of Bay Bridge. Powell Street is within walking distance.The outstanding design reduces some room space. The hotel has not changed significantly since my first stay in early 1990's. Although the rooms had minor improvements, there is more to be done.The rooms are clean and comfortable. Wifi is available. The restaurant staff is very friendly. The breakfast is very good. The Equinox restaurant was closed, leaving me somewhat disappointed.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4e356e76f3c857aad7dfa029d3d343d7" url=""><![CDATA[A great alternative to city centre Amsterdam My wife and I booked this hotel to be close enough to Amsterdam without the high car park prices and busy city centre.The railway station is adjacent to Golden Tulip. It is a ten minutes ride to Amsterdam Central Station for a modest fare.The rooms are the average size for the Netherlands, well maintained and clean. The wifi makes it a good choice for business travelers as well.The staff was very helpful and provided valuable information to help us to take the best of our stay. The Zaanse Schans park is a must. It is a short drive/bus ride or, ideally, by bicycle. The cycle tracks are excellent everywhere.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>