<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="3624544208b8826cec531b338bc79170" url=""><![CDATA[A good choice In. contrast to the previous review I found the staff very friendly and helpful and all spoke good English. One in particular spent a long time translating a menu for us. The hotel is in an excellent position and how quiet the rooms are will depend on if you have one by the street or inside. We had one inside which was very quiet but lacked a little natural light. The windows are tall but face a small courtyard with rooms above. If you want ventilation you will have to stand on a chair to open the top hung window although there is air conditioning. The rooms were clean but basic, i.e laminate floors instead of carpet but better clean laminate than stained carpet. The bathroom was fine but beware of sudden changes in water temperature when using the shower, also our friends in another room had to run the water for a while to get it hot.The breakfast consisted of cereals, toast,bread,fruit, juices, pastries , bacon and scrambled eggs. My friends and I thought it was ample and good value. There are safes in the rooms to hire for 1.5 euros a day. All things considered I think for a 2 star hotel in that location it was a good choice. You could easily spend a lot more and get a lot less for it. I was more than happy with our stay and think the hotel deserves the positive reviews it gets from the majority of posters.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a394d9e6feb6ab48a722144dbde67178" url=""><![CDATA[We don`t usually do 2 star... We don`t usually do 2 star hotels but the extortinate prices of most things in florence made it a bit of a necessity. I rely a lot on the reviews from trip Advisor when making a hotel choice and so far I have not been let down. We booked this hotel based the previous positive reviews. The Europa is in a good location for most of the sights. We booked a suite which was a good size with nice furniture. The room was clean but dark due to having only one window facing in to a small courtyard, the plus side was that it was very quiet with no street noise, that is apart from the building work which started one morning at 06.30. To be fair we were out most of the day so it was`nt a problem. The room had air conditioning and a safe ( no Charge ! )The breakfast was very basic but enough to start off the day. There is a coffe machine but 4 out of the 5 days my Capaccino was luke warm. The staff were friendly and helpfull. There was nothing about the hotel which dissapointed me and I would reccomend it to anyone who would not usually do 2 star.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bba831bae48bc09ef619c39c5f08bf1c" url=""><![CDATA[I would be happy to stay there again We stayed at the Metro for 4 nights at the end of March in a superior room. We asked for non smoking but on arrival we were told the rooms were smoking, but were brand new and would not smell. They did. To be fair to the check in staff we were told in advance we could change but after a very long day we could not be bothered and decided we would leave the windows open. I regretted this after the first flush of the toilet which wouldn`t stop filling up and flooded the bathroom. Fortunately I found the stop valve and prevented it flooding the bedroom. One call to reception and staff were quickly on scene. No further problems. Whilst on the subject of the bathroom, it was TINY, the smallest I have encountered in any hotel. Anyone sat on the loo would be instantly kneecapped by another person opening the door.As previously mentioned in other postings the breakfast is a nice touch. The chocolate muffins are excellent but you need to grab them as soon as you go in otherwise someone else will. The breakfast room itself is not very big but has an informal atmosphere. The all day coffee/ tea was also very welcome.The hotel is in a good location for most things. I agree with previous posters about Heartlands brewery just around the corner, good choice of beer and food. Also worth a visit is the place directly across the road from the Hotel Metro, Brendans I think it was called. Reasonably priced and not too far too walk back ! No complaints about the staff, ther were friendly and informative but one observation. I asked for a quote for a taxi back to Newark airport and was told 90 dollars including tip. I had used Carmel from the incoming flight which was 60 dollars including tip.Reception staff had not heard of Carmel and suggested if I booked a company from the phone book they might not turn up ? I`m sure there are better hotels in New York but the Metro ticks most of the boxes and I would be happy to go there again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>