<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="cb6e62a3a7225cc58a62082766450e0c" url=""><![CDATA[Gracious hospitality in Gramercy My husband, adult daughter and I spent 3 nights at Hotel Giraffe. Arrived on a Friday and left on Christmas Eve day. We did the same thing 3 years ago and stayed at The Hilton New York, which had a great location, but we wanted a different area of Manhattan to explore. Considered The Millennium Hilton, but are so glad we settled on Hotel Giraffe. MUCH less frenzied and relaxing, with the added benefit of free continental breakfast, afternoon wine and cheese, coffee/tea/cookies 24/7, and fast/free wireless internet access. It was great to walk into the lobby and be able to get hot coffee or chocolate after walking for hours in the cold, exploring the Flatiron and Gramercy area. The lobby has comfortable chairs and couches grouped for conversation areas or playing games. With a subway stop in close proximity, we were able to access lower Manhattan, up to the Empire St Bldg and Rock Center with no problem. All the staff were responsive whenever we needed advice or help with how to... They had a laptop with printer set up and on-line in the lobby for patrons use... meaning easy printout of airline boarding passes and email checking with ease, so you don't need to lug your laptop along. The quick elevators were usually sitting with open doors waiting for us to ascend. My husband and I had a deluxe King bed room. Had a nice upholstered chair and ottoman, 2 desk areas, full closet, 6 drawers, laptop accessible in-room safe, and loved the ceramic bathroom with lighted, magnifying mirror for shaving and make-up application. Bathroom door had opaque glass in upper half of door that felt classy. Our daughter had a smaller Queen bed room. Although sq footage was smaller, it had French door access to a small balcony and full blind that had a switch by the bed for raising and lowering... very nice touch. Although we already had our restaurants picked out, the Hotel Giraffe owner also owns some restaurants and offers hotel patrons last minute reservations. We were in walking distance to Gramercy Tavern, Giorgio's, and great little Greek restaurant called Kellari's Parea Greek Bistro. But then in Manhattan it seems there's always a great little restaurant just around the corner - but being able to convene in the lobby and have a glass of wine BEFORE venturing out was a great cost benefit that made the room price in this beautiful little boutique hotel worth it. Super clean, efficiently run, secure, and relaxing.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>