<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="fc93a71cd8821710183b9399c6783a9f" url=""><![CDATA[Great Place! My friends and I stayed at the Laurel Inn on New Years Eve. The hotelhad free parking and was located near some great restaurants. The rooms were clean and comfortable and were decorated very nicely. The price is also very reasonable. I would definitely return to the Laurel Inn.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1f63142c2577837c3f87d9ad80b5f780" url=""><![CDATA[Great Hotel!!!! Stayed at the Hotel David last year with my boyfriend. The hotel was very nice, quiet and clean. The breakfasts were pretty good also. The location was good and the staff was very helpful. Came back to italy in 2006 and stayed at a different hotel farther away from the city center, boy, was that a mistake. Next time I'll stick with the Hotel David!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1e17c44293027998d3c6f7e80c8e31b2" url=""><![CDATA[The fun never stops at Hotel Ungherese After getting lost on the bus from the train station and almost getting pickpocketed, my friend and I were happy to finally reach the hotel...but our greeting was less than welcoming. After being checked in at a snails pace, all the while carrying our 30 pound backpacks, we were led to our room on the terrace. After reading all of the reviews on TA and on Rick Steeves' website, we reserved a room on the terrace. Little do the reviews tell you that you are ON the terrace. It is a public space and opens up right onto your room AND the rooms on the terrace have a bathroom with the shower directly over the toilet! This would not have been bad if it was what we were expecting, but we had no idea. Given, this is a historical building and there are limitations, we admit that we are spoiled and need a separate shower. We asked Sabrina if there was another room available and she was nice to give us another room the next day. This room was spacious and had a separate shower which we were very grateful for. My friend and I are in our 30s and are old enough to know that you cant always get what you want but after we had asked for a different room we felt that the hosts had labeled us as difficult and no matter how nice we tried to be we never felt welcome. I would not stay at this hotel again but If you do decide to stay keep in mind that the walls are paper thin and the terrace bathrooms do not have a separate shower stall. On the plus side, the terrace is nice and the rooms are spacious compared to other places we have stayed in Italy.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>