<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="490d748b21196d2bbb16123f2752373f" url=""><![CDATA[Worthy of its Name I stayed at the Majestic more than 1 year ago, however I feel compelled to comment on this wonderful hotel after reading numerous other reviews.My experience with the Majestic was superb from check-in to check out. I found the staff to be very helpful. My room was a Jr. Suite with nice windows which opened to the Passig de Gracia - very nice feature. The amenities in the room were worthy of a 5 star hotel. The decor was modern and the room was very clean. The hotel fitness center is quite nice as hotels go. The equipment was new and the locaton on the same roof deck as the pool made for a very enjoyable time when finished. The views of the city from the roof top are oustanding.I did not eat in the hotel restaurants - however I did have some drinks in the off-lobby bar and again the service was incredible. I have no bad comments for this hotel - which in these days of travel is a fine statement about the service and facilities available at the Hotel Majestic. Outstanding.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4ef9de26ed5ce5b5bddde9d8f48ccc32" url=""><![CDATA[A Fair Review of SJM OK, lots of negative messages regarding the San Juan Marriott on this board. Having stayed at this hotel approx. 20 times during the past 5 years, I feel I have some balanced perspective.My most recent stay was in April 05. The hotel facility was previously a different hotel (Diplomat) which was destroyed by a fire in the mid 80's. Marriott bought the building and renovated in the late 90's. Many of the ongoing renovations are replacement activities from the original hotel (such as old windows and doors). Prior to initiating major renovations, particularly to the rooms, both the website and the hotel advise all guests.I agree that during the past few years the service has been spotty. Sometimes good/sometimes bad but honestly more often good. I have never found any part of the facility (hotel, gym, casino) to be run down. In fact there is constant cleaning occuring in the common areas of the hotel.there The rooms are of varying size but I have never stayed in what I'd consider a small room. In the tower section of the hotel it is better to stay on floors 14 and higher because there is some noise from the lobby music - also the cabana wing is less noisy. The beds are very comfortable (soft mattress) and the housekeeping and overall upkeep has always been excellent during my stays.The pool area is quite attractive with nice landscaping, chairs, umbrellas and wait service for drinks. People who are complaining about excessive children most likely were visitng during school holiday time. I have not experienced an overwhelming number of out of control children at the pool. The beach area is public beach (city of San Juan) and not owned by the Marriott - however the hotel does provide chairs and umbrellas. The water is clean, particularly for an urban setting however there is a serious under-tow/rip-tide possibility at this beach - BE CAREFUL when swimming.The restaurants and room service are expensive - in fact I think more expensive than comparable restaurants in SJ. However in the immediate area of the Marriott (within 1/2 mile walking) are many restaurants from mid-range chains (Uno) to fine dining (Ramiros). There are also 2 Japanese restaurants within close distance (1 next to the hotel). I have never felt unsafe walking in the Condado area of San Juan - even late at night.I have found that in the past year, the SJ Marriott rates are almost always on the high-end (rarely less than $225 per night for city view room). In the past there were more frequent weekend specials and I've stayed for as little as $140 per night. For the current rates charged, there are other hotels in the city (Ritz Carlton or Intercontinental) which might provide a better experience for the money.Bottom line - if you're spending more than $225-250 and seek a true luxury experience then spend a little more and stay at the Ritz Carlton. If you want a relaxing stay in a clean, comfortable hotel with many options for dining outside the hotel AND you can get a rate of $225 or less, then I'd recommend the SJ Marriott.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="0b11e97e83c291e826b67e4f8bb91a8c" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic Hotel I stayed at the GH Singapore in August and have to say it was one of the best hotel experiences I've had. Of the many positives, location very near Orchard Road and overall quality/condition of the rooms are the most significant. Orchard Road is a 1/2 block walk from the front door of the GH. There are numerous shops, restaurants, malls all within 5 minutes walking - fantastic location. The rooms appear to have been recently renovated - as the decor is very modern/contemporary with fresh, clean, minimal design and such features as a flat panel plasma tv, wireless internet and plenty of room - large by comparison to other hotels.The fitness center and spa at the GH is also very nice by comparable hotel standards. All equipment is new, clean and would be appropriate for any fitness center. The spa facilities are also very nice with sauna, steam, whirlpool and roomy changing areas.Generally speaking, the service I experienced from the front desk staff upon check-in, to wait staff for room service, to fitness center attendees to my massage therapists was of upmost courteousness and professionalism. The staff really went out of their way to ensure my comfort.The only negatives to mention are the rather long taxi queue in the morning - at the front of the hotel. After a 20 minute wait on my first morning, I learned that hotel guests can prebook taxis the previous day - this information would have been nice to know. If you need a morning taxi then best to prebook with the bell staff. The second slightly less negative experience was with the checkout which was longer than usual - maybe 10 minutes due to a shortage of staff at the counter.The positives of my stay so far outweigh the 2 minor negatives that I will definitely stay at the GH Singapore on future visits.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b0b999d66d1d4fcccb27e0a58efd7bf6" url=""><![CDATA[Very Nice Hotel - Mixed Experience Just returned from a 4 night stay at La Concha and while overall very pleased, it was a bit of a mixed bag....On the positive side, the hotel facilities are beautiful, very South Beach inspired decor, outstanding pool areas, excellent lobby bar. The room (ocean view - 9th floor) was similar in decor - very contemporary. The bed was very comfortable with lots of pillows. The ocean view was fantastic from the room (if only there were balconies..) Each service experience was fantastic, especially Luis in the lobby bar who was very friendly. The bar does get very busy at night but it was staffed by 3 or 4 bartenders and service was good. The Fitness Center is very nice - all new equipment on par with a top line health club. The Valet parking was prompt and courteous.Check-in and check-out were prompt, efficient and courteous.I have traveled to San Juan more than 25 times and this was one of my favorite places - much better atmosphere than the Marriott. As a single traveler I find the Marriott way too family friendly (too many kids in the pool area for example) and there were noticeably fewer kids at La Concha.On the negative side, the air conditioner in the room had issues upon my arrival and also a few days later.. it would not keep the room cool. In both instances a call to the front desk and quick response (within 10 minutes) from Engineering fixed the problem. Also a little surprised to see some stains on the carpet and scuff marks on the wall (from the desk chair) . The windows in the room were also very dirty on the outside - there had been a lot of wind and rain and I know the outside windows cannot be cleaned everyday but nevertheless.. a bit annoying with an ocean view. As another reviewer wrote, I had a similar issue with the wireless internet - requiring use of an ethernet cable, which also had to be brought to the room. The room service menu was also missing from the room. It is odd that there is no hotel directory but not a particular negative for me.Regarding the construction - there were 2 mornings where the hotel-condos immediately next door were pretty loud with hammers, etc.. But the work was done during the day and if you weren't in the room during the day then not an issue. The noise was not noticeable in the hotel pool area. The hotel property itself was having some finishing touches - painting mainly - but not a difficulty or disturbance at all.The Condado area is undergoing a renaissance and while not there yet - it is well on the way to being a true destination spot.Final note - the Argentinian restaurant Uomo - about 10 minutes walking past the Marriott - is absolutely the best restaurant I've been in San Juan.. Fantastic...La Concha is definitely a great place and currently a good value (vs. other properties nearby) and upon completion of the condos and additon of the spa will prove to be even better.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>