<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="04d0b0e53f8cca05c29fa2bfffab831b" url=""><![CDATA[Okay design hotel does not quite hit the mark I stayed here for one night en route from Australia to Europe in July 2008. We got a good rate through the SIA Singapore Stopover program, but I do think the usual advertisted rates for the hotel are a little high for what you get.This is very much a hotel populated by young and beautiful guests. The room was of minimalist design, very small but perfectly comfortable, and the small bathroom had been laid out very well. The bed was comfortable. The overall design of the hotel reminded me very much of the Adelphi in Melbourne - right down to the glass-edged rooftop pool cantilevered over the street - but it comes off as a slightly pale imitation of that hotel. There is an awkwardness to the design: for example, you have to catch two elevators to get from the ground floor reception to the guest rooms. There are a number of bars and nightclubs located in the hotel, but my sleep was not at all disturbed by any noise whatsoever - the room was completely quiet. The hotel is also just a short walk along the river from the popular Clarke Quay dining and nightlife area (Singapore's main nightlife area for the young people, according to the taxi driver who took me to the nearby Asian Civilizations Musuem) and many other riverfront dining options on both sides of the river. We enjoyed drinks and tapas at the hotel's riverfront EM Bar in the evening, where you can watch the joggers puff past you and enjoy very reasonably priced happy hour drinks in a relaxed garden setting. In fact, this was the only relaxed part of the hotel - and the most enjoyable. A downside is that the hotel is quite a walk from the nearest MRT station, although taxis in Singapore are of course quite cheap and there are always several outside the hotel.In summary, it is an okay hotel but I think they are trying a little too hard for the artistic ambience that it claims to have. Worth trying once if you can get a good online deal.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b9003f4cb621166eea7d2338a7732d6f" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect "cocoon" for a Singapore stopover Standard twin room - 1043
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>