<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="b85dfec7cb7708a2c9cf7f4285819500" url=""><![CDATA[A fantastic holiday--we will return. Here is from the good,bad and the ugly. . We stayed in Club Golden,at Bahia Principe from dec.7- to dec.20-06. Our flight was a long one,because we made a stop over in Puerto Plata to pick up passengers returning to Edmonton.Our checkin was a little slow.It is at Air transat check-in away from the lobby.All the other guests had their luggage loaded up and were on their way.AND WE WERE STILL LOOKING FOR OUR LUGGAGE.Yes this property is huge,but to their credit,it has a nice layout.Shuttle service straight through the property from the lobby to the beach,Half way to the beach are two pools and A la Carte Restaurants,At the beach are two pools,with lunch and bar-services at each one.The beach is beautiful,soft sand, no coral or schells to cut your feet on. Now I read some reviews about seaweed,,somedays there is some,all a person has to do is go a little to your left or right,And you will find a place with crystal clear water.We loved the buffet and we arrived mostly at opening time. The layout of the food was beautifully arranged,,lots of variety ..If people would only step back for a moment and look at the beautiful display and carvings and appreciate it. We let Julio, the manager know ,how much we liked the set-up,he booked us at two A la Carte Restaurants (steakhouse and seafood) also excellent. Later we found two t-shirts and a bottle of rum in our room.Maid service was very good,She would make beautiful figurines with the towels with flowers on them. At night another maid would bring fresh bath towels and beach towels again ,,then she would leave little chocolates and a little sign with Good night on it.Some people have complained about service people entering your room,while they are taking a shower ect..Please read all the information in your room,when entering your room,all it takes is hanging the (Do not disturb ) sign on the door.There is also a card ,that asks you when ,,would you like to have your room cleaned???(AM NOONor PM) leave it for your maid..All you poor people that complained about walking.I can't understand it ..You have shuttle service and a beautiful walkwaybeside it.Now no bragging here,as for me I am not far form being 70,and I walk every morning at day break for one hour on the beach.My wife would join me later,then we watch the sun with allit's glorious colors rise above the ocean,since our suite was close to the beach,it took us 15 min.to walk to the buffet..to top it off \,my wife had a knee replacement,But what the heck,,,we are walking in the garden of Eden,Back home we would be shovelling snow.All in all ,we recomend this place.We give this place 5-stars in all catagories and shall return this winter.They also added 700 new suites and planning a Brazilian RestaurantSpecial Thanks to Julio Carrion(manager)Camilo at Air Transat check-inDaniel at reception (check-out)WE WILL BE BACK HERB VI
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b33acbf23470173bae33cc1216c369ab" url=""><![CDATA[We loved Grand Palladium Bavero Hi,My husband and I really enjoyed Grand Pallidium,the junior suite was great to stay in,the people were very friendly,and the food was great,the weather super, we had a little rain,and it was dry in no time at all,the sun was hot,just do not leave your towel on the beach.we lost one towel when we went for lunch.other than that,it is a great place to be..we will be back. Viola ..Alta. Canada
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>