<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="b6d21969fa068194d6cb40da609b821a" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location but Choose Another Hotel My husband and I stayed here before a flight to Dominica earlier this year. The location was outstanding but the hotel itself left room for much improvement. Based on the physical structure of the building we assumed it was not constructed to be a Radisson. It has an overall feeling of The taxi dropped us at the entrance to the hotel which is actually on the side of the building. There was no one to greet us and help with luggage. This would present a problem for older guests or people with disabilities. The lobby entrance is dark, thick with cigarette smoke and generally feels dreary.We paid for Club level services and it was a waste of money. The room itself was average and the bathroom was tiny. However, on the plus side, the Sleep Number bed was outstanding. We were supposed to have complimentary bathrobes and had to call for them. Another service we paid for was nightly turndown service which we never received. The room safe did not work properly so we requested service. The and whatever he did left the safe still not working. Hot breakfast was supposedly included with the cost of the room; it was not.The hotel is constructed in such a way that many things simply do not One selling point for the Club is private check-in and check-out but this is done on the top floor of a separate tower. The swimming pool and billiards room are also located in a separate tower. We expected that at the very least they would provide a written explanation of where things were located on the property but that happen. This made for a frustrating stay to say the least.Overall, we felt we paid far too much money for what we received. stayed at much cheaper hotels with nicer accommodations and better service. Checkout was a zoo and the clerk was not the least bit concerned that we were dissatisfied. We were scheduled to stay at the Radisson on our way back from Dominica but changed our hotel.Completely separate from the Radisson, the location is outstanding. There are several stores and some great restaurants within walking distance sure to check out Yerba and the Asian Fusion restaurant down the street. The local bus (Number 21) costs only 75 cents and goes to Old San Juan. If you feel like walking about an hour, you can walk to Old San Juan. The beach is a couple of blocks from the hotel.We strolled along the main street at night and never felt threatened in terms of safety. There were always tourists and joggers out and about. We do not recommend the Radisson but do highly recommend this area of San Juan.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>