<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="61e2276f2dfa0d8e12f9cc13710ee4c3" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic location and service My wife and I stayed here on a Saturday evening due to having a work Christmas party. We ended up getting the room for $183AUD including overnight parking (unlimited entries) and for this price in Sydney we weren't expecting much. We were pleasantly surprised at the room as we had stayed in much worse for a dearer price. The room was very clean (and looked new I might add), bathroom was adequate as well.The room has everything you need - a safe, TV with a couple of foxtel channels, iron, tea/coffee and in-room internet (but really pricey at AUD$22 for 24hours - an internet cafe is the best bet) and of course a bed. Even the wardrobe seemed to be larger than other places we have stayed at. Some people have complained about the size of the bathroom, but it was big enough to do the job! Unfortunatey we didn't spend too much time in the bathroom so it didn't worry us one bit. In regard to the view, there was none!! We were looking directly at the building opposite and we could see the street down below (pretty uneventful really), but for the price we paid we weren't complaining.We did have a couple of dilemma's with the room and they were:*The toilet half flush button was not working at all, meaning we had to use the full flush all the time.*We noticed what looked to be mould above the shower on the ceiling (hard to describe but the ceiling in our shower was not flat)*I had a hole in my bath towel*no fly screen on the opening windowWe did mention these on the checkout questionaire so hopefully these will get resolved.I must thank the night person who brought up the first aid kit at 1230am. I managed to get scratched pretty bad and they came up straight away and patched me up!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e2b000bfe1f902c6652d9575d8380d5a" url=""><![CDATA[Good location but will not stay again My newlywed wife and I stayed here on our first night as a married couple. Actually we stayed here for 3 nights (we booked a special package - stay 3 pay for 2). We arrived after our wedding reception at approximately 12.45am and we were checked in straight away. Our bags were brought up to our room by the bellboy - fantastic.When we booked the room we made a note to the reservations office that it was our honeymoon and we had requested either a harbour view or a floor high up. We ended up with the latter (approx 15 floors up from memory). The view was ok and if we looked to the very side of our living area we were able to see a glimpse of the harbour bridge. Lucky for us if we looked into the reflection of the windows of the hotel opposite we could in fact see the harbour.When we had settled into the room (approx 20 mins later) I phoned reception and requested a bottle of champagne or wine be sent up (because I was assuming this would be included already and 'waiting in our room'). We were expecting a no problem sir it will be up shortly but instead we were cut off and were told that we would be receiving a call back from the night manager. About 10 minutes later the manager phoned back and said sorry we are unable to offer you any champagne as you did not request it when you booked. WHAT? AM I HEARING THIS RIGHT??? We could not believe what he had just told us!! To be denied this on your own wedding night really got us down. I mean we have had friends and family stay in cheaper accommodation on their own wedding night and they even got a surprise in their room (strawberries AND champagne). But for us we got NOTHING. Only a room on a supposed high floor. We really felt like we were staying in a motel at this point on. Because thats how we felt we were being treated.Don't get me wrong, the room was lovely and spacious, bathroom fittings were ok etc. The location was great as well (5 min walk to Circular Quay, the Rocks etc). We would not stay again though and I would definitely NOT recommend it for honeymooners unless you ensure you email the property 1 week before checking in to make sure you get your complimentary bottle of champagne, even though they will probably try and charge you for it!!!!! How ridiculous...
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>