<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="c10d52e7d063a7f3113513f9e5fd1fee" url=""><![CDATA[Great service, location, and value! The Granados 83 is a really great hotel. We stayed there 13-16 July and had not one problem during this time. It's in a great location in the L'Eixample district and is up the Ramblas from the heavily tourist populated Barri Gottic district (we visited here one evening but found it too hectic for a relaxing weekend in BCN and headed back to our hotel's district to relax!). We felt the area where the hotel is gave more of an insight into Barcelona life with less hustle and bustle and a lovely relaxed atmosphere in the area. The hotel has a very comfortable, trendy New York loft style. There's a great terrace bar and swimming pool on the roof which is great by day to catch some sun and enjoy a drink while relaxing and by night it's great to return up there after a meal for a night cap in the balmy night air with some cool music in the background. FOOD: The reception and bar staff are 'very' helpful - just ask them for recommendations for where to eat and you won't be disappointed. Over the three nights we stayed we ate near the hotel. The nicest meal we had was in 'Windsor Restaurant' a few blocks from the hotel. Try the DELICIOUS gastronomique/tasting menu incl wine) - I would say the nicest meal I've ever had! Have a drink in the Dry Martini bar near by before your meal. Very stylish place and a great way to start the evening. They have lots of different types of martinis and they also do other cocktails including a delicious Bloody Mary and beers etc. Also excellent is the more expensive (but worth it) La Dama Restaurant for fine, delicious food and excellent service meal and wine). Finally, go to Cerveceria Catalana for excellent tapas and a wonderful atmosphere - we ate here on our first night as we were looking for something light on arrival - grab a place at the bar or wait for a table - again all three of these places are a stroll from the hotel.Overall Barcelona is a great place to visit for a weekend. Do take the Tourist bus (jump on anywhere and buy a ticket) to get your barings. It's a wonderful way to see the city especially in the summer where it might be too hot for too much walking - The Parc Guell is lovely - our tip, grab a sandwich and drink on the way there (a street on the way uphill has a supermarket on the left near the top of the road). We thought in hindsight it would be nicer to grab a quiet place to sit and eat in the shade and enjoy the nice atmosphere and music playing around the park than sit at the cafes which are perfectly good but busier. Le Pedera is probably best visited earlier in the morning. We passed by in the morning and there were no queues, later in the day the queues were very long.Have a great time in Barcelona - everyone seems very friendly and are not just putting it on for the tourists - we were very impressed by the service we received from everyone!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>