<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="211a00d92f6dd1cf699a4ffea4a5312d" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel My wife I stayed in Hilton Broad St for 4 night's last weekend enjoyed our stay. We arrived at Boston Logan at 3:30pm and got a taxi to hotel, cost was $25 incl tip we were checked in by 4:45pm.Check inn was prompt, staff were friendly and we were happy with the room as it was a good size, incl all mod cons you would expect for a 4**** hotel.We did not have breakfast but did have food in the bar a few times and it was good. The location of the hotel means that restaurants, shopping etc is within walking distance away and there is a taxi rank outside.Overall we had a good time in Boston and would stay in this hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="81e536061cd038372ab7cbc01e3b032c" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel We stayed at Langham Place for 3 nights over a weekend and were pleased we chose this hotel.All the staff were very friendly and were happy to assist in any way they could.The room was modern and clean with a fantastic powerfull shower, however we found the room to be on the small side as we expected a larger one for the p/n incl breakfast we paid.We dined in Ming Court on our first night and had a great meal, we were surprised at how reasonable the food cost when I recieved the bill.The Shopping Mall next door has a good selection of shops, cafes and restaurants and you can go there from the hotel via an enclosed walkway.We found the best shopping to be in Causeway Bay. If you dont want to use the subway station at the hotel a Taxi from hotel will cost HK$80 incl tip one way.We did not use the hotel spa or pool but they looked great when I went to have a look around.The Bar was busy and had some good live music and there was happy hour each evening between 18:30 20:30 where drinks were 2 for 1.Free Internet with 6 Laptops was available at a location near the bar and a large Flatscreen TV to keep you up to speed on World News and Sport.The only problem we had during our stay was coming back to our room in late afternoon to find the room had not been cleaned.Each morning we left the room at 09:30 and pressed a button to request room to be cleaned so it was dissapointing to find room not cleaned on our return.I mentioned this a checkout and even filled out a form so I hope this problem will be sorted out.We had a great time at Langham Place and would stay here again when I next visit Hong Kong.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>