<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="208c59984d2ea2bf21181a5e6318b312" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect Location! You cannot ask for a better located hotel in Barcelona. The Le Meridien, is centrally located on La Ramblas - the street that never seems to sleep in Spain, yet is a few meters off the road so that you never hear any sound if you don't want to.Really nice rooms. I love European stying so I enjoy these rooms - they are a bit small for the price but quite chic. Big 42 inch plasma in the bedroom and another smaller one in the bathroom. The room I am in on the club floor has a lot of funky recessed lighting and if I had one complaint its that even with all the lights on it's not very bright at all. Opening the curtain does the trick but then you've got a bunch of houses looking into your room.Stay here if you plan on going around town and yet need someplace safe to come back. Barcelona is notorious with pickpockets and this hotel is probably one of the safest places to walk back home without a hassle (since the street is always crowded). It's also perfectly located, the central square is a 2 minute walk away and from there you have every conceivable mode of transportation around town. I chose the hop on hop off bus that departs from there - buy the two day ticket, it's great value at 23 Euro. Overall, nice hotel, nice service and location location location.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b42466270f3eaa5edcc51c7c00975592" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect Location - easy to stumble back! Given the multitude of vices available in Amsterdam, this hotel is ideal! You can stumble home using any transportation medium - your two feet, the train, tram, canal rides, subway or taxi!The closest hotel to Amsterdam Centraal Station, it has a subway and taxi stop right outside and super attentive bellmen and concierge's who can arrange tickets to just about anything you need (I chose to watch an Ajax Amsterdam soccer match).The rooms are not much to write home about but when on holiday that's the least of my worries. I'm up and out early and back late, so as long as I have a comfortable bed, I'm fine. Probably the best part about the hotel is that it is extremely safe. Located just outside the Red Light District and in the center of all activity, when inside you are cocooned from it all. You do pay a price for the location and the safety though, but in my opinion it's well worth the added expense. There's another NH which seems pretty nice as well, a couple of km down the road, right next to the main square with the year round fair and outdoor eateries. When I'm in Amsterdam next, I'll make sure I try that out as well.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b492e5d3bbc4c2615803ee7cfce0a38e" url=""><![CDATA[Great Business Hotel The Marriott Frankfurt is a great business hotel, centrally located near the railway station and major roadways in Frankfurt. It is also situated in the tallest building in town, though in all honesty the views of the city, while panoramic, are nothing much to write home about. What I liked about the Marriott was that it was easy to get around town from. The parking though was ridiculously expensive, 10 Euro each time you parked! Keep in mind that in Germany there are parking spots reserved for women so make sure you park in the right spot! Another point to note is that a couple of wrong turns from the Marriott (very easy when your GPS talks to you in German) and you find yourself in this huge red light district, not the ideal place to be with family around. By and large this is a nice hotel though, decent rooms, though a little worn, but good food (nice sports bar and coffee shop) and excellent location.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>