<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="da05a3620c6deeb55cf358b6624563c4" url=""><![CDATA[A good deal in Honolulu view from my room
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e85e2321511084a9e889670f79a027aa" url=""><![CDATA[Good deal in Sydney room 1718
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9cd3d8b257154289876b48663aae2e23" url=""><![CDATA[AMAZING! This hotel is incredible! The exterior of the hotel looks like what you'd expect from a Comfort Inn, but that's where it ends. The lobby is immaculate, the staff is smiling and friendly and always quick to offer service. The furnishings appear new both in the lobby, the hallways, and the guestrooms.The hotel itself is located on a busy street which makes public transportation very convenient. Multiple bus lines stop within a block of the hotel and connections to other buses, streetcars, cablecars, and trains is simple. If you're a cab-taker, don't call ahead. Just step out the door and wave one down (it's much faster that way). Fisherman's Wharf is within easy walking distance. Lombard Street (world's crookedest street) is only four blocks away, but it's uphill all the way and the climb would challenge a mountain goat. Best of all, the hotel is off the touristy path. The surrounding area is almost entirely residential, so it's clean, safe, and quiet (and slightly less expensive than the touristy areas).I was really amazed by the size of the and comfort of the guestrooms. Even my room with one double-sized bed had two chairs and a table with room to spare. Plenty of dresser space and lots of hangars, too. Unless you opened the windows, you'd never know you were in the city - it was very quiet. The only noise I ever heard from the hallway was when people were talking directly in front of my door. I was steps away from the soda/ice machines and never even heard them. I didn't have a view of the bay, but it wasn't that important to me. From what I understand, it's worth paying for if you're into that kind of thing. The bed was comfortable. Housekeeping is very attentive - I couldn't find anything they missed. The bathrooms have a really cool light fixture: when you flip the switch, the light goes from dim to bright gradually and automatically. Very helpful to avoid blinding yourself when you have to make a midnight run. They have a curved shower curtain bar which makes the shower feel bigger and keeps you from rubbing up against the curtain while you're showering.There are only 11 floors and they have two elevators. Both are quick, clean, and spacious. You have to pass the front desk to get to the elevators, but they don't check to see if you're a guest. Anyone can walk in off the street and access guest floors, so follow standard safety precautions. They do have a security guard who works overnight in addition to the regular staff. I regularly took public transportation and walked the streets around the hotel at all hours of the night. The neighborhood seems very safe and well lit. I can say with certainty that this guy has the easiest job in town. It's nice that he's there, but he certainly doesn't have much to keep him busy, except maybe the newspaper.Somehow, this place only has 2 stars. Amazing! You'd be foolish to spend more money for the same facilities and services at another hotel. I'll definitely stay here again on my next trip to San Francisco!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>