<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="f526027f249614d7f440014137cb3886" url=""><![CDATA[Nice but overheated Firstly I thought i already wrote a review on this hotel, but apparently I didn't, so here it is 4months late..!The staff were polite but a bit stern at times, I wouldn't really call them friendly. They all spoke good English but I speak Spanish and that was a real benefit - they seemed a lot, well, happier, when they talked to me than when they were being forced into English. Don't get me wrong, they weren't rude, they just weren't exactly happy.The hotel looks beautiful. Our room was spotless and the bathroom was huge but like previous posts the room was hot, stuffy and there was no circulation of air - we had to resort to opening the window at nights just to get some air, and this was in January, when Madrid aint exactly warm. If you have any kind of breathing difficulties I would think twice about staying here.The location is excellent - quite quiet despite being only a couple of minutes from Puerta del Sol. There is what appears to be a Goth Club just along the road, there isn't really any noise from this (our room was at the front and not far from it), but it does mean you get some interesting characters walking along the road at 2am! But again there was no problem with this.Breakfast was good, didn't eat there apart from that.Basically if you get cold easily and can speak a couple of words of Spanish, even just hello, please and thank you then you will love this place. Little tip on Madrid - the metro system is excellent - quick, clean, well signposted and not as crowded as e.g. London's. If you fly into baracas then the metro is linked to this (ok it's a bit of a walk from some of the terminals) and it's counted as part of zone 1 / whatever they call it - so buy a 10 journey ticket from a machine for (I think??!) 6 euros 80 - meaning that a trip to Sol for this hotel is only going to cost you 0.68 euros - or roughly 40p. Bargain!!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>