<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="4c028eae35b83d436213e4fb0d9e3e1b" url=""><![CDATA[Old South, still suffering from Katrina My husband had meeting at this hotel last week. The rooms are smaller than most newer hotels. We understand the mgmt is still housing some of its staff in order to stay open since Katrina. New Orleans definitely needs everyone's business to rebuild. Everything was clean, flowers in lobby beautiful. Problem with locks is that the keys demagnetize when in the same pocket as credit cards or cell phones. Had to return to front desk twice to get re magnetized. Reception food was lovely, nicely done in their top floor room. Disappointed at the pool...Advertised as roof top pool...was more like a wading pool, not long enough to be a lap pool. Exercise room had lots of new equipment.Was given good direction to coffee shop 2 blocks down the street. Hotel book says their restaurant opened at 6 for breakfast, but doesn't open untll 6:30, Had to wait til we got to airport to get breakfast.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b824dbada07e4d23321fab743a6e7d42" url=""><![CDATA[Small hotel with small rooms My husband chose this hotel for the price and location for a meeting in May. I joined him for 2 nights. The room was adequate, but small. The bathroom was cramped at best. There was no place to set or hang cosmetic bags, except on a towel rack that was right against the toilet. One had to shut the bathroom door by backing into the toilet or sink. Good things about the hotel was the coffee and tea service in the morning and the wine reception in the afternoon. The staff were all extremely interested in the welfare of all the guests. Friendly, as welll as accomodating. They allowed us to extend our checkout until 1 when his meeting was over. The hotel was a couple blocks from Union Square. The theater district had a number of homeless sleeping on the street. We found a number of small breakfast cafes in the area, trying a different one each morning. All were reasonably priced. The hotel is only about 3 blocks from a Cable Car stop.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8ef2daaa43db8c06481175d3c9e4b976" url=""><![CDATA[Band kids were not well controlled, resturant service bad Husband, dtr, and I stayed here in order to get flight out next morning. Hotel room as expected for Embassy Suites, Noise level on bedroom side from road very loud and disturbing. H.S. band in hotel for Fiesta Bowl were still running wild at 11pm. Service at resturant was terrible, food mediocre. Would not eat there again, would not stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>