<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="42e5a94bb4a81bb8d4d718191b59fab3" url=""><![CDATA[Great Introduction to San Francisco My husband and I stayed at the Handlery March 2-3-4. We loved it ! The price was competitive, our room was small but very clean and the staff couldn't have been nicer!From the minute we walked in we were greeted with big smiles and friendliness and when we left we were encouraged to come back soon. Desk staff Erica and Manny were great and John, the concierge was wonderful. he gave us good tips and directions that were flawless.Saturday night we asked if we could change rooms because we had the neighbors from Hell and the change was made quickly and kindly. No questions asked.We ate our meals at The Daily Grill and found the menu to be varied and everything we had was delicious. Again, everyone was very friendly and helpful.We would go back again in a minute.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="51ddd7ecaead1cfefaa09368f061f86f" url=""><![CDATA[Don't believe all the reviews !! My husband and I stayed at this hotel pre- and post-cruise. I read some reviews of the hotel after we had booked and wondered just what kind of place we were going to, because some of the reviews were pretty awful. I must say that our experience was just great !Yes, it does have a small lobby, but it is clean and comfortable and the staff, while young, went out of their way to make us comfortable and get us in a room as quickly as they could. Our rooms were very clean and we had no problems with noise or disturbances from other guests.My husband accidentally left our entire camera case in the taxi that took us to the hotel and three different shifts of desk clerks made calls on our behalf trying to get it back for us. I am pleased to say that a wonderful cab driver brought it to us on his day off and got it to us with just minutes to spare before we left for the pier.Yes, the hotel is in a somewhat transitional neighborhood, but no one bothered us and if you want a great breakfast (at any time of the day) take a minute and walk about a block to the Hurricane Cafe. They have great food at pretty reasonable prices.I would stay at this hotel again.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>