<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="4">
		<document id="3b039edb7cda7ba61cbb114620b91a68" url=""><![CDATA[Good location, nothing to criticize A hotel in the typical Sofitel style, despite extenal appearances! Room was large and had typical Sofitel furnishings. Bathroom was particularly spacious and well-fitted. View was onto a blank wall not var away - though I wasn't there for the view, others might want to check when booking if they want to see something more interesting.Location - just off Piccadilly, not far from Trafalgar Square - is handy for tourists.Prices are a little steep (with rooms that expensive, should we really expect to pay for an internet connection these days?), but what else does one expect in London?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5bf2fa9a6c83bb2ec0b5e61465c37143" url=""><![CDATA[Love it, hate it! Huge, soulless, impersonal place; dingy rooms, dated decor; bar often full of hearties from the vast conferences it accommodates ... ... ... ... but I still keep going back - typically every 8 weeks or so.The place is efficient. It's in the ideal location for the various offices I need to get to (and obviously at the centre of the NY action being right on Times Square). Perhaps the main plus point is that the beds are amongst the most comfortable I've experienced - and I do little more there than sleep. ... ... and there's a certain fascination in watching newcomers to the hotel fail to cope with the lift/elevator system!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="26de69afb2e92c4e8f2a6cfc78a72649" url=""><![CDATA[Good - but standard rooms are not 5-star quality I spent two nights at the Okura for a business conference. I came away with mixed feelingsI drove there. It's conveniently located, 5 minutes off the Ring. The hotel has its own good, if expensive, underground car park.Front desk staff were firndly and courteous, and extremely efficient, both on check-in and check-out: could not be faulted. Unlike some other reviewers, I had no difficulties with the housekeeping, room service and restaurant staff.The basic facilities at the hotel are fine, and the restaurants (Ciel Bleu on the 23rd floor, and the Teppanyaki restuaurant on the ground floor are excellent, as are the bars on the 23rd and ground floor. Having said that, the prices match the quality of the experience - far from cheap! Breakfast was good, if a little quirky with breakfast cereals in plastic bottles!Conference facilities and food were well above average.I was in a standard room that was comfortable enough, but a little small, and fast reaching the point where refurbishment will be needed - somewhat tired and faded. There were minor niggles: a shortage of power sockets around the desk; slightly defective sound insulation from the corridor outside; a very small, incredibly narrow, bath ... ... ... all of which made this an experience worth less than the advertised 5 stars, though by no means bad.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="83f4cddfc61530efdf1a4a868f8b111c" url=""><![CDATA[Bland but adequate This is a huge, soulless airport hotel. Unless you have reason to be staying at the airport - for travel reasons or, like me, for a conference, you wouldn't use it and would choose a nicer alternative in town. However, if you do have to be there, it's not at all bad of its kind but don't expect the same standard as, say, the Sheraton at Schipol or the Hilton at CdG, to name but two.Rooms are spacious, with reasonable facilities, though internet usage charges are an irritant. As far as room quality is concerned, I suspect (having read others' reviews) that it is patchy. You can strike it lucky and get a recently redecorated room or you can hit one that is tired and faded, as I did. Noise insulation really is excellent, by the way.Front desk staff were excellent; cleaning, on the other hand was below par - at least in my room. Food is of an adequate standard, but no more than that - but there are plenty of places to eat in the terminal, the short walk being the main (if not the only) attraction of this hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>