<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="44282a55f4939a97bd2045e2f9a21a41" url=""><![CDATA[Stay here at your own risk! Travelling with friends (we are 50 somethings) we wanted a nice hotel in Venice. Booked and confirmed 2 seperate rooms a month in advance at Hotel A La Commedia. The hotel looked beautiful in the pictures and is very convenient to the Rialto Water Taxi stop and St. Marks Square.Upon arrival we were told we were being upgraded to a 2 bedroom suite # 115 with a sitting area for the same price as the two rooms we booked. This isn't what we wanted as one of our travelling companions was fighting a nasty flu bug and we didn't want to catch it, but we tried to go with the flow and make the best of it. Little did we know that that this part of the hotel is directly over a nightclub that doesn't start to get cranked up until 11:00. And doesn't quiet down until after 2:00am. The floor was shaking and the walls were rocking! We called to complain and were told the hotel is full and we could not be moved. They acted so surprised to hear my complaint. I asked to speak to the manager and was told he would be in in the morning and the staff would make him aware of my concerns. I checked with the front desk twice the next morning and the manager was never available to speak with me, although there was a gentleman in a hotel jacket who was lurking around while I was having my discussions with the front desk but did not engage in the conversation. However, once I would walk away he would then go speak with the front desk person. So much for customer service. All this for only 840 EU a night! Having read a TripAdvisor review from someone who just stayed there it is obvious that this is a common or even nightly occurence.When I went to settle the bill, the front desk man offered to buy us a drink at the hotel bar for our incovenience. We had no other charges at the hotel. I told him don't bother, just write up the bill, let me check out and you can deal with my friends at American Express in 30 days. I will do everything in my power to make it as difficult as I can can for them to ever receive payment. The suite room was beautiful, the bathrooms over the top. But there is a basic flaw in the soundproofing and design of this hotel and it is obvious that they take advantage of short term tourists who are at their mercy.Show them they need to change their ways. Boycott the the Hotel A La Commedia until they fix the problem or are upfront with their guests about the condition. You couldn't pay me to stay in this Upgraded Suite unless I was deaf as a stone.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>