<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="6562e6c1d2e36f445811683c2c277696" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel but not quite 5-star Just returned from a 4 night package booked through Hotels.com and my impression is of a very good 4-star hotel but not quite 5-star. Nothing too specific but it didn't have that extra something that you expect from 5-star quality. The staff in particular seem desperately to please but don't seem able (or are told not) to think outside the box and go that extra mile that 5-star really requries..Previous reviewers are completely correct that this is a very central hotel and whilst there's Berlin's finest shops on the doorstep, there's little by way of quality bars and restaurants nearby. Indeed the closest restaurant is a KFC.Overall, this isn't a great hotel - but neither is it bad. There's plenty of good reasons to stay here: the rates seem excellent in comparison to other 4 5 star centrally placed hotels; good pool spa; centrally located;; and others. If they just removed that 5th star that they're clearly very proud of from their logo, I'd be writing a much more favororable review!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cc9dc61c896a941c6291741947e7965a" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent service This is an excellent quality hotel right in the heart of SF. The service from all staff was superb, location good, bar restaurant great and so on!!This was just a quick one night stay before flying back to Europe. I was intrigued by the most romantic hotel in SF label when searching as we were at the end of our Honeymoon. Truth is it's a chain hotel that pretends not to seek out the corporate clients even though there were plenty of them. However, unlike so many other big name chains, the Omni seems to treat it's private guests very specially going that little step further for customer service. (Too often I find the chains trying to get the corporate money and just neglect those of us that want a nice hotel).Lots of nice little touches too numerous to mention here means I shall return here (and to any other Omni).And was it romantic? - Well this is not a boutique hotel - it's a large-ish city centre hotel. But given those constraints - surprisngly yes!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>