<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="19899803345b4827d0b7b1bdec83f037" url=""><![CDATA[Amazing Hotel!! This was an amazing hotel! We booked through expedia and got a very reasonable rate (somewhere around 150 per night). We arrived around 11am and our room was ready, which was an unexpected surprise. The rooms were small but comfortable, and had wicked flat screen tv's, ipod alarm clock decks, and beautiful stall showers with great water pressure! Best of all, the beds were rediculously comfortable! The hotel was in a great location - within walking distance to Union Square, movie theatres, and great shopping. I should also note that there was a great restaurant called Bucca right across the street. The gnocci was out of this world!The concierge was particularly helpful! We wanted to eat at cheesecake factory but heard that there tends to be a 1 to 1.5 hour wait during dinner hours. We had our concierge call (eventhough they dont' take reservations), and we waited no more than 2 minutes. Brilliant! This was an incredible hotel and I wouldn't hesitate to recommend it for one second!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7cfc91b6240b29b26780144c226b4afc" url=""><![CDATA[Perfect hotel for LA This was an excellent hotel! We booked through their website for $161 per night (AAA rate) and opted to choose our room when we arrived. This was a great idea, as we ended up getting a MASSIVE room overlooking universal studios, with a seating area, and a very comfy king size bed! The hotel itself was great - the staff were extremely helpful, it had a good coffee bar for the morning, a large bar, and a restaurant with a big buffet breakfast (although we did not eat there). The hotel was in a great location - within walking distance to universal studios, and very close to the City Walk, which was fun at night! We drove to downtown LA (grauman's chinese theatre) in 10 minutes, and were at Rodeo Dr. within 15. This hotel is beautiful and is a great choice if you're looking for something a bit more reasonable priced in central LA. I highly recommend it! Parking wasn't too expensive (I think $17 per day), and the lot was easy to use! I highly recommend this hotel. I have stayed at the Sheraton Universal and this is just as good, if not better.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>