<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="d7595d9c7a76d5ea84e241f624d075c5" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic Hotel Jazz First time in Barcelona for 3 nights away with my sister for sightseeing, shopping and eating/drinking!! The Hotel Jazz is a perfect place to stay - in fact I couldnt fault it in any way!! I have staying in many 5 star hotels, including the Bellagio in Las Vegas just a couple of months ago, and the Hotel Jazz was of equal standards and comfort. The staff are efficient but also friendly and speak good English.Upon arrival we took the blue Aerobus from outside the airport terminal and got off at the Placa de Cataluyna (cost 3.75 euros each) - the hotel is a quick 5 minute walk away down the Pelei but the entrance is just off the main street (we walked past it without realising at first). Although we arrived at 1030, we were able to get into our room immediately. Our room was on the 5th floor and only felt slight rumble from the underground which wasnt a problem. The windows must be triple glazed because we didnt hear any traffic noise when they were closed. Just a couple of tips in relation to eating out ; the hotel charges 14 euro each for breakfast if not included in your package - we visited a local bakery a couple of blocks away for our breakfast which cost 7 euros for both of us and a small supermarket which is in the straight that runs next to the Cafe D'Or. Previously people on tripadvisor recommended Cafe D'Or for breakfast and dinner - we ate tapas there and it was cold and quite horrible so really disppointed, but the staff were friendly enough. The main restaurant you must visit is Les Quinze Nits in Reial Square ( about half way down Las Ramblas on the left hand side) for quality and very reasonably priced food - it opens for dinner at 2030 and when we arrived at 2020 there was a huge queue of about 100 people!! - we didnt think we would get in but did - we sat outside which was a bit nippy but kept our jackets on. Although I had kept hold of my bag with the tightest of grips for the entire trip I lost my concentration momentarily and hung my bag on the back of my chair. I was promptly spoken to by the security chap at the restaurant to hide my bag away which I did. We also ate at the Hard Rock Cafe for a non-Spanish meal and it had a great atmosphere and good food. For great views of the city, take the smallest lift in the world !!! up the Columbus tower which is located at the bottom of Las Ramblas - however, warning its not for those who are claustrophic or dislike heights. For tours round the city we took the orange Barcelona Tours bus - they arent marketed as much as the other bus company but they are better as you get headphones for the tour which you can select for your language - instead of hearing the same thing being said 5 times over in different languages!! - it took us to all the main sights and we could get off and on as much as we wished. We were really aware of our bags so thankfully didnt get anything stolen, but there is quite a strong presence of police in the Las Ramblas area. We loved Barcelona and will definately be returning! One thing you must take with you is a phrase book and try the language (Catalan or Spanish) as some places do not speak English.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b225269e151c0e59722eccae626524ea" url=""><![CDATA[Good tourist location but not over impressed with the room Stayed at the Fishermans Wharf, San Francisco for 3 nights during a holiday to USA in September 2004. We checked in at the main reception which looked nice and gave a good first impression however, were then directed to our room which was in another building on the next road along - not impressed about having to drag our cases along the street at 1030pm particularly after 13 hours of travelling! The standard of the room was OK but there was a faint smell of smoke and we had quite a busy road outside our room. However, we did not spend a lot of time in the room as we were busy out and about during our stay - a good point is that the hotel is well located for the attractions on Fishermans Wharf and for accessing the transport links into the city. Also, there was a really good guy in the reception of the second building who gave us some excellent information about how to get around the city and some other tourist bits of information. I guess on reflection you do get what you pay for and we didnt pay 5* prices, I would class it as an average place to stay with no frills.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7ed276848c1ac3494757cf8b8dcc9190" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel with quality rooms and service Found this hotel on last minute.com and were guided to it by previous reviews. Got the aerobus to Placa de Catalunya and then walked the short 10-15 mins to the hotel - this was late at night but did not have any problem walking through the area which was really safe. The rooms are huge and are of a high standard decor with really thick curtains that dont let the light in which is great if you want a late lay in! Nice jacuzzi and terrace area on the roof. The only slight negative of our stay was that on our first morning we decided to have the hotel breakfast (not included in rate so paid seperately) and on checkout were shocked to find out that it was 17 euros each - whilst it was nice and of good quality, the choice was quite limited and no where near worth the total price of 34 euros plus tax!!!!!Anyway, Barcelona is great and would seriously recommend the Fat Tire Bike Tours - cant remember the name of the meeting point where the tour started but they have a website you can look at. The tour stopped off at a majority of the major sights in Barcelona and it was a great way to see it all with an informative guide. Ate out for a couple of nights in the restaurants in passag de gracia which is about 2 blocks along from the hotel - would recommend BaBaReBa for good quality food and service, however we would say No No to a restaurant called NoNo which had very basic and limited taste food and uninterested staff. On way back to the hotel on most nights we stopped off at the Haagan Daaz icecream parlour which is just one block away in Rambla de Catalunya. Would definately recommend the use of the Metro which is a quick and easy way to get round - they do a one day travelcard type thing for about 5 euros which is great value and allows you to go all over the city and sights.This was my second visit to Barcelona in a year and it didnt fail to wow me again!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>