<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="816995954801e6236ccc433695c5e4e1" url=""><![CDATA[Consistent as always The wife and I were there from 1/04/05 - 1/07/05. The quarter was nice, all the sugar bowl tourists were departing. The hotel was it's usual value for the dollar. If you want to stay in the most convenient location in the French Quarter this is it. You get more than what you pay for when you consider the location. I only live three hours from New Orleans and I have stayed in the French Quarter dozens of times, and the Bourbon Orleans is always my first choice. I would give the facility between 3 and four stars, but they only charge a three star price. Clean rooms with new furnishings, marble bathroom, decent restuarant, room service, minibar, ppv tv, valet parking. The location is in the very center of the quarter so you can walk or catch a streetcar to get anywhere. Give the keys to the valet and relax! ...Try a hand grenade from Tropical Isle directly across Bourbon!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="12292f066079359a3754adaed24a1601" url=""><![CDATA[It's o.k. My wife and I stayed at the Royal sonesta in mid January. I would rate this hotel as average. It has the atmosphere of a luxurious hotel in the lobby, but when you get to the rooms this image disappears. Rooms are small, and not all that clean. Even though the hotel seemed to be quite empty, we were given a room somewhere in the back overlooking the ruins of some other run down property. The first night we were there, we were disturbed by a knock on the door. It was a security guard investigating a report of someone smoking marijuana on our floor. I was much more irritated by this intrusion than I would have ever been by a neighbor smoking pot (especially since we were staying at ground zero of the party capital of the south). Anyway, it seems as if what is left of the NOPD/LA state police are now based and housed in the Royal Sonesta. If you do not like law enforcement officers (and everyone knows the reputation of law enforcement in NOLA), this is definitely not the place to stay right now. They have a state police H.Q. on the first floor. After we checked out, I realized we were overcharged on several things. We were overcharged on two nights of our stay. We were also charged for a pay per view movie in the room. We only turned the T.V. on a couple of times to watch the news or check the weather. We definitely didn't watch a movie. The positives are that this hotel is located right on Bourbon St. and it has on site parking. They also have a decent champagne brunch on Sundays. We only stayed here because the Bourbon Orleans was booked up (after a recent remodel, it is much nicer!). I would only stay at the Royal Sonesta again if everything else was booked up.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>