<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="2dec353e89ee21cffe0322d244183c72" url=""><![CDATA[Bells and Whistles-Lacks Basics We were so excited to stay at the Hotel Vitale after reading all the reviews. Upon arrival, we were expertly greeted, made aware of the $42.00 a day valet fee, and expedited quickly to our basic yet comfortable room with a nice view of the bridge. We began to unpack and quickly noted that there was no dresser for our 6 days worth of clothing, so we lived out of our suitcases and one hanging closet. We walked around and loved SF and the close proximity of transportation and necessities. Keep in mind that on the weekends, most eateries in the financial district are closed. We were peacefully sleeping when at 5:00AM four large tables crashed out in the hallway. An employee evidently was preparing for a future event on the 7th floor terrace. The next morning, housekeeping knocked quietly and quickly and came on in at 8:00AM to our shock. The next day, when we returned at 4:30PM to prepare for dinner with family, housekeeping was in our room and we had to wait outside. Also, if you don't get downstairs before 7:00AM, you will miss the complimentary coffee and must pay $3.00 a cup. Overall, they went above and beyond the call of duty for what they feel is important, but a dresser, housekeepting at reasonable hours, and complimentary coffee are important to us. Not bottled water, bittersweet chocolates, robes and pricey spa products for sale everytime you go into the bathroom. Wish it would have been better.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2e17222cf13af22427ae3f7226e13ee9" url=""><![CDATA[A Gem My two children and I stayed at the Chancellor for four nights this month during a two week road trip from South Carolina to San Francisco. I had read the reviews and chose the Chancellor because of location primarily. We were checking in after three nights in the Bellagio in Las Vegas so I wasn't sure about how the kids would react after all of the flash and grandiosity of the previous hotel but they loved the Chancellor as did I for several reasons. First, of course location, location, location. So close to great eats (Sears was awesome for dinner and breakfast), great shopping, parking (reasonable), drug stores, transportation whether you want a quick ride to the Wharf on the F line or a thrilling ride on the cable car. It was warm in SF when we were there but we opened the windows and everything was fine with very little noise. Because the hotel is small and we saw the same employees (who would quickly recognize us) over and over again, the children were able to be a little more autonomous than usual so they were allowed to go downstairs alone to get the complimentary popcorn, apples, and cookies. My son used the ethernet connections in the lounge with me in the evenings and everyone was so friendly to him. My debit card was lost at one point and I called the front desk to ask about the location of a Wachovia bank in SF. They called around and found one that was open that day, a Saturday, called the bank to confirm the hours, mapquested the directions, highlighted the route and sent me on my happy way. I think that the age and size of the hotel give it a unique and friendly feeling that really makes you feel a part of SF. My 10 year old daughter took the yellow duck she was given at the Chancellor into every hotel pool we visited on our way home. I watched as it floated around as she was playing and on several occasions adults picked it up and read the inscription on it and asked my daughter about it and that began a lengthy and colorful conversation about her awesome trip to SF and her stay at the Chancellor. Thanks Wes.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>