<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a0b7adbf466bd7c4258f03bd72ded58e" url=""><![CDATA[My opinion...the best hotel in Barcelona...by miles! Tripadvisor is god...long live trip advisor!. I always use trip advisor to steer me in the right direction and it has never let me down. I searched through 400 hotels on trip advisor and found the Hotel Catedral and booked it without hesitation. I told my wife the next day that out of 400 hotels, the hotel was ranked 378 (in Jan 2007, and as i write now in April it is ranked 250). The hotel is BRAND NEW, it only had a few reviews and the only bad one, the guy writing the review had a problem with his travel company and not the hotel, so why dis the hotel (the hotel even posted a reply saying how they tried to help the guy). So where o start. Location: Perfect...outside of the Cathedral and one of the main squares in Barcelona (be careful with taxis though as there are several Cathedrals in the city, you have to ask for the one on Avinguda de Cathedral). In the Barri Gotica area, 2 mins walk to Las Ramblas (which is very overrated and not what i expected, but everyone seems to go there), 5 mins to placa de Catalunya (excellent for shopping, department stores, fashion stores, shops...and where all the hop on hop off buses go from...get the bus turistic as there are lots more of them and the route they run is much better than the others). The hotel is 5-10 mins walk to the marina/port area (lots of restaurants there). You CANNOT get more central. Taxis have problems finding it sometimes, ask them to drop you at te Hotel Colon (which is 100 yards away and is an established hotel in barcelona...and is twice the price and nowhere near as nice).Hotel: Staff were amazingly helpful, ringing the Nou Camp for us for our tour information (which was ok, but you need to hire the audio guide at 3 euros to really appreciate it as it is not guided), ringing restuarants etc. The gym is small but modern and effective (4 cardio machines and free weights). The rooftop pool area is great for sunbathing and looks cool (its an infinity pool, but can be a little chilly in less sunnier temperatures). The outdoor Bar area is one of the best in Barcelona, really trendy/cool place. The breakfast in the hotel was excellent, cereals, croissants, breads, american hot breakfast/medditeranean hot breakfast...they even did a spinach omelette for my friend who was vegetarian...excellent!. Where to eat in Barcelona: El Xalet (in the Montjiuc mountain). 15 mins in a taxi (about 10 euros). Well worth it, its open 1.00pm to 1.00am..but if you go later in the day make sure the hotel books a table for you. It is a revolving dining area and has an outdoor terrace that has the best views in all of Barcelona...unbelieveable!. Also go to Tabloa De Carmen in Poble Esapnyol....which is a 4 course meal, as much wine/sangria as you can drink ad a 1 hour authentic flamenco show...cost about each but i drank that in sangria alone....if you go to the early showing (7.45pm and 10.30pm) you can stroll around the village area before going in (during the day you have to pay 6 euros per person just to walk around). Its excellent. Other places to mention are Taller de Tapas (although Cal pep is recommended by people, there is no menu so you dont totally know what you are eating, you just pick plates up and hope for the best), which is excellent value for money (especialy lunchtime) and is open all day. Taxidermista s also a cool place, a former taxidermist shop...very smart, good food and in a cool square called place reial. Go to the hotel OMM for a drink in the bar, but i wouldnt eat in the restaurant MOO as it is extremely weird...they put distilled soil in some of the dishes and actual cigar ash in some of the desserts....weird, weird, weird and expensive!. Commerc 24 is hard to get into, book ahead, and is the place to be (great value for money too...surprisingly).Look at some of the walking tours, they do a gourmet walking tour which takes you to places to try the local delicasies and explain te history of catalan food...The hotel provides a FREE walking tour every Sunday at 10.00am for an hour....i Love this hotel!Also, if you are there on a wednesday, check with the hotel as they do wine tasting evenings and cookery classes (i think every first and third wed of each month, but check with the hotel). Tell me another hotel anywhere in the world that does this...I love hotels in vegas and have stayed in some of the best hotels there (which are some of the best in the world), and i rate this hotel on a par with the hotel Paris/Mandalay Bay...yeah it is much smaller, but as an all round package, i know that in 12 time this hotel will be in the top 10 hotels on Tripadvisor. Part of me didnt want to write this review, i didnt want it to get too popular and expensive (i booked through justonehotel.com and got it for per night including full breakfast). But Tripadvisor has helped me and this is what its all about....this place is...the business.Enjoy...Phill
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>