<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="b454c1c3c8c1c546b67afa104fce278c" url=""><![CDATA[Very impressed by the hotel I stayed 1 night.Location: Located about 10 min by shuttle from the airport, it is also 5 minutes walk from the metro station, and about 25 minutes to CentralInterior design: Extremely attractive. I had only a relatively normal room. It was in fact quite big, extremely well designed and comfortable. I visited a junior suite. Perfectly designed as well. The design style is modern, warm. I find it one of the best designed hotel I have seen anywhere.Service: Perfect from reception to the breakfast staff.Breakfast: The room is great, the staff uniform attractive, the buffet extremely rich.Price: Amazingly cheap - 1200 HK$ for my room and 2000 HK$ for a suite. They want to compensate for the location not being in Central. I used to stay at the Mandarin Oriental or the Shangri-La. For the kind of room or breakfast qualities, it would cost about 5 time sthe price. I looked at the Regal hotel at the airport. I sincerely think the Novotel Citygate is really amazing, and where I will stay in my next trip in HK.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7394e43513b7e8e59c568c1293a120cf" url=""><![CDATA[Great room with magnificient harbour view I stayed 2 nights between China and Singapore.HK hotels were full and the only choice given to me by the Hotel Information agent at HK airport was Suite 1201 at the Intercontinental. (US$500 perr night, I think)Room - Very spacious, with a magnificient viw from the bed.Breakfast - Was not included in the US$20 price of the room! That was exagerated. Don't forget to discuss that at booking time!Service - Excellent.Location - Not too far from the train transfer from the airport or from the ferry to the island. Maybe 200 meters walkikng distance. It is a little long with a heavy bag, but OK if you are in shape.Business center and internet - Excellent, but this is HK and it is not free.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b44bfd68a5ec8d14598f7d87e088a272" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent stay I stayed 3 nights.Location: very convenient for my business meetings, all within 10 minutes by car.Design: Outiside, it is a little old. But the interiro has been upgraded. The room we stayed in was very good.Breakfast: Great buffet, and very friendly staff.Price: We paid about 1000 USD for the 3 nights, which was very good for the quality of experience we had.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>