<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="6bfd61728b119939b9c2a0ac43845a09" url=""><![CDATA[Specific Pros and Cons I booked this hotel for my family of five, kids 11, 11, and 8. Room had 2 double beds and a rollaway.Pros = Value, we got this room at $150/night with free parking and doughnuts/muffins in the office. Microwave, frig, large room on the corner (room 49) of the top floor. For 5 people, in this city, this was pretty cheap, given what I was finding. The front desk woman was helpful. There was an elevator, albeit very slow, that really helped with all our bags. Bathroom was small, but adequate - overall the room was spacious.Neutral = Location was safe, and not too far from Ghirardelli Square - maybe 7-8 blocks? But with kids, it's not totally ideal - next time I would probably stay at Union Square, where there is a cable car turnabout right there. You cant catch the cars near the hotel, according to the desk. But that said, it was a reasonable walk to Ghirardelli and not that bad to the Wharf. The cleanliness of the room was fine - it wasn't blowing me away, but it wasn't dingy either. It is definitely a budget hotel, and if I weren't in the heart of SF, I would not have considered this as big a bargain.Cons = For those who don't like entering your room from the outdoors (motel style), this isn't for you. My wife doesn't like that - so that was a negative. We were reluctant to open the windows, because it just opens to the catwalk outside where people are walking. There was a sign outside the office that I didn't see until we left that said something about a health issue regarding asbestos. WTF? Since we were leaving I decided not to think about it. Also, the cable had pretty limited channels. There was HBO but no ESPN. Overall this was a good value in a decent location with free parking, which is huge. I might stay here again if I were alone or with buddies, but with my family I would probably look for something a bit closer to the cable car turnabouts or where I was closer to the Wharf or Union Square - if I could afford it.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>