<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="4b53fd9d8a1ed1064bd1358bdf8c001e" url=""><![CDATA[Problematic stay I stayed here in December. A fairly problematic stay. I enjoyed the Palace and Westin St Francis more. But it is OK if you get a cheap rate. Problem 1: Got a corner room with no drawers! Fortunately I was only here for 1 night, so I just lived out of my suitcase. But really.Problem 2: Bed was short-sheeted. This is becoming a common problem at all chains. Housekeeping used a sheet that was too short, so my feet were scraping against scratchy mattress fiber. I had to remake the bed myself. A complaint the next morning at front desk garnered compensatory SPG points. When I asked for late checkout, I was offered 1pm. I had to press for 4pm, which I am entitled to as a Gold member.Problem 3: At check in (late in the evening), I asked for my package. The staff member said to come back tomorrow when the concierge was there. Since the package contained toiletries, I needed it immediately, and only when I pressed did she send a bellman to unlock the concierge's closet and retrieve my package. Problem 4: Rate was 20 dollars higher on the bill than the booked rate. This was solved at checkout.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="12dd3fca616cc78bb3c24fdc1e3e600e" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent service The Aloha spirit was prevalent throughout the hotel. The service was simply excellent all around, from valets to front desk. I asked for, was offered and accepted an upgrade to a better room (for $25 a night). The shower heads were not my favorite type (Ritz-Carlton type, non-adjustable pressure). The a/c worked wonderfully. The hotel is a solid three stars. Room was mostly clean, except for a patch of dried snot on the bedroom wall. The hotel has a policy to offer a late checkout till 10pm for $100 extra. It was totally worth it in my book if you have a late flight out, although many other customers might find it steep. I guess it depends on individual preference. They're not trying to take advantage of anyone, but the hotel is a business not a charity.The free internet access (wifi in the lobby, and two huge macs) was wonderful. I regret waiting till my last day to use the iJoy massage chairs - those things are great and make it worth staying here for that fact alone!Security was good. Valets were usually fast - tell them when you need your car, tip them appropriately, and they will usually have your car ready when you want it.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>