<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="6">
		<document id="5e751b3a7299deeba6f46c295ae127de" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful Resort, with Helpful Staff I stayed at this resort from Feb. 25 through March 2nd with my wife and 1 year old daughter. The resort is very child friendly and the staff at the resort were falling all over themselves to get to my daughter the whole time we were there. She loved all of the attention! I must say that all of the positive reviews I read were right on. This resort is beautiful with extremely well kept grounds. The staff, especially the wait staff go out of thier way to make your stay comfortable. The room was spacious and updated and included a sunken living room which added just enough extra space. The food was good although it does start to get repetetive after a few days. But you are going to find this at most all inclusives. The food was still of high quality and was delicious. The beach has plenty of room for all of the resort guests. As an added bonus, if you stay at the Bavaro you can go and eat or play at the other two Iberostars: Dominicana and Punta Cana which are right next door. However, guests at the other resorts can not come over to the Bavaro. The drinks seemed to be a bit weak for my taste but since it is an all inclusive you can make up for that by asking for extra rum, gin, etc in your drinks. The activities at the resort are lots of fun and the nightly shows for the most part were very good.Overall, I would highly recommend this resort to anyone, especially families looking for a beautiful resort that is child friendly. My wife and I would go back without hesitation.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="47d5d81e88fe9ea10934e505aaa19fcf" url=""><![CDATA[The old bait This hotel is in serious need of a facelift. Or I should say, the rooms are in need of a face lift. When you walk into the lobby area it's very pretty and inviting. However, when you get to your room, it's a different story. Hence this review title of bait switch. The beds are comfortable enough and the rooms are plenty large. However, the bathroom is gross and in serious need of updating. I actually saw two rooms during my stay since I asked to switch my first room and the bathrooms look edexactly the same; dingy, dirty, and badly in need of updating. The small square tiles in the shower were in need of more grout and alot of caulking was missing around the tub. The bathroom reminded you of a Motel 6. I would stay elsewhere if you can. However, if you book of priceline or hotwire the way I did, good luck to you.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e1da965775506a87c8069542008e1451" url=""><![CDATA[Good, Not Great This hotels location is great and within walking distance to everything. You are right next to Union Square, China Town, and about a 15 min walk to the Embarcadero. The hotel rooms are small but nice. So if you are looking for lots of space, look else where. The room has a desk, bed, flat screen t.v. and an updated bathroom. I did not use the restaurant, or fitness center so I can not comment on those. There was free wireless internet, which was a great perk. I slept well and did not hear any street noise. I would stay here again if I was in the area. Of of course I was here for business and received a rate of $199/night, which was less than half of what they normally charge. But I think $400 is the going rate for 4 stars in the area.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1d0125c0f4e17e88ff83675f0b4e67b6" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel This hotel is a nice 4 star property. The lobby area has the wow factor with a very cool, contemporary look. The room are all a decent size with lots and lots of granite in the bathroom. The room are clean and have all of the amenitiers you would expect from a four star hotel. All of the rooms have balconies which is a nice touch. I did not eat in the restaurant or frequent the bar because of the prices. In one word . . .REDICULOUS. Other than that I would recommend the hotel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="155197b05355a66e8b0d96aab9a14832" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel for the price My wife and I stayed at this hotel for one night before a cruise of Feb. 11, 2005. The hotel was very clean and the staff were friendly and helpful. The room was small but clean and contained everything we needed. The hotel is two blocks from the heart of the Condado area and a 25 cent bus ride from Old San Juan. The breakfast was nothing fancy, but consisted of cold cereal, oatmeal, sweet rolls, yogurt, and fruit. Just enough to kickstart your day! I thought this hotel was an exceptional value for the money and would not hesistate to stay here again for a day or two. If you are going to stay longer, you would probably want to go with one of the bigger hotels in Condado.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="33ef2cae68d3ecfdef7ae29d74c45365" url=""><![CDATA[Good stay at Millenium Hilton I stayed at this hotel with my wife and 17 month old daughter from July 20-22. The hotel rooms have clearly been renovated recently and they've added some nice touches. The bed was very comfortable and the large flat screen t.v is built into the wall. The bathroom was nicely renovated and decorated as well. We had a room on the 20th floor over looking the World Trade Center site. Although, it is not the most pleasant of memories, I the view was a good reminder of all that happened that day. I booked the hotel through priceline and got a great rate and a great room. I even requested to be moved initially because the original room they gave me was too close to the elevators. I was moved without a problem. The front desk staff were courteous and helpful. The location of the hotel is perfect is you're looking to be in the SOHO/Financial district and close to the Hudson River. It's only about a 10 minute walk to the river. I highly recommend this hotel.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>