<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="a94020f5a4062924b9c567ef8cab6050" url=""><![CDATA[Only one criticism I stayed in a single room for two weeks while on a course, and agree with other posts that this is a good, central hotel in an excellent position, with very pleasant and helpful staff. The single rooms are quite small, although comfortable enough and clean(I had just enough space to work on my laptop). For the price it is really excellent value. I would make only one criticism. The water is very hot, the shower cubicle is very small. It is very easy to knock the hot water to maximum. The water is then scalding hot - there is nowhere to go: you have to reach through the water for the tap or to get out! OK when you know the problem, but I don't think it would pass the health and safety test in the UK. This may only apply to the single rooms though. There is no restaurant, but the breakfasts are good, no fresh fruit juice being my only complaint, and you can always go across the square for a change.I would certainly book here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7c1a63e0f892cac8922a60b5c4db8827" url=""><![CDATA[Like the curate's egg - good in parts El Convento has the possibility of being one of the great hotels, but is let down by needless inefficiencies. Its position, architecture and ambience are superb, but there are too many problems, individually small but adding up.We stayed for three nights in November. Like other previous respondents we arrived at a reasonable time to find no room available, nor any forecast as to when one would be. Eventually, at about 4pm we were given the keys to a room which was not made up. This was quickly remedied but annoying. No complaint about the reception and concierge who were pleasant. The new room was satisfactory, although not large.Again like many others, we found the lift out of order one day.The barman at the Tapas bar was downright unpleasant, although we were later informed that this bar is not part of the hotel. Best avoided, there is plenty of choice in the area. The main hotel restaurant was adequate and although not inspiring the staff were pleasant and efficient.The maid service left something to be desired with heavy dust in some areas.Other complaints were they lost our laundry (found eventually), and the telephone did not work. When we did manage to make a call, the pen did not work!However, that did not mean we did not enjoy our stay. Staff at the front desk was always helpful, especially Carmen, and other staff were always pleasant. The design and ambience of the hotel are stunning, at the centre of a beautiful historic city. The complimentary bar between 6 and 7pm is a lovely idea, and although the pool is small, the deck area has a beautiful aspect and is a pleasant place to relax.We still think this is the best place to stay in Old Sann Juan, but just wish they would get their act together.We booked through expedia.co.uk at a reasonable rate with no problems.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>