<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="c84adc76cf529173f07904bfa9888fd3" url=""><![CDATA[An English Perspective We stayed as group of 12 including our 4 year old for our wedding from May 9th to May 23rd. We were booked into the Punta Cana side and myself and my partner were automatically upgraded to Diamond. This didnt mean much. Just that we could use the Diamond pool and eat at other restaurants. We didnt use any but settled for what the rest of the wedding party could use. We were told on booking our wedding that we could have a room upgrade but when we asked about it whilst checking in they said all rooms are the same and that no upgrade was available. Maybe without our daughter they may have put us in the Ambar section for adults only?? There were a couple of snags with what we should have had in our room on arrival as bride and groom and 10 days into the holiday and 5 days after the wedding we got our welcome gifts. I noticed people who had paid for the upgrade had their welcome gifts handed to them immediately. But a few visits to reception and speaking with the wedding co-ordinator we finally got them. Not worth waiting for really. A figurine that broke, small bottle of rum and a t.shirt each. We should have had a basket of fruit on arrival but I couldnt be bothered to ask anymore. I'll narrow things down.....Cleanliness / Service: It is spotless and there are constantly people working whether it be in the grounds themselves, maids doing rooms, and a few times we noticed managers looking over everything to make sure everything was up to scratch. We left a tip everynight as a group after meals,breakfast and tipped at the bar. A dollar isn't mush to us compared to what they earn in a month. One waitress in the main lobby said they earn $200 every 30 days which to us could be a days wages. This lady in particular worked away from her 3 children to make a living and was due to have a weeks holiday to go and see them. You see the same people working at breakfast and again later that day for evening meals. Our maid wasn't the best compared to what other people in our group had. We had 1 towel sculpture when we arrived and had no more until 4 days later when my partner gave her $10 and asked her to do one as a romantic gesture. We stupidly thought we may have them more regularly as we left more tips. But she didnt. It is petty but maybe we had the moody one? The rooms were clean and we always had towels but I thought the it could be a little more updated. It didnt feel like a 5 star hotel when you were in your room. More like a 3 or 4. Food: There seems to be a debate on this subject but each to their own! I am a fussy eater unlike my husband who will willingly try anything. Breakfast was ok. We are cereal eaters of a morning but I knew the milk would be different so we didnt even attempt to have any. I stuck with toast for most of the time and only missed it a couple of days when we felt a bit worse for wear!! The oddest thing was mashed potato at breakfast??! Lunch / Dinner was ok. Big choice of salad etc and the usual chips,burgers,chicken,pizza,pasta. Again I stuck to these type of foods to be on the safe side but the other half tried most of it. It wasn't very hot but to be honest you had to make do or not eat. I would definately recommend the Japanese. We went twice and it was fab. Especially if you are in a group and get your own chef. The Italian is also nice. We had our wedding meal in the terrace attached to the restaurant and we had a ball!! The others weren't very nice. The Garden Grill is vile, bbq the same sort of food just that its outside and by the beach. Mexican we didnt try because we heard that was horrible and the fish restaurant we couldnt reserve. We didnt reserve as soon as we arrived. Our best man booked a few group meals but when we went to book one we still had our 6 for the 2 weeks left. Evening activities - Although we have a child we still like a bit of variety on the evenings. Once the show had finished it meant all trudging round to the square only to watch the same thing each night. Even if it wasn't the same it sounded it. From there if your in a family its basically home time. The karaoke bar was open til 1am but for the size of the hotel its not very big and very rowdy. Especially when the yanks were there. They are so loud! I think they like the sound of their own voice because even by the pool or restaurants they had the volume turned up a few notches. This does not go for all of them so I am not tarnishing them with the same brush!! The disco til 2am was so-so. Music was ok from time to time but for the variety of nationalities they had to cater for everyone. We didnt meet many English but there are a range of foreigners from Argentinians to Canadians. Overall the evenings were the same. Not very exciting and quite repetitive.Pools - We stayed by our pool most of the time which was one of the smaller ones on the Punta Cana side in the middle of the complex. We did venture down to the beach pool but it was too crowded and noisy (again a lot a shouting and voices raised) so we stayed away. The snack bar down there was awful. Alot of flies which I know are unavoidable but still horrible. The food as usual was cold to warm and seeing poeple walk round in thongs in the eating area didnt exactly help our appetite. If you missed breakfast and were hungry you had no choice but to go to the pool snack bar. It was a bit of a hike and not even worth it. We thought it would have been better if they had a few snacks at the other pools. It is a nice hotel but I dont think I would return. Its big but good enough to not see the same people twice. There are lots of other classy hotels along the same beach so I think I would prefer to try them out. Staff are lovely.Its clean and you can make the holiday what you want it to be.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>