<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="7b1248d7209479a1770a470af9d59d5e" url=""><![CDATA[Drab I have just returned from a 7 Day holiday in New York City and unfortunately made the mistake of booking the Affinia Dumont. I made the choice after reading other trip advisor member reviews and seeing that the hotel is ranked as one of NY's best. I have always been delighted with previous hotels I have booked as a result of trip advisor but certainly not on this occasion. This hotel is best summed up as drab and dreary. Let me explain. The reception area is similar to that of a travelodge/motel. The carpets throughout the hotel are dirty and worn, the room is dreary, no colour anywhere and the hotel smells musty. There is no bar, no restaurant and no where nice to relax after a day in the city. The Affinia is way overpriced for what it offers. Friends were staying at various other hotels in NY and were much closer to everything, paid much less and had much more facilities. The Affinia Dumont may cater for a business person who needs a bed for the night and the company is picking up the tab but if you are a tourist looking to enjoy NYC then please book another hotel. I met friends at the Novotel and can vouch for the superior condition/quality of this particular hotel. To be fair on the Affinia staff, they were friendly and welcoming and the bed was very comfortable however The Affinia is simply just not worth the money.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6c354083bbfb0a5637be3d03f1fb55a4" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic City, Wonderful Hotel We stayed in this hotel in September 2005 for 11 nights. We arrived at Barcelona Airport late afternoon and caught a train from the airport to Sant Adria del Besos (4 euro each taking approx 30mins) Since the tram outside this station wasn't operating we got on a bus that was put on instead, and this dropped us off outside the hotel. Taxi Fare would have been 30 euro. We took advantage of a room on the 22nd floor which provided breathtaking views of the city. The room was modern and clean. Facilities included air conditioning, pc point with free internet access for those with their own laptop, television, safe, and minibar providing 5 free drinks daily (1 beer, 1 coke, 1 lemon and 2 water). We were slightly dissapointed that the large double bed was in fact 2 single beds pushed together but they were joined by brackets so didn't come away from each other. The hotel pools were very small however as we were rarely in the hotel we would not have been in a position to use them anyway. We did use the sauna which was again very clean and free towels provided. Across from the hotel entrance about 75metres is the underground station El Maresme/Forum(Line 4) and I would recommend you buy a T 10 given 10 rides on the underground system. NB The underground closes at 12am Mon-Thurs but is open until 2am at weekends. Taxis are reasonably inexpensive so if you have ventured into the city centre it doesn't cost a fortune to get back to the hotel in the early hours. Barcelona has so much to offer from a sandy beach to gothic architecture to modern art. The hotel offers free internet access from 2 pc's on the 1st floor and this is useful for finding out places of interest or local restaurants whilst you are there. The hotel bar is well stocked and nice for a quiet drink although did lack a bit of atmosphere. Olympic Port is only 30minutes walking distance for those looking for a more lively nightime scene. Overall a modern, clean and friendly hotel and we will definetly consider staying there on our next Barcelona visit.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>