<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="5">
		<document id="7ce1807ea5506e2d5c347d665e158690" url=""><![CDATA[Great View and Lots of Space We stayed at this place for four nights in April, 2007.We had a one bed room apartment with a large living area, a good sized bed room, a small kitchen, and a very small bathroom.The hotel is located one block from the top of Nob Hill, and our apartment was on the 18th floor. The view was spectacular, and our living room was a wonderful setting for entertaining friends.A breakfast of coffee, juice, and pastry or bagel is served under the watchful eye of two women--one of whom is grim and who seems to regard hotel guests as beggars. Insist on a bear claw.The furnishings are dated and a bit beat up, but the spaciousness of the apartment and great view more than compensated for these deficiencies.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="12116d1bc40c3655f1f707ee60da8653" url=""><![CDATA[We Liked the Service and Location We stayed at this hotel December 24-31, 2007, for a rate of $235 which included compact car, valet parking, and breakfast.This property has recently undergone a complete remodel, and we loved the location, which is a short walk from the beach and dozens of shopping and dining options.We had a standard room on the 16th floor with a mountain view. The room, with balcony, was decorated in a pleasing contemporary style. It had two comfortable beds, desk and chair, dresser, fridge, excellent flat-screen TV, and a weird coffee machine that made two cups of coffee. The room was a little on the small side with no table for dining and only the desk chair for seating.The bathroom had a large shower, but no tub. The towels were plush and large. It was good.Breakfast was limited to two choices and the coupon could not be applied to other options. Each morning I chose an omelet, toast, and coffee. The waitresses were extremely pleasant, but a waiter we had one morning was a little on the boorish side.We made good use of the business office in the lobby which offered free internet access.The service from the front desk, cleaning staff, and valets was superb--it spoiled us for other places we stayed later on our trip.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="aca1f9a61a69a8b135782c60ad17a4a5" url=""><![CDATA[A Good Alternative if the Rate is Right We stayed at this property for three nights in July, 2007.We booked through Priceline at $145 (the rack rate was $152-$195).We were first put into a small room with two queen beds. I requested a larger room and was given a suite with one-bedroom which had a comfortable king bed, two night stands, dresser, TV, and closet. The city skyline could be seen from the bedroom window.The living room was large and bright--with lots of windows that looked out onto a neighborhood of auto dealerships, Budget car rental, etc.The property is located a 10- to 15-minute walk from stores such as Nordstrom and Macy's, entertainment, and major restaurants.Parking and an o.k. breakfast were included in the rate. The business people and tourists in the breakfast room were similar in appearance to those we see at Hampton Inn, Hilton Garden Inn, etc.Nearby dining options include a well-established Korean restaurant, Whole Foods grocery store, a 24-hour greasy spoon (Hurricane), and Amore Italian restaurant (which is a good option if you aren't up to walking more than three blocks).I was pleased with our upgraded suite, but I would have been unhappy if I had to spend three nights in the small room with two Queen beds. I took a peak at a Deluxe King room; it was a better option.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dd96ff1c67b26620b3025ad110485d93" url=""><![CDATA[Great Location for Sightseeing This hotel has a perfect location for walking to all the important sights.We had a very large, quiet room with high ceilings (#37). The bathroom was unusually large, too.Breakfast was o.k., but the quality of the baked goods was not as good as we had elsewhere. Also, breakfast was served in a make-shift breakfast room because the reception area and breakfast room were being remodeled. The food may taste better in the more attractive surroundings.The staff was pleasant and helpful.While searching for a restaurant recommended by one of our guidebooks, we stumbled on a delightful restaurant at which we ate several times: Hostaria il Desco at Via del Terme 23, which is near the Rialto Bridge. This restaurant, which opened less than a year ago, is already popular with locals. They have great prices and delicious food. Check out the special lunch menu and ask for the set dinner menu.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="12145626a9f45263cc68a2e950f2c121" url=""><![CDATA[Plus and Minus If you like boutique hotels, you will probably like this place. However, be aware that some interior rooms are very dark and that the location is close only to the Zona Rosa.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>