<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="8d71430985461bf5c6f8dd5fc5e612b4" url=""><![CDATA[Beware Ritz lovers - don't stay here After staying at the Ritz here in June 07 we wer eager to come back to Puerto Rico so when my husband received info on a conference here we leaped at the opportunity. We debated on staying at the Ritz again vs the El San Juan where the conference was being held. The room rate was around $400 per night more for Ritz concierge level so we made what turned out to be a poor decision based solely on $$$ and booked at the El San Juan (they had a package to receive a 5th night free). A friend said he stayed there in the past and it was fine. If I had followed my usual routine and readTrip Advisor reviews we would have made a different decision and booked at the Ritz - foolish me. We chose a La Vista tower room because they were renovated. While there we visited a non-renovated garden lanai room Access to the pool was great (right out a patio door), however, the rooms are very much in need of updating (dark, dingy, icky tile, etc. - also the room key doesn't work on the patio door so you have to go around to the front to get back in from the pool unless you leave it unlocked). The trip wasn't what I would call a disaster, however, if you are accustomed to the level of service at a Rtiz property, the El San Juan is not for you. We arrived at 2pm and were told our room may not be ready until 4 pm check -in but they would call us soon as it was ready. We rechecked at 3:45 and it still wasn't ready. By 5:00 we noticed others just walking in and receiving rooms right away and we still had not received a call. We again approached and only then were given a room right next to the elevator. It was only about 4 feet away from the elevator door that we passed it by. When we asked for another room they did not even try to hide their displeasure with our request. Throughout our stay we heard this same story over and over about the delays in checking in. We ended up on 4th floor 5 doors down from the elevator. Our beautiful view was the roof of the lobby with all its A/C equipment, etc. When I made reservations they said the only difference in the next room level up was that it was a higher floor. I just closed the drapes and never opened them again. The room itself was clean and an average size. It had been remodeled and had a tile floor which was much better to me than carpeting. However, the bathroom was very small, no tub, only a pedestal sink and a tiny shower that another reviewer aptly noted leaked all over the floor. There was no full length mirror in the room. Our package included 2 complimentary drinks and $25 casino credit. We did not receive the amenities at check-in, however, we requested it on our 2nd day and they complied. The first 2 nights we were awoken after the casino closed at 4 am by boisterous guests out in the hall. We complained via our cell phone because the room phone was dead (I had to unplug it to use the outlet for something else - because the room had no other outlets - and didn't plug it back in.) They would not listen to our concerns because we were not calling from a room. We heard doors slamming and people in the hall all through the 5 nights we were there - not peaceful at all. If you want a restful night you would have to bring earplugs with you. I will briefly list other cons. To get a lounge chair you had to get out there before 7 am. We learned that many come out early as 4 am to lay towels and claim chairs. Supposedly if a chair is unattended for 20 minutes the staff open it up, but we saw this happen only on our 4th day after many people complained. There was patio space for more chairs so I don't know why they had out such a limited number. Also, upon questioning staff we learned they had 4 chairs reserved for investors that were never occupied for 2 days. Bar service for both drinks and lunch was only for very patient guests. They were never busy, never in a hurry, totally apathetic to guest needs. The fitness center was average (thankfully, no extra charge for it). However, to get to it you had to sign in at the spa. One day the attendant did not even look up and greet us. Needless to say, there is no daily newspaper or turndown service, no robes, no slippers, no shower cap. They did have shampoo, conditioner, shower gel and lotion that smelled good. The onsite deli/pizzeria in the adjacent Galleria advertised to open at 11 am didn't open till 11:30 am. The food and service at the Palm Restaurant were superb. Our reservation had been lost and the manager treated us to dessert. The great table promised at the in-house Italian restaurant was actually right on top of a very noisy table and a family (the child behaved better than the adults on the other side). There was also a party of 12 in the room that was very, very loud. The food was excellent, the service below average and the ambiance poor. If you go there request a free standing table in the dining room with a window. The onsite Smoker's Suite supposed to open at 5 pm was still closed at 6 pm on Saturday night. Concierge said it was a concession and there was nothing they could do. Also, taxes and resort fees added almost $100 per day to the daily room rate. Pros - drink prices were very reasonable and very potent. The housekeeping staff did an excellent job. Management walking floor in hotel were friendly. In summary, if you love the way every staff person at the Ritz ends a sentence with my pleasure and you know they mean it - spend the extra and stay there. It is worth every dollar.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>