<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a67b8a08ed84887c27685b000ef2774a" url=""><![CDATA[Nice place, OUTRAGEOUS prices. I would NOT recommend this hotel for the average middle class traveler or for the elderly. While I am not cheap by any means, this hotel went far beyond my budget. A lot of walking is required and climbing stairs to get to various places in the hotel. There is even a tram to take you to different areas.HOTEL:Upon arrival we paid for an ocean view room with 2 queen beds. (For 4 people). Theygave us a shoe box sized room with a garden view. They offered us an ocean view with one full and an air mattress. That was unacceptable! They finally upgraded us to La Casitas, off the main hotel up on a hill where we had to be driven there, in a golf cart or a mini van if we got lucky, because it is too far from the main hotel (the driver expected a tip every time). Although the room was large and the view was beautiful they only offer 2 full size beds, which was a problem for us since we were four. We were also put on the second floor with a long flight of stairs to climb. There were also multiple long flights of stairs down to the pool, which was a huge problem because I was with my parents who are in their late 60s and my mother has health issues, they were not fit enough for the climbing and long walk. To get to the main hotel we had to call the hotel transportation and wait outside to be picked up which took anywhere from 10-15 minutes, just to get to a restaurant to eat. The second day we demanded the ocean view room we originally paid for, we argued on the phone 3 times and they made us wait 2 hours while they discussed whether they would move us. We threatened to leave and they finally moved us to the ocean view room with 2 queen beds on the first floor in the main hotel. To go down to the marina in order to get to the water park, ferry to Palomino Island (the beach) or the shops and bar grill, we had to take an elevator down, walk across the entire hotel, and then take a tram down. The tram usually had a long wait because so many people needed to get on it. PLEASE NOTE: there is NO BEACH AT THE HOTEL. You need to take the ferry to what they call their private beach, which is their ONLY beach. The at the beach is also extremely overpriced and they give you barely enough food to hold you for an hour.FOOD:I know resorts usually have expensive food, but the prices were just not a little expensive, they were OUTRAGEOUSLY expensive. There is no choice but to eat within the resort and ALL the restaurants are overpriced. There were no reasonable prices or even just a little expensive places to eat.It doesn't make sense to rent a car to try to find food cheaper off the resort because parking at the resort is $15/day. Besides the cost of renting a car, and there really are no decent places to eat outside the resort.Be prepared to spend between $15 - 22 for a hamburger and fries.Breakfast, lunch and dinner averaged over $100/meal for four people.Also be prepared to WAIT 30-40 minutes for your food everywhere. La Caribe gave me and my mother our breakfast after 30 minutes and gave my father his 20 minutes later, with no apologies.The drinks were incredibly watered down. I ordered a few alcoholic drinks that had almost no alcohol in them. The tropical drinks go from $12 - 15 a drink. And don't expect fancy tropical drinks. They are in regular plastic cups or hurricane glasses.The sandwich shop you can get a sandwich from 9pm to 1am at $10 and up. But be prepared to wait on a huge line then wait another 20 minutes for them to make the sandwich, and they expect a gratuity even though it's considered take out.SERVICE:Besides not getting the right room when we arrived, then giving us the run around the next day to get the right room and waiting hours, the first day at La Casitas I needed a hair dryer. There was none in the room. I called the front desk at 8 in the morning; I didn't receive the dryer until 9am. The hotel elevators did not work. There were two and one was broken for the entire week.The plumbing is awful! The water pressure is way too low in the showers and the water is always luke warm.The room at the main hotel had no coffee maker...forcing us to buy the overpriced coffee at Starbucks in the lobby, or go to Daniels Cookies, another coffee shop where they expect a gratuity for making your coffee.On the way home we called for a bell hop to take our luggage out front and were told there was a 30 minute wait. We could not wait because we had to get on the bus to the airport in 20 minutes.There is a small internet room with 4 computers with free internet. 3 were constantly not working and one was always being used.The staff is not very willing to help with anything and half of them were very rude!KIDS/WATER PARKIf you have kids there is a water park that is $20 /person for 3 slides. That's about all that encompasses the water park. Long lines to use the slides. We went here because I have a 15 year old son.If you don't like kids don't come here! It's crawling with small kids running around, screaming and crying constantly.. AND they are up ALL night long!!!There is NO QUIET place in the hotel!NIGHTLIFEThere pretty much is none. There is a small night club with not much going on, and usually empty at night.CASINOForget about getting any complimentary free drinks and sandwiches. There are NO waiters to be seen offering anything. But there is a bar in there to buy drinks. And the machines don't pay out at all!POOLS/ BEACHThe pools are nice but loaded with kids! Get there early! The beaches are beautiful but again, get there early to get an umbrella or you'll have to rent one for the day. Any activities at the beach again, are very expensive.SIGHTSEEINGDon't expect to do any sight seeing after exhausting all your funds for food and activities at this hotel. Just to go to Old San Juan for shopping, its $50 per person.We did no sight seeing.SHOPSI know its to be expected, but I have to mention, yes.. everything in the shops are triple the amount of what you would pay at home.IN CONCLUSIONFor such an expensive place it is NOT WORTH it. Be prepared to spend a fortune on food, wait in long lines for virtually everything, and get aggravated by the less the helpful staff! If you are elderly or handicapped, or even have health issues, don't go here. If you don't like kids, don't come here. If you don't have tons of money to waste, don't come here! You don't get any breaks here.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>