<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="7acd5dd213222ee4ce6442cca3aee776" url=""><![CDATA[Second Trip... Would go there again We went for a week in April and were pleased so we did it again in November. Again, we were very happy with our stay. My review is based on going during off season....Its not quite as crowed.......... 1. Resort: Grounds are maintained and beautiful. Everything is in walkable distance ( not a huge resort ) but there is a tram if you're feeling lazy, with at the max of a 10 minute wait.2. Pool: 2 pool's really nice size. Were clean, maintained. 2 swim up bars which you can also access from outside the pool......... I drink champagne which they had. Good selection of liquor....I saw Gran Marnier, Ketel One, Absolute, Captain Morgan.....If you like to be treated like a prince/princess, they did not come around the pool and ask to get your drink, you had to get your own., which is right there where the chairs are...no biggy,,,,,............Many chairs around pool.....no problem getting one 3. Rooms: Very Average, large, clean. Nice size deck/patio Nice bathroom......double sinks, all tile, jacuzzi. I know people complain of low water pressure and cold water, but for the week we were there it was just the opposite.......hot water, lotsa pressure.... (we were there in off season ! ) We saw NO bugs in the room the entire week and we were on the 1st floor, but in the afternoon we did smell bug spray outside the rooms........That's good......they were preventing problems. ABSOLUTELY MUST BRING HIGH WATTAGE LIGHT BULBS. We brought 4, and it made a world of difference. 4. Food: Let me say we are bland eaters. ( Do not like heavy garlic or anything spicy or with unusual flavors ) All I can say is we loved the buffet so if your taste is opposite ours you will hate the food at the buffet. They do have specialty nights and one night was international with garlicky, seasoned foods and we did not like it. We did not go to the restuarants, so no comment. FYI: There are 2 Buffets, one on the beach and one in the development. Food taste is very individual so you'll have to decide for yourself whether you like it or not......5. Shopping: They do have a nice number if huts on the beach for shopping and they do have a dominican shopping mall about 5-10 minutes by cab ( $8.00 one way). Both sell dominican stuff and haggle with the price, don't pay more than 1/2 the asking, or if buying more than 1 maybe even a little less. It was fun to go to the shopping mall, just for the heck of it.......Its basically what they sell on the beach, but more of it in a dominican mall atmosphere.6. Beach: Sorry, but I'm a pool person, didn't stay on the beach, But when I shopped at the huts the beach looked beautiful and calm. The people said it was gorgeous except for 2 days out of the week where the water was a little dirty with sea weed due to high tide 7. Activities: There is a spa for many different treatments. By the pool/beach massages, hair braiding. Also horseback riding, trips to Santo Domingo. Samoa Island, etc, mountain trips, so on and so forth. I don't do anything except site by the pool so I can't comment7. Negatives: They are chinzy with bathroom towels....you have to ask for more ( leaving a few dollars helps).....Same with beach towels ............Chair coverings on the beach don't really keep out the sun.....can't really think of anything elseOverall, I think Punta Cana is a great vacation for your money. I happen to like this resort. I'm sure there are other resorts just as good, maybe better, but I can't recommend any other since this is the only one I've been to. I'm comfortable here so I'll come back again,,,,,,,,,,,,,, ANY QUESTIONS, PLEASE FEEL FREE TO E MAIL ME
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="607f5dfb74ae6cbc9b551af5575f914f" url=""><![CDATA[Wonderful Resort A + We went Easter week. We are a childless couple in our early 60's who travel alot and like to stay in very clean, comfortable, above average resorts. We are not real demanding or complaining people, but we do like our reasonable requests to be met and I can say they were........ I will list my opinion by categories:: 1. ----- LAYOUT---- The buildings look quaint and are well taken care of.....The greenery is lush and is lanscaped beautifully. The grounds are clean and the landscaping is quite beautifUL......The inner courtyard is just lovely ....The resort is small enough ti walk to everything, although a shuttle was available for those who can't or prefer not to walk.......You can hop one about every 10 minutes at the most..........2.-----POOLS (two)-----Beautiful, clean, can be cool at times, 2 great pool bars with wonderful drinks, some top shelf liquor and very drinkable champagne available..(Yea! my drink ) .Chairs avaiable, although I went out early (around 8 am) and placed towels where I wanted to sit, but there are many, many chairs available.......3.-----FOOD-----Didn't eat at the restaurants so I can't comment, but the buffets were great. ( one within the development, one on the beach) great selection of all kinds of food........flavorful, but not over seasoned ( We are pretty bland eaters so their food selection appealed to us) I think they go middle of the road because when you cook for large crowds you have to appeal to all....Some spicy, garlicky lovers may hate this type of cooking........WE DIDN'T...........4-----ROOMS----- Clean, large , saw 1 bug.,,,husband killed it...didn't see any more ( we were on the first floor as requested maybe thats why we saw a bug...other friends did not..they were on higher floors )...Bathroom clean , warm to hot water all week , no problem, Bed comfort average, Decor was below average, no musty smell.....MUST TAKE LIGHT BULBS LIGHTING VERY DIM ....5.-----ENTERTAINMENT-----Not much to say here...Evening stage entertainment was nice, something to do , but I preferred to sit in the lobby and drink champagne and listen to the music.......Casino is teeny, tiny.....we laughed, but it didn't stop us from playing for a short amount of time (gamblers always think they're going to win no matter what casino they are in !!,,,,There is also bowling and pool tables available.....6.-----BEACH-----Very clean, sometimes with a little seaweed, in the water some days without any, lots of chairs, nice beach for walking, can walk very far passing all the different resorts............-----OVERALL-----A CLEAN, COZY, RELAXING, COMFORTABLE RESORT......WE ENJOYED OUR STAY VERY MUCH AND PLAN ON GOING BACK THIS YEAR........HAVE NO DESIRE TO TRY OTHER RESORTS.....BY THE WAY, IF YOU ARE A PERSON WHO ENJOYS THEIR ALCOHOLIC BEVERAGES, THEY ARE ALWAYS AVAILABLE ANY WHERE YOU GO IN THE RESORT INCLUDING THE POOL HALL AND THE SHOWS, ETC.......ENJOY YOUR TRIP!!!!!!!!!!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>