<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="fa97484539871cb6facfe1aa1a626ccb" url=""><![CDATA[ok hotel. value for money given the location. stayed 2 nights in a superior room. comes in 4 themes, Chinese, Indian, Malay, and Modern. dont ask me which one my room was themed after, i dont know any different.value for money: price is just about right, given size of room, quality of room and location of hotel.hotel room: size is just a little small, but that's ok given that its not a room to be enjoyed but to sleep in. they have cable tv (korean, japanese, sports, news, etc) and LCD tv so that's pretty cool.toilet: no bath, just shower. however, the toilet gave out a stink smell. not very obvious if you leave the door open and aircon turned on. but if you are in the bathroom, you can smell the stink. maybe its just my room, or those that are connected to the same faulty plumbing.internet access: free! that's a plus point. and when you check in, they ask if you know how to use it, and if you have a laptop, they will offer you a LAN cable for connection. of course, you would have to return it or they will charge it to your room, haha.distance to nearest MRT station: not too good. have to walk quite a distance, as it is smack right between the 2 nearest stations.getting a taxi: not many taxi drivers know about this hotel, as its not very well known yet. even if it is probably the ONLY hotel in these parts. since a majority of drivers are chinese, if you can tell them the chinese name (which is nothing like link hotel, duh!), they can probably relate to it better. of course, showing the map of the hotel location might help a bit.nearby food and convenience kiosk: 5 stars! the famous tiong bahru food court (upgraded to a 2-storey building recently) and a few seafood restaurants are just a walk around the block. one seafood restaurant turned me off. i waited 30 min and then checked with the waitress, only to find that the food will take another 30 min. i left at that point. moral of the story: ask before you sit down how long it will take for your orders to be served. and next to the food court is a 7-11 24-hour convenience outlet. next to the 7-11 is a nice little restaurant that sells shanghainese food, like small dragon steamed buns, fried rice cakes, etc.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>