<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="af7f9dec046e31ffd075c2301c0c52a2" url=""><![CDATA[NEVER AGAIN TRY ANOTHER HOTEL FIRST. We must have had the same server in the hotel restaurant that the previous reviewer had!! She also had issues with timely serving. When our breakfast order (for 4) was finely taken and farrived, we had to remind her about the cream for our coffee yet again. When it was delivered in a chipped one serving pitcher, we were told to share it); told us to get the jellies from the next vacant table (when asking about jam) and that she had to handle room service next--perhaps making this her excuse for poor service?!! I think management may be short on staff and are putting the wrong people in the wrong jobs due to labor shortages right now? We had a confirmed reservation number for a king bed, but upon check-in, computer said queen, and there was no changing that--sorry! So we paid king rates for a queen bed because the computer said there was a king bed in the room?!! This was really irritating as the hotel had availability and their internet server had a spring special going on, as well as an advertised queen rate. Never called and offered to move us, even upon asking of king availability (due to the fact the computer said we had a king room??) They didn't even come down and check the room to see--very strange!! Employee attitude was poor. At the beginning of our stay, we kept trying to explain ourselves and ask for a manager, we were informed we had been speaking to the manager (one of the desk help)(?!). We were only staying 3 nights, and didn't want to fight with staff the entire trip, so quit even trying as the frustration would ruin the trip. Room service order arrived incorrectly (no croissants that day) so delivered what they wanted, no call to see what else we'd like (we didn't dare wait and see how long it would take to correct the order--so ate it as is). Its a shame, cause the room we had (looking at the pool) was quiet and nicely furnished, great location, but I'd never stay there again.....if you do, get everything in writing prior to your stay, don't rely on the confirmation number.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>