<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="c67848e65abd24ed2ec734e8f87693b6" url=""><![CDATA[Snug gem! Tucked away behind the Pantheon in the Latin Quarter, this boutique hotel is really worth considering. You won't find a pool, or air conditioning apart from a fan - but you will find pleasant, helpful staff and clean, compact but very comfortable and affordable rooms. The area is ideal for some interesting walks: try the Jardin des Plantes or the Luxembourg Gardens (magic!). There are restaurants just around the corner, at one of those wonderful happening intersections.Ideal for couples and explorers-on-foot.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a67dc6b794d3644c0c525f87abee750c" url=""><![CDATA[Best Part of Barcelona! 'Tourists' want to take their environment with them like a snail in its shell; 'Travellers' relish the local, the unique, the colorful. Fortunately, my wife, our friend and I are Travellers, or we might have missed this absolutely fantastic over-the top gem of a place. Sergio and Abel obviously love L'Antic Espai: it's obvious, from the eclectic and eccentric decor to their concern that the guest too should feel this is their home. The hotel is a restored townhouse, and is accessed through a 'door in a door', then up the stairs. Location is great - near Las Ramblas, shopping and the best tapas in Barcelona (superb French restaurant around the corner too!). The rooms are tiny (of course) but sumptuously furnished. The beds are very comfortable; a/c ensuite bathrooms 'like new'. We stayed in two different rooms - just because the best one became available and the boys thought we might like to try it! Overall, it's the decor and the 'style' that you'll remember. This is more an experience of a home than a hotel. Poke, pry, ask questions - you're with enthusiasts! Oh, and if you read that negative review from the man who never came, let us tell you that there is nothing wrong with the business end of things - except it becomes more of a pleasure!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>