<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="890075a7ed49c2544af68afd46ad0ab9" url=""><![CDATA[Best Employee of our Trip After 5 weeks touring Germany, Poland, Austria, Hungary, Czeck Republic, this hotel won our award for Best Employee! Martin at the front desk speaks many languages, and truly anticipates everything you might need to make your vacation effortless! Location is terrific! And being that close to a major train station (Zoogarten) makes life easy for excursions of every kind. We received a large room on the courtyard, with a balcony. It was perfect for sharing a cocktail with friends before the evening events, or OJ the morning after. Our friends' room was also on the courtyard, and while not as large as ours, had a HUGE bathroom! One surmises that each room is different. This may not be in the hot and trendy spot, as another review complains, but it is just of Kurfurstendamm home of the best name fashion designer shopping outside of Paris, and all the accompanying real estate. (IMHO) So it just depends on what trends you're into, I guess. Breakfast is not included in the room and runs about $10Euros. Just so you know who is reviewing, we are a middle-age hetero couple. I travel extensively on a very generous expense account, but have travelled Europe on my own account 5 times for over 4 weeks each trip. This hotel is a bit above average for what I would accept on my own tab. I think it's very well priced for location, accommodation, and the fact that it is in Berlin - not a cheap town to explore. I'd stay here again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1b4139daac1c3b55babe4893b38fe690" url=""><![CDATA[Just Sleep on the Floor! The beds are SO hard I woke up in pain every night. The floor is literally softer than the bed! Problem is the rooms are so small that you cannot find the floor after you put your suitcase on it. And there is ONE vacant electric plug in. It's under the desk in the bedroom, so don't think you're going to use hair appliances or anything in the bathroom where you might actually find them useful...Check in was a mess - computer problems. Hence a mixed-up reservation. Staff is all Shanghai Tang'd and pretty self-impressed with their cool hip. But that's pretty much all they should be impressed with.Friends called to leave me messages, which I never get. Oh, lady, phone will be beeping if message waits. There is absolutely nothing in your room to tell you how to actually retrieve a message should you be fortunate enough to get one. (Dial ** if you're wondering.) They checked and said I had received a message all right. But my phone never beeping. Turns out they have been forwarding my messages to a different room... I'd skip this hotel in a hurry....
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>