<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="6b12ba01ee46f20c9aa670e20db3371c" url=""><![CDATA[Loved it We spent two weeks at the Sirenis Cocotal Resort in the Dominican Republic from January 17 to January 31, 2007 and we have nothing negative to report. We landed in the Punta Cana Airport. This airport is open and hot. Passengers have to board the plane outside and walk across the tarmac. The resort picked us up at the airport in a nice air-conditioned bus and it took over one hour to get to the resort, because of the stops the bus has to make to let passengers off at other resorts. We had no problem checking in at the front desk and we did get the ocean view room we requested when we booked. The resort is huge. It is actually two resorts in one, because the Sirenis Tropical suites is just on the other side of the wide walkway that leads from the lobby to the ocean. All the buildings are three stories high.The place is immaculate and kept that way, very well organized and the rooms are cleaned fast and thoroughly. The beach is huge with plenty of palm trees and there is shade for the people who seek it. We never had to fight to get chairs. It was windy most of the time and the ocean not as calm as we would have liked, but there is a huge reef farther out in the ocean and the waves break there, so the ones who get through are not strong. For the people who like to lounge around the pool, it is huge and friendly. Because of the Sirenis Tropical suites resort next door there are many families with children, but it is not a problem. Dining: There are two buffets and seven a la carte restaurants. We find booking for the a la carte restaurants a large problem, but you have to stand in line for over half an hour most of the time. We went twice to the Asian (the shrimp were good), twice to the Seafood (Try the grouper, it is excellent). I had an upset stomach for a night because of the shrimp cocktail in the pineapple. I found it too rich. The Steakhouse was okay. I found the steak too salty.Lunch we had in the restaurant close to the ocean, by the pool. In the evening, it is the Italian and Mexican a la carte, but it is a buffet during the day. Wonderful crepes for desert.The staff is friendly and attentive, and they make a distinction between the different guests, the way we found in Samana last year, where they catered mostly to French speaking guests.Because the resort is so large there are a lot of people, however, we never felt crowded. Everything is laid back and it is fairly quiet, except for a couple of days, when a bunch of young people was being towed around on a rubber dingy by a motorboat trying to plunge them into the water. That was quite annoying because it was too close to the swimming area and therefore noisy and the stink of diesel overpowering.There are resorts on either side of the Serinis Cocotal, about half an hours walk along the beach. A nice walk, except for the aggressive vendors in the gift shops who will intercept people who walk by them. The food was good, plenty of variety. The soups were delicious. This was actually the first resort been to where the beef was tender enough to be edible. The pork and chicken was excellent and prepared in different ways. Lots of fresh salads and salad dressings, not just vinegar and oil. Deserts were fine, too. The lobby is large with plenty of chairs and tables to relax. There are two bars and no problems getting drinks. On the weekends there is entertainment in the lobby with a singer was great) and Karaoke (I comment on that!)One of the disappointing things was the fact that there is not much for shopping around the resort, except for the gift shops, and they carry only the usual souvenirs. We found prices high. And they only carry rum. One vendor brought us Gin, but he wanted 1,500 pesos 55.00 US dollars for 1.20 liters!!) Then he came down to 1,000 pesos, which is still around 37.00 US dollars. (We got 27 pesos for 1.00 US dollar at the hotel. There is no other place to exchange your checks and they take advantage of that.) We bought our duty free liquor on the plane. Not as cheap as buying it in a store in the Dominican, but still a bit of a saving.Going home, it took almost two hours to get back to the airport, because some passengers in the resorts on the way ready, so we had a bit of a rush at the airport. It is hot standing in line to get processed and light clothing is recommended. There are no liquids of any kind permitted in the carry on luggage, so we had our lunch on the bus (we packed it in the morning). All in all, we had a wonderful holiday and probably go back there.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>