<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="133ad29fe6511b7c32da7145afa0c43d" url=""><![CDATA["...Luis Anymore Champagne? Si!" My wife and I were at the Excellence between April 15th and 23rd. We are a couple in our mid-thirties from Toronto. been to Punta Cana several times in the past. This resort was by far the best stayed at anywhere. The staff were #1. We ate at all the restaurants except for the Lobster House. The food was very good. Room service was good and pretty quick. There is a good selection of liquor and the staff will make you anything you like. Our last day there was spent on a four poster the flowing white drapes and all. The hotel had given us a bottle of Spanish Champagne which we took to the beach in a bucket of ice. the X-Lounge beach bar was kind enough to few more bottles for us. that for a day at the beach! The staff bring around pizza, nachos, fruit kabobs, sandwiches, etc. during the day. The no reservation system is great in our view. If you go between 6:30 usually get a table right away. Otherwise they give you a pager and you simply go have a drink, shop or listen to music for 15-40 minutes. The staff remember you. The Marti bar staff remembered each day that I came by for an expresso mid-afternoon and around 7pm. It was also nice not having to drink out of disposable plastic cups, as was the case at other resorts been to. A frosted mug of draft is very nice. Once night they set up a boxing ring and had 4-5 three round fights. That was interesting.For those who like bottled beer vs. draft, you can only get bud, bud-lite and MGD at the Martini bar (sometimes at the Kafe However, your maid will get you as much presidente in the bottle as you like. Just ask (tip). If I was going back, bring a little cooler to fill up at the ice machine before hitting the beach each day. Your fridge is full of beer, water and soft drinks. I have nothing but good things to say about the resort and staff. I took the advice here on Trip-Advisor and went to stall to get some cigars. I think a male family member or friend was covering for her, because he wanted to charge me $24 for one VERY cheap cigar, which should have been $3 at most. not talking about a Cuban cigar that I might buy here in Toronto for that $25, talking a plastic wrapped Dominican no-name. Anyway, no big deal. Great place, great staff, wonderful time. All that for Cdn$1,299.00 plus tax! Wow!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>