<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="927195788bae655a4f088a66e47b4b77" url=""><![CDATA[Lovely Weekend My husband and I spent four nights at the Fairmont San Francisco last weekend. We had a fabulous weekend and the hotel only added to our wonderful weekend. This hotel has a beautiful lobby that reminds one of grand hotels of years long past. They just don't make them like that any more. Our check in was superb. We are President's Club members and that may add to the perfect service but I hope that everyone experiences the same friendly, helpful welcome we received. Our room was on the 19th floor overlooking the bay. The views from the upper floors overlooking the bay are about as great as you will get in the city. The room was a nice size with a very comfortable bed and nice sitting area and a nice working desk. I too, as someone else mentioned, miss not having tea making facilities in the room. We didn't even think about getting tea sent to the room. My bad.The location of the hotel is just the very best. A tip that we will share is that if you take the cable car down Powell to Market, and you are over 65, you can buy a month pass for city transportation for $10 at the green kiosk right by the cable car turning platform. They also have two and three day passes but the monthly senior pass is the best buy. They didn't even ask for our identification cards. Drats! So for the 4 days we were in San Francisco we could cable car, bus, trolley, or surface rail cars for $20 total for both of us. We used all forms of transport and went far and wide and found the service was excellent. And, the Fairmont is perfectly located to use the public transit services to the fullest. A couple of things did not come up to our expectations and we commented on these on our Satisfaction Form we filled out and left with the front desk on our departure. Our housekeeping services were not top notch. Every morning when we would leave the room there would be dishes sitting outside the rooms on our hallway. When we came back to the hotel in the evenings the same dishes were still in the hall and a full day's worth more dishes had been added. I don't know if the responsibility is housekeeping or food services but we found it objectionable. We pointed this out to the front desk twice and the dishes were picked up shortly thereafter but the next day it was just the same. And, the dirty glasses in our room were not removed nor clean glasses put in the room each day. When we call down to housekeeping and said we did not have clean glasses in the bathroom, a gentleman brought up one glass for us. I didn't bother sending him back for another one so we shared our one clean glass as I had given him the two dirty glasses that were still beside our door. (we tried leaving the dirty glasses in the room and setting them out in the hall - neither plan resulted in clean glasses in the room.) There are no chocolates on the pillows in the evening, nor fresh flowers or fruit in the room when you check in. This is rather standard in first class hotels such as The Four Seasons, or The Peninsula. The prices at the Fairmont are similar to the top hotels but the little extras that the other hotels provide aren't part of the Fairmont experience. Now that being said, let me tell you that we were in San Fran for my birthday and that came out at our check in. We came in that evening after spending the afternoon walking around China Town and found chocolate covered strawberries and a bottle of champagne from the hotel. That we thought was brilliant! First Class, Top Drawer and all that. This is not our first or last stay at this hotel. We would not stay in another hotel in San Francisco because we like many things about the hotel. The location, the quite good breakfast buffet, the wonderful halls lined with historical pictures and just the general feel of the hotel. We would overlook the small deficiencies because we like this hotel very much and would recommend it to anyone going to San Francisco and especially someone going for a first visit to the city.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="762ee565c19e07bce01f01ffda04af82" url=""><![CDATA[A Great Location and a Great Stay My husband and I began a four-week tour of Eastern Europe in September by staying for four nights at the Berlin Marriott. It was a wonderful stay. The location of the hotel is superb! You are right at Potsdamer Platz metro station, The Sony Center is just across a small street. There are lots of places to eat within a five minute walk and anyone you want to meet from Berlin knows the location. We did three days of walking tours with Berlin Walks and our wonderful guide was Sarah. We highly recommend this company for the on you own tourists. Our hotel room was on the 8th floor looking our on the Bears exhibit and with good views of the city. Our room was a standard room but it was plenty spacious for us as we were out of the room from early morning to early evening. Everything was clean and there were adequate amenities in the bathroom. The front desk and concierge were friendly and helpful. The cafe served us a wonderful steak salad dinner our first night in Berlin after hours of airplanes and terminals and we had breakfast each morning off the menu rather than the buffet and it was very tasty. Checking in and checking out were without any problems. We were much too tried from walking miles each day to use the gym or pool facilities but they looked quite nice. We would highly recommend this hotel to anyone visiting Berlin and we would definitely stay there again when we go to Berlin.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>