<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="a3e38f23b10b95dcb00759f6289253ed" url=""><![CDATA[Excellent hotel, minor glitches Just back from our stay (actually, at PUJ airport waiting to leave - there's free wi-fi, enjoy it like I am doing right now), and we're going to break down and analyze the main aspects, point by point:1) Reception/ Front Desk: - Great, friendly staff, will go out of their way to please you (they changed our room on request for example)- Good quality internet on the 2 Reception desktop PCs, Wi-Fi was patchy. In some spots/rooms you had a good quality of service, others you couldn't get it to operate at all.2) Rooms - Nice and large, with the built-in round bathtub. - We had an electrical problem and they fixed it as quick as they could, all we had to do is call the helpful front desk.- They're currently expanding the Royal part of the resort by building two extra villas. But whether you're in the beach or in your room, you won't hear it.3) Food / RestaurantsAll restaurants had their ups and downs.- The main restaurant of the Royal part of the resort (Thalassa) is great, and so is most of their staff. One glitch is the waiting time: since all waiters tend to all customers, sometimes orders will get lost in the shuffle or take more time than necessary. But on other days service was quick and efficient. But who cares, we're on holiday! Juan, Angelica, Angel Leonel, Rafael and Maria the concierge, for example, are a joy to be served by.- Breakfast consists of a buffet with some a la carte options. - Lunch a la carte is available to all Royal guests. One part of the menu changes daily while the other part remains constant every day.- Dinner only by booking. The menu differs from the lunch menus, and remained constant throughout our stay. - Food is overall great in quality, and they're willing to tweak the meals a little to your best liking. As for desserts, avoid the tiramisu, chocolate mousse... those are not their specialties, believe me. For something sweet, try the creperie La Bretonne on the regular side of the Catalonia.Thematics: - La Toscana: Great pasta, shoddy desserts. - Steakhouse: Good quality meat (not great).- Mikado: The chef does his little hot plate showdown on a table/room for 12 people. The overall quality of the food is good. The only restaurant without the AC system working and it was in dire need of one! For dessert, try the fried ice-cream.- Mexican: Spicy. My bowels felt it the day after, but the food is nice.- Grand Caribe buffet: lots of choice and lots of room (tables on one side, food on the other). The quality is what you'd expect from a large hotel buffet. - Beach buffet: Smaller and noisier. Tip: go early! Food selection is smaller than in Grand Caribe, but the quality is the same.- Pizza parlour: Let me tell you, I've worked in Italy for 3 months and tasted a great deal of pizza while there. The pizzas they make at Catalonia reminded me of some of the best I had in Firenze. Warning: they disappear from the serving trays FAST! Get it while you can.4) The Beach- Occasionally some coconut leaves on the water surface, some small boulders, but otherwise nice and clear water. Very warm, specially in the afternoon.- Beach chairs very nice, and lots of shade (even outside a palapa - the coconut trees do a magnificent job at that)- Drinks from the bar were all very nice and not watered down. Even without having to tip the bartender. Just smile.You can count on a LOT of Spanish tourists in the Summer months.The main hotel is just next door, and we can confirm that it has a definite family/regular feel.We highly recommend the Royal and we'd definitely be back!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>