<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="03d41319f9275bee982faeb9a5dbdaa5" url=""><![CDATA[Took my breath away I just want to start off by saying that if anyone has anything bad to say about this resort, then they have literally gone cuckoo for cocoa puffs!My husband and I went to the Grand Bahia Principe from March 31, 2008 to April 7, 2008. We went to celebrate our 10th wedding anniversary and to top it off we met my parents down there. They were celebrating their 32nd wedding anniversary. They were there from March 29th to April 12, 2008. I realize been a long time since our vacation but so many things have happened and I find it within myself to write this review until now...We got in at the resort at about 9:45pm on the 31st and there waiting for us was mom to resort from airport bad at about 40mins. Held my breath a few times as the roads are quite narrow and traffic was little congested at times. Upon arriving at the resort we were greeted with a nice hot wash cloth and a cold in was a came threw with our request, ocean view 3 floor corner 63 room bell boys carried our luggage to our room no problem. The room was beyond had a king size 4 poster bed, flat screen TV, a dinning table and a pull out of that for 2 people!, unbelievable. The bathroom was done in marble and the Jacuzzi was care package was left on our bed which consisted of a bottle of rum and 2 hotel we got in late and missed supper we did order room was long but that bother us, we were finally on ate at 5 of the Brazil, French, Gourmet, were beyond to say my favorite was the the chef cook in front of us was pretty grounds throughout the resort are staff take pride in their jobs and are always trimming, sweeping, and picking up the tiniest of leaves on the is always greeting you with a warm happy smile.The pool at the is have to say the best part of the pool is the swim up was always nice to go and have a dip in the cool water then head over to the bar for another waiters and waitress were coming around at least once every 45 mins to see if you wanted or better yet needed another as for the beach you could walk sand was white and the resort to the market which is about a 45 min walk to your right if you were looking at the ocean was really of things going our walk we saw a body building competition going those of you that are a little reserved, be goes on the beach!!As far as the disco, get to see can honestly say that we were in bed sleeping by what happens when your up at 6:00am and drink all did 2 Parasailing was good not as intense as I thought it would be. 2. Banana boat ride was a thrill in hardest part of that was trying to get back on the banana after been thrown def. do it again hands down!For those of you curious about hair braiding I did get it the beach 20 feet from the can also get it done down at the hair was shoulder length and I got extensions put in it so that made my hair go to my lower back and it cost me sure you barter with them!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! They did want always hear about not being able to find a lounge chair, well take it from me you can! Just sleep in till 10:00am and you have a you can sleep all you want back at home, but you may only see paradise one week out of the year, if lucky!Would I go back? Definitely! But not this many lost my dad the day after he and my mom got home, so this march taking my mom to and go with an open mind, trust me you be
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>