<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="eece54114ea93631cb7ed0cc17fb2540" url=""><![CDATA[Nice hotel. Convenient Location I chose this hotel mainly because it was one of the few 4+ star hotels not to jack their prices up considerably due to a soccer match being held the same night (which was the purpose of my trip anyway).The mention of Darling Harbour in the title is a bit of a misnomer, as it is one street off Chinatown, yet a good 10-15 min walk to the heart of Darling Harbour.The hotel is directly across the road from the Sydney Entertainment Centre. Very convenient for those attending concerts or basketball matches at that venue.Express checkout was very convenient. Porters and Front desk staff were quite friendly and efficient.The one downside is the power switch at the door (like many hotels these days) requires your room key to be inserted (or an unneeded card of any type will do). Housekeeping will remove the card if you are absent. In my case, my mobile phone and laptop failed to charge fully.Had absolutely no issue with the renovations at the property. There are many notices in the hotel advising of the renovations and the times you will experience noise (which from memory was from 0830-1800).While I did hear a bit of noise during those times, it wasn't enough to annoy me (maybe I picked a good day).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c2e14a51909c661e352ef89e507b52d0" url=""><![CDATA[Bit out of the way Nice 4 star hotel in a fairly quiet neighbourhood away from most of the tourist spots.Whilst internet access in the room is quite expensive EUR19.95 per day, there is a free PC in the lobby, although it can (understandably) get quite busy at times.Breakfast was nothing too special.Subway station is a quick walk from the hotel (Spittelmarkt on the U2 line).There is a small convenience shop hidden away at the back of the hotel (and across the road).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ef24b4a0cdbd20b82672a96bea1f297f" url=""><![CDATA[Ok if you get it cheap I got a cheap rate by booking well in advance. It certainly isn't worth it's standard room rate.I was on the 2nd floor. If your room number is in the 20's or above (eg 225, 326), be prepared for a looong hike to your room.There was no wireless access to my room (because it was so far away from the access point I assume). There was cabled access, but reception had no cables left.The restaurant is almost 5 star quality (and comes priced accordingly). As someone who arrived off a flight at 9pm and was on another flight at 7am, I only wanted a quick, basic, cheap meal. Even a burger or hot dog would have done. Ended up eating the chocolate in the mini-bar in my room.There is a piece of carpet missing about halfway along the corridor on the 2nd floor. If you get a room near this area, you may want to change rooms, as other guests rolling their luggage onto the exposed concrete are going to keep you up all night.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>