<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="7">
		<document id="5e84ba16fa6acc684042549c5882b24f" url=""><![CDATA[Great location, average hotel I stayed here for 4 nights in May, attending business meetings in Sydney.The location is fabulous, easy walking distance of Darling Harbour, Circular Quay/Opera House, The Rocks etc.The rooms are beginning to look a little in need of renovation the bathroom I had was fine - clean all the facilities but just tending a little towards renovating time.All the basics are there - flat screen TV (although the channel selection is a little biased towards local Aussie TV. I couldn't find CNN for example but there are LOTS of sports channels local channels), broadband internet a comfy bed.Breakfast is a little on the slow/bureaucratic side if there are more than 2 guests in front of you. Everyone has to stop, confirm room # sign receipt before they will seat you. Result is efficiency for hotel but queues for guests.Staff are VERY helpful will help you get taxis, decide where to go for the evening etc. Check-out is fast efficient.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d30c3a8b10c98278a6de99aa475feec2" url=""><![CDATA[Service is variable here I have stayed at the Raffles many times. It is the recommended hotel by my company.I have read some of the reviews below have to say my experience is it can be very variable, depending on who is on duty how busy they are!I have experienced some of the longest check-in queues 'jobs worth' attitude there but I have also experienced amazing customer service (late check-outs to 10pm on one occasion, v attentive concierge).The rooms are nice, slightly above average business style rooms - many with great views. All 'necessities' are there - Internet, fruit, big TV, comfortable bed etc.Location is good - right next door to Chijmes, shopping centres, subway etc.I think, as with many hotels, it all depends how busy they are.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="47d9d6ab0c12b41f099204836f6640a6" url=""><![CDATA[Good hotel but ageing The Grand Plaza is located very well with very easy access to Orchard Road.The reception is efficient, the staff very helpful indeed. As other reviewers have noted, they try very hard to please.The rooms are adequate. Nothing very special, decent bed, decent TV Internet access.However, possibly my fault as I booked the same week I stayed there - I found it VERY expensive for what was on offer. I paid SG$ 450++ for an Executive Floor room.The Executive Floor lounge is small the breakfast is limited to say the least. The bedroom I was in was fine relatively modern but the bathroom was old fashioned the shower was older than me!All in all, fine hotel, great service but way over priced for what you get in my case.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f68ddc7f6a3709f4cbe126c70f77aba9" url=""><![CDATA[Great hotel, good location I have stayed here several times find it great. Rooms are very clean (as you'd expect in Tokyo) relatively large. All facilities are there.Breakfast is good, with freshly squeezed orange juice as well as all the basics.Check in can be typically regimented Japanese style but very efficient fast.Getting to the airport is very easy efficient again - via the limousine bus (not sure what is 'limousine' about it but it is great gets you there relatively fast).Access to the GREAT shopping night life is Shibuya is 100m from the front of the hotel.Only slight negative are the TV channels - you need to be clever to get English working.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="11d477b08770056023be7c683159995b" url=""><![CDATA[Expensive ... but great This is a great hotel in many waysGood location next door to Marina Square shopping which, itself is next door to City Hall MRT station.Great staff, always smiling prepared to help.Good location for large business event. We held a 250 person conference there it went very smoothly.Rooms are comfortable with all facilities you come to expect (good bed, internet, decent TV, comfortable bathroom with decent shower).Food is ok, if a little unexciting in the restaurants.Concierge is very happy to recommend places to go out to see advise how best to get there.Staff are flexible too. I had to extend my stay due to the problems in Thailand there were no problems accomodating me at short notice.All in all great - only niggle is the price. It seems expensive, even for what you get.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4eabd8ba89d37cb520fa46cda4bb76fa" url=""><![CDATA[Hotel good, Staff great! I have stayed at the RC Millenia several times have always found it special a great example of the 'classic' Ritz Carlton style.The staff are happy to go to almost any lengths for the guests seem genuinely friendly.If the staff can capture one of your preferences (from the type of pillow you like to the types of beer you drink) - they will record it work hard to ensure you get it.The location is great, superb views of the harbour.I'd stay there every time I visit Singapore if I could.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7e469b34d5687be6a94b6eab5d15ff75" url=""><![CDATA[Great place to see Florence from A great place to stay as several others have said.Angela her husband are great hosts. Very helpful, eager to ensure you have a good stay, rightfully proud of Florence the area.I have to disagree with SkiingTourist below. This is a Residence, which means you do NOT get meals. Having said that, Angela does provide very basic croissants, cakes fruit juices etc. for you to eat if you want. We did not pay anything additional for cleaning?A great location as well - quiet but easy access into the centre, (via Bus #23). Nice little cafe Trattorias close by as well. A short walk to the Pallazo Michelangelo, complete with it's stunning views sunsets over Florence.If/when we go back - we'll definitely stay there again!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>