<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="9">
		<document id="21db66c04dc1184f9babe14412f04db9" url=""><![CDATA[Headquarters Hotel for New Orleans Rebirth The New Orleans Marriott provided us with a safe, comfortable, and friendly home base for a recent convention. The hotel has recovered from the economic setbacks of Katrina nicely, with very high service levels, lovely common areas and nice guest rooms with luxurious beds. The location is central to all French Quarter activities and within walking distance of Bourbon Street and all major restaurants, as well as the wickedly indulgent Royal Street where I dropped a mortgage payment on the most fantastic hat I've ever seen at Le Fleur de Paris.Food and beverage was well-executed and service was snappy, and the staff were gracious and friendly.Book a stay at this nice hotel in this magnificent city and help New Orleans rebuild its economy. The city is open for business and the French Quarter is fresh as a daisy.P.S. One of our friends, who had been to New Orleans in the past, said that since the Hurricane, Bourbon street smells better!P.P.S. We experienced no challenges with the hotel elevators that some previous reviews mentioned - all worked really efficiently and fast!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="246fddad3cce713e31ea709bcb3c1c64" url=""><![CDATA[Impeccable Service Despite High Volume This huge, theatre district hotel is a buzzing hub of transient activity, and it's amazing that it is so well maintainted with such great service given the volume of guests it moves in and out every day.Every staff contact was highly competent, professional, and friendly. You felt that you were in the hands of a hospitality consultant for New York at every turn. Even our special room service requests were correct.Our room was well soundproofed with extraordinary beds and the usual Marriott big workspace which I believe is superior to other brands. We had a handicapped room, which was a surprise but actually turned out to work pretty well.If you can bear the celestial midtown pricing, this hotel is a rock-solid winner in a great location.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4745e6d362b6ac5761d886461993cef1" url=""><![CDATA[Quiet, competent, quality Stayed at the Intercontinental for a conference, on the Concierge floor. All as expected in the clean, comfortable room. Pillow-top mattress and plenty of pillows as expected in a hotel of this quality. Room was clean, housekeeping came promptly every day. The housekeeping staff did one thing that is a pet peeve of mine - they changed the radio station from the public radio station I'd selected (which is hard to find on the dial) back to the classical music station they use for turndown service. This is so vexing, but obviously they've been trained to do it. Nice bath amenities. Shower curtain rod curved out - yay!Fresh orchid in the bathroom.Plenty of service staff in all public areas, restaurant, bar - food and beverage very solid. I ordered room service breakfast and asked for a couple of special things (eg: 2 egg omlette instead of 3, skim milk, salsa on the side) which usually most hotels mess up in some way, but it came within 20 minutes exactly as ordered. The cost was extremely reasonable for room service in a hotel of this quality. Also, many, many great restaurants within walking distance plus the Dallas Galleria shopping mall across the street.Business center was outsourced but the costs were not outrageous as they are in some hotels - $2.99 access fee and 60 cents a minute (it's much worse other places).Service was uniformly cheerful and efficient.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="88ea01f52456c6261003c949f0ab4327" url=""><![CDATA[Brand new decor but an energy hog This hotel has a brand-new, sleek and styllish lobby and remodeled guest rooms with flat screen HD TV's, but with the brand new remodel, its too bad operations didn't change out all of those energy pig incandescent guest room light bulbs with planet-friendly compact flourescents. (I stayed at a competing brand's high-end property the next night and the CFL's in the guest room looked great).Decor is elegant if a tad overbearing (kind of like Carmella Soprano's bedroom). Both guest room and bathroom had weird and awkward angles. Bottle of Evian was . . . six bucks. Why do hotels nickle and dime their guests in such a shameless way? Flat screen TV, nice bed with nice pillows.When can we have in-room recycling? And the hotel has a towel re-use program with the fatal flaw I'm seeing in many guest rooms: not enough towel bars to hang up your towel and have it be dry!Front desk failed to deliver my messages to me.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f11a82992694fb3bf048a594af1af71d" url=""><![CDATA[All renewable power and excellent service, too We stayed at the Hyatt Regency Dallas for nearly a week as part of a conference. The property is HUGE and well-maintained and renovated.Positives:-great coffee shop in lobby area so you're never without that latte-many dining options, including a very pleasant open restaurant that's great for breakfast or lunch (although the service was so attentive it was sometimes difficult to finish a sentence)-the big observation tower bar is a great place to get together with spectacular views-the bellman (I think his name was Steve) has been there for 24 years and loved the place and knew everything-nicely decorated rooms-you can request a mini fridge - empty-room service and housekeeping service was lickety-split-HVAC system maintained indoor comfort - which is more than I can say for most hotel rooms that are either too hot or too cold!-the hotel purchases ALL of its energy from renewable sources. Yay!Negatives:-closet was miniscule, which was a struggle for two women with a full set of conference, shopping and casual wardrobe for a week-the bathroom was designed, which always leads to something that looks great but is non-functional - in this case it was hooks for the towels instead of racks so that they could completely dry. Sigh. I would be delighted if the trend to use hip designers to do things would go away and we could get hotels back to focusing on function.-Like many large Hyatt Regencies, the room was a little on the small side - you can only really watch TV from bed, and the work space is only one table (Mariott does a much better job with work space), but these were minor issues and overall things worked pretty well.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="57e44bfac930fa4e892dbc5b848796f2" url=""><![CDATA[Many amenities but some business and design challenges This review is written from the perspective of a business traveler on a stay of several nights, attending a meeting in the hotel.The five star rating makes sense from the perspective of hotel amenities - high end bathroom, excellent bed, full service, flat screen TV, etc.From an international business perspective, the five stars make a little less sense. The hotel was full of people from all over Europe, the U.S. and the Persian Gulf, but very few staff had enough English to interpret any but the most basic requests. When on vacation, it's my job to know the host hotel's first language. When traveling on business in a luxury business hotel, it's their job to have enough English to accomodate international travelers.This was particularly frustrating when speaking to the hotel operator on the phone - e.g. I asked for an electrical adaptor and the response was what time do you want the wake up call? The concierge and front desk staff had very good English, so there was always a recourse - but it often involved going down to the desk. (The adaptor episode led to a very drawn out adventure where I was certain the housekeeping staffer would start a fire - in her zeal to be helpful, she was attaching several appliances with incompatible voltages together, and I had to use body language and some high school theater background to register my increasing alarm).The staff was universally friendly and eager to please; sincere intention to take care of guests was ever-present. Wireless did not work in my guest room but worked very well in the lobby. Wired internet access in the guest room is 20 Euros - that's 30 bucks for you Americans, and reinforces my irritation that higher-end hotels love nickle and diming us to death.From a design perspective, I give the hotel mixed reviews. Strengths included an easy to navigate hotel footprint, attractive modern design, the incredible mattress - I had no back pain for the entire stay, and others in my group had similar feedback; linens and pillows were abundant and very high quality. Plenty of work and sitting space, tons of closet space.Weaknesses - will someone shoot these designers for me, please? I think half the people who design hotel rooms never actually sleep in one. The odd sweeping diagonal of the entrance to the sleeping room meant that you must have the door to your sleeping area closed in order to fetch your clothes - this caused endless awkward reaches for things in the closet.But the most senseless was the bathroom. Beautiful granite finishes - but the counter space was minimal and piled with signs and amenities - with no shelf space underneath for the guest's actual belongings. This is one of my pet peeves. Where am I supposed to put my medications, hair stuff, lotions, potions? This is all more important to me than whatever soap or shampoo the hotel thinks I need.The shower design was actually dangerous - the tiny shower booth had a flimsy, aluminum-framed glass door which cracked when I pulled it shut. Despite two requests, nobody fixed it - and it could have shattered into the shower stall. But since the shower itself was so small you couldn't extend an arm in any direction, and since the only shelf space for toiltetries was 2 inches by 2 inches, I opted for the luxurious tub with shower attachment instead.The entrance to the toilet (also flimsy frame with glass) was less than 24 inches wide, so you had to be very careful entering it lest you incur a bruise or break the door - and there was also a bidet in there . . . taking up useful space. Re: temperature. The bellman helpfully told me that guests can only adjust the temperature 2 degrees on their own; any other adjustments must be managed by front desk, and the heat was blasting all over the building, even though it was quite temperate. (Our meeting room was exhaustingly overheated most of the time). Four phone calls and I was able to get the heat off in the sleeping room and get it cool enough to sleep in.The hotel has a very nice relaxed restaurant with a fine buffet breakfast that caters to many cultures. It did take a heroic act of intervention to get a cup of coffee and banana to carry away one morning when I was in a hurry. As a business hotel, it's important that guests can accomodate their meeting schedules with the ability to vittle themselves on their own. There is also no sundry shop on site, so tough luck if you forgot any key items.I didn't find the transportation a barrier - a 25 minute cab ride or metro ride downtown got me wherever I needed to go.A couple of other things I appreciated - an oversized hotel safe, big enough for computer, jewelery, money, shoes, a small pet . . . and a remarkably helpful concierge who gave me special advice about maintenance on the metro that saved my one day off to sightsee. All of the staff were quite wonderful.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f9765c593f37ff4db5ddfe390e4e1657" url=""><![CDATA[Very nice Fairmont This is a lovely property, with high-end amenities and spacious guest rooms. Comfortable beds with quality linens, flat-screen TV, plenty of countertop space in the bathroom, and in-room recycling. A couple of features I thought particularly great for a business traveler: the very large desk is big enough to serve as a dining table and includes chairs on the opposite side of the desk to support dining or impromptu meetings. A thoughtful touch was that all of the hotel's information is on a tray at the foot of the bed rather than piled all over the desk - it is a nice change from having to re-arrange the whole work space in order to get something done.It was great to see in-room recycling in concert with Fairmont's eco-friendly practices, but it was disappointing to see incandescent light bulbs installed in all of the fixtures. However, I left a note for the Operations Manager asking about installing compact flourescents, and he sent me an email stating they'd have the lighting changeout completed by the end of December, 2007.Overall a comfortable and productive stay in a luxurious property.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2e15abce44ee619f3124a9840c56d4dc" url=""><![CDATA[Efficient, priced to compete, stylish rooms We chose the Millenium Hilton for our weekend in NYC because our rate, which included two breakfasts AND one night of champagne, was about $150 cheaper than the celestial rates of Times Square / Midtown properties WITHOUT breakfast.We were worried that being so far downtown would make transportation difficult, but with a subway station across the street, we had no problem most of the time; Saturday night cabs were scarce and the hotel only had one doorman on, so we left the long taxi line and hoofed up one block to catch our own - no big deal.We appreciated other TripAdvisor guest photos of the site, as it is across the street from the WTC site - the hotel itself was damaged in the 9/11 attacks and was closed for 18 months. (Now beautifully restored - no issues). The bellman told us a harrowing story of the day of the attack and his subsequent 9 hour walk home to the Bronx. This location, then, becomes a positive - the staff are happy to see you and grateful for your business, and you can walk a few steps out the door to see the moving WTC display or explore St. Paul's chapel, the 18thC church which miraculously survived the collapse of the towers.The room was better appointed than most brands, with a huge, flat-screen TV and glass and wood furniture. Room a little on the small side for two women who spent three days shopping, but then again, what hotel room would have held all the bags? OUTSTANDING bed.Our room overlooked WTC site, and the other side of the hotel overlooks the Brooklyn Bridge. Overall a very pleasant experience.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2820dd53081301692c061b91328e7273" url=""><![CDATA[Saved me when I was stranded On a night when over 200 flights out of Dallas were cancelled and the highways were fender-deep in water, I stayed at this Marriott because it was the closest place to the airport that had room as the hotels filled up. A couple of features set this hotel above its competition as a business hotel. First, the mattress is the best I've slept on - better than a Heavenly Bed, better than a Ritz. And not just because it beat sleeping on the floor of the airport like 3,000 of my fellow travelers!Second, the hotel actually acknowledges that you need to do work and so has a great electronics console as a sort of backsplash to the desk - lots of outlets, phone lines, and other plug-ins for all your gizmos so that you don't have to move appliances or crawl around on the floor. Finally, instead of a $5.00 cheapo clock alarm or one of those new weird pre-programmed radios (I hate those things), this clock radio had an iPod docking station attached to it. The room also had a flat-screen TV and wonderful uni-sex orange-scented amenities. And the nice man at the desk gave me a free toothbrush so I wouldn't have socks on my teeth the next morning when I got up to schlep back to the airport. And a free bottle of water, not one that cost $6.00 like the hotel I stayed in the night before.Also - compact flourescents in the guest rooms! Thanks for saving energy, and for keeping the bathroom light fixtures from melting a gal's makeup (even if it was day-old makeup). I only wish you would have had recycling in the guest room!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>