<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="295e736040148b500db62fc7d13f56b0" url=""><![CDATA[I did not want to go, but had a good time anyway!!! Ok, I really did not even want to take this trip, but the wife really wanted to do the DR. I ended up liking it anyway!2 adults, and 2 teens (16 and 13) made the trip.The basics: If you book the travel through Club Med, it is all totally painless. You are met at the departing airport, signed in, given your luggage tags and off you go through the airline process. when you arrive, you go to the club med booth (avoid the sleazy baggage handlers. They will yank the bags out of your hand, because they see the club med tag, and walk them 50 feet to the booth). At the booth you get your room key and you are off to the bus.The bus was beautiful, new and air conditioned. Its a 10 minute ride, nice. You get your wrist band and they take care of your bags.The place: The grounds are immaculate, very neat and tidy. The rooms are pleasant, nothing terribly special, but nothing wrong with them either. We had a nice balcony, not on the water, but you could see the water. As many have pointed out, this place is large. Just to be accurate, one day I took a walk from the reception desk to the furthest room. It was a solid 7 minutes at a brisk pace. So if you don't like walking you are in trouble! My room was 4 minutes brisk walk from the center of town.We had no problem with bugs, and never put on repellent.The food: If you can not find food you like here, there is something wrong with you. Remember, this is Club Med, relaxed and casual. If you are expecting a formal sit down dinner, you are staying at the wrong resort. Nice bottle of red wine on every table at dinner. They ALWAYS had the standard stuff for the picky eaters (burgers, chicken, pasta, pizza). But more fun to be had trying things like whole grilled fish (with the eyes!), Dominican stew, etc. Always lots of cheese and fruits around. Tons of nice desserts. I really think the spread of food for all three meals was fantastic.The beach: Nice enough, but you are on a private section. The pros: no other hotel's guests wandering through. The con: you don't see miles of sandy white beach, and you can't go for a long long walk. The water is ok, but not the crystal clear I remember from other places. They have wind surfers, small sailboats and snorkel equipment. Classes every day to learn. Never seemed to be a huge wait to get anything. But: always windy and a strong current. I could never manage to tack the wind surfer back and always had to be rescued!Never really had a problem getting a lounge chair. At some parts of the mid day, every chair has a towel on it, so they are all taken. But then it slows down. If you get out at a normal time, you will not have a problem at all. You do not have to go out at 7 in the morning and reserve a chair. Chairs always to be had at the pool side.The drinks: Bar always open. Its the basic Rum and Coke, Pina Colada style of things, all free. Local beer ok. Again, if you are looking for a Grey Goose martini, you are staying at the wrong place! Never a line to get a drink.For Kids: We never saw our 16 year old daughter except for the hour before dinner for shower up. They can stay occupied the entire time, and they love it. They all cry when its time to leave. They do a talent show, all the kids are in it, its great. However, there is plenty of underage drinking going on, it seems. It is a wild time at the beach disco from 11pm to 4am, and its a mix of adults and kids. Kind of a bad idea. We made our kid come to the room at 11:45 at the latest, but some teens were there all night. Better hope your kids are trustworthy, or they will be drinking and having their first sexual experience!!!Sports: You can stay as busy as you like with tennis, volleyball, archery, ping pong, the gym etc. I would not say this is a place to get any good instruction or clinics, but they get you out there on the court and then you can arrange your own games. Easy enough. Be warned, it is HOT and HUMID!Language: Lots of French being spoken, but it was never an issue. English speakers totally welcome. (side note: while there are a few europeans who should not wear the thong, it was interesting to see that they are in general in much better shape then the average american. We really need to deal with this problem!!)Its Club Med. Lots of activities, lots of excitement if you want it, and just a very pleasant place. All the employees are nice, never had a problem at all. Recommended.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>