<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="3">
		<document id="3a1e0a3f4311eebecd40f48302ca7e0e" url=""><![CDATA[Really disappointed Stayed recently in this hotel and thankfully for only one night. Staff very obliging , location very central, quiet and refined and on the whole the hotel could be described as clean but our room was ludicrously small. We were in room 35 - top floor facing the front - and I am not exaggerating when I say the room housed a double bed and that was all. If we wanted to open the suitcase we had to put it on the bed and there was no room to put anything anywhere. The bathroom was also tiny - so cramped and box like - a small shower cubicle and a tiny sink and toilet. Maybe we drew the short straw because I saw other rooms that were being cleaned and they were much bigger. I would have not expected to pay the price I did for this room. I would also have expected a reduction for being given this room which needless to say we were not awarded. I heard the hotel manager asking another guest at breakfast if they wanted to change their room to something bigger as they were staying a few nights - maybe this is their policy - shove guests into the small room if they are not spending lots of time or money there. Disappointed. Be careful.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="698c3017f342c530d8ff558b29911912" url=""><![CDATA[Very impressed Just returned from a long weekend in New York. Have previously visited new York and been disappointed with the shabbiness and smallness of hotel rooms but was very impressed with the Marriott Marquis.Large clean and comfortable rooms, excellent location - central and safe.Loved the elevators - very state of the art and fast!Also loved the cocktails!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="603d7fd7881e8f80951a06271a77df11" url=""><![CDATA[Mixed but mostly good Just stayed 3 nights at the Red Lion Seattle. Plus points are location - very central location, excellent for shopping, safe area to walk around if a lady out and about shopping alone. Breakfast nice, clean, good complimentary wireless Internet access in room. Negative points, reception staff need some customer service training, at this price you expect a higher standard of customer care (got the impression they were happy to do what you wanted but didn't really go out of their way to be friendly, attentive etc) and also for the price, I would expect a better choice of TV channels in the room. Would go again if staying in Seattle but only if on business as couldn't justify paying the price out my own pocket. Paid $256 per night + tax - Internet special rate apparently...
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>