<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="b93f3d826f6e1cddafb7b4dd1b3872f1" url=""><![CDATA[Fantastic Location, can't beat it! I recently stayed at the Sofitel for 5 nights. Like others, I don't want to repeat the many great reviews already below, but would like to recommend the hotel.The hotel is in an excellent location, near the Theatre district. Within walking distance of fabulous shopping and many tourist attractions. Time Square is only a 2 minute walk away.The hotel itself is lovely, beautiful rooms, very friendly stuff (particlarly the concierge), who helped us booked a helicopter flight over New York, and had many great restaurant recommendations!The food is great, both the room service and the restaurant. Great if you've had a really long day and just can't be bothered eating out!Definetly recommend joining the Sofitel Privillege Club when you arrive, as this entitles you to a complimentary cocktail during your stay, and a 4pm checkout. Very handy indeed when flying home in the early evening.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d48bf33b450b8545dcf13087b270f914" url=""><![CDATA[Fabulous Location, Chic Hotel! Hotel Granados 83 is in an excellent location, about a 10 minute walk from Las Ramblas.The hotel is very chic. The rooms also have fabulous electronic blinds that convert the room into total darkness (great for afternoon siesta). Some nice touches, such a bottle of water and chocolates left in our room on the first night. Also every evening around 6pm, 2 bottles of red iced tea were delivered to the room.Upon returning in the early evening, our bed had always been remade, and a quick refresh of the room had been done.Several nice bars in the hotel. Try the Bar on Level A, where you can sip your drinks next to the pool.Staff very helpful, with regard to booking taxis, making phone calls to restaurants etc.There are numerous cafes and restaurants only metres from the hotel.Would definetly stay here again.For a great seafood lunch in the sun at the beach, try Can Majo.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>