<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="2">
		<document id="e43da49f0126d0c7e80bfacbf806cf2d" url=""><![CDATA[Convenient, great staff With some forethought and a little luck, the Queen Anne can be a gem. We booked a one-bedroom suite and were given room 404. It really wasn't up to par, so we asked to be moved and were given 414, which was a gem. This room has a turret and has been recently refurbished with new windows, new furniture and bedding. The bathroom is spacious with room on the lavatory sink and tub to put your sundries. If we go back to San Francisco, we'd request room 414.Included in the price of the room are sherry and cookies in the late afternoon from 4-6 p.m. and a passable breakfast in the morning. The staff was amazingly helpful and kind. We were treated almost as family. Manager Michael arranged our room move with sensitivity and speed. People on the front desk were friendly and helpful. Concierege Roberto recommended great neighborhood restaurants in the Fillmore area and rescued an evening out. We had booked tickets for a performance in the Rrazz Room at the Nikko hotel online, but when we arrived they had no record of the booking. I had left the confirmation slip back at the hotel. With minutes to go before the performance, we called Roberto who raced to our room and found the slip. The Fillmore area is an eight or so block walk from the hotel, but the number 3 bus will take you there from right in front of the hotel in about five minutes. Fillmore is filled with little restaurants and shops, and not the standard stuff you see everywhere. We ate a lovely French meal at Chouquet and had OK Italian at Via Veneto. Reservations are a good idea because this is a happening area and the restaurants are small. Roberto will gladly make them for you.If you're over age 65, you can ride the Muni buses and streetcars (not the cable cars) for 50 cents by showing any kind of a proof-of-age ID. Frankly, most drivers never bothered to check when we asked for senior fares. Take the offered transfers. They are supposed to be good for 90 minutes, but, again, the drivers rarely checked.A block and a half from the hotel, you can catch several buses to Union Square and the financial district and the number 2 to the Ferry Building. From there, antique streetcars run along the Embarcadero to Fisherman's Wharf. A note of caution: the cars are jammed in the late afternoon with returning tourists, so you may not get on unless you go to the Wharf.We rented bikes from Blazing Saddles at Pier 41 on the Embarcadero for a ride across the Golden Gate Bridge to Sausalito for lunch and a ferry ride back. It makes for a great half-day experience, and we were blessed with incredible weather -- sunny and in the 70s. Memorable.All in all, our stay at the Queen Anne was lovely. Two fireplaces in the lobby made homecoming a joy. The rooms can be a mixed bag but some, like 414, are downright special. This hotel was built more than 100 years ago, which means some small compromises, but not many. Don't expect the spit and polish of a chain. The location is quiet and a bit away from things, but excellent public transit resolves that.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="95afdc1a56dfe7a83f884260937070a4" url=""><![CDATA[Completely exceeded expectations We made a decision in July to go to Paris in September. Hotels recommended by friends were booked, but the Dusquene Eiffel was available. The great Trip Advisor reviews clinched it. The only room type available online was the comfort double, but the attentive staff responded with the offer of an upgrade to a superior room. Based on reviews, I chanced requesting Room 55, and it was available for four of the five nights we wanted. The fifth night was in room 25. The room and the hotel were wonderful. All rooms ending in 5 are corner rooms with views of the Eiffel Tower through french doors. Room 55 at the top of the hotel has the best view and a two-sided balcony from which you also can see Sacre Coeur and Les Invalides. The star attraction, of course, is the Eiffel Tower. At night, it sparkles in your window on the hour with the lights installed for the Millennium celebration. Magical, and surely one of the best views in all of Paris. Room 56 next door is smaller but also has direct views of the Tower from the bed. It would be nice if the hotel would put flower boxes and a couple of small chairs and a little table on the balcony. That would make it perfection.The hotel staff is everything the reviews say and more. They are knowledgeable, friendly, helpful and cheerful and will gladly suggest and make reservations at restaurants and even provide a computer-generated map to them. Even though we had been to Paris before, we really appreciated the advice of the staff. Special kudos to Amanda and Pritti.As others have said, Rue Cler is just a couple of blocks away behind the Ecole Militare Metro stop. This is a great place for coffee and a pain du chocolat in the morning though your table mates may be Americans armed with Rick Steve's Paris guide. There are wonderful cheese and chocolate shops and a nice patisserie. At the Ecole Militare Metro stop there is a small supermarket with a good selection of wine, fruit and staples.Use the Metro and invest in the Paris Visite pass, which is good for one to five days of unlimited public transit rides and discounts to some museums and attractions. Buy them at the Metro stations.We like mussels and went to one of the many Lyon de Bruxelles restaurants. It's a chain, but if moules are your passion, they are good and reasonably priced here. The nicest restaurant experience of the trip was at Fermette Marbeuf (5 Avenue Marbeuf). Its domed ceiling and tile work were enchanting and the food was superb. There's a 30 Euro fixed-price menu that is well worth selecting. We embellished it a bit, added wine and coffee and the tab was only 101 Euro, service included, for a special night of elegant service and wonderful cuisine.All in all, a lovely time at a lovely hotel with a lovely staff and a lovely view. A few reviewers seemed disenchanted with their rooms, but they seemed unused to the size of European hotel rooms and the prevalence of glass half-doors on showers. True, some of the rooms at Dusquene Eiffel are small and more basic, but if you can plan a little request room 55 or any of the corner rooms ending in 5. You won't be disappointed.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>