<author type="review" lang="EN" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="1">
		<document id="68b1089f62e22e7f65d0c20a6e4ef098" url=""><![CDATA[Beautiful Resort........food not so good My husband and I stayed at the Ocean Blue from May 3rd - May 10th 2007. We are in our early 30's and wanted to go away to someplace warm so we could lay on the beach and just relax. The All-Inclusive part of the vacation was what convinced us to go to the Dominican Replublic over another caribbean island.The resort was gorgeous!! The beach was the best part.....loved it. The pools were huge, just not sure if they were being filtered correctly....there were little particles floating in the water :(The rooms were standard hotel rooms with a large balacony and nice size bathroom. House keeping was very friendly; they cleaned/washed floors and restocked the refrigerator every day. There were many restaurants to chose from however, I would recommend eating at the buffet. It seemed to have the best selection of food. We actually didn't care for any of the food there. Maybe because we are used to home cooked meals and don't tend to go out to eat alot. Seems that they cook everything in Dominican Spices which didn't really agree with us. Don't eat the burgers......not quite sure what meat they made it with but they didn't taste the way a burger is supposed to taste....LOLLoved Mike's Cafe for a cafe latte or espresso.....There is a small casino and bowling that was fun. Definitely wear sunscreen! My husband didn't and got major sunburn the first day. Some hotel employees walk around with umbrellas to protect themselves from the sun since it is so strong there. The weather was great while we were there it was in the upper 80's everyday and it only rained one day we were there. Overall the resort is beautiful, well kept and the employees are very friendly. Very disapointed with the food but it seemed that there were alot of other people enjoying it so maybe it was just us?
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>